Chapter 1105: Hei Tribe's Huge Battle (1/3)

Two days later.

Blue skies and white clouds, the sun brightly shone in the sky. The surroundings were vast expanses of plains, one had unhindered vision.

Two Gu Immortals from Yao tribe floated in the air, they did not conceal themselves, they showed themselves confidently to everyone.

A female Gu Immortal, Yao Ju, had a round face, she smiled: "Today's weather is great, my mood has gotten better because of it."

Beside her, another female Gu Immortal from Yao tribe, Yao Zi Han, also sighed: "The weather is great, we are in a good mood, but it is the opposite for Hei tribe."

Her eyes shined with purple light, looking down at the empty grassland below her with much interest.

On the other side of the cloud, there were two male Gu Immortals sitting.

Both of them were middle aged, they had thick beards, they wore armor and had exposed arms, bulging with muscles.

Both of them were not wearing shoes, and their pants were very short, almost showing their knees.

The only difference was, one of them had charcoal-black skin, while the other had dark yellow skin.

These were distinctive of two members of another Huang Jin clan.

It was Meng tribe!

Meng Ji had dark yellow skin, he stared at the two female immortals from Yao tribe as he said: "That is Yao Zi Han, her eyes radiate purple light, that is because of Yao tribe's signature killer move, purple jade eyes, this pair of eyes can see through blessed lands and grotto-heavens, Yao tribe has a clear awareness of the situation inside Iron Eagle blessed land."

Meng Si, on the other hand, looked up and called out: "No big deal. If we really compete, our fists will do the talking."

Saying so, he suddenly raised his head, looking towards the east.

Only to see that aurora burst out in the east, golden light radiated as a beautiful palace flew over.

"Gong tribe is here!"

"Impressive, they even brought their tribe's Immortal Gu House, Golden Dawn Hall, Gong tribe is very determined."

"Gong tribe has always been acting like this, they emphasize on extravagance, don't bother about them!"

The righteous path Gu Immortals conversed.

Most of their attention was on Iron Eagle blessed land.

Iron Eagle blessed land was the headquarters of Hei tribe, it was a public blessed land, placed in just one tiny spot, if the entrance was not open, the outside world could not observe it.

Unless they had immortal killer moves similar to Yao Zi Han's purple jade eyes.

The righteous path Gu Immortals were patiently waiting.

According to what they knew, the demonic path Gu Immortals had already joined up and attacked.

As it turned out, during this chaos in Northern Plain, a rank seven demonic path expert called Huang Di had interfered. He had high cultivation level, and had obtained the true inheritance of a legendary person in Northern Plains, the earth path great expert Di Lao.

He had methods to attack the blessed land. Because Iron Eagle blessed land was a public blessed land, it was assembled together and did not have the defense of a normal blessed land.

Demonic path Gu Immortal Huang Di went out first, bringing a bunch of demonic cultivators and lone immortals to attack.

At some point, Iron Eagle blessed land was bound to collapse.

That way, it would be full of loopholes, even if the entrance was not open, righteous path Gu Immortals could enter freely.

"Everyone, I, Gong Er, would like to invite everyone to attack Hei tribe together." Outside Gong tribe's Immortal Gu House, Golden Dawn Hall, an old rank seven Gu Immortal dressed in a golden robe spoke.

"It's that old fellow Gong Er, our information was right, he indeed came."

"Hehe, Gong tribe wants to lead over everyone. If we enter their hall, he would definitely be the alliance leader."

"This is Gong tribe's habit. But Gong tribe brought their Immortal Gu House here, they have the strongest power among us righteous path members."

"Who would be so foolish to let Gong tribe lead them?"

The righteous path Gu Immortals sneered internally, nobody moved.

Gong tribe was a Huang Jin tribe, a super force, their supreme elders had grand ambitions, wanting Gong tribe to be the leader of the righteous path. But among Huang Jin tribes, none would submit to each other.

Earlier, Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had worked together but lost to Old Ancestor Xue Hu. The last remaining righteous path rank eight Gu Immortal was Prince Feng Xian, he was a member of Gong tribe.

Gong tribe had been spreading news that only Prince Feng Xian could rival Old Ancestor Xue Hu, thus, they grew in boldness.

Gong Er stood in front of the Immortal Gu House, he thought that he would be well received by the righteous path, but after a long time, nobody moved, there was not even any response or acknowledgment.

Even though he was old and experienced, his expression could not help but turn ugly.

"Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals greet senior Gong Er." At this time, three Gu Immortal flew over, getting close to Gong Er.

Among these three, the leader was a rank seven Gu Immortal, while the other two were rank six Gu Immortals.

The three immortals were humble, they smiled and emanated warmth.

Gong Er's expression soothed, he felt that the three Gu Immortals from Bai Zu tribe were amicable, and now, he could save his face, quickly inviting these three immortals into Golden Dawn Hall.

The righteous path Gu Immortals who saw this had complex expressions.

Because Bai Zu tribe was not of the Huang Jin bloodline, they had just become a righteous path super force. This was due to the famous rank eight Gu Immortal Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was a lone cultivator, but after the collapse of Imperial Court blessed land, he saw hope of creating his own super force.

In the current Northern Plains, righteous path super forces were mostly Huang Jin tribes.

To become a super force, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu got closer in his relationship with Yao Huang, working with him to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Even though they lost against him in a two against one.

But Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's goal was achieved.

He gained Yao Huang's friendship, and Yao tribe's recognition, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could create his Bai Zu tribe with his bloodline descendants.

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were all nurtured inside Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's grotto-heaven. Even though there were few of them, right now, during these chaotic battles in Northern Plains, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu sent three to participate.

"Bai Zu tribe..."

"Hmph, these Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals are as crafty as Heavenly Lord Bai Zu."

"We have differing viewpoints than Gong tribe, this caused Bai Zu tribe to gain benefits instead."

The righteous path Gu Immortals were mostly part of the Huang Jin bloodline, they had dominated Northern Plains, even though there was internal conflict among them, they were more resistant towards 'outsiders' like Bai Zu tribe.

"It is a pity that Bai Zu tribe is protected by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, we cannot touch them."

"Even so, we have many ways to deal with them, they want to establish a super force in Northern Plains, heh! It is not so easy..."

At once, the righteous path Gu Immortals gathered and discussed on how to deal with Bai Zu tribe.

Boom!

The immortals had just started talking, before they had gone any further, they heard a loud explosion.

Countless gazes looked down, they saw that on the grassland, space shattered like a broken mirror, the broken shards showed a gigantic expanse of scenery.

The scene inside Iron Eagle blessed land was shown in front of everyone.

Right now, killer moves like purple jade eyes were no longer needed, the immortals could see what was going on.

All of the righteous path immortals' attentions were drawn.

Inside Iron Eagle blessed land, there was chaos.

Large numbers of demonic path Gu Immortals were competing for Hei tribe's resources and treasures. Some were looting, some were fighting aggressively.

Crackle!

Lightning shot everywhere, causing rocks to shatter and fly. Many deep pits were formed, they were charred black.

Divine Lord Tian Du was covered in sparks as he shouted: "The lantern grass here is mine, who dares to compete with me?"

Old Lu and the others looked at each other, they could see that their gazes were filled with much wariness.

"Divine Lord Tian Du had gained two lightning path Immortal Gu, his battle strength rose drastically, we should retreat."

"That's right, this place is filled with treasures, why must we compete with him?"

These Gu Immortals were, without exception, all rank six bottom tier Gu Immortals, they quickly discussed this matter and left.

At the other end.

A desolate beast iron crown eagle cried out weakly, trampled by a boar.

There was a demonic path Gu Immortal on the boar's back, he was burly and wearing armor, he held a pair of bronze hammers as he said smugly: "You are just a lowly beast, you dare to sneak attack me?"

Saying this, his expression suddenly froze, he looked towards the east.

A peacock was flying over, immortal aura emanated as it spoke clear human language: "Zhuo Zhan."

"Oh, It is Fairy He Ruo!"Zhuo Zhan's expression changed, he smiled and tried to leave a good impression on her.

Peacock Flying Immortal He Ruo, rank six transformation path Gu Immortal.

"Trade the desolate beast under your feet with mine? I have just captured a desolate beast shadowless horse." He Ruo suggested.

Zhuo Zhan's eyes flashed with brilliance, he quickly nodded: "Sure, let's trade! I am very willing to accede to fairy's request, hehehe."

At another end.

Wind was intertwining like willows, it could be seen with the naked eye.

Gusts of wind was moving about continuously.

A figure descended from the sky, he said with agitation: "To think that a rank seven immortal material, green jade wind, is here."

It was the rank seven Gu Immortal expert Pi Shui Han.

"Brother Pi, this immortal material is mine, go elsewhere." A figure appeared as well, it was a scholar with graceful and elegant bearing.

Pi Shui Han's pupils shrunk, he said coldly: "So it is you, Unfettered Scholar."

Unfettered Scholar smiled calmly, he was also a rank seven expert, his reputation and abilities were not inferior to Pi Shui Han.

"Last time in Tai Qiu, we did not decide a victor, let's fight now!" Pi Shui Han took the initiative to request for a battle.

Unfettered Scholar's smile faded: "I heard that Brother Pi has created a new immortal killer move, let me take a good look at it."

...

All sorts of situations were occurring, the righteous path Gu Immortals were watching them unfold.

"Because of the demonic path Gu Immortal Huang Di, these demonic scoundrels had the initiative."

"No need to worry, Iron Eagle blessed land has a special structure, it is famous for nurturing desolate beast iron crown eagles. There is little ground in there, but the sky is huge and vast. The truly valuable thing are those round ball wooden eagle nests."

"Hmph, simply a rabble. Hei tribe's Gu Immortals have not shown themselves yet, the core resources have not even been uncovered, but they are already fighting among themselves."

The righteous path Gu Immortals were ready to strike.

But at this moment, a figure shot down at lightning speed, he was so fast, in an instant, he entered Iron Eagle blessed land.

"Who is he? He has sword path cultivation."

"It is a junior from Nian Er tribe. I think his name is Nian Er Ping Zhi!"

The righteous path Gu Immortals were shocked, this person had been concealed, he did not interact with any of the other immortals.

"Who is it?" In the blessed land, Qing Xuan Zi sensed something, he raised his head and called out.

Sword light flashed across at an incredible speed!

Qing Xuan Zi was beheaded.

"The person who killed you, Nian Er Ping Zhi." Sword light flashed by as a voice could be heard.

Chapter 1106: Hei Tribe's Huge Battle (2/3)

Qing Xuan Zi might only have rank six cultivation level, but he had undergone a heavenly tribulation already. Yet he could not put up any resistance and was killed by Nian Er Ping Zhi instantly.

At once, the expressions of the righteous path Gu Immortals who were not fighting changed.

Qing Xuan Zi's head fell to the floor, separated from his body.

The headless corpse was spewing out blood as it twitched continuously.

Qing Xuan Zi had died with his eyes wide open.

Nian Er Ping Zhi's sword light continued to shoot forward, moving with imposing aura.

"The next one dead is you." Nian Er Ping Zhi said lightly, his clear voice resonated in the sky.

The second unlucky person was also a demonic path Gu Immortal.

But Nian Er Ping Zhi had already revealed himself, such disturbance could not be hidden.

Thus, the demonic path Gu Immortal did better than Qing Xuan Zi, he managed to retreat for a while before Nian Er Ping Zhi caught up to him and killed him in one strike.

The righteous path Gu Immortals' expressions changed again.

A Gu Immortal from Liu tribe, Liu Zhuan Shen, smiled towards the sky: "Nian Er Fu, this person is the newest generation Sword Child from your Nian Er tribe?"

Bam.

Fog and smoke burst out, there was a voice that came from within.

This was a rank seven Gu Immortal, but from his appearance, he was very young, resembling a fat five or six year old boy.

The fat boy chuckled, he looked around sneakily, answering in a mature tone: "Indeed. This lad obtained the Sword Saint true inheritance, and was kept in the tribe by my first supreme elder for ten years. Therefore, when he came out for the first time now, he is excited to this frenzied degree."

Liu Zhuan Shen and the others' expressions changed mildly, they transmitted to each other.

"Sword Saint Nian Er, we were still discussing it earlier, this person was a rank eight Gu Immortal of Nian Er tribe. He was like Hei Fan in history, leading Nian Er tribe to become among the forefront of the righteous path in Northern Plains."

"Sword Sword Saint Nian Er was a prodigy, he had once cultivated light path, but switched to sword path successfully. After he died, he left behind the Sword Saint true inheritance, it has an extremely difficult and deadly test, it is rare to have actual inheritors for it."

"It is said that this Sword Saint true inheritance is split into three portions. After the first round, and obtaining the first portion of the Sword Saint true inheritance, one will be known as the Sword Child."

"To think that after three hundred years, a new Sword Child true inheritor appeared in Nian Er tribe!"

Wariness rose in the righteous path Gu Immortals.

If this person is allowed to continue developing, in the future, he will definitely be an active person among the Northern Plains righteous path. If he can progress and become rank seven, if he passes the second round and inherits the second portion of the true inheritance, he will become the Swordmaster true inheritor, nobody in the whole of Northern Plains would dare to look down on him.

In fact, the Sword Child with just rank six cultivation was already a force to be reckoned with.

In just a short time, he had once again killed another demonic path Gu Immortal!

Nian Er Ping Zhi roared with enthusiasm, he was extremely confident. He moved quickly, being one with his sword, only sword light could be seen darting around, his body was a blur.

Sword light changed directions, towards the closest demonic path Gu Immortal.

Sword light penetrated the demonic path Gu Immortal's body, but he showed a cold smile: "Junior, just because you killed a few weaklings, you gained the courage to challenge me this brazenly?"

Old Monster Corpse Poison said this as purple smoke rose up from his terrifying injuries.

The purple smoke dissipated, healing his body.

But Nian Er Ping Zhi's sword light shattered, revealing his true appearance.

Nian Er Ping Zhi's appearance could finally be seen, he had sharp brows and clear eyes, he was a handsome young lad.

Blech...

He suddenly covered his mouth with his hand, but he could not stop the purple poisonous blood from flowing out of his mouth and nose.

"Fight me again!" Nian Er Ping Zhi was heavily injured, but his eyes were burning with flames of enthusiasm.

"Then I will kill you before seeking the treasure here." Old Monster Corpse Poison smiled sinisterly.

"Hehe, youngsters these days, they are truly fearless and ignorant." Nian Er Fu took a glance before retracting his gaze.

Next, his figure disappeared in the air, before appearing beside Qing Xuan Zi's corpse at the next moment.

Nian Er Fu stretched out his fat little arm, waving at Qing Xuan Zi's corpse.

Immediately, Qing Xuan Zi's body and head was held up by a formless force, flying into Nian Er Fu's immortal aperture.

"Youngsters are so energetic, they don't even want their loot. This is a Gu Immortal's corpse, even though his Immortal Gu cannot be obtained, all of his dao marks are still here. Hehehe..." Nian Er Fu shook his head.

Even though he was a rank seven Gu Immortal senior, he was a greedy person, even when Nian Er Ping Zhi and Old Monster Corpse Poison were fighting, engaging in a tough battle, he did not help but instead, he was taking the Gu Immortal corpse that Nian Er Ping Zhi had left behind.

"Die! Die!"

"This is mine, nobody should try to take it from me."

"I, Meng Ji, am here, who dares to fight me?!"

...

The scene was getting more chaotic, because after Nian Er Ping Zhi attacked, the other righteous path Gu Immortals also started taking action, entering Iron Eagle blessed land. This way, all sorts of conflicts rose up, battles occurred over all sorts of resources.

The cries of eagles could be heard continuously.

A desolate beast peacock raised its head, showing a deep human emotion of desire in its eyes.

This was naturally the Peacock Flying Immortal He Ruo.

"So many iron crown eagles! Hei tribe's Iron Eagle blessed land truly lives up to its name." He Ruo thought: "If I can enslave all of these desolate beasts..."

Iron Eagle blessed land had less space on the ground and much more in the sky. The resources on the ground were much less valuable than the ones in the sky.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals did not show themselves, but they had mobilized all of their iron crown eagles, sealing the sky.

Large numbers of desolate beast iron crown eagles flew in the sky, anyone who trespassed was assaulted intensely by them!

Because of this, most of the demonic path Gu Immortals chose to take action on the ground, they wanted to first obtain the resources on the ground.

A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush.

To He Ruo, the iron crown eagles held immense attraction.

Because in her cultivation plan, her next transformation was the iron crown eagle transformation!

The desolate beast peacock flew in the sky, it was fast, in a moment, He Ruo attracted the attention of several iron crown eagles.

He Ruo was alert internally, she quickly retreated from the iron crown eagles that she lured.

She was alone, she could not fight so many desolate beast iron crown eagles.

She planned to lure one away and fight it alone, slowly capturing it.

...

"This is affinity wood?" Murong Qing Si landed, looking at the rootless tree growing in the pond, her eyes shone brightly.

"Fairy Murong, you are very perceptive, that is it." A lone cultivator Gu Immortal answered.

He was named Yun Liang, known as Cloud Gentleman, he had arrived before Murong Qing Si, he was concentrating on collecting the affinity wood here.

Murong Qing Si saw that Cloud Gentleman Yun Liang was taking action, she did not obstruct him, she only watched quietly.

She patiently waited until Yun Liang succeeded in keeping all of the affinity wood.

"I am ashamed for making fairy wait." Cloud Gentleman Yun Liang said with a polite and warm attitude.

Murong Qing Si smiled: "To tell the truth, this affinity wood is only a rank six immortal material, but it is very suitable for me. I wonder if we can spar and..."

Cloud Gentleman smiled, before Murong Qing Si finished her words, he said: "Affinity wood is very fragile, the collection process cannot have any interference. Fairy, if not for your patience, how could I have obtained it? We can spar, if you win, I will hand all of the affinity wood to you."

Murong Qing Si shook her head: "No need for everything, I only need half."

"Fairy, please."

"Gentleman, please."

The two fought without using their true strength, a victor was not decided.

Cloud Gentleman Yun Liang gave half of the affinity wood to Murong Qing Si, both of them left with satisfaction.

The vast majority of righteous path Gu Immortals conducted themselves with a lot of self restraint and politeness.

Nian Er tribe's Nian Er Ping Zhi and Nian Er Fu were exceptions among the righteous path.

Even though righteous path was flourishing in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, suppressing the demonic path and lone immortals, the righteous path Gu Immortals who came just now could not match the numbers of the demonic path and lone immortals.

The reason was: The rest of the Huang Jin tribes had their own territories and resources to defend. Even though the righteous path had many Gu Immortals, they had to guard different places, only these people could be sent out in the end.

In contrast, the demonic path and lone cultivators did not have such problems.

There was another reason, the super forces had huge assets, they had mortal forces under them. They were quite tolerant towards lone demonic immortals and lone immortals. As long as their benefits were not touched, they would not fight it out.

Gu Immortals were not easy to kill, if a grudge was established, they would go and attack their territories, it would be a huge headache even for super forces.

As the saying goes, he who is down need not fear falling.

On the other side, Unfettered Scholar and Pi Shui Han had decided a victor.

Pi Shui Han had a brand new immortal killer move, but he could not compete against Unfettered Scholar's trademark killer move — Thousand Disintegrations.

Pi Shui Han snorted, directly leaving without hesitation.

It was not worth going all out just for some simple resources.

Even though demonic path Gu Immortals were free, they often worked alone, when calamities and tribulations descended, they had to rely on themselves, they were not like righteous path forces with Gu Immortals in their tribes to rely on, and seek help from.

Thus, demonic path Gu Immortals and lone immortals were very wary of their calamities and tribulations, they often calculated the cost of fighting, it was okay to fight over resources, but if the immortal essence expenditure was too high, they would not proceed with a losing deal!

In the sky of Iron Eagle blessed land, the Immortal Gu House Golden Dawn Hall was still floating at the original spot, shining with dazzling golden light.

Gu Immortals of Gong tribe and Bai Zu tribe had not acted, they were talking inside the hall.

Gong tribe's Gong Er was already anxious, but he showed nothing on his expression, mentioning casually: "Everyone is fighting over Iron Eagle blessed land's resources on the ground, there is barely anything left. Is your tribe not going in yet?"

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals looked at each other, shaking their heads and smiling: "The precious resources inside Iron Eagle blessed land are in the sky. Hei tribe's Gu Immortals have not appeared yet, the battle is just in the middle stage now."

Gong Er was amazed and surprised.

Even though this Bai Zu tribe was in the righteous path now, protected by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, its foundation could not compare to the Huang Jin tribes.

At this moment, Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were acting calm and composed, with no anxiousness or hastiness at all, it was truly confusing.

Chapter 1107: Hei Tribe's Huge Battle (3/3)

"Fourth one!" Peacock Flying Immortal He Ruo took down another iron crown eagle, she was feeling very happy.

Desolate beasts were not common.

In the Northern Plains' ten great fierce areas, desolate beasts lived in groups, few Gu Immortals dared to venture into them.

And wild iron crown eagles and the ones Hei tribe nurtured had different battle strength.

And because Peacock Flying Immortal had good battle tactics, she made great gains, capturing four iron crown eagles.

"Hei tribe is famous for raising iron crown eagles, I really wonder how they did manage to raise so many iron crown eagles here?" He Ruo sighed as she looked towards the sky.

There were still large numbers of iron crown eagles flying in the sky. They were a huge group, He Ruo capturing four was nothing to the group.

"Strange... Hei tribe's Gu Immortals had not appeared since the beginning. Even after I captured four iron crown eagles, they are not going to care?"

He Ruo was wary, she was not overwhelmed by happiness over victory.

Suddenly, there was a loud sound!

A figure clad in wind and lightning rushed towards the eagle group.

He Ruo's pupils shrunk, she recognized this person: "It is Nu Er Gu! Heh, they are in for trouble."

Nu Er Gu came from Nu Er tribe, part of the Huang Jin bloodline, and a super force.

Nu Er Gu had a small head and big belly, his body was disproportional, his eyeballs were popping out, while his limbs were dry as twigs, he had pale skin resembling a sick person, without any hint of pinkness on his face.

But looks were deceiving, he was a famous expert among rank seven Gu Immortals, he was on the same level as Unfettered Scholar and Pi Shui Han in the demonic path.

Nu Er Gu's charge angered the iron crown eagle group.

At once, more than fifty iron crown eagles charged towards him.

Nu Er Gu was shocked, he did not expect that he would draw so much attention.

The eagle group attacked, casting huge shadows and shrouded Nu Er Gu's vision.

In the moment of crisis, Nu Er Gu used his signature immortal killer move.

His body inflated rapidly, expanding to six times of the original, making Nu Er Gu look like a highly pregnant woman.

Nu Er Gu stretched out his hand, patting his belly.

Boom!

A loud sound with huge sound waves caused the eagle group's movement to halt.

Boom boom boom!

Three huge sounds were made, sound waves spread out one after another, the eagle group's momentum was interrupted, their formation became messy and disorganized.

Nu Er Gu growled, as the surrounding iron crown eagles instantly felt dizzy.

Next, he flew rapidly away from the gaps between these eagles, getting out of their encirclement.

The eagle group chased for a while, before returning to their original spot.

Nu Er Gu had already landed on the ground, he was sweating as he looked at the sky, his belly had shrunk already, but he still felt some lingering fear.

On one side, one voice could be heard: "Nu Er Gu, why are you so pathetic?"

Nu Er Gu looked over, he saw that the person was over eight feet tall, he had bright red pupils and dark blue skin, with purple hair and sharp fangs.

Nu Er Gu snorted coldly: "Enough sarcasm, Guan Chou! If you have guts, charge in like me."

Guan Chou snickered: "Two fists cannot rival four palms, I am not as stupid as you."

"You!" Nu Er Gu was furious, he stared at Guan Chou, his eyes spewing fire.

Guan Chou laughed coldly, staring at him fearlessly.

Nu Er Gu was a famous righteous path rank seven expert, cultivating sound path. Guan Chou was not weaker than him, he cultivated transformation path. The two were Gu Immortals from Guan tribe and Nu Er tribe respectively, they had an equally strong background.

"As expected of a famous expert, even though he looked troubled, he is unharmed." He Ruo saw everything, she quickly retracted her gaze.

"Nu Er Gu is here, and Guan Chou's attention is also on these iron crown eagles. This means that the resources on the ground are mostly taken already." He Ruo quietly retreated.

She was only a demonic path Gu Immortal with rank six cultivation level, she did not dare to get too close to these two righteous path experts.

Iron Eagle blessed land's battle continued to rage like wildfire, all sorts of battles of different scales were unfolding.

Some battles ended with a winner and a loser, while other battles involved deaths.

Some made great gains, while some escaped with heavy injuries.

On the ground of the blessed land, resources were dwindling. Some bottom tier Gu Immortals were eliminated, either dead or injured, some wisely chose to retreat, while others had methods to preserve their lives, they hid somewhere and observed the situation quietly.

More and more Gu Immortals placed their focus in the sky.

Countless greedy gazes swept through the iron crown eagle group in the sky. As well as the hidden round ball wooden eagle nests that were concealed by the eagle group.

The scale of the eagle group was huge, this was the accumulation of Hei tribe after countless years, they had expended so much time, effort, and fortune into it! These were among the most valuable resources in Iron Eagle blessed land.

Even people like Nu Er Gu could not block the attacks of the iron crown eagles.

The number was too great!

Of course, it was also because Nu Er Gu was unwilling to waste immortal essence.

His goldfish eyes looked down, seeing more and more Gu Immortals, he shouted: "There are too many iron crown eagles, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals have not shown themselves yet, we should all go ahead and split up this eagle group among ourselves!"

"I concur!" Unfettered Scholar was the first to respond.

The two were in the righteous path and demonic path respectively, but in this situation, they came to a consensus — they should first deal with the eagle group and get the benefits.

The eagle group was huge, there were many Gu Immortals, if they worked together, these iron crown eagles were meat on the chopping block.

Someone struck first, causing the start of the battle between immortals and eagles.

Huge attacks were unleashed, driving intense fights.

Eagles screeched shrilly, while humans were also yelling loudly.

Attacks of all elements were shot out, lightning flashed as golden lights flickered.

Outside the blessed land, Gong Er sat inside the Golden Dawn Hall, looking down. In his vision, there were rainbow colored fireworks that covered the whole sky. But there was intense killing intent in the fireworks, at times, iron crown eagles died, their bodies were cut into pieces, while some iron crown eagles were also captured.

Gong Er's eyes shined.

Scenes of battles between the righteous path, demonic path, and lone immortals were secretly recorded by him using hidden Gu worms.

This was precious intelligence!

Ever since the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, large numbers of Immortal Gu were obtained by Northern Plains Gu Immortals. After Qin Bai Sheng held the auction, Gu Immortals obtained the resources they wanted. After some time of adapting, many Gu Immortals gained new methods, their battle strengths had increased drastically.

Gu Immortals who were doing the same thing as Gong Er were not few in number.

Everyone had the same intention.

Intelligence was very important.

Be it other super forces or lone Gu Immortals, in most cases, knowing what Immortal Gu your opponent had meant that you could find a way to counter them. Even if you did not have any ways to do so, it was still good to be on guard against them.

Gu Immortals fought the iron crown eagles as they observed, collecting information.

Underneath the intense battles were undercurrents of plots and schemes.

Gu Immortals were assessing themselves and their enemies, confirming their status in the current Gu Immortal world. After this period of cultivation, did they get stronger or weaker relative to others? Who could be bullied, while who could not be trifled with?

Iron crown eagles were just the material gain at present, while information was a long term gain.

Gong Er watched for a while, feeling more and more impatient.

The three Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals beside him had not moved at all since the battle in Hei tribe's headquarters started.

Just now, he brought Gong tribe's Golden Dawn Hall in order to gain great benefits, that was the only way to make this trip worth it.

Gong Er could not stand it anymore, he pointed down, telling the Gu Immortals that came with him: "Iron Eagle blessed land is taking damage, there are over a thousand flaws created. But now, not a single Hei tribe Gu Immortal has appeared, this is very strange. Go down and assist our comrades, and preempt Hei tribe's scheme. We of Gong tribe are the leaders of the righteous path, we have to defend our allies."

"Yes." The two Gong tribe Gu Immortals immediately acted.

The three Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals sat there inwardly laughing to themselves.

The outcome of this Hei tribe battle was decided from the beginning. Even if something strange happened, there was no danger. Gong tribe's Gu Immortals acted like this out of their own interests, they had selfish motives, but they still wanted to pretend to be grand and selfless.

At the same time, at the highest area of Iron Eagle blessed land.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were gathered, they looked at the battle, they had heavy feelings and ugly expressions.

"Why is he not acting yet?"

"At this stage, he has not done anything yet. Don't tell me, our agreement has been canceled?"

Some Hei tribe Gu Immortals asked this, feeling uneasy.

"He had already agreed, with his status, he will not go back on the agreement."

"Let's watch first. We set up three layers of defense, the iron crown eagle group is only the first."

Hei tribe's first supreme elder and second supreme elder spoke, calming the immortals.

He Ruo transformed into a desolate beast peacock, spreading her wings and fighting with three iron crown eagles.

This was just a small part of the huge battlefield, and she was just an insignificant Gu Immortal among countless others.

In the absence of rank eight, rank seven experts were the strongest, some rank six experts were attempting to gain benefits along the periphery.

Suddenly, there was a weird fragrance!

He Ruo's heart jumped, she quickly held her breath.

"I'm poisoned!" Sensing this, He Ruo quickly used her healing Gu worms.

Three iron crown eagles cried out, in an instant, they could not exert any strength anymore, they fell to the ground weakly.

A figure flew into the sky, capturing these three iron crown eagles and stuffing them inside his immortal aperture.

It was Old Monster Corpse Poison!

He laughed sinisterly, purple gas coiling around him. After collecting the three iron crown eagles, he looked at He Ruo with an evil grin.

He Ruo's heart shook, she felt her body turning cold.

"Hehehe, young lady, come with me." Old Monster Corpse Poison breathed out air towards He Ruo.

He Ruo had just suppressed the poison in her body, when she suddenly lost control of her body, she felt weak and fell towards the ground after Old Monster Corpse Poison blew at her from a distance.

"I was too greedy! I wanted to obtain more iron crown eagles and placed too much of my attention on them, neglecting the surroundings and being sneak attacked by Old Monster Corpse Poison!" Seeing that she was about to be captured by Old Monster Corpse Poison, He Ruo felt deep despair.

At this moment, a sword light flew over.

The sword light was fast as lightning, it boldly pierced through Old Monster Corpse Poison's body, before turning into Nian Er Ping Zhi a hundred steps away.

Old Monster Corpse Poison was bursting with rage: "Little rascal, you are still finding trouble with me!"

Chapter 1108: Tragic

Because of his interruption, He Ruo managed to suppress her poison and quickly escaped, regaining freedom.

Nian Er Ping Zhi's body was tattered, one of his arms was corroded until only bones were left, his face was turning purple, he was deeply poisoned.

But he raised his head and looked at Old Monster Corpse Poison, saying arrogantly: "You cannot leave until a victor is decided."

Old Monster Corpse Poison was furious, but within his anger, there was also regret.

Why did he attract this psycho?

"Every Sword Child in each generation is crazy. But this one is crazier than the rest." Far away, Nian Er Fu shook his head, waving his fat little arms.

An iron crown eagle screeched in fear, it flapped its arms desperately, trying to escape, but with the power of space path, the iron crown eagle vanished, entering Nian Er Fu's immortal aperture without resistance!

Old Monster Corpse Poison's method was vicious, he attacked Nian Er Ping Zhi, but most of his attention was still kept on Nian Er Fu secretly.

Nian Er Ping Zhi had rank six cultivation level, even though he inherited a portion of the Sword Saint true inheritance, he was not the match of a rank seven expert like Old Monster Corpse Poison.

Nian Er Ping Zhi could survive until now because Nian Er Fu had been assisting him from a distance all along.

Nian Er Fu was a space path Gu Immortal, he had a deep cultivation level, with countless methods at his disposal. He was looting resources all over the place, gaining a huge fortune, while protecting Nian Er Ping Zhi, preventing Old Monster Corpse Poison from dealing a fatal blow.

Old Monster Corpse Poison felt more and more regret.

Right now was a precious opportunity that one would not see in a hundred years, but he was fighting with a Gu Immortal here, while others were looting resources all over the place.

Old Monster Corpse Poison was famous and had a deep background. He had once joined Zombie Alliance as a living person, before betraying them later on. Northern Plains Zombie Alliance tried to capture him, but failed each time.

Nian Er Ping Zhi and Old Monster Corpse Poison fought, the battle getting more and more heated as time passed, even though he could not win, he had become famous from the fight.

From now on, Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world would know that Nian Er tribe had produced such an incredible genius!

Actually, Gu Immortals from other super forces would not offend a demonic path Gu Immortal so thoroughly.

But Nian Er tribe was different.

This Huang Jin bloodline tribe was different from the other Huang Jin super tribes — their tribesmen lived in blessed lands or grotto-heavens, they did not occupy any territory in the outside world of Northern Plains.

This way, they had little reservations.

Even if a demonic path Gu Immortal wanted to attack them, they could not.

After all, there were few methods to enter immortal apertures. Even if one could get in, they would be in the enemy's territory, they would lose a lot of their advantage inside.

"Youth is really wondrous." Nian Er Fu sighed, he spoke with an aged tone, but he had the appearance of a chubby boy, it was a really weird sight.

Only Old Monster Corpse Poison could feel his terrifying power.

During this battle, Nian Er Fu had already attacked dozens of times, not only did he save Nian Er Ping Zhi's life, he even successfully injured Old Monster Corpse Poison secretly a few times.

After capturing several iron crown eagles again, Nian Er Fu's field of vision was cleared.

A huge round ball wooden eagle nest was floating in the air, without any defense.

"I had heard of Hei tribe having this special rearing method, they use some sort of metal or ore, immortal materials that could increase the rate of the iron crown eagles' reproduction, and speeding up the rate of their growth. What kinds of precious immortal materials would be in this nest?"

Nian Er Fu was about to move, when his expression suddenly froze.

A figure moved like the raging winds, flying out of the nest before him, rapidly leaving towards the horizon.

Demonic path Gu Immortal Hui Feng Zi!

This was a rank seven wind path expert, publicly recognized as the fastest person in Northern Plains, even Yao Huang could not stop him. He had first joined Shadow Sect, before submitting to Heavenly Court, his identity as a traitor had not been exposed yet.

In a situation filled with chaos, Hui Feng Zi could act freely like the wind.

Not only was he fast, he was agile, he displayed the greatest advantage of wind path to its limit.

Soon, Nian Er Fu saw that Hui Feng Zi easily passed through countless obstacles, entering another eagle nest.

"Sigh, this lad is simply blocking me from my fortune!" Nian Er Fu gazed at Nian Er Ping Zhi, sighing loudly at the sky.

The battle between humans and eagles came to an end.

The number of iron crown eagles decreased, all of the round ball wooden eagle nests were invaded by Gu Immortals.

"Good, good, good! It is the rank seven immortal material domination copper!" Gu Immortal Shi Hou cheered, he had made great gains.

"This damned Hui Feng Zi, he dares to snatch what is mine!" Meng Ji was furious, he stared fixedly at Hui Feng Zi who was flying away.

Hui Feng Zi did not speak, but he felt very troubled: He did not touch that eagle nest. It seemed that someone who had already sneaked in made him take the blame for their actions!

Within the round ball wooden eagle nests, there were rank seven immortal materials in each one, either metals or ores, and they were huge in quantity.

Gu Immortals made great gains, they expressed joy on their faces.

This was simply a feast, they were looting all of Hei tribe's hard work. The stronger the Gu Immortal, the greater the gains, the law of the jungle in the Gu Immortal world was displayed here in full view.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were deadly silent.

They looked at the round ball wooden eagle nests that were fuming with smoke, some had fallen to the ground, some were incredibly damaged, spinning in the air.

These nests were the pride of Hei tribe, the symbol of their strength. But now, they were trampled and snatched away.

Anger.

Indignance.

Hatred.

Fear.

All sorts of emotions were in these Hei tribe Gu Immortals, they almost could not breathe.

"Enough!" A Hei tribe Gu Immortal stood up abruptly.

He had a huge body, he looked around with an angry gaze, fixing it on first supreme elder: "When are we going to wait until? You are counting on him? Can't you see? He had agreed to us on purpose, so that we would not keep the resources according to the agreement, we are trapped inside the blessed land and cannot leave."

"This is a scheme, he is toying with us! Everyone, where is your courage? Are you not angry? Don't you feel hatred? Will we sit here and wait for death, or go out and fight like courageous heroes? This is our home! But now, these outsiders are plundering and destroying it!!"

"Tie Sheng..." Second supreme elder had a complex expression, he called out to this furious Hei tribe Gu Immortal.

"First supreme elder, say something!" Hei Tie Sheng stared at Hei tribe's first supreme elder with an indomitable gaze.

Everyone also looked at first supreme elder.

Hei tribe's first supreme elder was silent for a while before saying: "In this situation, resources are just external things, so what if we give them up? If we do not receive his help, we will have no place in the whole of Northern Plains! We will wait and see."

Hei Tie Sheng heard this and his body shook, he took in a deep breath, stabilizing his body. He did not feel rage now, just intense sorrow.

"Seniors, in my humble opinion, I think that Lord Hei Tie Sheng is right." This time, a rank six Gu Immortal from Hei tribe spoke.

"I have the same opinion."

"If we do not fight now, when will we wait until?"

"The worst case is death anyway!"

More and more Hei tribe Gu Immortals stood up.

Hei Tie Sheng saw this and felt a strong surge in confidence, his gaze regained its sharpness.

"You..." Second supreme elder was shocked.

First supreme elder remained silent.

Hei Tie Sheng suddenly laughed loudly: "Three layers of defense? Even if we have thirty layers of defense, what can we do in this situation? Go! Let's face these enemies! How can Hei tribe's glory be tarnished? Hei tribe's resources are not so easy to take! They will pay with blood and their lives!"

Hei Tie Sheng took huge steps forward, he turned around and left the hall.

Seven Hei tribe Gu Immortals said nothing, but they followed him with firm expressions.

"First supreme elder, won't you talk to them..." Third supreme elder was uneasy.

"Forget it, forget it, let them go." First supreme elder sighed, he seemed to have aged by a hundred years.

Hei tribe's first layer of defense was broken already, the iron crown eagles were either dead, injured, or captured, none were left.

The Gu Immortals flew up higher into the sky, seeing dragon eagles.

A large number of dragon eagles formed the second line of defense.

"So many dragon eagles!" Someone's eyes flashed.

"Even though the dragon eagles are not as numerous as the iron crown eagles, they are still a huge fortune!" Someone critiqued.

Some impatient Gu Immortals had already started attacking.

The Gu Immortals gasped, some were surprised, they found something strange.

"These dragon eagles are not normal."

"That's right, I've interacted with desolate beast dragon eagles before, how can they be so hard to deal with?"

"These dragon eagles have stronger vitality and faster speed, is that rumor from long ago true after all?"

The immortals were reminded by this, fifty to sixty years ago, there were rumors in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world that Hei tribe had obtained a huge breakthrough in nurturing the dragon eagles, they created a brand new species of desolate eagles, they looked like dragon eagles, but were different.

"These are not dragon eagles, they are resonance eagles. These eagles were not created by Hei tribe, they were the fruits of my Qiao tribe's labor!" A Gu Immortal said with much anguish.

Everyone looked over, it was Qiao Dong.

He was a righteous path Gu Immortal, the first supreme elder of Qiao tribe.

Qiao tribe was a subordinate of Hei tribe, long ago, Qiao tribe had wanted to leave Hei tribe, and were taught a lesson by Hei Cheng, who went to pressure them.

No wonder Qiao tribe and Hei tribe had a conflict, there was lots of hidden background information!

The immortals had differing expressions, but they said nothing about this.

The law of the jungle was very common after all.

This Qiao Dong could become an immortal because of Hei tribe's support. Now that Hei tribe was in trouble, he joined in and attacked Iron Eagle blessed land.

Most righteous path Gu Immortals, the supreme elders of the Huang Jin tribes, looked towards Qiao Dong with coldness and animosity.

They did not like people who bit the hand that fed them.

But behind Qiao Dong, there was Liu tribe's Gu Immortal, Liu Zhuan Shen.

With a single glance, it was obvious that Qiao Dong was now under Liu tribe.

Liu tribe and Hei tribe had a poor relationship, Qiao tribe was a subordinate of Hei tribe, but now that Hei tribe was going down, Qiao Dong went over to Liu tribe, it was not strange.

"This traitor deserves death!"

At this moment, a thunderous voice came from afar!

Chapter 1109: Hmph!

No sooner said than done!

A shadow resembling a mountain crashed towards Qiao Dong.

In an instant, Qiao Dong was immobilized, he could only scream: "Elder Liu, save me!"

Liu Zhuan Shen swiftly appeared in front of Qiao Dong, his body shone with white light, causing all of the darkness to fade away.

"Hei Tie Sheng, with me here, you cannot harm Qiao Dong." Liu Zhuan Shen looked at the person with intense battle intent.

The Gu Immortals started stirring.

Be it the dragon eagles or resonance eagles, they were not important.

The important thing was, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals had finally acted!

With the rank seven Gu Immortal Hei Tie Sheng as the leader, seven rank six Gu Immortals followed behind him, standing before the immortals.

Hei Tie Sheng looked around, before his gaze fixed on Liu Zhuan Shen, he snickered, asking: "Is that so?"

Liu Zhuan Shen's expression turned to shock, he turned around and looked.

Qiao Dong was still standing behind him, floating in the air, but his expression had frozen with shock, he had no vitality left, he was dead.

"Immortal killer move life draining darkness!" Liu Zhuan Shen shouted before feeling intense anger, but his anger soon faded as only sadness and admiration remained.

He and Hei Tie Sheng were old rivals, they had fought for more than a hundred times. he was clear that this life draining darkness was powerful, but it could not be used easily, each activation had a huge cost.

Liu Zhuan Shen had never seen Hei Tie Sheng use this trump card at the start of the battle.

From this, he understood: His rival for many years had prepared himself to die, he had the mentality of killing as many enemies as possible before going down.

Hei Tie Sheng looked Qiao Dong, the morale of the Hei tribe Gu Immortals behind him rose.

Hei Tie Sheng was an experienced person, using this chance, he used his methods.

At once, the resonance eagles formed into groups, moving in formation. Each of the Hei tribe Gu Immortals went to an area and defended territory.

With Gu Immortals here, the second line of defense stabilized, they were hard to deal with.

This made many Gu Immortals who invaded Hei tribe furious.

Ruining a person's wealth was like killing their parents!

This hatred was huge, and because Hei tribe was weak, they lost their only Immortal Gu House Dark Prison, the only problem was Green City Rampage. But in this situation, Hei tribe was only struggling at death's door.

"I'll fight you!" Pi Shui Han pounced.

He waved his hand, as tides began to form, charging towards Hei Tie Sheng.

The tides flew into the air and stopped, turning into glaciers as the temperature fell.

"Be careful, this is Pi Shui Han's signature killer move — Flood Glacier!" A rank six Gu Immortal from Hei tribe shouted.

Hei Tie Sheng laughed lightly, he and Pi Shui Han had deep enmity too, he was not surprised that Pi Shui Han attacked him.

"He is just a loser, so what?" Hei Tie Sheng's eyes shined with dark light, he did not move, he only looked over.

The white glacier was covered with black water, in a few breaths' time, it disintegrated.

Pi Shui Han grunted, spitting out a mouthful of blood, falling from the sky.

"Against so many enemies, consecutive killer moves are not easy to use." A figure appeared behind Hei Tie Sheng.

It was Huang Di!

This was the rank seven demonic path Gu Immortal who communicated with the other demonic path members, entering Iron Eagle blessed land first and causing the righteous path to lose the initiative.

He had earned immensely, right now, he was using the chance to attack and kill Hei Tie Sheng!

Hei Tie Sheng did not move, he did not even turn around, he only waved his sleeves.

Immediately, dark light burst out like waves, sending Huang Di far away.

Huang Di struggled to get out of the black tide, showing shock on his face. His seven orifices were spewing out black blood, he drilled into the ground without even a bit of hesitation, vanishing.

"Simply a rat, what can you do?" Hei Tie Sheng snorted, looking around, shouting: "Who is next?"

Nobody came.

Hei Tie Sheng had incredible battle strength, he was even stronger than Pi Shui Han.

The immortals could tell, this person was prepared to die, he was oozing with fighting intent and was fighting without reservation, in this situation, his battle strength was at its peak.

Why did everyone come to Iron Eagle blessed land?

To gain fortune!

If their goal was fortune, why would they fight with this person to the death?

The Gu Immortals moved away, evading Hei Tie Sheng.

Battle commenced.

One side was the collaboration of righteous and demonic, they had great numbers, but Hei tribe had the territorial advantage and large numbers of desolate beast resonance eagles to help them.

Battles raged on.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were all prepared to die defending their home, their battle intent was high.

The demonic path Gu Immortals just wanted a fortune, they did not want to die, they were heavily restricted.

The intelligence of Gu Immortals could not be matched by iron crown eagles.

At once, the second line of defense was extremely stable!

Hei Tie Sheng saw that everyone was avoiding him, so he approached them instead.

"Meng Ji, hand over your life!" Hei Tie Sheng shouted angrily, pouncing towards the Meng tribe rank seven Gu Immortal who was closest to him.

"Hmph, would I be afraid of you?" Meng Ji fought back courageously.

Boom boom boom!

The two fought as the sky rumbled, intense shock waves were sent out.

After several rounds, the proud and arrogant Meng Ji turned around and fled.

He was courageous, but Hei Tie Sheng was beyond courageous, he was a lunatic not afraid of death!

He fought with Meng Ji by causing injuries to both of them, he was trying to go down together.

After several times, Meng Ji could not stand it anymore, he immediately retreated.

Hei Tie Sheng was going to chase him, but he heard the Hei tribe Gu Immortals cry for help, he turned around to help them out.

"Guan Chou, take this!" Hei Tie Sheng charged forward, dark light burst out and engulfed the surroundings.

Guan Chou was a transformation path Gu Immortal, he had turned into a lion. He roared as he crashed into Hei Tie Sheng.

At the next moment, the lion that Guan Chou had transformed into flew out like a rag doll.

Hei Tie Sheng charged at him again.

Guan Chou screeched, turning into a little bird and flying away.

"Coward!" Hei Tie Sheng could not catch up, he snorted.

His gaze swept around, he targeted the rank seven Gu Immortal who was closer to him, Liu Zhuan Shen.

Liu Zhuan Shen was very perceptive!

Seeing that Hei Tie Sheng was approaching, he retreated.

Hei Tie Sheng chased after him, so Liu Zhuan Shen went over to Divine Lord Tian Du.

Divine Lord Tian Du's body shook, he turned around and left.

Liu Zhuan Shen then lured Hei Tie Sheng towards Unfettered Scholar, he snorted as a three-way battle started.

Boom boom boom!

A moment later, in an intense clash, Liu Zhuan Shen and Unfettered Scholar were forced back.

Hei Tie Sheng continued to fight everyone, he was unstoppable.

In the sky, Hei tribe's first supreme elder sighed: "Tie Sheng, this child..."

He knew that Hei Tie Sheng had a special technique, he could expend his lifespan to increase the power of his killer moves.

He was fighting by consuming his life!

The righteous and demonic Gu Immortals did not want to die, that was true. But with just this reason, there was no way anybody could contest him.

Hei Tie Sheng was a huge setback to the Gu Immortals.

These were all people with high cultivation level and impressive methods. In the earlier battles, the weaker Gu Immortals were already eliminated.

But no matter how strong Hei Tie Sheng was, he could not reach the level of rank eight.

He could not turn around the situation singlehandedly.

Resonance eagles were captured or killed, while Hei tribe's Gu Immortals died one by one.

Fight!

A fight to the death!

Towards the end of the battle, Hei Tie Sheng was the only one left.

He was bathed in blood, he stood proud and straight, looking at the Gu Immortals around, he laughed loudly: "Alright, come and kill me!"

The immortals looked around, but nobody moved.

Liu Zhuan Shen's expression was complex, he knew that Hei Tie Sheng was already out of steam. His immortal essence was expended, he was not a threat.

But he was unable to attack!

Hei Tie Sheng moved his lips: "Then let me!"

Saying so, he charged towards the Gu Immortals in front.

Charge!

His final charge.

He died while charging.

It was tragic.

It was courageous.

Hei Tie Sheng died, the immortals had no obstacles left, they went towards Hei tribe's final line of defense.

Twelve flying eagles blocked them.

Enemy eagles with overflowing killing intent, absolute eyebrow eagles with divine aura, shadow eagles with indistinct figures, whale swallowing eagles with huge muscular bodies...

Without exception, they were all ancient desolate beasts, having rank seven battle strength.

Hei tribe's first supreme elder and the other six elders descended from the sky.

At this moment, they no longer placed further hope in being saved, they came out to battle.

Ancient battle formation, Green City Rampage!

The top four supreme elders joined forces, their might could rival rank eight Gu Immortals.

The righteous and demonic Gu Immortals split up at once.

Resources were more important.

By now, everyone had already earned a lot, but they paid a huge price too. Their mental energy was depleted, their immortal essence was also expended, who would fight against Green City Rampage in this state?

Whoever got caught would simply be unlucky!

In the sky of Iron Eagle blessed land, there were twelve eagle nests that were in peculiar shapes.

These eagle nests were not round ball wooden eagle nests, they held precious rank eight immortal materials.

Immediately, countless Gu Immortals fought over them.

The battle was a chaotic mess!

Green City Rampage went on a killing spree, lots of unlucky people died in the top four supreme elders' hands.

Humans die for wealth and birds die for food.

"This is too dangerous, let's go, let's go." Nian Er Fu grabbed the unconscious Nian Er Ping Zhi as he sneakily retreated.

"I cannot stay here." Pi Shui Han also retreated, he had obtained some eagle nests, and had gained large amounts of rank eight immortal materials.

Some astute Gu Immortals were leaving.

The twelve eagle nests were all lost.

Suddenly, in the air, there were ripples as a thirteenth eagle nest appeared, drawing everyone's attention.

The immortals shouted, pouncing over.

"This is mine." Chu Du suddenly appeared, blocking all the immortals.

"Ah, Domination Immortal!" The immortals were shocked, stopping their movement.

Chu Du was powerful, far stronger than Hei Tie Sheng!

Liu tribe's entire strength as a super force could do nothing to him. In the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world, only people like Qin Bai Sheng could fight him.

At this stage in the battle, everyone was in poor conditions.

But this was the first time Chu Du was acting.

At once, nobody dared to go forward.

Chu Du successfully deterred the immortals, it was to obtain this mysterious thirteenth eagle nest.

Green City Rampage came crashing, a voice was loud as thunder: "Chu Du, you dare?"

Chu Du laughed coldly: "Why wouldn't I?"

Boom!

The two sides clashed, the giant that Green City Rampage transformed into was sent flying by Chu Du in one move.

"The ancient battle formation is powerful, but it is powered by you people. In your condition, none of you can match me." Chu Du stood arrogantly in the air, looking at the immortals.

The immortals wanted to attack, but they also wanted others to do the work, so that they could reap the benefits.

"Simply a mob." Chu Du commented, before going ahead to grab at the eagle nest behind him.

Suddenly, a shocking change occurred.

An Immortal Gu House appeared, crashing towards Chu Du's head.

"Modest Thatched Hut!" A Gu Immortal yelled, he recognized that this was Dong Fang tribe's former Immortal Gu House!

"Scram!" Chu Du slapped, creating a huge sound.

Thud!!

Bam, Modest Thatched Hut was actually sent flying by his slap.

Gasp!

Everyone took in a deep breath of shock.

Chu Du successfully placed the thirteenth eagle nest into his own immortal aperture.

Next, his gaze fell on Green City Rampage.

The four supreme elders felt a wave of despair.

"Wait." Just as Chu Du was about to deal the killing blow, a voice resounded in the entire place.

An immeasurable aura, like a formless mountain, enveloped the entire area in an instant.

Rank eight Gu Immortal, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!

The immortals were shaken, the identity of the voice appeared in their minds.

At this point in the battle, a rank eight Gu Immortal had finally shown up!

It was not certain that he came in person, after all, only his voice was heard.

"Wasn't it agreed upon that the rank eight great experts would not personally interfere?" Some righteous path Gu Immortals who knew some inside information were confused.

At the next moment, the immortals heard Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's voice: "Hei tribe's battle ends here, the remaining members of Hei tribe have submitted to me. From now on, this is Bai Zu tribe's territory."

"We are willing to change our surnames to Bai Zu!" Hei tribe's elders responded.

The immortals were shaken, this matter was huge, the situation in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world would immediately change!

Smarter people knew: Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could say this because he had come to an agreement with the other rank eight great experts.

"No need to leave, I am holding a banquet for three days and three nights for everyone." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu said again.

The remaining Hei tribe Gu Immortals' faces twitched.

This battlefield which was still filled with blood from the battle earlier was going to hold a banquet. The change was too sudden and abrupt.

"Congratulations to Bai Zu tribe, congratulations to Heavenly Lord." The righteous path Gu Immortals quickly came to an agreement, giving many responses.

The demonic path and lone immortals were uneasy and agitated.

"Hmph!" Chu Du snorted coldly, it was loud and shrill.

He left with a billowing of his sleeves.

Under everyone's gazes, he flew away into the horizon.

Chapter 1110: Rank Eight Gu Immortals Cannot Be Schemed Against

"Hahaha, he is Domination Immortal indeed, I am leaving too." Amidst the silence, Hui Feng Zi laughed loudly.

Next, winds moved around his body, assisting him in his quick departure.

Countless gazes focused on him as well.

Hui Feng Zi was the fastest person in Northern Plains, Yao Huang had once tried to capture him but failed. That was Hui Feng Zi's greatest and proudest achievement.

Chu Du and Hui Feng Zi had huge guts, they did not give Heavenly Lord Bai Zu face, the other immortals had differing ideas, but nobody dared to leave.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not say anything, he watched as they left.

Hei tribe's first supreme elder quickly shouted: "Reporting to Heavenly Lord, forget about Hui Feng Zi, but Chu Du has taken the thirteenth eagle nest, Hei Fan true inheritance is inside it!"

The immortals heard about this and went into a commotion, they secretly started conversing quietly.

Everyone had heard of Hei Fan's reputation and fame. This person was the pride of Hei tribe's history, he was the one who led Hei tribe to their current status as a super force. If he was still alive, who would dare to attack Hei tribe?

"No need to worry, I know about that." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's spoke again, the tone of his voice was extremely calm and plain!

First supreme elder's heart jumped, his lips trembled, he wanted to speak, but no words came out of his mouth.

Second supreme elder suddenly said: "Reporting to Heavenly Lord, Iron Eagle blessed land is about to break apart. If we set a banquet here, it might not last for even half a day."

"Don't worry, we have already been prepared long ago." At this time, three Gu Immortals appeared together.

The immortals took a look, showing expressions of realization.

These three immortals were none other than the three Gu Immortals from Bai Zu tribe.

During the entire battle in Hei tribe, they were watching from the side, it turned out that they were following Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's orders, they were in charge of settling the aftermath of the battle.

Next, Bai Zu tribe's three Gu Immortals worked together, unleashing an immortal killer move.

The killer move's effect showed immediate result, in a moment, Iron Eagle blessed land which was shaking and breaking apart managed to stabilize.

Seeing this, a lot of the righteous and demonic immortals had changes in their expressions.

This immortal killer move had incredible effect, this was the first time they were seeing it, it had never been used in past records.

They realized that: Bai Zu tribe did not just have Heavenly Lord Bai Zu alone, the other Gu Immortals were also formidable characters.

"Gong Er greets Heavenly Lord." Next, Gong tribe's Gu Immortal Gong Er came forward alone, entering Iron Eagle blessed land and paying respects towards the sky.

In the absence of rank nine, rank eights were the dominating overlords!

Gong Er was a proud person, but facing a rank eight existence, he had to be polite, even though he was feeling moody on the inside.

During the final moments of the battle of Hei tribe, Gong Er wanted to use the Immortal Gu House Golden Dawn Hall to snatch the resources inside.

But the Gu Immortals of Bai Zu tribe smiled as they told him not to act rashly for his own sake.

Gong Er would naturally not listen to them, but soon, he received a message from Prince Feng Xian. The content was: Do not act rashly, otherwise, you are making enemies with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu! If Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is displeased and kills you, you deserve to die, I will definitely not take revenge for you.

Gong Er heard this and did not dare to act, even though he was extremely unwilling internally, he had suffered a huge loss of face.

He had mobilized Golden Dawn Hall to come here and control the situation, but his effort did not match the gains that he had. Originally, Gong Er wanted to act as the leader of the righteous path, but the other Huang Jin bloodline Gu Immortals paid no heed to him at all.

Bai Zu tribe's three Gu Immortals listened to him and went into Golden Dawn Hall as guests. Even though this gave Gong Er some face, the three immortals had hidden intentions.

Gong Er represented Gong tribe, he had to come out. When he greeted Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he felt extremely displeased towards Prince Feng Xian: "Damn it, curses! This time, I completely lost to Prince Feng Xian. Hmph, he is not one of us after all, he is just a son-in-law of Gong tribe, an external supreme elder in our tribe!"

Normally speaking, super forces with family based systems rarely had external supreme elders.

This was unlike Central Continent's sects, they could easily take in others as their external supreme elders.

External elders who join super clans or tribes usually had a close relationship with one of the tribe's Gu Immortals. For example, they could be husband and wife, or blood-sworn brothers.

Fairy Jiang Yu had once joined Hei tribe, she had been Hei Cheng's concubine on the surface.

Prince Feng Xian's true identity was that of a spy from Spirit Affinity House that had entered Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, he was in charge of the great plan of looking over Imperial Court blessed land, and controlling Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

In his early days, he had become the husband of a female Gong tribe immortal. Under Spirit Affinity House's secret help, he had become a rank eight Gu Immortal, he stayed out most of the time and did not interact much with Gong tribe.

Prince Feng Xian stayed inside his own Feng Xian grotto-heaven, he did not pay attention or communicate with his Gong tribe wife, he only stayed with his two female attendant Gu Immortals, You Lan and Le Yao.

Gong tribe was very unhappy because of this, but Prince Feng Xian was a rank eight Gu Immortal, Gong tribe's Gu Immortals could do nothing but hold in their anger.

This time, after Old Ancestor Xue Hu defeated the combination of Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, Gong tribe came up with a plan, they went ahead to brag that Prince Feng Xian was the only person who could defeat Old Ancestor Xue Hu. This way, they could use Prince Feng Xian's reputation to elevate Gong tribe's status in the righteous path. Secondly, they could also force Prince Feng Xian to become enemies with Old Ancestor Xue Hu. If the two of them fought, regardless of victory or defeat, it would benefit Gong tribe.

This plan hit two birds with one stone, but could a rank eight Gu Immortal be schemed against so easily?

This time, Gong Er was taught a huge lesson!

Prince Feng Xian secretly came to an agreement with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, one could guess that Heavenly Lord Bai Zu definitely paid a price for it. Prince Feng Xian concealed this matter, not informing Gong tribe about it. He sacrificed Gong tribe's benefits and kept the gains for himself. But at the crucial moment, he sent a letter, he did not leave behind any evidence that could be used against him. Gong tribe could only endure this silently, after all, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu only gave face to Prince Feng Xian.

Gong tribe did not have any other rank eight expert, strength was the foundation for talking on equal terms!

The three Bai Zu Gu Immortals stabilized Iron Eagle blessed land, it was not only safe now, they even started to repair it. For the next three days, Iron Eagle blessed land held a huge banquet.

In Hei tribe's former headquarters, Bai Zu tribe's rise was declared, the intention was quite extraordinary, there was profound meaning behind it.

Almost all the Gu Immortals joined the celebration, other than exceptions like Domination Immortal and Hui Feng Zi.

Other than these two, there could have been others. For example, the mysterious Gu Immortal who appeared during the battle in Hei tribe, the person who controlled Modest Thatched Hut. It was unknown whether they were hidden among the immortals now, or whether they had left secretly already.

The righteous path Gu Immortals mostly joined in the celebrations on the first day before taking their leave.

Gong tribe with Gong Er as the leading Gu Immortal was the first to leave. When they left, Gong Er walked with confident steps, but people could tell that Gong tribe was in a dejected state.

The second was Nian Er tribe.

Only two Gu Immortals from this super force came to Hei tribe.

One was the rank seven space path Gu Immortal Nian Er Fu, while the other was the current generation Sword Child, Nian Er Ping Zhi.

Even though the latter had only rank six cultivation level, he had gained much reputation in this battle in Hei tribe, he became famous overnight. But he paid a hefty price.

Old Monster Corpse Poison stared at Nian Er Ping Zhi with much hatred, he was gritting his teeth.

The grudge of both parties was immense now.

Meng tribe, Yuan tribe, Nu Er tribe, Ye Lui tribe, and the others took their leave one by one.

Liu tribe, Yao tribe, Guan tribe, these three tribe's Gu Immortals attended for the entire banquet, staying until the end. After three days and nights, they took their leave, they gave Bai Zu tribe ample face.

It was because these three tribes were different from the other Huang Jin tribes, they were quite close to the current Bai Zu tribe's territory, they needed to establish good relationships.

As for the demonic path and lone immortals, they left entirely after three days and nights.

The stronger they were, the earlier they left. There were also certain Gu Immortal experts who stayed back, attempting to get close to Bai Zu tribe.

If it were the other Huang Jin tribes, when holding a celebration, they would not invite all of these people.

But Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had been a lone immortal in the past, the lone immortals and demonic path Gu Immortals could accept his invitation and stayed here.

"See you, see you."

"Until we meet again, forgive us for not sending you off."

During these three days, Iron Eagle blessed land had been completely repaired.

The blessed land's entrance opened, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals and Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals stood at the entrance, speaking in polite tones as they sent off all of the leaving Gu Immortals.

The leaving Gu Immortals, regardless of their faction, sighed to themselves: After this battle in Hei tribe, the entire situation in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world changed!

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals surrendered, they had to send off these Gu Immortals who invaded their homes, they definitely felt uneasy and unhappy. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu made them do this, he was humiliating them.

Among them, Hei tribe's first supreme elder could feel it the most.

During the battle in Hei tribe, he suffered the heaviest injuries. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu personally used his healing methods to heal the rest of the Hei tribe's Gu Immortals, except him.

He was pale, he sent off the guests in an injured state, he spat out blood from time to time, he looked so pathetic, all of his face was gone!

Hei tribe's first supreme elder understood: "I purpose exposed the fact about the Hei Fan true inheritance earlier, I wanted Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to attack Chu Du. If he was killed, we could take revenge for Chu Du's invasion. If he failed, and Chu Du escaped, with his personality, he would definitely exact revenge on Bai Zu tribe. To think that Heavenly Lord Bai Zu chose to do nothing, he knew that this was my scheme, thus, he has been suppressing and punishing me secretly these last three days!"

Sadness, pain, hatred, fear, all sorts of emotions tangled together and filled Hei tribe's first supreme elder.

After sending the final Gu Immortal off, Gu Immortals of Hei tribe and Bai Zu tribe went to meet Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

In the highest level of Iron Eagle blessed land, the original discussion hall of Hei tribe, everyone met with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

"Greetings to Heavenly Lord." The immortals stood on the spot, paying their respects.

"Mm, everyone has worked hard." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu sat at the highest position, he smiled: "From now on, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals will change their surnames to Bai Zu. Hei tribe's resources have been taken by Northern Plains' immortals, that is an established fact. This is also the result that I had gotten after negotiating with the other rank eight experts. In the future, you cannot use this as an excuse to take revenge."

The immortals quickly responded in acknowledgment.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu paused for a while before saying: "But the Hei Fan true inheritance is not a small matter, it involves a rank eight expert. Even if I do not cultivate time path, I can use it as reference. Ignore Chu Du for now, I already know the location of Hei Fan grotto-heaven. After some time, we can forcefully attack it and obtain everything inside!"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not anticipate obtaining the Hei Fan true inheritance.

This true inheritance could not even be obtained by Hei tribe's own members, not to mention him as an outsider.

The true benefit was Hei Fan grotto-heaven, and the countless resources accumulated inside. This was enough to entice any rank eight.

Hei tribe's first supreme elder heard this and felt incredibly shocked!

"Hei Fan grotto-heaven's location is the biggest secret in our tribe. Including me, only the rest of the top four supreme elders know! How can Heavenly Lord Bai Zu learn about it? Don't tell me, someone secretly submitted to him before this? This secret was told to him?!"

Learning about this, Hei tribe's first supreme elder felt a chill going down his spine, his body shuddered in fear.

He knelt on the floor immediately, kowtowing to Heavenly Lord Bai Zu in an extravagant manner: "I have failed in my task, I am greatly at fault! Please punish me, Heavenly Lord!"

"Oh? What failure is it?" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu looked at Hei tribe's first supreme elder, showing an expression of a vague smile.

Hei tribe's first supreme elder felt cold sweat on his forehead, he could not tell the Heavenly Lord Bai Zu about his scheme three days ago, that would be offending the great expert!

Thus, he shifted the topic: "In this battle in Hei tribe, we anticipated that Fang Yuan would appear to reap some benefits. In the entire battle, we had used investigative immortal methods continuously, but we could not find him at all. I have failed in capturing Fang Yuan, it was my mistake!"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu smiled: "Your investigative method is quite unique, it can actually expose an otherworldly demon. I am afraid that Fang Yuan truly did not come. That is a pity, if he appeared, I would have captured him. With this bargaining chip, I would not have to pay such a huge price."

As it turned out, Hei tribe and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had already discussed to set a trap against Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was the culprit behind the matter of Imperial Court blessed land, it was widely known, the Northern Plains Gu Immortal world knew that Fang Yuan had Fixed Immortal Travel and Spring Autumn Cicada.

Hei tribe's battle was an opportunity not seen in hundreds of years, to think that Fang Yuan did not come. This was out of their expectations, after all, Fang Yuan had Fixed Immortal Travel, it was easy for him to show up.

They did not know about the matters after the battle of Yi Tian Mountain. Right now, Fixed Immortal Travel was in the hands of Heavenly Court.

As for the investigative immortal killer move that could expose an otherworldly demon, it also had a peculiar origin.

Hei tribe had once had an otherworldly demon. When he was a mortal Gu Master, he displayed incredible talent and attracted the attention of the higher-ups.

The Quartet Sparrow Battle Tactic that he came up with was a game that the top four supreme elders of Hei tribe loved, they could not stop playing it even until now.

After soul search, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals found out that this person was an otherworldly demon. Thus, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals did thorough research on his body, even though his life was lost in the process, they obtained an immortal killer move that could expose an otherworldly demon.

This secret was only known by Hei tribe's top four supreme elders, the rest of the Hei tribe Gu Immortals did not know about it.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu continued: "Never mind that Fang Yuan did not come here. Your Hei tribe was smart and knew to join my Bai Zu tribe in the nick of time, it is a good thing. Three days later, I will help you get rid of your problem, you will be able to separate and move on your own. Don't worry, as long as you sincerely forget the past and live on as a Gu Immortal of Bai Zu tribe, think in the interests of our tribe and contribute to the tribe, I will definitely notice and reward you for your hard work."

"Yes! We obey the orders of Heavenly Lord!" Hei tribe's Gu Immortals quickly responded.

Hei tribe's first supreme elder even knelt on the floor, shouting loudly with an attitude of gratitude and joy: "Heavenly Lord, you are magnanimous, you forgave us for our incompetence, we are truly in awe at your grace! You even thought about our problem and are going to help us resolve it, you are truly the savior of our tribe...."

Saying this, he kowtowed with his head heavily hitting the floor, tears were flowing endlessly down his cheeks.

But inside, he felt icy chills.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was highly skilled, he immediately wanted to get rid of their Green City Rampage. This formation would no longer belong to Hei tribe's top four supreme elders from now on.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was extremely pleased, he allowed them to leave after saying some words of encouragement.

He sat and did not move, he was thinking in his head.

"Hei tribe's Gu Immortals have just joined us, their status fell drastically, they are definitely not in a tranquil state, they will need a lot of time to adjust to their new life."

"However, it is good that Hei tribe's first supreme elder has this attitude now. My effort of suppressing him was not wasted, I can spare his life."

"It is too bad that Fang Yuan did not show up, otherwise, if I could capture him, my gains would be greater! Now, I can only pay the price myself."

To ensure that the other rank eight experts did not act, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu paid a hefty price, he felt pain thinking about it.

"However, there can only be gains after putting in the investment. Right now, Bai Zu tribe finally has the foundation to firmly stay in Northern Plains!"

"And there is also Hei Fan grotto-heaven, if I can take it down, my losses will be replenished."

"Of course, I cannot rush this, I need to let the tribe recuperate now, and ensure that there is peace! After this battle, I have gotten on the nerves of the righteous path. If I attack Hei Fan grotto-heaven now, the other rank eights will not watch me quietly from the side."

"Thankfully, Hei tribe lost all of their fortune now, the righteous and demonic immortals are satisfied by their gains. These forces would conflict and restrain each other, for the short term, they will not find problems with Bai Zu tribe."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu thought about all these things, in this short period of time, he clearly assessed the circumstances of Bai Zu tribe and himself, he was clear about his goals, and was prepared to start his future plans!

Chapter 1111: Fang Yuan's Third Earthly Calamity

Southern Border.

Mountains were standing tall, greenery was widespread, mountains winds howled endlessly.

More than ten Gu Immortals, thousands of li apart, formed a huge circle.

In the sky above this circle, an old Gu Immortal was using his immortal essence, concentrating as he set up the formation.

The framework of a formation was already placed, covering a gigantic surrounding area, a huge illusory light lump was within.

This huge light lump was shining in many colors, dazzling and bright, it was the giant dream realm.

After the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, the place was in shambles. Spectral Soul was plotted against by heaven's will, Fang Yuan obtained the fruits of his labor, and his main body was trapped in the dream realm, constantly getting weakened by it.

Even though the Southern Border Gu Immortals did not know about the details of the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, they knew about the immense benefits involving this giant dream realm.

The Gu Immortals here came from the respective righteous path super forces in Southern Border.

After a difficult negotiation, they came to an agreement, they were going to control this giant dream realm together.

This dream realm was too important, none of the super forces could take it down alone. They were afraid of the demonic path and lone immortals coming to gain benefits, thus, the righteous path joined up and occupied this place, setting up a super Gu formation here so that they could slowly devour the benefits of the dream realm later on.

"Rise!" The old Gu Immortal in the sky suddenly shouted, profound light shone from all directions around his body.

Following him, the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals put in effort, large amounts of immortal essence was expended, countless mortal Gu were flying, Immortal Gu flew out of the Gu Immortals one by one, landing in their respective spots.

Many Gu Immortals were sweating and nervous, some of them had trembling fingers.

They had already spent nine days and nights here setting up the Gu formation.

Now, they were at a crucial moment of arranging the super Gu formation.

"They are about to succeed!"

"Are we not taking action yet? If we don't do it now..."

"Sigh! There is no chance. Around them, there are hidden Gu Immortal experts, I suspect they have Immortal Gu Houses defending them!"

"In that case..."

Conversations were quietly taking place.

Demonic path and lone immortals understood the value of this giant dream realm. Even without this dream realm, this place had undergone a mysterious battle, there might be some Gu Immortal corpses or inheritances left behind, they were all treasures!

But the righteous path Gu Immortals acted with caution, they did not give these demonic path and lone immortals any chance.

Without any chance, these Gu Immortals wisely chose to retreat.

Boom—!

With a loud sound, a huge pillar of light burst up into the sky.

The pillar of light appeared quickly and vanished just as quickly.

A huge super Gu formation gradually concealed itself, vanishing from the immortals' sights.

"After so much hard work, it is finally completed!" The old Gu Immortal who set up the formation slowly descended.

The righteous path Gu Immortals gathered together.

"In setting up this formation, my Wu clan used five Immortal Gu. Thus, thirty percent of this dream realm should belong to my Wu clan."

"Hehe, this makes sense. But... my Luo tribe contributed just as many Immortal Gu as your Wu clan."

"What are you talking about! If we did not work together and used our immortal essence, could we have created this super Gu formation?"

"In my opinion, in terms of contribution, my clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You, was the main person in charge of setting up the formation, he definitely ranks as the highest contributor!"

Even though the super Gu formation was set up, the righteous path Gu Immortals had not decided how to split up the super dream realm yet.

At once, sounds of discussion became louder and louder, they were progressing towards an argument.

Arguments would have no use in terms of getting a result, of course.

The righteous path Gu Immortals left unhappily, starting to plan for their own share of this pie.

A few days later.

Shang Liang Mountain.

"Xin Ci greets Lady Qing Qing." Shang Xin Ci paid her respects.

Shang Qing Qing looked at Shang Xin Ci, nodding in satisfaction: "I was right about you. You have done well as the clan leader, the members of Shang clan are starting to show some unity."

"I was able to achieve this all thanks to Lady Qing Qing's nurturing." Shang Xin Ci said with sincere gratitude.

Shang Qing Qing went into the main topic immediately: "I called you to come here because I have some questions. After becoming clan leader, the first thing you did was to get rid of the arrest warrants of the black and white demons. But do you know, that Brother Hei Tu of yours is not Fang Zheng, he is Fang Yuan instead."

"Fang Yuan?" Shang Xin Ci was perplexed.

She did not expect that Lord Shang Qing Qing had called for her to talk about Brother Hei Tu.

After Shang Xin Ci became Shang clan leader, her vision had broadened, she learned many secrets, she knew that the beautiful lady in front of her was a high and mighty Gu Immortal who transcended mortals!

This Gu Immortal was actually talking to her regarding a mortal Gu Master, how could she not be confused?

Shang Qing Qing had a solemn expression as she said: "Xin Ci, you have to listen to my following words very carefully, they are very important."

"Yes, I will listen and learn."

"This Black Demon that you know of as Fang Zheng, his real name is Gu Yue Fang Yuan. He has a startling background, he is not an ordinary person. He appeared out of nowhere and is extremely dangerous. He is a demonic path Gu Immortal, he committed a huge crime, not only Southern Border, but Central Continent, Eastern Sea, Northern Plains, and Western Desert Gu Immortals are all pursuing him now." Shang Qing Qing said in a solemn tone.

Shang Xin Ci opened her mouth, she was in shock.

At once, she felt like her ears were playing tricks on her.

Since when did Brother Hei Tu become an immortal, and he was so dangerous that Lady Shang Qing Qing felt wary of him?

"Don't suspect your hearing, why would I joke about these things? You and the demon Fang Yuan had some friendship back then, tell me everything about it now." Shang Qing Qing questioned.

"Ah... ah, yes, yes." Shang Xin Ci regained her senses after some time, she began to recall: "I first met Brother Hei Tu in the merchant caravan, he was such a kind person, he saved me from that horrible predicament..."

Shang Xin Ci recalled the past, as she got deeper into it, a hint of tenderness was showing on her face.

Throughout the process, Shang Qing Qing listened on the side, not saying a word.

After Shang Xin Ci finished, she mustered up her courage and tried to explain for Fang Yuan: "Lady Qing Qing, is there a misunderstanding? Fang Zheng, I mean, Brother Fang Yuan is clearly a mortal Gu Master, how can he be such a great demon?"

"Hehe." Shang Qing Qing showed a mocking smile: "If he is not a great demon, who is? His craftiness and deviousness is not something you can imagine. He turned the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world upside down, Central Continent's Heavenly Court has not even managed to catch him yet. Nobody knows where he is, or what evil scheme he is planning next. Your encounter with him might not be as simple as you think, I can tell that there was a scheme involved in this!"

"Do you know? Because of your relationship with him, my Shang clan is facing great pressure from Southern Border's Gu Immortals. From now on, you have to keep a clear distance between you and him, there cannot be any relationship between the two of you. Be a good Shang clan leader, you may leave."

Shang Xin Ci could only leave.

"You are letting her go?" After Shang Xin Ci left, a figure appeared, standing beside Shang Qing Qing.

He was thin and looked very pale, it was Shang clan's Gu Immortal Shang Tan Mo.

Shang Qing Qing smiled: "What else can I do?"

Shang Tan Mo said solemnly: "We cannot listen to her words alone, we need to soul search and see it for ourselves!"

Shang Qing Qing smiled even wider now: "Look at this?"

Saying this, she stretched out her hand from her sleeve.

Her hand was no longer a human hand, it was like a twig, there were flowers growing on her nails.

Shang Tan Mo saw it and was dazed: "I forgot that you have this immortal killer move, it is more reliable than soul searching."

"I already know all of Fang Yuan's interactions in Shang clan city. He came here for a fortuitous encounter in cultivation, as expected and worthy of the user of Spring Autumn Cicada. This is nothing much, he did not set up any hidden schemes after all." Shang Qing Qing said.

Shang Tan Mo nodded: "Then I am assured, but, how will we explain this to the outsiders?"

Shang Qing Qing smiled coldly: "Them? They are just using Fang Yuan as an excuse to get a bigger share of the dream realm, now that I have this result, I can shut their mouths."

Shang Tan Mo's eyes shined, he looked up, his gaze pierced Shang Liang Mountain as he looked at the giant dream realm: "Maybe... my Shang clan's Gu Immortals have been too polite for a long time, people think we are no longer adept at fighting."

The situation was still changing.

Over in Northern Plains, the battle at Hei tribe had ended, there were just some loose ends. The righteous and demonic factions, as well as the lone immortals, had their own gains. Hei tribe was history, Bai Zu tribe took them over and changed the situation in the Gu Immortal world.

In Southern Border, they were fighting over the giant dream realm, the righteous path Gu Immortals worked together and managed to keep the demonic path and lone immortals out of it. But within the righteous path itself, a competition for shares of the giant dream realm was about to begin!

No matter where and when, people will always fight over benefits and resources.

More than ten days passed like this.

Northern Plains, northern icy plain.

Fang Yuan placed his immortal aperture, looking at the sky, muttering: "Finally, this is the third earthly calamity!"

Heaven and earth qi rumbled, there were no clouds or fog, there was a peculiar and strange scene of tranquility in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Flying birds appeared from thin air.

They were glowing with a slight green light, they flew extremely quickly, in Fang Yuan's vision, he saw long lines of light caused by their movement.

The cry of the birds was extremely crisp, filled with endless vitality.

"Spring dawn jade oriole." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he recognized these flying birds.

They might have tiny bodies, like sparrows, but they were genuine desolate beasts!

"These birds are very special among desolate beasts, they have a lot of rule path 'life' dao marks in their bodies, but they have very short lifespans. After the egg hatches, they can fly in the skies immediately. Everywhere they go, their dao marks will rain down and change the terrain of the environment, pouring down endless life force. After a dozen or so breaths of time, their lifespan would be expended and they would die."

Fang Yuan muttered in his mind, he could see that in this area of Mini Northern Plains, the thin layer of ice on the ground was already starting to have sprouts growing out of them.

Soon, under the influence of the spring dawn jade orioles, grass grew taller, rapidly growing and there were even wildflowers mixed among them.

"What is going on? What earthly calamity is this? Heaven's will is trying to help me develop my immortal aperture?" Fang Yuan was confused.

Chapter 1112: Spring Dawn Jade Orioles

The cries of the birds were unceasing and pleasing to the ears.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Northern Plains was originally wilderness covered in frost, but now, green plants could be seen sprouting rapidly.

The power of the earthly calamity was huge. In just a dozen breaths of time, a gigantic area surrounding Fang Yuan was already covered in greenery, it was a grassland.

Grass, trees, and flowers grew rapidly, it was as if this was an entirely new place.

Fang Yuan stood on the peak of Dang Hun Mountain, he had a heavy expression, he focused his mind.

This was his third earthly calamity, he bought Dang Hun Mountain with him again.

But the situation now was very strange.

The earthly calamity involved spring dawn jade orioles, it was helping Fang Yuan to develop his immortal aperture.

Half a month ago, when treasure yellow heaven opened, Fang Yuan did not choose to go Hei tribe and take a risk, instead, he went back and developed the sovereign immortal aperture.

He had developed many areas, but because Mini Northern Plains was the place where Fang Yuan would be undergoing tribulation, he did not develop it.

Right now, this earthly calamity was helping Fang Yuan to do it, this was out of his expectations.

This was a good thing for Fang Yuan.

"But heaven's will can act in unexpected ways, it is not so kind, there are surely traps that it set, I need to inspect for them." Fang Yuan stood at the peak of Dang Hun Mountain, observing vigilantly.

Mini Northern Plains was huge.

The grassland formed by the earthly calamity could not fill the whole of Mini Northern Plains, it only covered the part of the frosted land that was around Dang Hun Mountain.

Looking at it, the greenery was growing thicker, soon, sprouting trees grew taller, rising at an observable pace.

At this rate, a huge forest was going to form.

Fang Yuan felt surprised and joyful.

The power of the earthly calamity was usually used for destruction, against regular people. When used to develop the immortal aperture, it had truly shocking effects. If Fang Yuan wanted to transplant this huge forest into his immortal aperture, it would cost him a lot of time and effort.

The spring dawn jade oriole had a short lifespan, as they died, they turned into jade green life force, fading in the air, but at the same time, more spring dawn jade orioles formed, moving forward in their place.

At once, the sky was filled with the figures of these desolate birds, they were so numerous, like a flock of sparrows, it was a grand sight.

"Wait!" Fang Yuan's expression suddenly changed.

"Go." He suddenly thought of something, he called out as he pointed.

Instantly, sword light flew out, moving at lightning speed.

Rank seven Immortal Gu — Flying Sword!

Spring dawn jade orioles were fast, but they could not match the speed of this sword light. But they could move agilely, they did not travel linearly, Fang Yuan used up some effort to kill one.

A wave of true meaning rushed in soon, entering Fang Yuan's mind.

In an instant, Fang Yuan felt like a spring dawn jade oriole, from the start of life to flight, and until his death. In a short period of time, he experienced life and death, his mental state was transformed.

Fang Yuan fully absorbed this true meaning, clarity returning to his eyes.

Right now, he was a transformation path grandmaster, it was no longer as hard for him to absorb Reckless Savage's true meaning.

If he was like an empty basin earlier trying to hold buckets of water, he was like a well now, taking in Reckless Savage's true meaning in huge quantity, with much greater ease than before!

Fang Yuan frowned, at this moment, he realized the scheme of heaven's will.

Fang Yuan's earthly calamity was very unique, because of the immortal tribulation tempering aperture method and the nature of the northern icy plain, his earthly calamity had two portions.

One was controlled by heaven's will, the other was influenced by Reckless Savage's true meaning.

In the previous two earthly calamities, the portion controlled by heaven's will formed first, before the part of the earthly calamity formed by Reckless Savage's true meaning appeared. But in this third earthly calamity, Reckless Savage's true meaning appeared at the start!

Fang Yuan did not expect this.

This was the first time he was seeing this!

Fang Yuan suffered a minor loss.

Between Reckless Savage's true meaning and developing the blessed land, the former was much more important than the latter.

Because Reckless Savage's true meaning could directly raise his transformation path attainment level, it could only be obtained during each tribulation, the costs and risks involved were high.

As for developing the blessed land, he could do it at any time.

"Heaven's will knows about my vigilant nature, this is a good scheme to prevent my transformation path attainment level from rising rapidly, I wasted a lot of Reckless Savage's true meaning." Fang Yuan smiled, not feeling dejected.

He flew out like lightning.

In the air, his body shook, as countless strength path phantoms appeared.

Strength path killer move — Myriad Self!

Myriad self charged forward, forming a huge tide of humans, rampaging towards the spring dawn jade oriole flock.

Spring dawn jade orioles were desolate birds, they could move freely among the myriad self army while chirping continuously.

Myriad self had little effect, Fang Yuan quickly used other methods.

Sword path killer move — Triple Layered Sword Wave!

Swish swish swish!

Silver-white sword waves burst out like tides, containing an unstoppable sharpness, pushing forward.

The speed of the spring dawn jade oriole was faster than the sword waves. Fang Yuan sent out three sword waves, even though some were killed, the result was not many.

He frowned, understanding: "In the previous two earthly calamities, heaven's will already learned a lot about my foundation. Be it myriad self or triple layered sword wave, it knows about their weaknesses. In this earthly calamity, the spring dawn jade orioles counter my two killer moves. Heaven's will is plotting against me by intentionally setting up these situations."

In the previous earthly calamity, there were wind flowers with sharpness like blades.

But Fang Yuan had Dang Hun Mountain, using it as his base, he could defend himself to a great extent.

But now, even though Fang Yuan brought Dang Hun Mountain, the spring dawn jade orioles were formed from Reckless Savage's true meaning, he could not sit around and defend himself, he needed to go on the offense or he would lose his greatest benefit.

"Thankfully, I retrieved flying sword Immortal Gu!"

Fang Yuan activated this rank seven Immortal Gu, sword light rampaged according to his will.

Spring dawn jade orioles died at Fang Yuan's hands, but more and more spring dawn jade orioles died on their own.

If Fang Yuan did not kill them, he would not receive infusions of Reckless Savage's true meaning. Heaven's will purposely caused this, Fang Yuan's losses were not small.

This was not just a loss of Reckless Savage's true meaning, but also his green grape immortal essence.

Even though flying sword Immortal Gu was powerful, it was rank seven, each activation needed a huge amount of green grape immortal essence! But each attack only hit one spring dawn jade oriole, Fang Yuan was wasting a lot of his resources for limited results.

"It seems that I need new methods in the next tribulation. Old moves are losing effectiveness." Fang Yuan thought of wisdom Gu.

If he had the light of wisdom, this problem was easy to solve. With his grandmaster attainment level and wisdom path methods, he could very easily deduce new immortal killer moves.

But even though Fang Yuan had his immortal zombie body, he did not dare to use it.

After fifteen minutes of the earthly calamity, there were still spring dawn jade orioles forming.

Mini Northern Plains was not just budding with greenery, there was a huge forest, the trees inside the forest were huge, they were dozens of meters tall, each of the tree trunks resembled pillars.

At this time, Fang Yuan tried other methods like poison spit. In the previous earthly calamity, this killer move was very effective, but now it was useless against the spring dawn jade orioles.

Growl growl growl—!

In the huge forest, trees raised their heads and cried out loud.

Next, they uprooted from the ground, becoming huge treemen.

Fang Yuan noticed the changes on the ground and snickered: "So this is the portion controlled by heaven's will. Hehe, I was vigilant and got rid of half the forest in advance, now it seems that my preparation was not in vain."

Countless treemen pulled out their roots from deep underground, charging towards Dang Hun Mountain.

They moved slowly, but each of them were huge. Fang Yuan changed his mind and chose to defend. He landed on the peak of Dang Hun Mountain, looking at the treemen moving towards him. It was a scene of greenery, it was like the entire forest was pushing towards him, he felt suffocated.

Fang Yuan stretched out his finger and tried to attack.

Flying sword Immortal Gu charged over, turning into a bright light, piercing a great distance ahead, many treemen were penetrated.

These treemen stopped moving but soon, their injuries were healed and they continued climbing towards Dang Hun Mountain.

Fang Yuan used triple layered sword wave again.

The dazzling sword waves engulfed the treemen with sharp sounds. There was nothing left of them, the effect was great, but soon, treemen behind filled up the gaps.

Fang Yuan frowned.

"These treemen are not desolate beasts, but they are close to that level. Not only are they very durable, they can absorb life force and recover rapidly."

The life force naturally came from the spring dawn jade orioles.

Every since the first earthly calamity, event though heaven's will could not control the entire earthly calamity, it could influence Reckless Savage's true meaning and create a combination.

Last time, it was the snow moons and wind flowers, now it was the treemen and spring dawn jade orioles, they combined perfectly, gaining huge effect!

Fang Yuan suddenly opened his mouth, spitting out a mouthful of poisonous air.

The poisonous air spread around the treemen, dozens of them started to move slowly, their green leaves turned purple. In a few breaths' time, their movement became slower and slower, until they collapsed on the ground, the entire tree's branches and leaves started rotting, turning decayed.

Poison spit's effect was quite good.

But Fang Yuan could not continuously use this killer move, there was a huge drawback, he needed to get rid of the poison in his body first, otherwise, he would die.

The treemen started to climb Dang Hun Mountain.

Soon, these treemen experienced the power of Dang Hun Mountain, their souls shook, their bodies trembled, many leaves fell.

However, there were too many treemen, they advanced forward, pushing each other up the mountain.

Dang Hun Mountain was indeed a secluded domain of heaven and earth, just at the base of the mountain, a hundred treemen died, Fang Yuan did not use any immortal essence.

Fang Yuan looked at the scene, his frown was deepening.

Even though these treemen were troublesome, they had little threat.

Because they moved slowly, Fang Yuan could attack from a distance and kill these treemen slowly.

Fang Yuan felt something amiss: "This earthly calamity is too easy, don't tell me, because heaven's will felt that it cannot kill me this time, its focus went to depleting my foundation instead?"

Chapter 1113: Giant Disaster Blazing Tree

To eliminate these treemen, he would need to expend a lot of immortal essence.

The number of these treemen was greater than the first earthly calamity's snow monsters, and they had strong regenerative abilities. Fang Yuan could see many severed twigs that were stabbed into the ground growing with new budding leaves.

Unless he used killer moves like triple layered sword wave to completely decimate these treemen, to avoid any future problems.

Otherwise, when these trees grow, they would expend a great amount of the earth qi inside the immortal aperture.

But using triple layered sword wave or flying sword Immortal Gu to kill these treemen was too wasteful!

"If I were a fire path Gu Immortal, this would not be a problem to me." Fang Yuan thought of this, when he suddenly heard a sound, fire was starting from those treemen's corpses.

The fire burnt rapidly, in the blink of an eye, it spread and covered countless treemen!

The fire continued to rage on these treemen's bodies, turning these treemen into charcoal, their leaves were completely incinerated, a great number of them died.

The fire was nourished by the treemen and became larger, it was almost twenty meters tall!

Raging flames advanced towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was stunned.

What is going on?

Evidently, this was part of the earthly calamity.

But why did the earthly calamity start burning itself? What was heaven's will trying to do? Was it trying to resolve Fang Yuan's problem?

Fang Yuan quickly ruled out the possibility.

What a joke, how could heaven's will help him?

Roar—!

There was a huge figure standing among the roaring flames.

In the orange-red flames, a sixty meter tall giant stood up!

"This is?!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk to pin size, he subconsciously gritted his teeth: "Giant disaster blazing tree!"

This was an ancient desolate plant.

In history, immemorial red heaven often had these giant disaster blazing trees.

But this type of ancient desolate plant was rarely seen in the five regions, although not extinct.

Giant disaster blazing trees could be created from any type of tree. When a forest fire starts, after countless lifeforms are killed, there was a chance of forming this giant disaster blazing tree.

The giant disaster blazing tree's body was covered in raging flames. It burned endlessly, nothing could get close to it. More impressively, this giant disaster blazing tree would cause bad luck to whatever life forms got close to it.

"Heaven's will, truly insidious! Evidently, heaven's will has noticed the protection of Dog Shit Luck on me, it created this giant disaster blazing tree to destroy my good luck!"

Fang Yuan felt a huge challenge.

Normally speaking: If he encountered a giant disaster blazing tree in the wild, he would wisely choose to evade it. But now, this giant disaster blazing tree directly appeared in his immortal aperture, it was draining his immortal aperture's earth qi and bringing him disaster and bad luck, negating Dog Shit Luck's effect. If he left it alone, soon, Fang Yuan would be extremely unlucky, nothing would go right, he might even face a huge disaster. As for refining Immortal Gu, he could forget about it.

Flames raged on, crackling sounds could be heard from the burning trees.

The blazing tree had appeared in a very peculiar location, it was close to Dang Hun Mountain.

Even though Fang Yuan activated his defenses, the huge flames were still causing his eyebrows and hair to dry up.

"This is only the periphery, but the temperature is already like this, what would the center of this blazing tree be like?" Fang Yuan sighed, leaving.

He left Dang Hun Mountain.

He had Landscape as Before, he could restore Dang Hun Mountain before it was completely destroyed.

The problem was how to kill this giant disaster blazing tree which reached partway up Dang Hun Mountain in height!

Sword marks targeting death!

Triple layered sword wave!

Poison spit!

Fang Yuan used many killer moves, but they were ineffective. The poison in the air was completely eradicated by the flames, flying sword Immortal Gu pierced the giant disaster blazing tree and returned to Fang Yuan, but the giant disaster blazing tree only shook intensely, before turning to normal.

As for triple layered sword wave, it managed to put out the flames, it got to the blazing tree and destroyed many branches and leaves. But soon, the flames spread again as the blazing tree returned to normal, its injuries vanished after a few breaths of time.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance, immortal aura burst out around him as he cried out: "Strength path giant hand!'

Bam.

A giant hand appeared out of nowhere, pushing the air and grabbing at the blazing tree with an unstoppable aura.

But the blazing tree was huge too, it was almost half of Dang Hun Mountain's size.

The strength path giant hand grabbed the giant disaster blazing tree and tried to lift it up.

But after some time, even after trying hard, there was no effect.

The giant disaster blazing tree had countless roots, they were like snakes deeply rooted in the soil, sucking in earth qi fiercely, it also had the spring dawn jade orioles flying in the sky to replenish its life force, it was stable as a mountain, unmoving.

As time passed, the entire strength path giant hand started melting in the flames, almost half of it was gone.

Fang Yuan dispelled this giant hand, he had an idea after some inspiration.

Rumble!

A second strength path giant hand flew out, but this time, it grabbed at Dang Hun Mountain instead of the giant disaster blazing tree.

Fang Yuan could not lift the giant disaster blazing tree, but strength path giant hand had the power of Pulling Mountain, he could lift Dang Hun Mountain.

Whoosh!

Wind currents blew, Dang Hun Mountain was brought into the air by Fang Yuan, before he tossed it directly towards the giant disaster blazing tree.

With a loud sound, the entire ground shook intensely.

The giant disaster blazing tree was suppressed under the mountain, the huge flames were no longer apparent, there was only a ring of fire left around the mountain's base.

Fang Yuan floated in the air, staring at the battlefield expressionlessly.

The giant disaster blazing tree could not move, it was attacked by Dang Hun Mountain's soul path dao marks, but it had incredible vitality and tenacity, it was still struggling intensely.

Blazing flames started to roast Dang Hun Mountain, liquefying some of its rocks.

It was not so easy to get rid of the giant disaster blazing tree.

Fang Yuan was in a heavy mood, looking around, it was a scene of red.

A sea of fire!

The flames had spread to the entire forest, and even the grassland.

As expected, heaven's will's arrangements were just to nurture the growth of the giant disaster blazing tree, how could it be so nice to him?

Fang Yuan's breathing became rougher.

He saw that more and more giant disaster blazing trees were forming in the sea of fire, their roots were digging into the ground as they sucked in earth qi to strengthen themselves.

The first plant was not destroyed yet, but so many others were forming!

Not just that, these giant disaster blazing trees were growling, they stood up and turned into giant blazing treemen!

They had only one target, Fang Yuan, who was in the sky.

Boom boom boom!

Under Dang Hun Mountain, the first giant disaster blazing tree also became a treeman, it was not giving up, attempting to flip over this mountain.

It had incredible strength, each time it struggled, Dang Hun Mountain shook intensely, causing a huge and scary sound.

In an instant, the situation became as bad as it possibly could!

Fang Yuan could ignore the snow monsters earlier and slowly kill them

But he could not ignore these giant disaster blazing treemen. Even though they moved slowly, they had a terrible influence on the immortal aperture. Not only did they suck away earth qi and damage the sovereign immortal aperture's foundation, they would even bring Fang Yuan a lot of bad luck!

What should he do?

The light of the fire flickered on Fang Yuan's face, a smile slowly appeared on his face: "Thankfully, I made my preparations!"

At the same time, Shang Xin Ci who was in Southern Border stared at the lamp in front of her in a daze. In the fire, it seemed to show Fang Yuan's former appearance.

"Brother Hei Tu..." Shang Xin Ci thought to herself.

"Clan leader, clan leader?" She heard something close to her ears.

"Ah." Shang Xin Ci regained her senses, she looked at Xiao Lan, Xiao Die, Lady Wei, Zhou Quan, and her other subordinates.

"Sorry, my mind was wandering again." Shang Xin Ci quickly apologized.

"Miss, this is the third time you've gone into a daze." Xiao Lan muttered.

"I was disrespectful, I am truly sorry." Shang Xin Ci quickly said again.

Zhou Quan and Lady Wei glanced at each other swiftly, before coughing: "Now, let's continue the topic from before, how will we take in the Gu Master groups that were controlled by Shang clan's former young clan leaders."

After the meeting, everyone left the hall.

"Xiao Die, how is the clan leader? Why is she constantly in a daze?" Zhou Quan asked.

Xiao Die showed an expression of worry: "I am not sure too, it seems that after the higher-ups met with her, she became like this ever since."

"Higher-ups?" Zhou Quan's expression changed, he already knew about the existence of Shang clan's Gu Immortals, this was not something that he could settle or interfere in.

Ye Fan could not hold it in anymore: "Let me go talk to Lady Xin Ci, maybe as an outsider, I can learn something from her."

"Young master Ye, you are not an outsider." Xiao Lan smiled.

"We will trouble you, young master Ye." Lady Wei nodded, agreeing with this.

A moment later, Ye Fan arrived at Shang Xin Ci's study room.

The doors were shut.

Through the small hole in the center, Ye Fan saw that Shang Xin Ci was holding onto a piece of paper, looking at it carefully.

She was so deep in thought, even when Ye Fan walked with heavy steps, she did not notice it.

Ye Fan was about to cough and remind Shang Xin Ci that he was here.

But suddenly, he heard Shang Xin Ci's soft whisper: "Brother Hei Tu... what kind of person are you..."

Ye Fan's heart jumped, he instantly understood, the paper in Shang Xin Ci's hand was none other than the black demon's arrest warrant. It was his drawing!

Ye Fan felt a sense of hollowness in his heart, his strong limbs were turning frail.

He stood outside the door, he hesitated for a long time before gritting his teeth, turning around and leaving.

From start to finish, Shang Xin Ci did not discover him.

Ye Fan walked out of the mansion, arriving at the street. This was the inner core of Shang Liang Mountain, an important place in Shang clan, it was flourishing with bustling activity.

But Ye Fan had a worried expression, he had a question inside him — Hei Tu, what kind of person are you?

Northern icy plain.

Chu Du's arms were behind his back, he watched this vast icy plain.

Suddenly, his body shook: "It's here!"

He received Fang Yuan's transmission and quickly used the Immortal Gu in his hands.

Rank seven calamity beckoning Immortal Gu!

At the next moment, the sovereign blessed land's entrance opened.

First, spring dawn jade orioles were sent out of the entrance by a formless force, next, one by one, the giant disaster blazing trees were dragged out without managing to put up resistance!

They were unwilling, they were furious.

The sky was rumbling with thunder, heaven's will was furious too.

But it was no use!

Two hours later, the third earthly calamity ended.

Fang Yuan collected his immortal aperture, appearing in the northern icy plain.

Chu Du obtained quite a bit of Reckless Savage's true meaning, he cried out with an excited tone: "Walking on a long road for countless years, today I obtain the blessing of azure clouds. Flying above rivers and lakes on these clouds, nothing can obstruct my view of this world."

His voice resounded over the surroundings, the disposition of the Domination Immortal was fully emanated.

"May I ask you for your name?" Chu Du greeted Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Obstacles and difficulties fill this road, life and death matters little against calamities and tribulations. My body flies like willows with the wind, regardless of wind or mud I still fly free."

After pausing, he returned the greeting to Chu Du, saying plainly: "I am Liu Guan Yi."

Chapter 1114: Obtaining One of Two True Inheritances

Time passed quickly, several days went by.

Lang Ya blessed land, inside a cloud city.

Fang Yuan was sitting in his secret room, cultivating.

Using connecting heaven Gu, his divine sense communicated with a certain female Gu Immortal's will in treasure yellow heaven.

"Your pill azure incense is of lower quality than Gu Immortal Xi Zi, the price should be cheaper." Fang Yuan bargained.

But that female Gu Immortal was not like Fang Yuan, who used his divine sense to conduct the deal.

She had left her will in treasure yellow heaven, to manage transactions with goods.

And unfortunately, this was a resolute will, it was obstinate in nature, it would not give in.

As expected, the female immortal rejected with no hesitation at all: "The price is like this, buy it if you want, it is up to you!"

Fang Yuan was not giving up yet, he continued: "Will you reconsider? I am buying in bulk."

The resolute will was obstinate, it did not agree.

Fang Yuan was a little annoyed.

These last days, when developing the sovereign immortal aperture, he had to trade in treasure yellow heaven, to sell his own resources and buy all sorts of resources.

But after the third earthly calamity, he felt that his transactions were not going smoothly.

The female immortal's resolute will was one of them.

But this was quite a good situation already.

Fang Yuan had been encountering this recently: Gu Immortals would come in and raise prices with ill intent, or he might see some shortage of certain materials, after rank eight Gu Immortal experts bulk purchase everything.

"Even though I have Dog Shit Luck's protection, in the third earthly calamity, the giant disaster blazing tree destroyed a lot of my good luck."

Thinking about his third earthly calamity, Fang Yuan sighed.

"If I did not think about it carefully and decided to work together with Chu Du before the third earthly calamity, I would have been done for. Even if I passed the tribulation, I would be heavily injured and stuck with bad luck. Currently, I am only facing some small obstacles, they are of no real concern to my cultivation."

Fang Yuan quickly gathered his thoughts, his divine sense continued to negotiate with the female immortal in treasure yellow heaven.

Since she did not agree to lower prices, Fang Yuan could only accept this.

"I will buy your pill azure incense."

The female immortal's resolute will was stunned.

Fang Yuan was making a huge purchase.

He had to pay almost ten thousand immortal essence stones in this deal!

But Fang Yuan was not shaken.

With his accumulation from before, he was extremely affluent. Even though the third earthly calamity expended a lot of his green grape immortal essence, he could still afford ten thousand immortal essence stones.

After buying the pill azure incense, Fang Yuan retrieved his divine sense, no longer staying in treasure yellow heaven.

After inspecting it, he ensured that the pill azure incense had no problems, transporting them into his sovereign immortal aperture.

His consciousness quickly entered his immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture was split into five regions and nine heavens, Fang Yuan placed strength path immortal zombies in all the different areas.

Soon, one strength path immortal zombie flew over under his manipulation, using Gu worms to store the pill azure incense.

There was no choice, his sovereign immortal aperture was too huge, he could only use these strength path immortal zombies as laborers.

Every time he was in this situation, Fang Yuan thought of Hu Immortal land spirit and Star Form land spirit, if he had a land spirit, the job could be handled by them, he did not have to waste so much time on this.

The land spirit was basically the steward of the blessed land.

They were very convenient to have.

But it was a pity, Fang Yuan had never heard of any land spirits appearing in an immortal aperture before the Gu Immortal dies.

This pill azure incense resembled jade smoke, it constantly blew around, creating a hazy area.

Fang Yuan placed all of the pill azure incense into Mini Azure Heaven, causing this huge area to become more misty.

Even though the strength path immortal zombie could not smell anything, the pill azure incense was very fragrant, it was very amazing, it had the smell of ink and grass, extremely elegant and long lasting.

After placing the pill azure incense, Fang Yuan set up some Gu formations.

These Gu formations were made with mortal Gu, their only use was to keep the pill azure incense within a certain area, preventing it from dispersing away.

"I accumulated so much now, it is enough to feed change soul Immortal Gu three times." Fang Yuan was satisfied.

The pill azure incense would not renew itself, when he used it, it was gone for good.

If he had to produce pill azure incense himself, it would be troublesome.

Pill azure incense grew in places with primeval essence as well as pill crane groups, azure pine forests, ink bamboo forests and herb incense Gu. These four things, including beasts, plants, and Gu, were needed, and each of them had to be of a certain quantity, otherwise they could not produce pill azure incense.

And this exact amount was a trade secret.

Gu Immortals who sold pill azure incense had a firm grasp of this secret, they prevented the secret from leaking.

At this point, Fang Yuan could only temporarily store the pill azure incense.

Pill azure incense was the food that change soul Immortal Gu ate, but the good thing was, it was widely sold in treasure yellow heaven. Fang Yuan had accumulated a lot of it now, it could last for some time.

After more inspections, Fang Yuan modified the Gu formation, he took a final look before leaving, only to see that Mini Azure Heaven had a small area of thick azure spots, it was different from before.

Even though Fang Yuan placed great emphasis on developing his immortal aperture, on the whole, the sovereign immortal aperture was still very barren.

The point was, the sovereign immortal aperture's space was simply too big!

Fang Yuan placed so many resources inside, if it were the normal aperture of any other Gu Immortal, it would be filled already.

Speaking of which, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had quite a lot of dao marks, but in influencing such a huge area of space, the dao marks' effect was very small.

Fang Yuan retrieved the divine sense inside Mini Azure Heaven.

The pill azure incense was already placed, the development of Fang Yuan's immortal aperture had reached a certain stage.

Before this, Fang Yuan had already bought several batches of resources, he settled the feeding requirements of Sword Eyebrows, Wave Sword, Flying Sword, and the other rank seven Immortal Gu.

"Rank eight Immortal Gu and rank seven Immortal Gu already have their food. Now, the development of my immortal aperture should be to resolve the feeding requirements of my rank six Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan assessed.

The first criteria of development for a Gu Immortal's immortal aperture was to be self sufficient in feeding one's own Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was a strength path immortal zombie previously, his immortal aperture was dead, he did not follow this rule.

After reviving, he went steadily and surely, settling the feeding requirements of the rank eight and seven Immortal Gu to some degree.

Next were the rank six Immortal Gu.

There was a need to say, Fang Yuan simply had too many Immortal Gu.

It was a shocking quantity!

But there was no choice, Fang Yuan had to raise so many Immortal Gu, not only to resist the tribulations as well as heaven's will, but also against other Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan's circumstances were bad.

In the past, he had Shadow Sect, which concealed him from deductions. But after the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, this protection was gone, Heavenly Court placed his name on the Demon Judgment Board, they were determined to kill him. Northern Plains' Gu Immortals had deep hatred towards him, because Fang Yuan destroyed Imperial Court blessed land and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, this was something that created more enmity than digging the graves of these Huang Jin bloodline tribes.

The other Eastern Sea, Southern Border, and Western Desert Gu Immortals were all after the luck path true inheritance. Even though Fang Yuan did not obtain the true inheritance of all living being's luck, nobody would believe him if he said it.

All in all, Fang Yuan's identity could not be exposed, a lot of Gu Immortals were trying to find him.

Earlier, during the battle of Hei tribe, Hei tribe Gu Immortals had worked with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to try and ambush Fang Yuan, in the end, because he was vigilant, he did not go to Iron Eagle blessed land and escaped. Of course, Fang Yuan did not know this currently.

Thus, Fang Yuan traveled outside using a fake name — Liu Guan Yi.

If he said his true identity, Chu Du's attitude might have been completely different!

Currently, Fang Yuan had worked together with Chu Du.

Half a month ago, when treasure yellow heaven opened, Fang Yuan received Chu Du's letter.

In the letter, Chu Du stated the situation clearly, he informed Fang Yuan that flying sword Immortal Gu had an information path inheritance's clues!

At that moment, Fang Yuan was enticed.

Earlier, he was still thinking about the benefits of information path.

With strong information path methods, he could set agreements with others and not be afraid of them being broken. He could also secretly remove the alliance agreement that was on him, he could easily betray or break his word without any restraints.

He could even collect intel and make wiser decisions after knowing more details.

Information path and wisdom path were complementary.

Information path searched for information, while wisdom path used this information to deduce, they assisted each other.

The information path inheritance insignia on flying sword Immortal Gu was incredible, even the wisdom path Gu Immortal Tian Xia Xin was interested and wanted it from Chu Du.

Chu Du had told Fang Yuan about this situation. He wanted Fang Yuan to know about the value of the true inheritance, so that he could change his mind.

Fang Yuan thought about it and decided to deal with Chu Du.

He agreed to let Chu Du get Reckless Savage's true meaning, but Chu Du had to compensate him.

After the battle of Hei tribe, Chu Du snatched the thirteenth eagle nest under Fang Yuan's guidance.

Days after that, he and Fang Yuan met in Northern Plains secretly, making a transaction for both sides.

Fang Yuan obtained flying sword Immortal Gu and the eagle nest, while lending out calamity beckoning Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan could not give the immortal tribulation tempering aperture method to Chu Du. Even though this was an immortal killer move, and Immortal Gu were unique, but Chu Du could use other Immortal Gu in place of these.

Different Gu worms could produce similar immortal killer moves after all.

Chu Du was a powerful rank seven expert after all, his reputation made him a legendary figure in the current Northern Plains!

With his help, Fang Yuan successfully passed the third earthly calamity.

In the first two times, he was gravely injured, the situation was too dangerous. But in this third earthly calamity, he only suffered some setbacks, the biggest problems were resolved by Chu Du.

Calamity beckoning Immortal Gu was simply too incredible.

No wonder Mo Yao wanted to use this Immortal Gu to help her lover Bo Qing undergo tribulation.

But eventually, she failed.

Calamity beckoning Immortal Gu was only rank seven, but Bo Qing was undergoing the myriad tribulation that would lead him to rank nine!

Fang Yuan did not want to seek the information path true inheritance with clues on flying sword Immortal Gu yet.

The turbulent flow sea area was a problematic place, it was easy to get lost, and many Gu Immortals often traveled in it.

Fang Yuan placed his attention on the eagle nest.

The thirteenth eagle nest in Iron Eagle blessed land was usually concealed, it only appeared when Iron Eagle blessed land was near the point of breaking apart.

Inside this nest, there were clues to Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Fang Yuan had explored it for some time, he had some gains!

Compared to the information path true inheritance, the Hei Fan true inheritance, which could delay the time in his immortal aperture, was far more useful and important.

Fang Yuan had decided: While he still had this period of free time after undergoing tribulation, he was going to obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance!

Chapter 1115: Opening Heavenly Crystal Eagle Nest

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Purple Heaven.

A faint purple light was shining in the haziness.

In the vast sky, there was a floating eagle nest.

This eagle nest was like a three-storey building, there were no doors or windows, it was like a huge crystal.

A type of translucent crystal, twice as thick as a human's forearm, interlinked with itself, forming this tight eagle nest that had the same color throughout.

This crystal was extraordinary.

Fang Yuan had recognized that this was heavenly crystal, a rank eight immortal material!

Heavenly crystal came from the sky, it was very light and could float in the sky, it would never fall to the ground unless there were external forces.

Regardless of what was inside the eagle nest, just the outer nest itself contained five hundred kilograms of heavenly crystals! Just this heavenly crystal alone had immense value.

Evidently, this eagle nest was the thirteenth eagle nest in Iron Eagle blessed land.

Its value surpassed the sum of all the other eagle nests, firmly holding the highest position.

After Fang Yuan and Chu Du collaborated, Chu Du went to Iron Eagle blessed land and at the final moment of Hei tribe's battle, he displayed great strength and took this eagle nest.

However, before Chu Du left the battlefield, Hei tribe's first supreme elder shouted and let all of the immortals know that the thirteenth eagle nest had clues to Hei Fan's true inheritance!

This was a problem for Fang Yuan.

After Chu Du knew this, he renegotiated with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan knew he had to concede.

Flying sword Immortal Gu, the Eastern Sea information path true inheritance, and this thirteenth eagle nest, as well as Hei Fan's true inheritance, they had a lot of value when put together!

Even though Chu Du was solely a strength path cultivator, that did not mean he could not sell these for a good price.

Thankfully, Chu Du was firmly set on Fang Yuan's tribulation method.

Fang Yuan exploited this to deepen his cooperation with Chu Du, he spent a lot of effort and much discussion to barely reach an agreement.

Chu Du would use Calamity Beckoning to get Reckless Savage's true meaning from Fang Yuan. In the future, he will take thirty percent of Fang Yuan's gains from these two true inheritances.

"Chu Du is a normal Gu Immortal, he does not want to cultivate information path and time path on the side, thus, he has little interest towards the two true inheritances."

"Unlike me, I can cultivate all paths, any true inheritance can be used for my own cultivation!"

"Even so, I really admire his resolute decision, he can give up when needed to. Northern Plains' Domination Immortal, he is truly formidable, his title is well deserved!"

Fang Yuan inspected the eagle nest as he gathered his thoughts.

He and Chu Du were allies in terms of benefits. They had little relationship, they were just making use of each other.

Against Chu Du, Fang Yuan felt quite wary.

He knew that Chu Du was not giving up, he still wanted the immortal tribulation tempering aperture method.

Chu Du had brains and brawn, he was not a 'stupid' Domination Immortal.

His brawn allowed him to singlehandedly cause trouble to the Huang Jin super force, Liu tribe. During the battle of Hei tribe, he caused the immortals present to be unable to attack.

His mind was not to be underestimated. After Liu tribe's battle, he rarely appeared, he nurtured his disciples in secret, helping them become immortals, luring out Reckless Savage's true meaning. During the negotiation with Fang Yuan, his eloquence made Fang Yuan recognize this person's shrewdness and wisdom.

Domination Immortal had grand ambitions, how could he be satisfied with just Calamity Beckoning?

And the bigger worry for Fang Yuan was, Chu Du seemed to have guessed his true identity.

During the third earthly calamity, which was their first collaboration, the latter two lines of his poem were 'flying above rivers and lakes on these clouds, nothing can obstruct my view of this world'.

Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan[1].

Vaguely, it seemed like he was pointing out Fang Yuan's true identity.

Of course, he could be overthinking it.

But many things had happened, Fang Yuan would rather be overly vigilant than miss out any important details.

Chu Du's appearance was very suspicious, during the first earthly calamity, he almost took Fang Yuan's life!

Fang Yuan was suspicious: Chu Du was influenced by heaven's will and was a part of a plot, the 'human calamity' against Fang Yuan.

Cooperating with a person like this was simply 'asking favors from a tiger'.

Thus, during the first cooperation, after the third earthly calamity was over, Fang Yuan did not talk much to him, he quickly left.

Chu Du let Fang Yuan leave without saying anything.

First, calamity beckoning Immortal Gu was in his hands. Second, he and Fang Yuan had an alliance agreement. The information path Immortal Gu used was borrowed from other Gu Immortals. Third, he could not catch Fang Yuan in terms of speed!

With Chu Du's strength and skill, he had a wide network and knew many people.

Fang Yuan considered one point as well. To guard against heaven's will, Fang Yuan gave Chu Du a lot of self will Gu. At least, Fang Yuan did not need to worry that heaven's will would cause any negative influence on Chu Du.

"I need to be very careful when cooperating with Chu Du, if I make a mistake, it would lead to a disastrous end!" Fang Yuan alerted himself mentally, he placed his attention on the strength path immortal zombie again.

He controlled a strength path immortal zombie and slowly got closer to the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

These last days, he had been using investigative methods and collecting clues, looking into Hei Cheng's memories, to aid with his deductions.

"If I am not wrong, this time..."

Fang Yuan had confidence as he used his Immortal Gu.

The strength path immortal zombie which got close to the heavenly crystal eagle nest went through a complete transformation. It was originally emanating death energy, but in a moment, it became alive, turning into Hei Cheng, indiscernible from the real one.

'Hei Cheng' gradually got close to the heavenly crystal eagle nest, placing his hand on the eagle nest.

Fang Yuan's divine sense continued to explore, entering the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

At the same time, Gu worms flew out, coiling around 'Hei Cheng' as they flew in a spiral.

Refinement path killer moves were used one after another, impacting on the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

These refinement path killer moves were all mortal killer moves, they were modified by Hei Fan in the past, passing down for generations. Before Hei Fan died, he instructed his descendants that any new member of Hei tribe who became an immortal must learn these refinement path methods.

After several generations of research by Hei tribe's Gu Immortals, they gradually understood: These refinement path killer moves were the key to opening the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

Many Hei tribe Gu Immortals had used the refinement path killer moves on the heavenly crystal eagle nest in order to get Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Of course, they all failed.

Because they lacked the most critical element — attitude Gu!

In these refinement path killer moves, there was a crucial step that needed the aura of attitude Gu to activate.

This step obstructed generations of Hei tribe Gu Immortals, nobody could inherit Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were not fools, after understanding this, they immediately went to search for attitude Gu.

After a lot of effort by generations of Hei tribe Gu Immortals, they finally found some clues, they gained a breakthrough in this.

By the current generation, there was Su Xian's Night Elopement, she became Hei Cheng's wife, in the end, she joined Hei tribe as an external supreme elder.

Her surname was not Hei, she could not learn about deep secrets like Hei Fan's true inheritance.

But she came with a motive, with her sister Blazing Heaven Demoness' help, she stole the information about Hei Fan's true inheritance that generations of Hei tribe immortals had accumulated.

Using these results, she found some suspicious points.

But when she was close to success, there was a change in the situation. Hei Cheng killed Su Xian Er, Fairy Li Shan had a falling out with Blazing Heaven Demoness as a result, Su Xian Er left behind the crucial clues as well as a lot of familial emotion and immortal essence to her daughter, Hei Lou Lan.

After becoming an immortal, Hei Lou Lan used these clues to get back the attitude Gu that had been lost in the northern icy plain for many years!

But after some twists and turns, this Immortal Gu ended up in Fang Yuan's hands, being heavily used by him.

These last days, Fang Yuan had been familiarizing himself with the refinement path killer move, he even disguised himself to ensure that there were no issues.

Refinement path killer moves were used, turning into flames and lightning, attacking the heavenly crystal eagle nest. Each hit caused the heavenly crystal eagle nest to shake slightly, giving off a clear sound.

Gradually, the heavenly crystal eagle nest's movements became larger, and the sounds it made became louder, until it resounded in the sky.

"The final blow!"

Fang Yuan was nervous.

With his skillful method, he drew a trace of attitude Gu's aura and fused it into a translucent ripple as it flew towards the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

The ripple fused into the heavenly crystal eagle nest, vanishing immediately.

The heavenly crystal eagle nest continued to shake, light was emitting from within it. Gradually, the entire heavenly crystal eagle nest started shining in nine colors.

Red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, purple, white, black!

Nine colors filled the world, the light was dazzling and forced 'Hei Cheng' to retreat to a distance.

Ding ding ding...

As the light faded, the sound of chimes could be heard in the sky.

In front of 'Hei Cheng', this heavenly crystal eagle nest that had been closed for years finally opened itself!

Each of the pillars of heavenly crystal started moving and unraveling, making Fang Yuan think of a Rubik's cube. The nine colored heavenly crystal weaved and moved, eventually, an entrance was formed on the surface of the heavenly crystal eagle nest. The entire process was fluid and dazzling, he subconsciously held his breath from the incredible sight.

"I understand!" Fang Yuan's heart jumped, he understood the method that Hei Fan used.

"The heavenly crystals were originally colorless and translucent, but they no longer are now!"

"These heavenly crystals have nine colors, they should come from the respective immemorial nine heavens. But Hei Fan fused them together, using these rank eight immemorial immortal materials through refinement path methods. He caused their colors to fade away, so that they looked like a whole entity."

"Before Hei Fan died, he left behind some refinement path methods. Using these methods, one could reverse refine these heavenly crystals, allowing them to regain their original appearance, and open up the eagle nest from the inside."

Thinking about this, Fang Yuan's assessment of the heavenly crystals' value increased again.

Heavenly crystals were an immortal material that could be produced naturally in grotto-heavens with deep foundations, other than in the immemorial nine heavens.

Originally, Fang Yuan thought that these heavenly crystals were formed in Hei Fan grotto-heaven. But in fact, they came from the immemorial nine heavens.

They had higher value as a result.

Because there were only two heavens left from the immemorial nine heavens, the other seven were destroyed already.

In the past, when Hei Fan searched for these heavenly crystals from the immemorial nine heavens, he definitely spent a lot of effort. Right now, it was getting harder for Gu Immortals to get these heavenly crystals, the only source was the scattered fragment worlds of the immemorial nine heavens that were hidden in the five regions.

"Hei Fan true inheritance, here I come." Fang Yuan restrained his excitement as he controlled 'Hei Cheng', carefully entering the eagle nest.

[1] Two characters in the poem can be read as Fang Yuan, even though the exact character used is not the same. Back

Chapter 1116: A Dead Egg

Fang Yuan controlled 'Hei Cheng', slowly getting into the eagle nest.

Light in nine colors shone on 'Hei Cheng''s face interchangeably.

His vision was covered by heavenly crystals, it was a grand and beautiful scene, like something out of a dream or illusion.

The eagle nest was not big, it was like a small room.

At the center of the room, there was a huge egg, other than that, there was nothing else.

'Hei Cheng' glanced at it.

His gaze was focused on this egg.

This egg was the height of a young man, it was oval shaped and had a glass-like shell, it was reflecting the light of the nine colors, it was extremely beautiful.

But Fang Yuan sensed acutely that this egg was covered in death energy, it was devoid of life.

Sensing this, he no longer cared about it, he placed his attention on the other aspects.

He searched and explored, after some hours, other than the heavenly crystals, he had no other gains.

"How can this be? Hei Fan was a time path great expert, how can the true inheritance that he left behind only have one empty heavenly crystal eagle nest? Where are his time path Immortal Gu? Where are his immortal killer moves?"

Fang Yuan thought quickly, soon, he placed his attention on the dead egg again.

"Perhaps to find Hei Fan's true inheritance, that dead egg is the key!"

Fang Yuan guessed.

At this stage, the memories that he had obtained from Hei Cheng were no longer useful. Fang Yuan had surpassed the generations of Hei tribe Gu Immortals, he was at a step that they had never reached before.

To obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance, Fang Yuan had to rely on himself.

'Hei Cheng' walked around the dead egg, using his Gu worms to observe and research it.

A moment later, Fang Yuan confirmed again that this was a dead egg.

An absolutely dead egg.

There was no disguise.

This way, Fang Yuan's guess that Hei Fan's true inheritance was hidden inside the egg shell was thwarted.

"Don't tell me, Hei Fan's true inheritance has already been stolen by someone. The Immortal Gu stored here are taken away already? I am not the first person in here?" Fang Yuan could not help but think.

This was not impossible.

This world had too many secrets!

After Fang Yuan's secret transactions with Sixth Hair, he did not dare to underestimate anyone.

Even though he was a transmigrator, in this world, he was not the only one. There already was one who did well enough in life to become a rank nine venerable.

Righteous path, demonic path, lone cultivators, countless elites and geniuses, heroes and conquerors, throughout history, they were shining like brilliant stars in the sky.

Fang Yuan was just one of the stars.

Fang Yuan's guess was not random, he had his evidence.

According to the intel obtained from Hei Cheng, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals had realized that attitude Gu was the key. While searching for attitude Gu, they also researched their methods, replicating attitude Gu's aura, attempting to 'deceive' the heavenly crystal eagle nest to open.

In Hei Cheng's memories, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals did not succeed.

But that did not mean that nobody had succeeded!

A Gu Immortal might have secretly opened the heavenly crystal eagle nest, taking Hei Fan's true inheritance for themselves, while nobody knew.

And this might not even be a Hei tribe Gu Immortal.

This example was very common throughout history.

The most famous example was Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

This person was the ultimate thief, in his life, he stole many Gu Immortals' true inheritances, countless forces hated him greatly.

Fang Yuan inspected it a few times over, there was indeed nothing else.

With his current methods and knowledge, if he found nothing, there was likely no Hei Fan true inheritance.

Fang Yuan felt very disappointed.

He was banking on Hei Fan's true inheritance to slow the rate of time in his immortal aperture.

Of course, he had Chu Du's help now, he did not need it temporarily.

But what about the future?

If one did not have huge worries, they would worry about smaller things.

Cooperating with Chu Du was dangerous, he was asking for favors from a tiger, heaven's will would also seek to instigate him.

Even if Fang Yuan did not need it now, with this assurance, he could have many ways out in the future if he encountered trouble.

"Even if there is no Hei Fan true inheritance, this heavenly crystal eagle nest is an entire nest of rank eight immortal materials, it has great value."

In fact, other than the Immortal Gu in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture, all of his other resources accumulated could not match half the value of the heavenly crystal eagle nest!

Of course, this was excluding Dang Hun Mountain. Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley were in Lang Ya blessed land, and the trade of guts Gu was solely handled by Lang Ya Sect now. He only took his share of the profits monthly.

"However, what is this dead egg? I actually could not recognize it using my own knowledge. If Hei Fan's true inheritance is still around, this dead egg might be the clue that Hei Fan purposely left behind."

Even though hope was slim, Fang Yuan was intending to follow this route and investigate.

He first went to treasure yellow heaven, because cultivation experience and knowledge was also sold here.

Among which, there were desolate beast encyclopedias, maps of Southern Border, books on ancient desolate plants.

Fang Yuan's divine sense looked around, choosing carefully, he bought some and looked at them.

Last time, he spent nearly ten thousand immortal essence stones to buy a large amount of pill azure incense. But this month's profits were not here yet, his funds were low.

But after seeing these, even though Fang Yuan learned something, he did not manage to find information regarding this mysterious dead egg.

Fang Yuan was not disappointed, instead he was a little happy.

The more mysterious this dead egg was, the deeper its origin, and the greater hope he had regarding the clues to Hei Fan's true inheritance.

"This dead egg is very likely to be an immemorial desolate beast's egg!" Fang Yuan's readings were not without result.

But in this case, the knowledge from treasure yellow heaven was basically useless.

Because this knowledge were mostly limited to rank six and seven.

Immemorial desolate beasts had rank eight battle strength, but rank eight Gu Immortals would not sell their knowledge in treasure yellow heaven. They had no lack of such money. In any case, most Gu Immortals would not buy them, because with their level, they could not interact with immemorial desolate beasts.

In the current world, most immemorial desolate beasts were inside white heaven and black heaven. Other than that, they were in the forbidden or catastrophic areas in the five regions, like the Northern Plains ten great fierce areas, or places like Earth Trench and Earth Abyss.

"Should I ask directly in treasure yellow heaven, putting up a high price for the origins of this egg?" Fang Yuan thought about it and denied this idea.

It was too eye-catching.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were not all dead.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals could easily deduce some information.

This was not good for Fang Yuan.

If rank eight Gu Immortals were drawn to him, they would be a problem.

Fang Yuan could not afford to face these existences yet.

He did not feel much dejection from treasure yellow heaven's uselessness, because he knew that he had someone who could help him with this problem.

That was Lang Ya land spirit!

Lang Ya land spirit was the obsession of Long Hair Ancestor, he had been a rank eight Gu Immortal, a refinement path supreme grandmaster, he was famous throughout history and had great reputation.

Which paths would have Gu Immortals with the widest knowledge?

Wisdom path, information path, and refinement path.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals could deduce secrets, information path Gu Immortals could search and find intel, while refinement path Gu Immortals had to refine Gu, they needed to know lots of immortal materials.

As one of the greatest refinement path experts in history, Long Hair Ancestor's knowledge was undeniably immense.

Fang Yuan sought help from Lang Ya land spirit.

This was not a smooth process, Fang Yuan was troubled by Lang Ya land spirit's attitude.

Recently, Lang Ya Sect was very unhappy with Fang Yuan, they felt that he was cultivating for himself and did not contribute to the sect. Now, Lang Ya Sect was developing in Tai Qiu, the falling star hound was causing them problems, their progress was minimal as a result.

"Fang Yuan, if you kill the falling star hound, I will let you read such books in our inventory. If you want to exchange for it, use a hundred contribution points." Lang Ya land spirit said coldly with a low tone.

Fang Yuan smiled: "I will exchange for it."

A hundred contribution points was almost all that he had now.

However, even so, Fang Yuan wanted to exchange for it, he did not plan to go to Tai Qiu.

Lang Ya land spirit snorted, he was about to speak again, but Fang Yuan said: "First supreme elder is truly impartial, handling matters according to sect rules. Lang Ya Sect's rise is inevitable."

Lang Ya land spirit was so angry his chest was puffing, his hair stood on ends as he breathed roughly, he contained his anger: "I heard that you have a deep relationship with Twelfth Hair, I remember this child had praised you before. Recently, he challenged the falling star hound, he suffered great injuries and his desolate beasts all died, he is very dejected. Are you going to visit him?"

"Thank you for the concern, first supreme elder." Fang Yuan had a heavy and sorrowful face, as if the one injured was not Twelfth Hair but himself.

"After exchanging for the books, I will go to Twelfth Hair." Fang Yuan assured.

Lang Ya land spirit was helpless, he could not do anything to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan got what he wanted, going to Twelfth Hair's cloud city along the way. But he did not meet with Twelfth Hair in person, a mortal Gu Master said: "My master is unwilling to meet guests, please go back."

Fang Yuan was not welcomed, but he did not leave, he asked with concern.

However, the attitude of this mortal Gu Master was very cold, Fang Yuan could not get any results, he had to leave 'helplessly'.

If not for the land spirit's awareness of matters in the blessed land, Fang Yuan would not even put up this show.

He knew clearly, how could a mortal hairy man Gu Master act like this to a Gu Immortal? Evidently, he was backed by a hairy man Gu Immortal. And this person was none other than Twelfth Hair, who held a grudge against Fang Yuan.

"My relationship with Lang Ya Sect has reached this stage... of course, a lot of the 'credit' goes to Sixth Hair. Lang Ya Sect has a lot of value, I need to restore and maintain a good relationship with it in the future, but that is not an urgent matter."

Returning to his own cloud city, he checked the information and was not disappointed.

"So this egg is the upper extreme heavenly eagle!"

Fang Yuan's heart shook.

Upper extreme heavenly eagles were immemorial desolate beasts with rank eight battle strength!

After his surprise, Fang Yuan was filled with joy.

He realized: his hard work was not in vain. If this was an egg of the upper extreme heavenly eagle, then Hei Fan's true inheritance was not taken away yet, it was waiting for him!

Chapter 1117: Upper Extreme Heavenly Eagle

Upper extreme heavenly eagle.

Fang Yuan had known about this immemorial desolate beast since long ago, but he did not know what its egg looked like.

Upper extreme heavenly eagles were space path immemorial desolate beasts, a mature adult upper extreme heavenly eagle could freely travel in the immemorial nine heavens or in grotto-heavens.

This ability was amazing.

Outside of the immemorial nine heavens, there were extremely thick heavenly wind qi walls. Grotto-heavens were situated in the sky, if they did not open up, it was hard to detect them from the outside world.

But as long as the upper extreme heavenly eagle had gone to a place before, it could follow its instincts and travel through space, returning to a former location.

It was an immemorial desolate beast with rank eight battle strength, it could fly extremely fast. Hei Fan could obtain an egg of the upper extreme heavenly eagle, he must have paid an extremely high price if it was not by chance.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle's only weakness was its lifespan.

It only had eighty years of lifespan.

Ordinary mortals had about a hundred years of lifespan.

The great immemorial desolate beast, upper extreme heavenly eagle, had less lifespan than even a mortal, it was truly astounding. Other immemorial desolate beasts often had hundreds of thousands of years to live, the upper extreme heavenly eagle could not compare to them.

However, it had the ability to prolong its life.

When it died of old age, it would produce an egg.

Inside this egg, there would be all of its memories as well as the accumulated space path dao marks over its entire life.

When the chick breaks out of the shell, the upper extreme heavenly eagle would live another life, it would grow up again, but with its previous life's memories and dao mark accumulation. Without any unexpected mishaps, the upper extreme heavenly eagle would only become stronger.

Of course, when it is an egg or eagle chick, the upper extreme heavenly eagle would be at its weakest.

After understanding this, Fang Yuan had a bold guess: "This upper extreme heavenly eagle's egg must have been left behind by Hei Fan!"

Why did he leave behind this egg?

Evidently, the upper extreme heavenly eagle had gone to Hei Fan grotto-heaven before. It was the key to entering it.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals had always been searching for the grotto-heaven that Hei Fan had left behind. But in Hei Cheng's memories, they had no gains.

"Hei Fan's true inheritance must be inside his own grotto-heaven. This is not strange, because if he did not have food path methods, it would be best to keep all of his Immortal Gu inside the grotto-heaven and sustain their own feeding, that has most assurance."

"And Hei Fan grotto-heaven has no tribulations. According to Hei Cheng's memories, Hei Fan had obtained a certain fragment of the immemorial nine heavens before his death. If I am not wrong, he must have fused this fragment of the immemorial nine heavens into his immortal aperture before dying."

"It is a pity, even though he has no tribulations, he had no lifespan Gu, his lifespan extension methods were also at their limits, he could only die."

"But why is the heavenly eagle egg inside the eagle nest dead?"

Fang Yuan was faced with a difficult question.

There were two answers.

One was that the heavenly eagle egg had naturally died. Hei Fan left the living egg behind, preventing it from hatching, he used the heavenly crystal eagle nest to create an arrangement. But because nobody came to inherit it after a long time, the heavenly crystal eagle nest was not opened, the egg died eventually after a long time.

The second possibility was that the heavenly eagle egg had no life force left because Hei Fan did it. This egg was not truly dead, it needed a special method to unseal it.

If it was the first possibility, Fang Yuan naturally could not obtain any benefits. He could only get a heavenly crystal eagle nest and a dead immemorial egg. They had great value in themselves but that was all.

From Fang Yuan's perspective, he would naturally prefer the second possibility.

But if that was the case, what was the special method that could unseal the egg?

"Assuming the second case, how can I unseal this dead egg, to let it regain life force and even hatch?" Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

He thought for a long time, but there were no answers.

It was not strange.

This egg was quite literally dead. If not for that, Fang Yuan would not have confirmed this at the start so easily.

"If I were Hei Fan, I would definitely leave behind clues to resolve this problem after setting up this dead egg, so that descendants could inherit this." Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration.

He realized he had subconsciously ignored something.

It was the refinement path methods that Hei Fan had once modified and left behind on purpose.

"I used these methods to open the heavenly crystal eagle nest. If I use these methods again, will it work on the dead egg?" Fang Yuan had a bold assumption.

But he did not act yet.

Because this was just a hypothesis, there was no proof or evidence backing it.

Fang Yuan was vigilant, he started using wisdom path methods, he went deep into analyzing these refinement path methods, placing focus on deducing them.

He quickly discovered something strange.

What was strange?

Some refinement path killer moves were very strangely modified. The original versions were better and had stronger effects than the newer versions.

Hei Fan's modifications were simply going the reverse direction.

What was he trying to do?

Fang Yuan suddenly thought about some historical records regarding Hei Fan that were inside Hei Cheng's memories.

Hei Fan was a rank eight Gu Immortal, during his later years, he liked to nurture juniors, but he often taught them: "When learning, you have to think for yourself, don't just blindly follow and idolize your seniors' experiences. Only by thinking for yourself and learning them can you go further on the path of a Gu Immortal."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan looked at the refinement path killer moves with new ideas.

He tried to remove the 'failed modifications' that Hei Fan did in those killer moves, he made a shocking discovery.

"So these refinement path killer moves are not failures, by combining them, they form a brand new killer move!"

"Hei Fan had purposely added in unnecessary steps in these refinement path killer moves, they are failures individually. But together, these parts can combine into a whole!"

What made Fang Yuan more surprised was that this new killer move was a type of blood path method.

The great rank eight time path Hei Fan, researching blood path?

This was not strange.

Ever since Blood Sea Ancestor appeared, blood path's power was known to all. All the super forces restricted the growth of blood path, while researching it secretly themselves.

This was something happening even in Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, not to mention Northern Plains, a region with Gu Immortals that sought battle strength greatly.

Fang Yuan was much more confident in blood path than refinement path.

He was a blood path grandmaster! Blood path was his most used path in the past.

With some research, Fang Yuan realized: Hei Fan had purposely concealed this blood refinement killer move, it was to be used on the upper extreme heavenly eagle!

But this blood refinement killer move was not complete.

With Fang Yuan's knowledge and blood path attainment, he could tell that this blood path killer move was not complete, it was only a portion.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan was not disappointed, instead his eyes were shining brightly.

"Hei Fan must have the complete blood refinement killer move, he used the first half to process this upper extreme heavenly eagle dead egg. He only left the other half to his descendants."

"But he did not pass down this blood path killer move directly to his descendants, he used a unique method to conceal it."

"His first motive must be to test his descendants, so that a skilled Gu Immortal who could think for themselves inherits this. The second reason was that blood path was notorious, if the great Hei Fan's true inheritance used a blood path method, it would cause a huge commotion. Hei Fan did not want that to happen."

Fang Yuan was scheming and shrewd, he could easily tell what Hei Fan was thinking in the past.

After clarifying this, he was even more assured that this upper extreme heavenly eagle was not truly dead, it was just processed by Hei Fan through a special method.

That made things easier!

Fang Yuan was no longer an immortal zombie, he could easily draw blood from his own body.

However, just as he was about to use blood refinement, he stopped his actions.

"So close! I almost failed to notice Hei Fan's intention..." Fang Yuan's forehead was filled with sweat.

Why did Hei Fan leave a blood path method for his descendants?

Wasn't it really strange?

Everyone knew that Hei Fan was a time path great expert, at this level, he could easily use time path methods to leave his inheritance behind and imitate methods of other paths.

But he used blood path instead of his strongest time path, why was that?

There was only one possible reason, the blood path method could do something that time path could not.

What else could it be?

As a blood path grandmaster, Fang Yuan first thought of — bloodline recognition!

The inheritance that Hei Fan left behind was meant for Hei tribe descendants. The inheritance of a super force's Gu Immortal was usually kept to the clan or tribe itself, the first condition was to be blood related. Very few Gu Immortals would leave behind inheritances that could be obtained by others.

Attitude Gu, the refinement path method left behind for generations, they were just the first two precautions.

The blood refinement method that uses one's bloodline was the third.

"If the inheritor is not a Hei tribe descendant and does not have Hei tribe's bloodline, then blood refining this dead egg might cause a backlash. Or rather, the immemorial desolate beast upper extreme heavenly eagle that hatches would be the enemy of this Gu Immortal!"

Fang Yuan thought of this and felt even more sweat on his forehead.

Especially the last part, if he truly became enemies with an immemorial desolate beast, of rank eight battle strength, he would be in deep trouble!

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was very fast, Fang Yuan could not outrun it, he had weak defenses as well, he would definitely die.

"It seems that I can only use a proper bloodline to refine the egg." Fang Yuan wisely stopped.

Some days later.

In a part of the sovereign immortal aperture.

Hei Cheng's hair was a mess, he had a very tired and weak expression.

Fang Yuan manipulated the strength path immortal zombie, flying towards him.

Hei Cheng jolted like he was hit by lightning, his body shook as he shouted in fear and shock: "You, what do you want?!"

Earlier, Fang Yuan had soul searched him, forget about that. Now, he was using all sorts of methods to 'torture' Hei Cheng, he was truly in misery, he felt that he was better off dead.

Hei Cheng was Fang Yuan's captive, at this stage, he had already given up. His Gu Immortal demeanor was gone.

But he could not even bite his own tongue to suicide.

Fang Yuan had thought: Hei Cheng still had some value, even though Hei tribe was gone, Hei Lou Lan was alive.

Thus, Hei Cheng was in a state where he could neither die nor live in peace.

"Don't worry, this is likely to be the last time, I am confident of it." Fang Yuan manipulated the strength path immortal zombie, smiling as he got closer.

Hei Cheng was about to cry, he struggled intensely: "You say that every time, it is always the last time! No, no, no! Ah—!"

Chapter 1118: Future Rank Eight Battle Strength

Hei Cheng's expression was distorted, he screamed in great agony.

Fang Yuan did not care, he continued to use his blood path killer move.

With blood asset Immortal Gu as the core, this blood path killer move was an immortal killer move!

Because of this power, Hei Cheng felt immense pain, blood from all over his body and even bone marrow were drained out, gathered into a lump.

Next, Fang Yuan controlled the strength path immortal zombie and swallowed it whole.

Hei Cheng was drained of much of his blood and fainted, his entire body was skin and bones, he had a pale expression, like he had died.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly, several mortal Gu flew out entered Hei Cheng's ears, going into his bloodstream and traveling.

These blood path mortal Gu were huge, when they traveled in Hei Cheng's body, there were bumps over his body, as if rats were moving rapidly in him.

Soon, these 'rats' became smaller and smaller, Hei Cheng's body started inflating, color was restored on his face. But he was exhausted mentally, as if he had just overcome a huge sickness.

He slowly opened his eyes, looking at the strength path immortal zombie, he muttered: "Spare me, spare me. I am willing to surrender, I will be loyal to you..."

Fang Yuan did not reply to him.

Hei Cheng had said this many times.

Fang Yuan did not care to have a subordinate like Hei Cheng.

Fang Yuan was already wary of the featherman Gu Immortal Zhou Zhong, not to mention Hei Cheng. With the outside situation as it was, Fang Yuan could only trust himself.

In fact, sometimes, he did not even trust himself.

After the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Fang Yuan had lost his memories.

After knowing the secrets of heaven's will and his rebirth, he realized that the fortuitous encounters that he remembered in his previous life were likely arrangements set by heaven's will!

Right now, Fang Yuan's focus was on manipulating the strength path immortal zombie.

After swallowing Hei Cheng's blood, the strength path immortal zombie's body shone with a thin layer of blood-red light.

Under Fang Yuan's expectant gaze, this blood-red light slowly faded, entering the strength path immortal zombie's body, turning into blood which those of Hei tribe's bloodline had.

"Success!" After several inspections, Fang Yuan was excited.

These last days, he had been preparing to refine the egg.

Disguising his bloodline was not a problem for Fang Yuan.

He was a blood path grandmaster, he had a deep foundation in his previous life.

But he had to take into account Hei Fan's blood refinement method, it was a bit troublesome. Fang Yuan had to deduce and modify it several times, after torturing Hei Cheng many times, he finally succeeded.

"With this blood, I still cannot use it on the egg. I need to integrate this blood path killer move into familiar face, so as to be certain!"

For the next ten days, Fang Yuan focused on deductions.

But he had high attainment levels, blood path and transformation path were both grandmaster. Ordinary Gu Immortals could not achieve this, but he completed it in less than half a month.

Looking at the time, a month had passed in total.

He was only about a month away from the fourth earthly calamity.

With everything ready now, Fang Yuan made good use of his time, immediately targeting the egg.

As he had expected, under the effect of the blood path killer move, the lifeless egg started to produce life force.

As more and more blood went in, this life force also grew stronger, and became more amiable with Fang Yuan.

Eight days and nights later, the shell cracked from inside, as a small bird came out.

This bird was newly hatched, but it was not small, it could stand at the height of a youngster.

The small eagle looked at the strength path immortal zombie that Fang Yuan had become, it had a warm gaze, affection could be seen from within its sharp eagle eyes. It was like a child seeing their parents.

"Come, come here." Fang Yuan manipulated the immortal zombie, saying.

The little eagle quickly jumped to the immortal zombie, looking at him with dark eyes that showed an innocent gaze without any wariness.

The immortal zombie stretched out its arm, patting the eagle's head.

There was only a layer of yellow feathers on the young eagle's head, it was very sparse, Fang Yuan could feel its scalp, it had a good feeling of warmth.

While patting it, the young eagle lowered its head without any resistance. Not just that, the eagle's eyes were shut, it opened its beak and chirped cutely, as if it was trying to get Fang Yuan's attention.

Fang Yuan could discern many things, he internally praised: "Hei Fan is amazing, he actually removed the memories of the upper extreme heavenly eagle from its previous life, only its space path dao mark foundation is left. If it had its memories, this upper extreme heavenly eagle, as an immemorial desolate beast, would be hard to control."

"And this blood path killer move can actually enslave an immemorial desolate beast. No, enslave is not the word, the true effect is to make the immemorial desolate beast feel close to me, it is the sense of kinship, of being a close bloodline relative."

"This way, it should not be hard to get it to carry me and find Hei Fan grotto-heaven."

Just when he had that idea in his mind, the eagle chirped anxiously, its body was wavering unstably.

"Hungry?" Fang Yuan controlled the immortal zombie, pulling back his hand as he pointed at the heavenly crystal eagle nest: "Go eat!"

The upper extreme heavenly eagle's food were heavenly crystals!

After getting permission, the little eagle chirped happily, it jumped over and pecked, causing a small piece of heavenly crystal to fall out.

The little eagle carried the heavenly crystal in its beak, it did not swallow it, instead, it turned to the strength path immortal zombie.

The strength path immortal zombie smiled at the little eagle, saying warmly: "Go eat."

The little eagle understood, it raised its head and swallowed the small piece of heavenly crystal.

Next, it continued to eat.

The hard heavenly crystal broke apart like tofu inside its beak, Fang Yuan watched, slightly startled.

One could not look down on this bird, it was a genuine immemorial desolate beast — upper extreme heavenly eagle!

"This means, from now on, I control battle strength on the level of an immemorial desolate beast? No, it is too young, it cannot have such high battle strength."

"It seems to understand my words, that must be Hei Fan's doing. Since he can erase its memories, he can also make it learn human language."

"However, there is a huge flaw!"

"I need to disguise my bloodline, so that the upper extreme heavenly eagle feels close to me. The real me would not do, I would even get attacked by it. After all, such immemorial desolate beasts are very prideful, they are naturally aggressive."

Fang Yuan considered the other aspects.

For the next few days, Fang Yuan controlled the strength path immortal zombie, staying with the young eagle, watching it eat.

The young eagle did not eat all the time, it ate for a while before going to the strength path immortal zombie, snuggling up to it and sleeping.

It was extremely trusting of the strength path immortal zombie, it did not guard against it.

For the next few days, half of the heavenly crystal eagle nest was consumed.

This consumption speed gave Fang Yuan a headache.

In order to get an immemorial level battle strength, spending such immortal materials was needed. But the price of feeding it was truly very high.

The young eagle grew quickly.

It was the height of a youngster initially, but in a few days, it was as tall as Fang Yuan.

It stood on the ground, raising its head, it had a strong body and thick layer of feathers, it had sharp eagle eyes and dark sharp claws, when it scratched, heavenly crystals broke like thin paper.

The time was ripe, Fang Yuan was not going to wait any longer.

He recalled the strength path immortal zombie, taking back all of the Immortal Gu and mortal Gu in it, using familiar face on his own body.

The current familiar face had exceeded the original version, by adding in blood asset Immortal Gu and other mortal Gu.

This way, Fang Yuan could even disguise his bloodline.

Fang Yuan chose to leave Lang Ya blessed land, choosing a spot with nobody around, opening his immortal aperture and letting out the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

The young eagle saw Fang Yuan's true body, it did not have any suspicions, coming over to peck at Fang Yuan's palm lightly, it lowered its head, using its head to rub Fang Yuan's shoulder, it had a very warm attitude.

Fang Yuan smiled, instructing the young eagle: "Quickly bring me to Hei Fan grotto-heaven, I need to inherit Hei Fan's true inheritance."

The young eagle went in a daze, it remembered a certain part of its memories, chirping loudly as it spread its wings.

Fang Yuan saw the chance and jumped onto the eagle's back.

The eagle screeched, carrying Fang Yuan as it ascended, flying towards the southeast direction.

The surrounding air currents were wildly blowing past his ears.

Fang Yuan activated his Gu worms, sitting on the eagle's back stably.

He was very satisfied with the upper extreme heavenly eagle's speed, it was not inferior to sword escape Immortal Gu.

Most importantly, this upper extreme heavenly eagle was an infant eagle, it was far from maturity, it had yet to fully develop. A mature upper extreme heavenly eagle was huge, multiple times the size of a whale.

Fang Yuan also estimated: Its current battle strength had not reached rank eight yet, currently, it was at rank six level.

Even though it had a lot of space path dao marks, it did not have wild Gu. A major influence on desolate beasts and plants in their battle strength was their physical bodies. This was different from humans, humans had weak physiques, but desolate beasts had naturally powerful attack, defense, as well as recovery. Not to mention immemorial desolate beasts.

This was the first time Fang Yuan was interacting with the upper extreme heavenly eagle, his earlier assessment of it having rank eight battle strength upon hatching was wrong.

Even though he was disappointed, it was sure to grow into having rank eight battle strength in the future!

The upper extreme heavenly eagle traveled quickly, Fang Yuan sat on its back, once in a while, he fed it heavenly crystals.

During other times, Fang Yuan was not slacking, he was analyzing Hei Fan as a person.

From Hei Cheng's memories, there was lots of praise towards Hei Fan.

This time path expert who had led Hei tribe to a glorious era in history was not simple!

Fang Yuan reviewed the process of unraveling Hei Fan true inheritance, it was as if he was fighting against Hei Fan in terms of wits.

This was truly an extraordinary contest.

Hei Fan left behind the refinement path killer moves, heavenly crystal eagle nest, dead upper extreme heavenly eagle egg, and the hidden blood path killer move, they revealed to Fang Yuan this time path great expert's meticulousness, his shrewd planning and proud nature.

Those who could cultivate to rank eight were not simple characters.

Hei Fan was an expert at rank eight, his true inheritance was not easy to obtain!

Hei tribe's Gu Immortals tried for so many years without success. Of course, this was also due to the loss of attitude Gu.

But it was undeniable that anyone else would have failed. Only a shrewd and astute individual like Fang Yuan would be able to make progress while exploiting the appropriate opportunities, eventually making his way to Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

"After I get to Hei Fan grotto-heaven, will I get to obtain the true inheritance? I have a feeling that Hei Fan's test is not over yet."

"But the more tests there are, the more extraordinary the true inheritance, this is not a bad thing!"

Chapter 1119: Entering Hei Fan Grotto-Heaven

One and a half days later, the upper extreme heavenly eagle carried Fang Yuan and flew to the sky of an unknown location.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle's speed decreased, it started to fly around the air.

After a while of flying, it seemed to have confirmed the location, it pecked at a certain spot.

Instantly, Fang Yuan could hear a clear sound of a bell, as space tore open and his vision changed.

In an instant, the upper extreme heavenly eagle brought him into Hei Fan grotto-heaven, disappearing from Northern Plains' sky.

"The upper extreme heavenly eagle can truly cross space and enter grotto-heavens! It is so amazing as an infant, when it matures, it will surely be a huge help."

Fang Yuan praised in his mind as he looked around.

This grotto-heaven was huge and vast, it was an extraordinary sight.

Below Fang Yuan, there was an ancient forest. It was green and huge, birds and beasts lived in it, there was much life within.

"Musical trees." There were trees with rainbow colored leaves and countless birds flying on them, landing on the branches as they chirped, creating a beautiful melody.

"Qi death birds." One of the types of birds had plump bodies that pressed down on the branches, they were covered in qi currents and had distinct voices.

"Tea stream." Between trees, there was a smooth flowing stream, the water was a clear, pale green, it was steaming hot, making the leaves inside resemble tea leaves.

...

Fang Yuan took a look, finding many cultivation resources inside the forest.

He looked at the sky, this grotto-heaven's sky was azure in color.

"It seems that Hei Fan obtained a fragment of the immemorial azure heaven, after fusing it into his grotto-heaven, the sky never changed color again." Fang Yuan made an initial confirmation that this was Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Because in Hei Cheng's memories, he knew that Hei Fan had once grew musical trees and famously sold them in treasure yellow heaven.

This entire forest was made of musical trees, the scale was shockingly big.

Just as Fang Yuan was looking around, the entire world suddenly started to ring with sounds of a bell.

The bell rang ten times.

Next, a brass bell appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

"Heavenly spirit! There's indeed a heavenly spirit..." Fang Yuan's heart shook, he got nervous.

He did not have Hei tribe's bloodline after all, even though he deceived the upper extreme heavenly eagle, he still had to deceive the heavenly spirit to obtain the true inheritance.

...

In the north-east part of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, there was a tall mountain.

The locals named it Wang Gu Mountain, they revered it.

There was a cave in the mountain.

In the cave, three Gu Immortals were conversing.

"Without taking risks, how can we have great gains? To break free of this cage, we need to take on the risks of doing so." Gu Immortal Feng Jun had an agitated expression.

The other two Gu Immortals looked at each other with hesitation.

One of them, Gu Immortal Zheng Tuo, looked at Feng Jun: "This is a huge matter, if we are careless, we will die, how can we not act carefully?"

The other Gu Immortal, Zhou Min, was female, she had beautiful features: "Brother Feng Jun, please calm down. It is very difficult to deal with the heavenly spirit, we need to plan this wisely, we are not in a rush. Don't worry, the three of us are sworn siblings, we will work as one and move forward together."

Feng Jun raised his head and sighed: "The heavenly spirit is not scary, we have already gained its trust, using the killer move, blood light spirit suppression, that I created, I am very confident of success."

Zheng Tuo looked at Feng Jun: "Brother, I do not want to say this, but why are you in a rush? You said earlier that blood light spirit suppression was created recently. This immortal killer move has just been created, it is not perfected. Even if it is perfected, we need to practice it first, why are you so hurried?"

"That's right, brother." Zhou Min also said: "To deal with the heavenly spirit, we are not sufficient. We might as well convince Old Immortal Chen Chi to the west, he has three Gu Immortals under him."

Feng Jun snorted, saying in disdain: "Chen Chi is useless. He is about to die, yet he still acts so conservatively, we should not rely on him!"

Feng Jun shook his head.

Zhou Min frowned: "Brother, even if you look down on Old Immortal Chen Chi, he has the highest cultivation level. Even if we cannot work with him to deal with the heavenly spirit, we have to get him to watch on the sidelines and not interfere."

"Sister makes sense." Zheng Tuo added.

Feng Jun had a grim expression, after some hesitation, he said: "I am not going to lie, you both know I cultivate luck path. Recently, I have had an ominous feeling, something bad is going to happen. I have this indescribable sensation — if we do not take the chance now, we might not have a chance anymore!"

These words were simply Feng Jun's assumption, he had no proof at all to back him up.

But the other two immortals had grim expressions.

Zhou Min said: "Brother, you once had gone up Immortal Succession Mountain and cultivated the luck path inheritance that was on it. Even though your cultivation level did not reach rank seven, as the first inheritor, your dao marks are not less than that of a rank seven luck path Gu Immortal. I heard that with a certain number of luck path dao marks, the Gu Immortal will have a mystical promotion."

On the side, Zheng Tuo also added: "That's right, for refinement path Gu Immortals, their Gu refinement abilities would rise sharply, when refining Gu, they would be able to sense minute details. For fire path Gu Immortals, they would have a certain sense towards fire path Immortal Gu and desolate beasts. For wisdom path Gu Immortals, even without using any Gu, their own deduction abilities would be very strong. As for luck path Gu Immortals, they would have some sensation towards their own luck or the luck around them."

"That's right." Feng Jun sighed, his expression calming down.

Since Zhou Min and Zheng Tuo could understand him, that was good.

After all, the killer move, blood light spirit suppression, that he made could not be used alone, all three of them needed to activate it together.

Suddenly, at this time, the sound of a bell from outside became clearer.

"Did someone else ascend Immortal Succession Mountain, obtaining a true inheritance?" Zheng Tuo's eyes flashed.

"Regardless of who it is, we have to get them over to our side." Zhou Min immediately said.

"Listen, there are five rings already." Feng Jun's attention was drawn.

"Impressive, this person got to this point, in the past, even you, brother, only got this far." Zheng Tuo praised.

But soon, their expressions changed.

"Seven times." Zhou Min cried out.

"How can this be? Not only was I surpassed, even Old Immortal Chen Chi was surpassed?!" Feng Jun could not believe it, he was aware of the difficulties of going up Immortal Succession Mountain.

But next, a tenth bell sound rang out, it resounded in the entire world, continuing to spread.

The three immortals were like statues, they stood in their places, unmoving.

A moment later, Zhou Min snapped back to awareness, shock was expressed all over her beautiful face: "Did I hear wrongly, the bell rang ten times!"

Feng Jun's expression was dark: "According to the stone tablet on Immortal Succession Mountain, ten rings of the bell means that the person from the main tribe who is qualified to inherit Old Ancestor Hei Fan's true inheritance is here! Don't tell me my bad feeling is due to this person!"

"After so many years, I thought that nobody would inherit the first true inheritance on Immortal Succession Mountain! To think that..." Zheng Tuo shook his head, showing a complex expression.

He looked at the two immortals beside him, they also had differing expressions.

Zheng Tuo let out a breath of air, stabilizing his mind: "Let's go, according to the rules, when the proper inheritor appears, the heavenly spirit will welcome them personally, we need to go ahead and pay respects to them too."

"Pay respects? Pay what respects!" Feng Jun's body shook, he said shrilly: "Regardless of who it is? Why must we go and pay respects to them? We are also Hei tribe descendants with Hei tribe's bloodline. Just because our ancestors were criminals, we have to be subservient to the main tribe forever?"

Zhou Min quickly consoled him: "Brother, you make sense, I agree. Even though this is sudden, the result is not out of control yet. According to the rules on the stone tablet, even though the inheritor is here, the time has passed already. To inherit Hei Fan's true inheritance, they would need to pass a test. Whether we are going to find trouble with them or take down the heavenly spirit, we need to stay calm, stay cool."

Feng Jun was reminded, his mind cleared up: "Sister, you are right, we still have a chance! Go, we will go immediately, we cannot expose any flaws. I want to see how amazing this inheritor is, do they have three heads or six arms? Hmph!"

...

The brass bell floated in front of Fang Yuan, after ringing ten times, it went silent.

Fang Yuan tried to ask: "Are you the heavenly spirit? I am Hei Cheng, I opened the heavenly crystal eagle nest and hatched the upper extreme heavenly eagle, I am here to inherit Ancestor Hei Fan's true inheritance."

But the brass bell remained silent, it floated in front of Fang Yuan, unmoving.

"As expected... after devouring the fragment of immemorial azure heaven, even the heavenly spirit has become mindless." Fang Yuan's eyes flashed, he understood the reason.

This intel was obtained from Shadow Sect as well.

After absorbing a fragment of the immemorial nine heavens, even though the grotto-heaven would have no tribulations, if the Gu Immortal dies and becomes a heavenly spirit, they would not have control and would be mindless.

All in all, it was because of heaven's will.

Heaven's will originated from the five regions and nine heavens. Ordinary grotto-heavens were small worlds independent of the outside world. But once they absorbed an immemorial nine heavens fragment, they would let heaven's will in. Their personal authority would be greatly diminished due to heaven's will!

Shadow Sect had deep research in this.

In the past, a Shadow Sect member, one of the seven original split souls, Seven Star Child, had went ahead to devour a fragment of immemorial blue heaven, attempting to research a way to deal with heaven's will. Unfortunately, heaven's will made use of it and caused Seven Star Child to be stuck inside Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm, unable to get out.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm, because Starry Sky grotto-heaven had shattered and broken into many pieces, landed in many areas of Central Continent like all of the other grotto-heaven fragment worlds.

Among which, on a nameless mountain, Fang Yuan was invited by Immortal Crane Sect to explore it. Coincidentally, inside this fragment world, Fang Yuan explored the dream realm and obtained crucial pointers. Eventually, on Yi Tian Mountain, Fang Yuan obtained the result of Shadow Sect's plan after a hundred thousand years.

From this, one could see that by absorbing any nine heavens fragment, the grotto-heaven world would be under the supervision of heaven's will, it was not safe for Fang Yuan.

The safest place for him were blessed lands or grotto-heavens like Lang Ya blessed land.

They were privately owned, heaven's will could not look inside.

Long Hair Ancestor was a very famous figure, it was not hard for him to get some immemorial nine heavens fragments. But from start to finish, he did not let his grotto-heaven absorb any fragment of the immemorial nine heavens.

"Thus, this grotto-heaven is far less valuable to me than Hei Fan's true inheritance."

"Once I inherit Hei Fan's true inheritance, I will give this grotto-heaven to Chu Du, it will fulfill that agreement of splitting thirty percent profit with him."

Fang Yuan was still planning, when a few people appeared from the sky, their immortal auras were unconcealed, they rapidly got closer.

"What is going on? Hei Fan grotto-heaven has Gu Immortals?" Fang Yuan was surprised.

Chapter 1120: Shocking the Immortals

From far away, four Gu Immortals approached.

Fang Yuan had a serious expression, he watched without blinking.

This situation was out of his expectations.

"Why are there Gu Immortals here?" Fang Yuan looked at the heavenly spirit and asked.

But this Hei Fan grotto-heaven's heavenly spirit was too dull, it did not respond.

Fang Yuan felt a gloomy sensation.

After a while, the four Gu Immortals got close, but there was no animosity from them.

Fang Yuan prepared himself without showing any changes externally.

"I, criminal immortal Chen Chi, greet the superior immortal from the main tribe!" The leader was an old Gu Immortal. He wore a tall crown, he had a green-grey robe and white hair, after seeing Fang Yuan, he paid respects with a solemn expression.

"Criminal immortal?" Fang Yuan thought over this, but he quickly responded: "I am not worthy of being called a 'superior immortal', my name is Hei Cheng, I was fortunate to have inherited Hei Fan's true inheritance, to think that I could meet so many immortals after entering the grotto-heaven."

Fang Yuan had turned into Hei Cheng's appearance.

This was after careful consideration.

After all, with treasure yellow heaven's existence, even though Hei Fan grotto-heaven was isolated from the outside world, they could still find out about Hei tribe's information.

Hei Cheng had gone missing, and he lost Hei tribe's Immortal Gu House, but that did not hinder him from inheriting Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Most importantly, Fang Yuan had all of Hei Cheng's memories, he could disguise as him perfectly with no flaws.

Chen Chi raised his head, looking at Fang Yuan, he sighed in admiration.

Hei Cheng was publicly recognized as a handsome man in Northern Plains, he had a gentlemanly grace and many women had crushes on him. At this moment, even though Fang Yuan was in disguise, he even had a superior flair to Hei Cheng, with his looks, he was extraordinary and charming, he could take one's heart easily.

Of the four Gu Immortals who came, two were female, seeing Fang Yuan's looks, their hearts involuntarily beat faster.

The other was a young man with an ordinary appearance.

Chen Chi bowed again: "Superior immortal Hei Cheng, you have dazzling disposition, us criminal immortals of Hei tribe have waited for so long up until you finally came, heaven truly is not blind."

"I am flattered, but why do you call yourselves criminal immortals, what does that mean? I do not understand." Fang Yuan frowned, asking directly.

Chen Chi was about to answer, when a voice came from afar: "Superior immortal, it is normal that you do not know! Our ancestors were guilty of a heavy crime in Hei tribe. Back then, Old Ancestor Hei Fan's granddaughter, Hei Feng Yue, carried attitude Gu and roamed the icy plain. She was targeted by a mysterious Gu Immortal, at that time, our ancestors were her guards, but they failed to take care of her, Hei Feng Yue went missing and even attitude Gu was lost."

"Old Ancestor Hei Fan doted on his granddaughter Hei Feng Yue, but he searched for her to no avail. Our ancestors could not make up for this failure, they could only submit to punishment and were locked inside this Hei Fan grotto-heaven by Old Ancestor Hei Fan. They were our lineage, continuing to live here over the generations."

"So that's it." Fang Yuan understood, he meticulously observed them.

There were three new immortals that just came here.

Two males and one female.

They were Feng Jun, Zhou Min, and Zheng Tuo.

Feng Jun and Zhou Min were rank six, Fang Yuan took a glance at them.

Zheng Tuo flew in front, he was the leader of the three immortals.

He was the one who answered Fang Yuan earlier.

He had his rank seven cultivation level unconcealed. He had an ordinary face with a hunched back, when he flew over, there was a thin line of blood behind him, he was a blood path cultivator!

This made Fang Yuan surprised internally.

A blood path Gu Immortal appeared openly like this, but the other Gu Immortals were completely unfazed? They seemed used to it.

"Unless, this person does not cultivate blood path primarily, but only as a secondary path?"

"Even so, it cannot be shown openly."

Fang Yuan was a bit puzzled.

If this was in the five regions, this blood path demonic immortal would have already been a target of pursuit.

But at the moment, it seemed like he was doing pretty well, not only was there no animosity, he even had two subordinates.

These two were really daring, they were not afraid that this leader would attack them to increase his own battle strength!

The three immortals flew closer and greeted Fang Yuan as well, having a respectful attitude.

But Fang Yuan could tell clearly, this Feng Jun was not sincere, he held animosity towards Fang Yuan. He took several glances secretly with an unkind expression.

Actually, the rest were also like this.

Be it Chen Chi or the other Gu Immortals, they were solemn and cautious regarding Fang Yuan, while expressing kindness, they had ill intentions hidden, their attitudes were strange.

After greeting Fang Yuan, the three immortals talked to Chen Chi and the immortals behind him.

They spoke plainly, but they did not gather together, they floated in the air forming two clear groups.

Fang Yuan saw all of these, on the surface, he was talking to them warmly, but on the inside, he was memorizing these details.

"How many of you are there in this Hei Fan grotto-heaven?" Fang Yuan thought about this and asked.

"Not many. Other than the seven of us here, there are only two others." Chen Chi replied: "They will be here soon. Superior immortal, when you arrived, the heavenly spirit came to welcome you, ten rings of the bell resounded. They have also gone up Immortal Succession Mountain before, they know what it meant."

Immortal Succession Mountain?

Fang Yuan noted this name, but did not ask about it yet.

As expected, two more Gu Immortals appeared soon after. They were both males, they paid respects to Fang Yuan.

Like the other Gu Immortals, they also had strange expressions.

After the Gu Immortals gathered, the heavenly spirit finally made a move.

It suddenly shook, creating a loud sound as it drifted forward.

"The heavenly spirit wants to direct us to Immortal Succession Mountain, superior immortal, please follow us." Chen Chi saw this and said.

Fang Yuan nodded, he followed the brass bell heavenly spirit cautiously.

In this situation, he was alone, but the other side had nine Gu Immortals, two rank seven and seven rank six. If they suddenly attacked him, it would be a chaotic brawl with an unpredictable result.

However, even though the heavenly spirit was mindless, it could still welcome Fang Yuan, that showed that it carried Hei Fan's will, it was not completely unreliable.

Earlier, Fang Yuan could already tell that these people were not united, they were in different groups. The last two that came even seemed to be lone cultivators.

Precisely so, Fang Yuan decided to travel with them, he wanted to observe them first, and did not take action yet.

The heavenly spirit did not fly quickly.

Thus, Fang Yuan did not use the upper extreme heavenly eagle, he let it fly alongside him.

In this situation, he did not dare to keep the upper extreme heavenly eagle in his immortal aperture. If anything happened, even if the upper extreme heavenly eagle could not kill the enemy, it could attract their firepower.

Along the way, Fang Yuan talked to the Gu Immortals.

Initially, they were very wary of Fang Yuan, they spoke with him cautiously, there was a huge distance between them.

But what had Fang Yuan experienced? In the five hundred years of his previous life, he had interacted with countless people, he had shocking interpersonal skills in communication.

Soon, Fang Yuan got closer to them.

Gradually, there was even laughter coming from this group.

"Sister, look at Hei Cheng, he is truly a superior immortal from the main tribe! He is so charming and attractive, no wonder it was him... only people like this are worthy of Old Ancestor Hei Fan's true inheritance." In the group, a female Gu Immortal with long hair in two buns and bubbly nature looked at Fang Yuan as she transmitted secretly.

This was one of the female immortals who came with Chen Chi.

The Gu Immortal who had been referred to as sister was more elegant and mature, she heard the words and transmitted in a cheeky tone: "Hehe, it seems that you, sister, are infatuated. But yes, he is truly a dragon among men! He seems to be young and have high cultivation level, he also has such charm and speaks with great experience, he has a convincing tone and makes people feel engaged when talking to him. Sigh, I wonder if people like him are rare in the outside world? What kind of place is Northern Plains?"

Fang Yuan's ears twitched, he listened to all these words without missing any.

These Gu Immortal sisters used an ancient transmission method that had gone out of favor in Northern Plains long ago, this was exactly why Fang Yuan could eavesdrop on their conversation.

Even though this was a grotto-heaven, and mortal Gu could be prevented from being used, Fang Yuan did not receive a restriction in this aspect, he felt some assurance.

Actually, not just these two female Gu Immortals, the other Gu Immortals were also conversing, but they were not speaking as frequently as these two.

The other Gu Immortals were discussing Fang Yuan's background and battle strength.

These matters were more important.

"To think that this person has rank seven cultivation level! On our side, only Old Immortal Chen Chi and Brother Zheng Tuo match his cultivation level."

"Even though he is not displaying any Immortal Gu aura, the eagle flying beside him is extraordinary."

"This eagle is strange, it seems to be a desolate beast, but its aura is not normal."

"We have desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts in our grotto-heaven, but their aura cannot compare to this young eagle."

...

After some discussions, someone could not control himself anymore, he asked: "Superior immortal, I see that your eagle is not ordinary, it looks very imposing, we do not know about it, may I ask what its origins are?"

Fang Yuan took a look, it was the Gu Immortal named Feng Jun.

Fang Yuan thought for a moment, he smiled: "Hehehe, such good perception, you can tell that my beloved eagle is extraordinary. This is an upper extreme heavenly eagle, have you heard of it? If fully grown, it is an immemorial desolate beast. But right now, it can only be used for traveling, it cannot compare to my other ancient desolate beasts."

"Immemorial desolate beast!" At once, the immortals gasped.

Countless heated, shocked, and amazed gazes focused on the upper extreme heavenly eagle, observing it carefully.

Fang Yuan spoke casually, but he threw a bomb into these immortals' minds.

These Gu Immortals had varying emotions, they could not conceal their shock.

Next, when they conversed with Fang Yuan, their tone was unavoidably more polite and restricted.

Fang Yuan did not act with a forceful stance, he smiled like before.

But his smile, when they saw it now, felt completely different from before.

"Upper extreme heavenly eagle, an immemorial desolate beast!"

"Who is this person? He actually has an immemorial desolate beast with him?! It seems that even in the main tribe, he has a high status."

Chapter 1121: Finally Seeing Hei Fan's True Inheritance

"This upper extreme heavenly eagle is an immemorial desolate beast, no wonder it gives off such an abnormal feeling."

"If we are going to attack him, we will need to deal with the eagle first."

"Did you forget what he said? Other than this eagle, he also has other ancient desolate beasts, is he an enslavement path Gu Immortal?"

"If he is an enslavement path Gu Immortal, he would be easier to deal with. This path is vulnerable to direct attacks, even if he is an immortal, we are also Gu Immortals..."

"That might not work! Don't be hasty, we will see on Immortal Succession Mountain."

Even up until the immortals arrived at Immortal Succession Mountain, some Gu Immortals were still talking about the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

This was not strange.

An immemorial desolate beast which had rank eight battle strength upon maturity, this news was a shock to the immortals.

Fang Yuan listened to their words but he still showed a calm and composed expression, there were no flaws in his acting.

Unwittingly, the immortals' guesses of him had already distorted from reality.

Fang Yuan was happy to see this, the more wrong things they assumed, the greater his advantage.

If he was really treated as an enslavement path Gu Immortal, hehe, then they would get to see the power of a transformation path and strength path Gu Immortal!

Conversely, during the conversation, Fang Yuan continued to probe and obtained a lot of precious intelligence.

"These Gu Immortals seemed to have been isolated from the world for too long, they are not good at confrontations or dealing with people. Not just in terms of words, they are not as crafty as Gu Immortals outside, I could easily probe their background. They have barely any shrewdness, and their methods are outdated."

"All in all, these Gu Immortals are split into two groups. One is led by Old Immortal Chen Chi, the four Gu Immortals are related by bloodline. The other group are the three blood sworn immortals, they are Zhou Min, Zheng Tuo, and Feng Jun, they actually have a blood path leader. The final two are loners, as expected, they do not work with the groups."

Fang Yuan snickered internally.

Places with people will have competition for benefits.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven was no exception.

But evidently, the conflict here was small and low level, the Gu Immortals were not skilled at competing against one another. It truly paled in comparison to Northern Plains.

And most importantly, these Gu Immortals had very little knowledge.

Fang Yuan had already probed, these Gu Immortals could not get into treasure yellow heaven, or rather, they did not even know about its existence.

But...

Look at their identities, they were descendants of criminals, it made sense that Old Ancestor Hei Fan prevented them from connecting to treasure yellow heaven.

If they could connect to treasure yellow heaven, it would be different.

Not only would they have updated methods, they would be able to trade and gain knowledge, even without trading, they would grow in experience, it would be an immense growth.

Immortal Succession Mountain was a tall, lone mountain, it was not a famous mountain or river.

It had ten levels, getting smaller towards the top, there was evident signs of man-made design in it. Around the mountain were forests that had lots of resources in them, Fang Yuan was quite amazed.

Even though Hei Fan grotto-heaven was isolated from the world, it had no calamities and tribulations, and because it could not connect to treasure yellow heaven, the resources inside were truly too rich from generations of accumulation!

The immortals followed the brass bell heavenly spirit, landing in the single stone pavilion near the mountain peak.

The stone pavilion was very simple in structure, but even though it was just a pavilion, it had a grand atmosphere. The pavilion was supported by eight thick pillars. There was a stone tablet in the pavilion that was eye-catching. The stone tablet was huge like an elephant, it took up almost all of the space in the pavilion, there were words carved on it.

The brass bell heavenly spirit entered the stone pavilion, hanging on a pillar of the stone pavilion, there was a hook there, it stopped moving after getting into position.

Old Immortal Chen Chi said: "Superior immortal, you have just arrived, you must have many questions. Look at this stone tablet, it will answer a lot of your questions."

Fang Yuan was prepared, he looked at it patiently.

A while later, he finally understood everything.

It turned out that back then, Hei Fan's most beloved granddaughter, Hei Feng Yue, had vanished, along with attitude Gu.

Hei Fan lost his precious granddaughter, but there was nothing he could do, his lifespan was almost expended, he could only place his immortal aperture down and absorb the immemorial azure heaven fragment, losing his freedom.

The few Hei tribe Gu Immortals who could not take care of her were locked in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, not only was their freedom taken away, their immortal apertures were even taken out and fused into Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

This way, Hei Fan grotto-heaven became even bigger.

Before Hei Fan absorbed the fragment of immemorial azure heaven, he had already made his arrangements, leaving behind his true inheritance and the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

But he could not stop thinking about his granddaughter, he wanted his descendants to look for her, thus, he added an additional step, that was the aura of attitude Gu which was needed.

From his perspective: Even if he did not show up, with Hei tribe's power at that time, they could definitely find Hei Feng Yue's location and get back attitude Gu.

But in truth, he was too optimistic.

Or rather, because of kinship, he refused to accept the truth, he felt that Hei Feng Yue was still very likely alive.

Because of his miscalculation, Hei Fan's true inheritance went uninherited for all this time, until now, after Fang Yuan disguised himself and opened the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

This had to be considered an error by Old Ancestor Hei Fan.

But he was a rank eight great expert after all, before his death, he sensed this error as well.

He thought: If nobody from the main tribe inherits his true inheritance, what would happen?

If that happened, either Hei tribe would be wiped out or become weakened, without any worthy descendants.

What Hei Fan thought of was: in that case, he might as well prepare another batch, and let the people in the grotto-heaven inherit his true inheritance, passing it down in that way. They had Hei tribe's bloodline after all!

Thus, after setting up the heavenly crystal eagle nest, before his death, Hei Fan added a new rule to his true inheritance.

He set a timing.

Several hundred years later, if nobody from the main tribe obtains his true inheritance, then the descendants in the grotto-heaven would be allowed to roam Immortal Succession Mountain and find their own opportunities.

This was stated in the tablet: "Old Ancestor (Hei Fan) left behind his key true inheritance on Immortal Succession Mountain, he set up a lot of smaller inheritances as well before his lifespan ran out. The other Hei tribe criminal immortals cried and grieved, they felt that they let him down, they died together with him. But before dying, they imitated Hei Fan and left behind their stone tablet inheritances on Immortal Succession Mountain, their true inheritances were hidden inside."

The Hei tribe members who were in Northern Plains were searching for attitude Gu, but there was nothing they could find.

Time passed, the time limit that Old Ancestor Hei Fan set had long since elapsed. Thus, in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Immortal Succession Mountain was opened up to the mortals to explore.

As a result, Gu Immortals started appearing in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

However, even though these mortals could compete for Hei Fan's true inheritance, it was too difficult to explore Immortal Succession Mountain. Although many mortals obtained the true inheritances, and a portion of them became Gu Immortals, there had never been anyone who got to the mountain peak and obtained the first true inheritance.

According to the stone tablet: if the person who obtains the first true inheritance becomes a Gu Immortal, they would be the owner of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, they would have the authority to forgive the sins of these criminal immortals, they would regain freedom and return to Hei tribe.

But before this, no matter how many generations had gone by, they could not have the Hei surname, they could only have other names, it would remind them of their identities as criminals.

After reading the contents of the stone tablet, Fang Yuan finally understood, the confusion inside him was lifted.

"No wonder these Gu Immortals have such complex expressions and emotions towards me, they have both kind and ill intentions at the same time."

Fang Yuan thought about it from their perspective, if it were him, he would be having even more complex feelings.

According to Hei Fan's rules, the time limit was over, so be it the Hei tribe main immortals or these criminal immortals, they were qualified to vie for Hei Fan's true inheritance.

These immortals had been enthusiastically raising descendants to obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance, to open up the grotto-heaven and regain freedom.

As for these Gu Immortals, they had already obtained other inheritances, they were not qualified to compete for Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Thus, the Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven did not have much conflict normally, they lived quite peacefully.

Originally, they did not think that anyone from the main tribe would come, after all, it had been so long, but nobody came. With Fang Yuan's sudden appearance, their preconceptions were broken. And because of the rules on the stone tablet, they had to go welcome him, even though they were against his arrival and mentally not prepared.

From their perspective, Hei Fan's true inheritance belonged to them already.

As long as they continued to nurture descendants, one day, someone would ascend the mountain peak and obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Thus, they did not want to see Fang Yuan's arrival, but they had no choice but to follow the rules.

The heavenly spirit might be mindless, but Hei Fan had considered this before dying, even though it was rather unreliable, it still firmly carried on Hei Fan's will after his death.

And Hei Fan still had one method of restriction.

Becoming a Gu Immortal would have calamities and tribulations.

Whenever they are unable to pass the tribulations, these Gu Immortals would come to Immortal Succession Mountain and ask the heavenly spirit for help.

The heavenly spirit would use the Immortal Gu in the first tablet's true inheritance to stall their calamities and tribulations. Even though they could be safe for the moment, they would be under the heavenly spirit's control.

The heavenly spirit only had to use a certain method in the true inheritance to remove the method of stalling calamities and tribulations, causing them to die.

Many Gu Immortals were able to pass the calamities and tribulations early on, but they did not know about treasure yellow heaven, even though Hei Fan grotto-heaven had a lot of resources, there was a limit to its variety, these Gu Immortals' cultivation needs could not be fulfilled.

Thus, after many calamities and tribulations, when they got stronger, these Gu Immortals were gradually unable to pass them.

Eventually, they had no choice but to seek help from the heavenly spirit, they all fell into Hei Fan's trap and became controlled by the heavenly spirit. Even though Hei Fan had died for many years, he still had great control over Hei Fan grotto-heaven as a result.

"Old Ancestor Hei Fan, as expected and worthy of the champion that led Hei tribe to its most glorious era! Even after he died, he still had complete control of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, these Gu Immortals all revere him."

"But what this tablet states might not be too factual. Heh. I don't believe that those criminal immortals were willing to die together with Old Ancestor Hei Fan! Evidently, regardless of their wishes, Hei Fan still acted in this ruthless and cruel manner, he is truly praiseworthy. If they were allowed to live, Hei Fan grotto-heaven might have been broken through from the inside already."

Thoughts flashed past his mind rapidly, Fang Yuan's gaze retracted from the stone tablet, he slowly raised his head to look at the brass bell heavenly spirit.

He asked: "Then, what should I do to obtain this true inheritance?"

Once he said that, the other Gu Immortals held their breaths and concentrated, looking over with concerned gazes.

Chapter 1122: Troublesome Final Test

The stone tablet in the pavilion stated: Be it a main tribe member brought over by the heavenly spirit or a criminal immortal who ascended the mountain, they had one final, most important test before inheriting Hei Fan's true inheritance.

But the contents of this final test were not written on the stone tablet, they had to ask the heavenly spirit.

The heavenly spirit was mindless, but remembered Hei Fan's instructions.

Thus, Fang Yuan asked it.

Soon, the immortals heard the brass bell heavenly spirit shake, creating a long and loud sound.

When the sound vibrated off the pillars, there were changes to the tablet. At the end of the original content, new lines were appearing.

The immortals gasped upon seeing it.

"This says that Hei Fan grotto-heaven is the true inheritance itself. Whoever obtains the true inheritance becomes Hei Fan grotto-heaven's owner!"

"But to obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance, there is one final test, it is actually this?"

"No wonder Old Ancestor Hei Fan set a rule that if the inheritor appears, all of us need to go and welcome him!"

"Old ancestor is magnanimous, he planned meticulously. Even though we are criminals, he had never forgotten us, he is still concerned about us descendants."

The immortals discussed, they felt admiration towards Old Ancestor Hei Fan, some had red eyes as they almost cried.

Fang Yuan looked at the new information, he was frowning, his expression had turned heavy.

The contents clearly told him what the test was.

"As long as I pass the final test, I can obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance. But what is this? It wants me to obtain the votes of half of the Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven?! And I must complete it within three years in the grotto-heaven's time."

Fang Yuan shook his head.

Old Ancestor Hei Fan's final test was out of his expectations.

Evidently, he was siding with the Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

As an outsider, it was very difficult for Fang Yuan to obtain their support.

But Fang Yuan soon reacted, he understood Hei Fan's intentions.

Old Ancestor Hei Fan set the rules to encourage his inheritor to take in these Gu Immortals within Hei Fan grotto-heaven. After all, Gu Immortals were hard to nurture, by taking them in, it would benefit Hei tribe greatly.

Thus, this not only tested the inheritor's abilities, their interpersonal skills were also tested, whether they could be a skilled leader to unite others or not.

Hei Fan was using his true inheritance to choose a leader for Hei tribe, he was not just looking for a Gu Immortal expert.

"Old fellow, you are already dead, why are you considering so many things, it is so troublesome!" Fang Yuan thought, but on the surface, he sighed as he spoke in heartfelt fashion: "Ancestor Hei Fan was thinking for Hei tribe the entire time, he put in so much effort, as a descendant, I am deeply moved!"

"Yes, yes!" The immortals heard his words and responded.

Originally, these Gu Immortals were feeling very worried, after all, if Fang Yuan obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, they did not know what would happen to criminal immortals like themselves.

But now, with Old Ancestor Hei Fan's arrangement, their welfare was assured.

Fang Yuan kept his moved expression as he turned around, standing before the stone tablet, facing the immortals in the pavilion, he asked: "Then... how can I obtain all of your support?"

As Fang Yuan had expected, what he obtained was silence.

Times were different now.

Initially, they were wary of him, but now, Fang Yuan needed to get half of the Gu Immortals' recognition, in that case, the situation was reversed, it was completely different.

The immortals looked at each other, nobody spoke.

Only their gaze towards Fang Yuan changed.

Earlier, they were cautious and tried to express kindness while concealing their ill intent, but now, they had distant gazes, they got on their high horses and thought about it internally.

Fang Yuan was not rushed, he stood on the spot, waiting for their reply.

After a while of silence, the most experienced and oldest Gu Immortal, Chen Chi, could not hold it in anymore, he coughed: "Today's matters progressed too quickly, we are simply unprepared for it. Sigh, maybe I am getting old, all this thinking is making my head hurt, I cannot process it yet. Superior immortal, you must have had a long journey to reach here and are tired, right? Why don't you go take a rest first and relax, we can think about this later."

"This old fox." Fang Yuan snickered internally.

Old Immortal Chen Chi's words were well received by the Gu Immortals present, they answered him with great enthusiasm.

They were fragmented earlier, but now, it looked like they were united, dealing with the outsider Fang Yuan together.

"However, so what if I agree to your stalling?" Fang Yuan had expected them to respond in that manner, his expression did not change, he nodded and said reluctantly: "Immortal Chen Chi, you have a point."

Chen Chi showed a smile of victory, but soon he concealed it: "My accommodations are crude, but we have some tea for you. If you do not mind, it would be my great honor to accommodate you."

Chen Chi invited warmly, but he did not give a clear reply to Fang Yuan's words.

Fang Yuan smiled in a reluctant manner, nodding: "I will trouble you in that case."

He called it 'crude', but Old Immortal Chen Chi was naturally just being humble.

His accommodations were not crude at all, instead, they were very elegant and grand.

A number of palaces sat on top of a mountain peak.

This mountain seemed to be man-made, the top was flat, palaces were erected all over it, there were golden bricks and green tiles, with many beautifully crafted pillars.

Chen Chi and his Gu Immortal subordinates lived here.

Not just them, a large number of Gu Masters and mortals as well.

"These are all my descendants, hehehe, please excuse them, superior immortal. At my age, I enjoy having descendants and nurturing them." Chen Chi explained.

Fang Yuan nodded: "This shows that you are someone who values relationships."

Chen Chi looked at Fang Yuan with deep meaning: "Who would not like people who values relationships and loyalty? Hehehe."

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed too.

Seeing Chen Chi and Fang Yuan talking so harmoniously, the other three Gu Immortals had relaxed emotions.

Just like this, Fang Yuan stayed here for the time being.

Strangely, since the first day, Chen Chi had not shown himself again, and did not meet with Fang Yuan again. Fang Yuan was not anxious, he waited patiently.

Four days later.

In the palaces.

Fang Yuan and Chen Le strolled in the long walkways.

Chen Le was one of the female immortals, she had long hair in two buns and a bubbly nature. In terms of bloodline, she was Old Immortal Chen Chi's great granddaughter.

"Young master Hei Cheng, look at that lotus, I love its color!" Chen Le pointed at the lotus pond and smiled.

This walkway was quite special, it crossed over the entire lotus pond.

There were lotuses inside the lotus pond of all colors, they were floating aimlessly, it was a beautiful sight.

These last days, even though Old Immortal Chen Chi did not meet with Fang Yuan, Chen Le was keeping him company, to look at all the scenic sites in the palaces.

"This yellow lotus is cute, pure and innocent, it really suits you, Le Er." Fang Yuan smiled.

Chen Le lowered her head, she was embarrassed, she said faintly: "Young master, what are you saying? Le Er... Le Er was just happy from seeing these flowers."

"I feel very happy seeing you as well, Le Er." Fang Yuan smiled as he extended his arms, holding Le Er's hands.

Chen Le's body shook, she subconsciously wanted to get free, but Fang Yuan's hands were holding her tightly.

Chen Le's face was bright red, even with her Gu Immortal cultivation level, her brain was in chaos, she struggled as she murmured: "Young master, young master, you..."

Fang Yuan took a step forward, his body almost completely touching Chen Le.

Chen Le quickly moved back, because her body was unstable, she fell backwards.

Fang Yuan held her in his arms as she fell.

"Be careful, don't fall." His gentle voice entered Chen Le's ears, when Chen Le reacted, she was already lying in Fang Yuan's arms.

Chen Le raised her head, she saw Fang Yuan, who was smiling with a hint of cheekiness in his gaze.

Chen Le was extremely embarrassed, she punched Fang Yuan's chest softly: "Young master, you are too naughty, you bullied me!"

Saying this, she struggled out of Fang Yuan's embrace.

Fang Yuan gasped, he took a step back, showing intense pain on his face.

Chen Le quickly moved forward, asking him with deep concern: "Young master, how are you?"

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply: "To speak the truth. not long ago, I engaged in a fierce battle. It is not easy to inherit Hei Fan true inheritance. Many Gu Immortals in the tribe are not willing to see it happen."

"So you are injured? Why didn't you tell me!" Chen Le stomped her feet, her embarrassment was gone, she looked at Fang Yuan's chest as she asked: "Does it still hurt?"

"It is a small injury, it is no issue. But with higher cultivation level, my dao marks are deeper, the injuries I suffered are more severe." Fang Yuan smiled, before shifting the topic: "However, your great grandfather refined Gu and suffered injuries, he is in a similar state as me, right? Otherwise, why would he not meet me for the last few days?"

Panic flashed across Chen Le's eyes, she stammered and tried to respond to Fang Yuan.

Old Immortal Chen Chi could not refuse to meet Fang Yuan without any reason, thus, the excuse he gave was that he had suffered a backlash from Gu refinement failure, his injuries were severe and he could not meet guests.

Of course, at this timing, how could he suddenly get injured from refining Gu?

Both parties knew the reason, they did not speak it.

On that night, the four Gu Immortals including Chen Chi engaged in a secret discussion.

Chen Le reported: "Ancestor, young master Hei Cheng asked me about your injury today."

"Oh? He finally lost his patience huh..." Chen Chi smiled.

"Thankfully, I managed to conceal it, he was not suspicious. But as time passes, I am afraid..." Chen Le was worried.

The other three Gu Immortals looked at each other, smiling.

Chen Le was well protected by her family, she was unhardened and innocent, she did not know that Fang Yuan knew about it clearly. The fact that he asked about Chen Chi's injuries was a subtle reminder.

The male Gu Immortal Chen Li Zhi thought for a moment before saying: "It seems that we have to talk to this Hei Cheng properly."

Chapter 1123: What is this Gu's Name?

Old Immortal Chen Chi shook his head, he said with an unmoved expression: "So what if we wait a few more days? There is no rush."

Chen Li Zhi said worriedly: "He understands the situation, if we drag this out, he might get annoyed. If he is forced away and goes to Zheng Tuo's side, it would be troublesome."

"Little Zhi, don't worry." Chen Chi smiled, analyzing: "The final test of the true inheritance requires half of the Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven to support Hei Cheng. Right now in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, disregarding Hei Cheng himself, there are nine Gu Immortals. We have four people on our side, we are nearly half of the total. This is a huge quantity, as long as he gets our support, he would already be one step from winning. As long as he gets one more person's vote, he would succeed. There is no way he did not consider this."

"Even if he gives up on our side and go to the other Gu Immortals, he would face trouble. The situation is different now, he is an outsider, if he wants our support, he has to give up some benefits, he needs to put up something for our gain. Moreover, those three, Zheng Tuo and the others, are more ambitious."

Chen Li Zhi did not speak, instead, Chen Wan Yun said: "Old ancestor, actually, I have an idea. If Hei Cheng cannot get half of the Gu Immortals' votes, wouldn't he fail? As long as Hei Fan true inheritance remains on Immortal Succession Mountain, one day, our descendants would ascend to the top and obtain it, right? We have been guarding Hei Fan's true inheritance for countless generations, even Old Ancestor Hei Fan gave us the rights to vie for it, are we really going to give it to an outsider?"

"Hei Cheng is not an outsider, he is from the main tribe." Chen Le rebuked.

"Le Er, don't forget, the main tribe is enjoying freedom and glory in the outside world. As for us, we have been trapped here for generations, suffering in torment!" Chen Wan Yun said grimly.

Chen Le had a bitter expression, she stopped talking.

Chen Chi shook his head: "Yun Er, I had considered your words long ago, this would not work."

"Firstly, it is extremely difficult for mortals to ascend Immortal Succession Mountain, even if we nurture them and a lucky person shows up, when would they finally inherit the true inheritance? Decades? Centuries? Nobody knows."

"Secondly, even though Hei Cheng is alone, don't forget about the Hei tribesmen behind him, there are a huge number of Hei tribe Gu Immortals. If he fails, that is only his personal failure. Hei tribe's Gu Immortals are going to continue coming here. By then, can we stop them all? Are we going to stop all of the main tribe's Gu Immortal? Can we? Other than the four of us, can Zheng Tuo and the rest be trusted?"

These Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven did not know about treasure yellow heaven, after so many years and generations, they could not connect to treasure yellow heaven. Thus, they had no idea what happened to Hei tribe. Fang Yuan lied and concealed the truth, he easily deceived these Gu Immortals, running around them in circles.

Chen Chi's words made the rest of the immortals' expressions change.

Chen Le added: "That's right, today, young master Hei Cheng told me that it was a tough process to defeat those Hei tribe Gu Immortals and obtain victory. Even until now, he is still injured."

Chen Chi nodded, continuing to analyze: "Hei Cheng was able to emerge victorious, he is not ordinary at all. He has rank seven cultivation level, and the upper extreme heavenly eagle with him, he has great prospects. If we help him now, it would be giving him timely assistance, when we return to the main tribe, we will have a firm foundation under him, wouldn't that be great?"

"However, we are not going to help him without any rewards. He has to pay a price, if he does not give up some benefits, he would not cherish our help. He would not feel gratitude towards us."

"Old ancestor is right." Chen Li Zhi said.

"We will not go wrong listening to ancestor!" Chen Le smiled.

Chen Chi sighed eerily, he looked at the three Gu Immortals, saying with deep emotions: "I am old, my lifespan is almost up. I only want you descendants to live better in the future. When I go into the door of life and death, I will rest in peace."

"Ancestor, don't say things like that, you will definitely live a long time." Chen Le's eyes turned red.

Chen Li Zhi said firmly: "Ancestor, don't forget about lifespan Gu! To obtain our support, that Hei Cheng has to give us something, lifespan Gu is definitely one of our conditions."

Chen Chi's eyes flashed deeply, he looked at Chen Le: "Forget about lifespan Gu, at the very least, we need to make sure Le Er fulfills her wish, and gets together with her lover."

Chen Le's face was flushed red with embarrassment, she stood up as she stomped her feet: "Ancestor, you are making fun of me again!"

Hahaha...

In the secret room, laughter was echoing.

At the same time, Fang Yuan stood on the garden of his accommodation, raising his head towards the night sky.

This Hei Fan grotto-heaven had a clear day and night, daytime was long, while night time was short.

This was something that only happened in grotto-heavens, blessed lands usually did not have day and night.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven's night sky had no stars, but the darkness was not pitch-black, if one looked closely, it had azure color.

A cool wind blew, Fang Yuan's arms were behind his back, he looked at the sky as he sorted out the information that he had obtained recently.

These last days, he had been interacting with Chen Le, obtaining a lot of precious information from this gullible girl, he had clear and extensive knowledge regarding Hei Fan grotto-heaven and the Gu Immortals inside it.

Moreover, he had developed his ideas regarding Hei Fan true inheritance further.

"It is almost time, in just two days, the time will be ripe." Fang Yuan thought, cold light flashed across his eyes, shining deeply.

Two days went by in an instant.

It was noon, bright sunlight radiated in the palace, making it extremely lively.

Winds blew, birds chirped, it was a beautiful sight.

From outside Chen Chi's room, Fang Yuan's voice could be heard: "I came here without informing you, I hope you can forgive me."

"He finally lost his patience. But he already waited for quite some time." Chen Chi was not surprised.

The entire group of palaces was a huge mortal Gu House, Fang Yuan's actions were all under his observation.

The door opened on its own.

Chen Chi sat on his bed, half lying down, he said weakly: "Esteemed guest, you are here, but I am unable to get up and attend to you."

Fang Yuan quickly walked in, standing in front of the bed, saying worriedly: "It seems that you are heavily injured. You are a rule path Gu Immortal, after considering deeply, I thought of a way to lighten your injuries."

Chen Chi had no injuries: "Superior immortal, I am grateful for your concern, but my injury is not something that can be healed easily."

Fang Yuan smiled: "Friend, you might not know, my immortal killer move is a signature method of our tribe. Even though the core Immortal Gu is still in the tribe, I know the content of the killer move. I will pass this immortal killer move to you, you can change the core and it might help with your injuries."

"How can I accept this great gift?" Chen Chi quickly rejected.

Fang Yuan said warmly: "I feel like we are close friends, these last few days, I have been imposing on all of you. The killer move will be my gift in return."

"Superior immortal, this gift is simply too valuable." Chen Chi continued to reject it.

Fang Yuan's expression changed, his tone became very worried: "How can an immortal killer move express my true sincerity? Oh! Honestly speaking, this Hei Fan true inheritance's final test is troubling me greatly. I hope you can give me some advice."

Chen Chi heard this and his eyes shined, he understood Fang Yuan's words. He was here to exchange benefits for support.

Chen Chi subconsciously sat up, saying: "In my humble opinion, this matter is like refining Gu. When refining Gu, the fire is very important. It has to be large at times, and small at other times, we have to deal with important matters more patiently. Hehe, I am ashamed! I have a lot of interest in Gu refinement, so I spouted nonsense, please ignore me."

This was not nonsense, it was simply bullshit!

As a rule path Gu Immortal, why are you so interested in refinement path?

But Fang Yuan knew what he was trying to say, he smiled: "The main tribe has countless books on refinement path, as long as I obtain the true inheritance, I will be able to grant everyone freedom. When you return to the main tribe, these books will all be accessible to you. And I have collected a number of refinement path methods and Gu recipes as well. When I succeed, I can give them all to you, why not?"

Chen Chi nodded, showing a pleased expression.

But he quickly said: "I love refinement path, it is truly a time wasting hobby. But my nephew Chen Li Zhi is an enslavement path Gu Immortal, he is so envious of your upper extreme heavenly eagle."

Fang Yuan's expression sank: "There is only one upper extreme heavenly eagle, it cannot be given away. But there are a lot of iron crown eagles in the main tribe, they are famous in Northern Plains. I can assure that everyone will get one once we return."

Chen Chi's joy flashed on his face, he sighed: "In the past, Old Ancestor Hei Fan suppressed Qiao tribe, it was to obtain their secret of raising eagles. To think that after so many years, they had already developed to this extent. But our ancestors were criminals, when we return to the main tribe, what circumstances will we face, I am truly worried!"

"No need to worry, I can assure that everyone will be very welcomed back in Hei tribe, after all, your return means that the tribe becomes stronger as well." Fang Yuan paused before saying: "As for the crime, it occurred so many generations ago, once I get the true inheritance, I will spare everyone. You have all defended Hei Fan grotto-heaven for so many years, your merits outweigh your crimes, and because you also helped me obtain the true inheritance... Hehe, when I return to the main tribe, I will uphold justice for everyone!"

Chen Chi smiled: "Superior immortal, you are a dragon among men, an absolute genius, your words are truly reliable, after hearing this, I am somewhat assured."

"I thank you for your trust. We all have Hei tribe's bloodline, we are one family. However... as for the other immortals outside, it will depend on their performance." Fang Yuan vaguely suggested.

His meaning was: first come first serve, whoever supports him first will gain greater benefits when they return to the main tribe.

Chen Chi nodded, he was a sly fox, he naturally understood what Fang Yuan meant.

He smiled: "Superior immortal, your words are truly enlightening, they are amazing. Especially the word family, it is so apt."

Saying so, he looked at Fang Yuan, seeing his slight smile, he felt deeper confidence, he asked: "What do you think of Little Le?"

Fang Yuan's smile faded, he answered: "Intelligent and eloquent, innocent and lively, she is very attractive."

"I will not lie to you, Le Er is secretly in love with you. Sigh, it is a pity! Superior immortal, you are such a talented person, how could she match you. Sigh, as her ancestor, I am unable to fulfill her wish. I only hope that Le Er, this poor child, is able to forget about superior immortal and find her own happiness in the future." Chen Le sighed.

Fang Yuan no longer smiled, he frowned as he considered, before saying solemnly: "I will not lie to you either, I am in love with Chen Le, I am willing to marry her as my wife!"

If he really loved her, he should be yelling happily in excitement, he would not show a solemn expression after considering it.

But Chen Chi ignored it completely, as if he could not understand it.

Fang Yuan snickered internally, he could understand why. This Chen Chi kept saying he was thinking for his descendant's future, but was that true? He was sacrificing Chen Le to gain his own benefits!

Chen Chi laughed loudly, Fang Yuan's reply was very satisfactory to him, even though he said it reluctantly.

He went overboard, his smile vanished, he sighed deeply: "Sigh, it is a pity that my lifespan is running out, I will not be able to attend you and Le Er's wedding."

Fang Yuan instantly understood, this old fellow was asking for lifespan Gu! His expression turned grim, he stopped smiling, he said dryly: "That's not the case at all, in my opinion, you are truly hale and hearty, your appetite is truly great."

Old Immortal Chen Chi chuckled as he looked at Fang Yuan directly, he showed a determined expression that was not backing off: "I am truly ashamed, actually, I am a very greedy person, not only do I want to attend the wedding of superior immortal and Le Er, I also want to see the children that you have after getting married. After all, those are my descendants as well."

Fang Yuan began to prance around, his eyebrows were tightly pursed, he said directly: "Lifespan Gu are hard to find, they are very precious, I am unable to give them away."

"This treasure from heaven is truly hard to obtain." Old Immortal Chen Chi nodded, as if he had expected Fang Yuan's reply already, he continued: "But there is no need to worry. I'll let you know, this Hei Fan grotto-heaven also produces lifespan Gu, they are all gathered and collected. The heavenly spirit might be mindless, but Old Ancestor Hei Fan had his arrangements. If I am not wrong, there are definitely lifespan Gu within Hei Fan's true inheritance. I... sigh, I only need three hundred years worth of lifespan Gu."

"Three hundred years?!" Fang Yuan stared at Chen Chi angrily.

Chen Chi was still smiling comfortably.

Fang Yuan turned furious: "Three hundred is too much, I don't even have a single one! I will only give a hundred."

"One hundred and fifty." Chen Chi bargained, he finally put down his act.

Fang Yuan walked for a few more rounds, gritting his teeth: "Forget it, I will give you a hundred and fifty!"

"Deal!" Chen Chi clapped, smiling widely and happily, he stopped caring about his face.

After all, this was more than a hundred years of lifespan, how could a bit of face compare to it?

Chen Chi looked at Fang Yuan, smiling even more deeply now: "Superior immortal, I heard from Le Er that you have a lot of Immortal Gu, I wonder if you can let me have a look to broaden my horizons?"

Fang Yuan was stunned before flying into a rage, he gritted his teeth at Chen Chi.

This old fellow was too greedy, he said he wanted to take a look, but the truth was, he wanted Fang Yuan to use an Immortal Gu to exchange for his support!

Chen Chi saw Fang Yuan turning furious and his heart jumped, but soon, he thought that this was a rare chance, there would be no opportunities like this again. After they returned to the main tribe, would this occur again?

Thus, he quickly said: "Superior immortal, this is my final request, as long as I get it, the four of us will definitely support you."

Fang Yuan began prancing again.

He took heavy steps, as if the concrete floor had an unresolvable deep enmity with him.

Chen Chi observed his expression, seeing that Fang Yuan's anger was fading and he was actually thinking about it, he let down his guard.

He felt great joy inside him: "Success!"

As expected, after a moment, Fang Yuan stopped his movements, he stood in front of the bed with an Immortal Gu in his hand.

"Rank seven Immortal Gu!" Chen Chi shouted, feeling surprised and joyful.

"This is a sword path Immortal Gu, it is not compatible with me, otherwise, you would never see this!" Fang Yuan said angrily.

"What is this Gu's name?" Chen Chi's eyes were shining, he watched as Fang Yuan handed the Gu over to him.

"Wait, I'll exchange with this one instead." Fang Yuan suddenly changed his mind, he retracted his arm as he took out another Gu from his immortal aperture.

Chen Chi's gaze subconsciously moved to Fang Yuan's other arm.

No sooner said than done!

The sword path Immortal Gu activated!

Sword path killer move — Dark Assassination!!

Chen Chi was staring blankly, the bloody mark left on his forehead enlarged as blood started to spew out from the front and back of his head.

He was dead!

Chapter 1124: Dark Assassination

With Chen Chi's death, all the palaces started shaking.

The group of palaces were all mortal Gu Houses, they were under Old Immortal Chen Chi's control.

But Fang Yuan came prepared, at his will, he activated arrangements that were prepared long ago.

At once, the tremors of the palaces settled down and did not continue.

This was one of Fang Yuan's preparations these last days.

Mortal Gu Houses were nothing special to Gu Immortals. Unless it was regarding an Immortal Gu House, but how could these Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven have that?

Hei Fan was ruthless, before he died, he killed all of the criminal Hei tribe Gu Immortals. The inheritances left behind were naturally lacking some crucial information, there was no way they contained information about Immortal Gu Houses.

And with just these Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, there was little hope of them creating an Immortal Gu House.

Furthermore, even though the palaces were huge and grand, the methods used were too old. Fang Yuan could easily unravel them. Old Immortal Chen Chi letting him stay here for such a long time was a huge mistake!

"These Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven have lived in peace for too long, without great struggle and competition to spur on progress, they have basically no alertness." Fang Yuan looked at Old Immortal Chen Chi's corpse, snickering in disdain.

Chen Chi died with his eyes wide open, he was still in shock, Fang Yuan had attacked too quickly, he could not even react to show fear.

Fang Yuan confirmed that Chen Chi was dead, before keeping him inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Next, he used familiar face, turning into Old Immortal Chen Chi's appearance and leaving the room, walking out openly.

"Greetings to old ancestor!"

"Greetings to old ancestor!"

Along the way, Fang Yuan met many Gu Masters and mortals of all genders and age. After seeing Fang Yuan, they knelt down, expressing their most respectful greetings.

Every time, Fang Yuan activated his Gu worms, using a formless force to help them stand up, he asked them some questions in encouragement, these descendants of Chen Chi were extremely grateful to him.

They did not know that the real Chen Chi had already been killed by Fang Yuan, they were greeting the culprit.

They did not suspect a thing, because this was how Old Immortal Chen Chi usually acted.

Fang Yuan had been toying with Chen Le these last days, he obtained a lot of intel, among which were Chen Chi's habits.

Otherwise, with just familiar face, he could only disguise his appearance, he could not alter his actions to fit those of Old Immortal Chen Chi as well.

Fang Yuan walked openly and confidently. After a while, he arrived at a palace.

"Ancestor, why are you here?" Chen Li Zhi heard a disturbance and walked out of the palace, greeting him.

He looked at Fang Yuan with much puzzlement.

He was not suspecting his identity, of course, instead, he was thinking, ancestor was clearly using the excuse of being bedridden currently to delay the meeting with Hei Cheng. Why did he appear in public so openly today, going against the original plan?

"Little Zhi, that Hei Cheng came to me secretly earlier, we have already finished negotiating. Let's go in, I have a matter to discuss with you." Fang Yuan said slowly, he patted Chen Li Zhi's back, he walked ahead with his arms behind his back.

The entire group of palaces were mortal Gu Houses.

But these three Gu Immortals' accommodations respectively belonged to them.

On this point, Old Immortal Chen Chi could not interfere. He could not control the lives of his descendants to this extent, right?

Chen Li Zhi heard Fang Yuan's words and his thoughts shifted, his suspicions were lifted, he quickly moved forward, leading the way.

"Ancestor, please take a seat." He bowed, directing Fang Yuan to his seat.

"Please have some tea." Soon, he prepared a high quality tea and handed it over with both hands, having a respectful attitude.

After handing over the tea, Chen Li Zhi went down to sit at a lower seat.

After drinking the tea, Fang Yuan saw that Chen Li Zhi was seated far from himself, he said: "Oh, Little Zhi, bring your chair over, sit beside me."

Chen Li Zhi was shocked and pleased, he joyfully answered: "Yes, ancestor. I will stand beside you and listen to your guidance."

How could he stand?

There was a difference between sitting and standing.

When standing, one's muscles were contracted, they could move rapidly.

When seated, the body relaxed, even their mental state would be affected, they would let down their guard.

Fang Yuan wanted to kill Chen Li Zhi, he had to make ample preparations.

Thus, Fang Yuan pretended to be unhappy: "I asked you to move your chair, why are you being so reluctant? I have already talked to Hei Cheng, now, we need to deal with Zheng Tuo's gang. I need to entrust many matters to you, Yun Er and Le Er are both women, at the crucial moment, Little Zhi, you have to handle more responsibilities."

Chen Li Zhi had countless thoughts in his mind, he had a feeling of joy after receiving recognition.

"Yes." He quickly moved his chair, sitting beside Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan saw that the doors were open, he said: "Close the doors, these words are better kept as a secret from outsiders."

Chen Li Zhi had no doubts, he followed the instructions.

"Hei Cheng could not endure it anymore, he came to me. After negotiating with Hei Cheng for a long time, he promised us many benefits, he is very sincere..." Fang Yuan said slowly.

Chen Li Zhi listened attentively.

He wanted to ask what price Hei Cheng paid, but because his ancestor did not mention it, he did not dare to ask.

Right now, Fang Yuan started to satisfy his curiosity, he exaggerated the amount somewhat, causing Chen Li Zhi to listen with joy and excitement.

"Hei Cheng actually offered a rank seven Immortal Gu?" At the end, Chen Li Zhi gasped, he was truly overjoyed.

"Will I lie to you? Take a look." Fang Yuan chuckled, taking out flying sword Immortal Gu.

"Good Gu, this is a good Gu." Chen Li Zhi quickly praised.

"Oh Little Zhi..." Fang Yuan said slowly.

Chen Li Zhi immediately raised his head, his ancestor was talking to him, how could he be distracted?

At this instance, sword light flashed!

Chen Li Zhi was startled, there seemed to be a flash of light just then?

Next, he looked at Fang Yuan's hand subconsciously, the flying sword Immortal Gu there was gone.

Why did the Gu vanish?

Chen Li Zhi was perplexed, but suddenly, he felt his body going weak, there was a warm liquid flowing down his forehead.

Suddenly, his world started spinning.

He fell onto the ground, kneeling. One of his hands was on the floor supporting himself, while he attempted to grab Fang Yuan's robe with the other, but he did not succeed.

Plop.

He fell onto the ground, completely dead.

Fang Yuan's warm smile vanished, his expression turned icy cold.

Doing the same thing as before, Fang Yuan suppressed this palace as well, preventing it from shaking, others could not see any problems.

Next, he gathered Chen Li Zhi's corpse and kept it in his immortal aperture, he opened the palace doors and left.

There were two female Gu Immortals remaining, Chen Wan Yun had greater threat, Fang Yuan's next target was her!

"Sister, I finally succeeded in my new move, concealment within." Chen Le smiled and said to Chen Wan Yun.

"Is that so?" Chen Wan Yun heard this and was overjoyed, she looked at Chen Le with an expression of satisfaction: "It seems that our Le Er is finally working hard. Let me guess, who is the person who motivated you to cultivate this hard?"

Chen Wan Yun pretended to think, she continued: "Hmm... I think this person has the surname Hei, and there is only one other word in his full name..."

Before she finished, Chen Le interrupted: "Sister, stop teasing me! I was very hardworking to begin with, okay!"

"Is that so?" Chen Wan Yun smiled as she saw Chen Le's shy appearance, she thought: "Le Er might be innocent and grew up under our protection, but she knows how impressive Hei Cheng is, thus she is trying to improve herself. I was going to remind her, but it seems that I was worried for nothing."

Chen Le could not deal with this glance, she took a step back, vanishing from Chen Wan Yun's sight.

"Sister, I used concealment within, can you find me? Hehe, do you know where I am?" In an instant, Chen Wan Yun could hear Chen Le's voice near her.

"Cheeky girl, after I find you, I will deal with you!" Chen Wan Yun showed an evil appearance, she was about to use her investigative killer move, when suddenly, she felt some disturbance outside, she was curious: "Why is ancestor here? Le Er, stop playing, go with me to greet him."

Chen Le was about to dispel her immortal killer move, but suddenly, she had an idea, she remembered the time when Old Immortal Chen Chi made fun of her, she pouted: "Forget it, I will listen secretly by the side, let's see if ancestor can find me. If he cannot find me, and I appear suddenly, he would be in shock. Hehehe."

"Oh you, you are too mischievous, you will not be able to get married." Chen Wan Yun shook her head, walking out of the palace to greet Old Immortal Chen Chi.

Fang Yuan had familiar face, Chen Wan Yun and Chen Le could not find out his true identity. But Fang Yuan did not have an outstanding investigative killer move, he could not find Chen Le, who was concealed. In fact, even if he had a killer move like that, he could not use it openly.

Once he used it, his immortal aura would leak, it would invite suspicion.

Only immortal methods like dark assassination could completely conceal the aura of Immortal Gu, without leaking a trace, one could sneak attack and catch an enemy unprepared.

Chen Wan Yun brought Fang Yuan to his seat, she wanted to call Chen Le to come out, how could she peek at them with such disrespect?

But thinking about it: "Old ancestor dotes on Le Er, he gained a lot of benefits just now after negotiating with young master Hei Cheng, he is in a good mood. Even if ancestor discovers Le Er in hiding, he would surely not blame her."

Thinking of that, Chen Wan Yun pretended to be unaware, passing the tea to him.

Fang Yuan drank a mouthful, he did the same thing again, asking Chen Wan Yun to sit closer to him.

Chen Le watched as she held in her laughter, she felt extremely excited.

Next, as she listened to Fang Yuan and Chen Wan Yun's words, she gradually focused and upon hearing their gains, she was very happy, but she started worrying for Fang Yuan: "Young master Hei Cheng paid such a huge price, will this affect him negatively?"

Soon after, Fang Yuan took out flying sword Immortal Gu: "This rank seven sword path Immortal Gu was given to me by Hei Cheng, adding on to his previous offer. Yun Er, I want you to go to the cave where the three immortals live, using this as a chip to convince the three immortals to support Hei Cheng, are you willing to do it?"

Chen Wan Yun quickly got up: "Ancestor, I will follow your instructions."

"Good, good, good." Fang Yuan chuckled.

Chen Le's gaze was focused on flying sword Immortal Gu as well.

This was the first time she was seeing a rank seven Immortal Gu, she could not hold in her curiosity, she wanted to jump out and give a surprise to her ancestor.

But at the next moment, a change occurred!

Dark assassination activated again.

How could Chen Wan Yun anticipate that her beloved ancestor, someone with such closeness to her, would attack?

Without any defense, this gentle female immortal followed in the footsteps of Chen Chi and Chen Li Zhi.

Chen Wan Yun was killed!

Fang Yuan retrieved Flying Sword, he sent the corpse into his immortal aperture, he got rid of the blood stains and left.

Chen Le was still concealed, she was covering her mouth with her hands, her eyes were wide open and staring, but her pupils had shrunk to pin size.

Her nostrils were expanded, she was breathing in deeply.

Her delicate body was shivering, tears were flowing down her beautiful tender cheeks silently.

Unbelievable!

Extreme terror!!

"How can this be? How can this happen!"

"What did I just see? What just happened?!"

"Is this an illusion? Definitely, this is all an illusion!"

"How can this be? Hehehe, hahaha, ancestor killed sister Yun Er?! How can that be!"

But the truth was in front of her very eyes.

Hearsay could be wrong, but seeing was believing!

Cold, cruel, she could not doubt what she saw at all!

Plop.

She knelt on the ground, collapsing weakly.

Her shoulders moved up and down, she was sobbing. On her lively face, there was fear, terror, confusion, and helplessness.

Her hands were still covering her mouth, she was desperately covering it, as if this could protect her.

Chapter 1125: More Killing

Why did her ancestor kill Chen Wan Yun?

Chen Le could not understand, she could not imagine why.

She sobbed, her body shuddered, she suddenly thought of Chen Li Zhi. Did ancestor also go to find and kill him?

This was a simple inference.

No matter what, she had to find Chen Li Zhi and tell him about this!

At the crucial moment, Chen Le did not think of Hei Cheng, she thought of the Gu Immortals who were her most closely related family members.

Chen Le realized what she had to do, she stopped crying, standing up and activating her immortal killer move, concealing her appearance and running towards Chen Li Zhi's palace.

But Fang Yuan did not go to Chen Li Zhi's palace as Chen Le was thinking.

He did not discover Chen Le, and he had already killed Chen Li Zhi, thus, his final course of action was to go to Chen Le.

To find her and kill her!

A moment later, Chen Le arrived at Chen Li Zhi's place.

"Why is there no one here?" Chen Le searched the palace, but did not find Chen Li Zhi.

Of course, she saw many mortals and Gu Masters.

But Chen Le did not alert them, even if she told them this shocking news, they might not believe her.

In the empty hall, fear and helplessness emerged again in Chen Le's heart.

Ancestor Chen Chi had killed Chen Wan Yun, Chen Li Zhi was missing as well, he was likely to have met with disaster.

Chen Le could not help but cry again.

"What should I do? Oh, oh no! Young master Hei Cheng!" Chen Le finally thought of Fang Yuan at this time, she jolted back to focus.

She felt that at this moment, the most reliable person was Hei Cheng.

She turned around, towards Hei Cheng's accommodation.

Almost at the same time, Fang Yuan arrived at Chen Le's palace.

Nobody was here?

"Strange, where would she go at this time?" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

The situation was changing beyond his expectations.

Fang Yuan raised his head and looked up at the sky of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, it was cloudless and azure in color.

Fang Yuan smiled at the sky, before going towards his own accommodation.

Where could Chen Le go?

There were only a few places.

Gu Immortals and mortals did not have many common topics of interest.

Returning to his accommodations, Fang Yuan turned into Hei Cheng, waiting for Chen Le to come.

At this time, a bright light was shot into the sky, it went up and spread out in all directions, it was bright and piercing to the eyes.

"Is this the thing Chen Le mentioned before... that warning of bright light, to ask the immortals to work together in defense?" Fang Yuan frowned instantly.

These days, he had been getting intel from Chen Le.

Among which, one of them was about the time when Gu Immortals first appeared in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, they struggled against desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts.

The first few generations of Gu Immortals joined forces to resist them. Normally, they would be in different parts of the grotto-heaven, but when one side was attacked, they would send out a signal during critical times, inviting Gu Immortals from other areas to help out, and paying them afterwards.

"As the number of Gu Immortals increased in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, they got stronger, and this warning of bright light has not been used for a hundred years. This time, it must have been sent out by Chen Le. Hehe, I underestimated this girl, she dealt with the situation well!" Fang Yuan smiled.

With his craftiness, he already deduced many things.

He had already killed three people, only Chen Le was left. And the warning method could only be used by Gu Immortals, it was clear that Chen Le had activated it.

Why did Chen Le activate this without meeting him?

Evidently, she had found out that one of the others had met with disaster.

No matter where she is hiding or what method she used, since she did not come to find him, that meant she was suspicious of him.

Then, the immortals were going to gather together now, how would Fang Yuan deal with them?

Actually, a moment ago.

Chen Le was about to find Hei Cheng, when she suddenly had a thought, even if she found young master Hei Cheng, what if he could not defeat her ancestor?

Chen Le did not know about Hei Cheng's strength, but in her mind, she felt that Old Immortal Chen Chi had deep and immeasurable power. This was the result of Old Immortal Chen Chi's authority that had been ingrained in her.

"I have to think of a perfect method!" Chen Le thus thought of the warning of bright light.

The alert of bright light soared into the sky, Chen Le's mind slowly calmed down.

"Will ancestor come to find me after seeing this light?" Thinking of this, Chen Le started feeling scared again.

She gritted her teeth, she decided to go find Fang Yuan.

From start to finish, she did not suspect that Fang Yuan was the culprit!

When bright light soared to the sky, Gu Immortals in all the other areas reacted.

"What happened? At this timing, old man Chen Chi actually sent a warning signal and asked us to go help him?" In front of their cave, Feng Jun frowned upon seeing the light in the sky.

Zhou Min also had a look of suspicion: "This matter is quite peculiar. Old Immortal Chen Chi has a total of four immortals, they are the strongest force among us. Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, what kind of ancient desolate beast can make Chen Chi ask us for help?"

"You think this matter has to do with Hei Cheng?" Zheng Tuo pondered.

"Most likely." Feng Jun nodded: "This warning of bright light has not been used for a hundred years, it is strange that it is activated at this time. Hei Cheng has already stayed at old man Chen Chi's place for some days. They might have come to an agreement now, and are working together."

"Old Immortal Chen Chi will definitely provide support if Hei Cheng is willing to give him enough benefits, it is not surprising." Zheng Tuo thought over it: "No matter whether there really is an ancient desolate beast attack, or if Chen Chi is trying to scheme against us, we need to go and investigate the situation."

"That's right, we have practised blood light spirit suppression and are at the crucial moment. In a few days, we will be able to suppress the heavenly spirit and take the true inheritance forcefully. We need to stall for time now, but we need to be careful of what the other side is planning. We will give in to them for now, in a few days, Hei Fan grotto-heaven will belong to us!" Feng Jun snickered.

Immediately the three immortals moved out, towards Old Immortal Chen Chi's palace.

At the same time, the two lone Gu Immortals also went there.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven was not small, but the Gu Immortals lived quite close to each other.

And because the three immortals used immortal killer moves, disregarding the immortal essence to travel.

In a moment, they were already halfway there.

At this time, a flying figure appeared in front of the three immortals.

"Its Chen Le!" Zhou Min was the first to recognize the person.

Chen Le was bathed in blood, she had a shocked expression, she seemed to be escaping for her life, the three immortals looked at each other.

Was there really an ancient desolate beast attack?

"Chen Le, slow down, we are here, what happened over there?" Zheng Tuo called out.

Chen Le saw these three immortals and was overjoyed with surprise: "Seniors! It is great to see you. That Hei Cheng is heinous, after failing to negotiate with our ancestor, he used a sneak attack and killed sister Wan Yun! I was the one who sent the warning, I escaped, but Hei Cheng is still chasing me, thankfully, I had my immortal killer move's concealment, I managed to survive."

"What!" The three immortals heard this and were deeply shocked.

"Hei Cheng is so daring?"

"He dared to attack Old Immortal Chen Chi, he is so vicious and ruthless, he is likely going to attack us as well."

"Strange, he has to get Hei Fan's true inheritance, without our support, how can he get it?"

"A life for a life is perfectly justified. We will have to take down Hei Cheng!"

"To play safe, we need to gather with the other Gu Immortals. Chen Le, don't worry, we are family, we will definitely uphold justice for you!"

"Justice?" Chen Le smiled suddenly, attacking.

Under the three immortals' shocked gazes, sword light flashed and stabbed into Zheng Tuo's body.

Zheng Tuo was caught unawares, even though he had a mortal killer move defending him, dark assassination was an immortal killer move, with rank seven Immortal Gu Flying Sword as the core, it could not be stopped, it cut him into half on the spot!

Instantly, Zheng Tuo died!

"Brother!!" Zhou Min shouted.

Feng Jun was furious, he clapped his hands, intense winds assaulted Fang Yuan.

"Oh brother—!" Zhou Min cried out, watching the two halves of Zheng Tuo's corpse fall to the ground, his organs and blood scattered in the air.

Feng Jun carried Zhou Min, dragging her as they retreated.

"Chen Le, are you crazy! You dared to kill my brother Zheng Tuo, I will fight it out with you!" Zhou Min growled, her beautiful face was flushed red: "I will kill you!"

"Kill me?" Chen Le stopped her movement, she scoffed as she looked at Zhou Min in disdain: "You?"

Zhou Min was furious, she struggled intensely, getting free from Feng Jun's arms: "Brother, what are you doing! Let go of me, this lowly bitch killed our big brother! She killed him! I will pull out her skull and use it as an offering for our brother!!"

"Calm down, sister! Don't fall for his provocations. How can this be Chen Le? Don't you know Chen Le? Earlier, that was a sword path immortal killer move! This is not Chen Le!" Feng Jun shouted, looking at Chen Le, his eyes were bursting with fire, filled with hatred.

"It seems that someone here has some brains." Chen Le smiled, her appearance changed suddenly, becoming that of Hei Cheng.

"You are indeed Hei Cheng!" Feng Jun's body shook.

"Scoundrel!!!" Zhou Min scolded.

"From their expressions, it seems that they were not aware that I was the killer. Strange... Chen Le did not use any information path Gu worms to tell them?" Fang Yuan was confused.

He did not know that from start to finish, Chen Le did not suspect him.

After creating the warning, Chen Le ran off to his accommodations.

Fang Yuan returned to his room long ago, but after seeing the warning of bright light while waiting for Chen Le, he thought he was exposed. Thus, he adapted to the circumstances and went out to weaken the remaining immortals' battle strength in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Since Chen Chi's side had three immortals dead already, the next largest group were the three immortals who were sworn siblings.

Thus, Fang Yuan turned into Chen Le's appearance, flying towards their cave.

In the end, he met the three immortals and used dark assassination to kill the most threatening of them, the blood path Gu Immortal Zheng Tuo.

Meanwhile, Chen Le went to Fang Yuan's room, she could not find him, she felt disappointment and immense worry.

She did not know that out of sheer coincidence, she had narrowly escaped death.

"I did not put any hope in this disguised assassination attempt, but the process was unexpectedly smooth. The Gu Immortals inside this Hei Fan grotto-heaven are truly incomparable to Northern Plains' Gu Immortals. After such a long period of peace, they have low vigilance. Anyway, I should kill these two first."

Thoughts churned in his mind like fireworks, Fang Yuan thought of many things, but only a moment had passed in the outside world.

His lips curled up, he charged towards Feng Jun and Zhou Min.

To kill!

Chapter 1126: Verge of Death

"He actually charged over!" Feng Jun's pupils shrunk, he was stunned by Fang Yuan's courage.

Fang Yuan charged forward relentlessly, even though he was alone, his stance was overwhelming, it was as if he was clad in wind and lightning!

Killing intent surged, it was like a terrifying claw, slashing towards the veil of life and death.

The Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven would often spar with each other, but when would they ever be in a life and death situation against each other?

"Retreat!" At once, Feng Jun only had one word in his mind.

In contrast, Zhou Min was spewing with anger, she said excitedly: "Good! Scoundrel, get ready to die!!"

She was already beyond furious, she wanted to take revenge for her brother, she wanted to tear this scoundrel, Fang Yuan, into pieces, to pull out his tendons and snap his bones!

Feng Jun dragged along Zhou Min as they escaped, but Zhou Min had already activated her immortal killer move.

Her eyes were wide open as they stared, golden white light shot out of her eyes. The light was extremely sharp, as if it was made of blades and daggers.

Zhou Min was a light path Gu Immortal, she was nurtured by a Gu Immortal from a past generation, she had sight light Immortal Gu.

And she was currently activating her strongest move — Farsight Weapon Light!

"It is this move." Fang Yuan saw Zhou Min's actions and came to a realization, his charging speed increased instead!

In his mind, he recalled a scene from a few days ago.

"Young master Hei Cheng, why are you sighing?" Chen Le asked: "Do you not like this scenery?"

"Thanks for your concern, Miss Le Er. The scenery is beautiful, I am truly impressed. But I have the mission of inheriting Hei Fan's true inheritance, I am very worried... As I recall, Zheng Tuo and the others are not easy to talk to..." Fang Yuan acted like he was troubled.

Chen Le frowned too: "Indeed... ancestor had said this before, those three Gu Immortals have their own ambitions, they are different from us."

"Birds of a feather flock together, those three are ambitious people! Even if I obtain your support, I will still be short of obtaining the true inheritance. Do you think these three would find trouble with me on the pretext of sparring? Will they obstruct us?" Fang Yuan asked.

Chen Le smiled: "No need to worry, actually, if you know about them, those three immortals are not scary. For example, Gu Immortal Zhou Min has a killer move called farsight weapon light, it is very powerful. Once she uses it, her eyes will shoot out golden white light, it can cut down anything. But this move is quite peculiar, the farther the distance, the stronger it is. If you are very close to Zhou Min, then this move is drastically weakened. If you are right in front of her, even a mortal killer move can block farsight weapon light."

A warm smile appeared on Fang Yuan's face: "Oh? There is such an interesting move, I am truly enlightened. Le Er, what other interesting stories are there?"

Chen Le looked at Fang Yuan, seeing his handsome face looking right at her, emitting lots of affection, it was so intense as if the summer winds were drowning her in bliss.

Chen Le had a flushed expression, she quickly turned around, not daring to look at Fang Yuan directly.

Her face was completely red, she looked afar as she stammered: "Young, young master, if you want to know, I will tell you."

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, some of these Gu Immortals' inheritances came from Old Ancestor Hei Fan, like the blood path one for example, it was a result of Hei Fan's research. And some came from the criminal immortals, like Zhou Min's light path inheritance, and Old Immortal Chen Chi's rule path inheritance.

These proper Gu Immortal inheritances were all very comprehensive.

The details of large numbers of mortal Gu, a few Immortal Gu, and all sorts of Immortal Gu recipes and mortal Gu recipes, cultivation experiences and information about the outside world.

Some of these contents were sensitive, like treasure yellow heaven, they were all erased by Hei Fan.

However, some information regarding the other inheritances was retained.

The Hei tribe Gu Immortals were quite close together. For example, outsiders might not about about farsight weapon light, but how could they themselves not know?

Thus, this kind of information was all left inside their inheritances. As time passed, mortals went up Immortal Succession Mountain and inherited them. Gu Immortals appeared and passed away, during this process, there were all sorts of reasons, like fighting over benefits or personal conflicts, they fought against each other. The Gu Immortals' methods were passed down over generations, everybody knew about their moves, these were no secrets.

Fang Yuan's preparation was not only regarding the assassination plan, he also collected a lot of other information.

Farsight weapon light!

This was quite a troublesome immortal killer move.

Under normal circumstances, when seeing an unknown attacking method, Gu Immortals would choose to retreat and observe cautiously. Nobody would charge in without knowing the situation and place themselves in trouble.

According to Fang Yuan's vigilant nature, there was a high likelihood of him doing so, unless the difference in their strengths was very big.

And that was exactly what Zhou Min wanted.

By the time Fang Yuan realized the effect of farsight weapon light, he might have already spent a lot of time, effort, immortal essence, or even gotten injured in the process.

When Gu Immortals battle, information often led to having an advantage!

Thus, under normal circumstances in the Gu Immortal world, they would keep their Immortal Gu secret, immortal killer moves were rarely used publicly. They would practise their moves in private. The Gu Immortal's immortal aperture was also rarely shown to others. Because the environment inside revealed the secrets of the Gu Immortal's dao marks. The resources inside were often food for Immortal Gu, all these could be used to deduce what Immortal Gu the Gu Immortal had.

Fang Yuan withstood the farsight weapon light, he charged forward with unparalleled vigor.

Of course, he was not rash.

His robe was previously stained with blood.

These blood stains were not eye-catching, but they were formed from an immortal killer move!

Blood path immortal killer move — Bloodstained Conqueror's Robe!

During the period before the opening of treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan was unable to develop his immortal aperture, because Lang Ya Sect was suppressing him, he had a tough time. But he did not waste his time, he deduced this immortal killer move to make up for his weakness.

Fang Yuan had many weaknesses.

But he considered it deeply, his greatest weakness was in defense.

During the second earthly calamity, this flaw was evident. If he did not have Dang Hun Mountain as a base for defense, Fang Yuan would have likely died.

Compared to investigative and information path methods, Fang Yuan would rather play safe and settle his weakness in defense first.

Due to his wisdom path and blood path grandmaster attainment levels, as well as the immense blood path foundation built during his previous life, Fang Yuan did not have much difficulty in creating bloodstained conqueror's robe.

At this moment, with blood asset Immortal Gu as the core, bloodstained conqueror's robe was showcasing its capability in battle!

The effect was superb!

Fang Yuan charged towards the farsight weapon light, his body did not waver, he had no injuries at all, his immortal essence expenditure was also reducing.

"Like what Chen Le had said, the closer I get, the lower farsight weapon light's power becomes, thus, even bloodstained conqueror's robe's immortal essence expenditure is falling."

Fang Yuan made such a decisive and wise choice, in the blink of an eye, he was already very close to Zhou Min.

They were less than a hundred steps away!

"Die die die!" Zhou Min cried out continuously, the sharp light in her eyes continued to shoot out brightly.

She was overcome with anger, she was not a threat.

Feng Jun, who was calmer, felt huge fear as his hair stood on end!

Fang Yuan's advancement made him feel an immense sense of danger.

The great shock made him use his most familiar defensive method subconsciously.

Immortal killer move — Luck Whirlwind!

Huge winds blew, Fang Yuan was pushed away by a mystical force.

Chen Le's words reverberated in Fang Yuan's mind: "Speaking of which, Gu Immortal Feng Jun is also quite strong. He is the only person who ascended Immortal Succession Mountain and successfully became a Gu Immortal. Such immortals are more formidable than us, who were nurtured by our seniors. Furthermore, Feng Jun cultivates the famous luck path..."

Luck path.

A Gu Immortal path with few members.

Luck path was created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, even though it was famous, actual luck path Gu Immortals were few in number.

As the origin of luck path, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind three true inheritances, self luck, all living being's luck, and heaven and earth luck.

Self luck was in Lang Ya blessed land, it was given to Long Hair Ancestor as payment, among which, Dog Shit Luck ended up in Fang Yuan's hands.

All living being's luck was placed in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. A portion of it was given to the winner of the Imperial Court contest. Fang Yuan had once possessed connect luck Immortal Gu, it was part of all living being's luck.

Feng Jun's true inheritance had also originated from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Back then, the Hei tribe Gu Master entered Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and fortunately obtained a portion of the true inheritance, he received qi luck Immortal Gu.

Thereafter, he cultivated to Gu Immortal level and passed it down for generations. The last generation had been punished after Hei Feng Yue's disappearance and the loss of attitude Gu, thus this true inheritance was left in Immortal Succession Mountain.

Feng Jun obtained this true inheritance, he had qi luck Immortal Gu, the move he was most familiar with and had practised the most was luck whirlwind.

This move was very special.

When the target attacks, by using it, it could repel the target.

When the target retreats, if it is used, it could drag the target back to the user.

Once this move was used, intense winds would form, but that was only on the surface, the key was that formless force.

Fang Yuan could not see this formless force, he was hit by the move again and was sent away.

At once, their distance enlarged.

As if his hard work had been in vain.

But Fang Yuan smiled as his lips curled up, he thought to himself: "Luck whirlwind... the second time already."

According to what Chen Le said, this move could not be used extensively, in one day, it could only be used a hundred times.

Just take it as a hundred, this might seem like a lot, but it was not!

Activating luck whirlwind was not as simple as it seemed on the surface.

The first issue was immortal essence, Feng Jun was a rank six Gu Immortal, he did not have a deep foundation, using this killer move would expend immortal essence, how long could Feng Jun last?

And immortal killer moves could not succeed with every use, each time Feng Jun failed, he would not only suffer a backlash, he would be unable to repel Fang Yuan, he would be able to get close and kill them.

Thus, it might seem like Fang Yuan could do nothing to Zhou Min and Feng Jun, but he actually had complete advantage in this situation.

Feng Jun and Zhou Min were walking on the side of a steep cliff, if they were careless, they would die without intact corpses.

"Die, go and die!!" Zhou Min was still furious, she stared at Fang Yuan as her eyes shot out white light.

"Retreat, we must retreat!" The calmer Feng Jun felt his mouth going dry, his heart was pounding as his body was covered in cold sweat.

Chapter 1127: Resolving the Situation by Killing!

The two sides did not fight for very long, but Feng Jun already had the intention to retreat and escape.

Fang Yuan first assassinated the strongest rank seven blood path Gu Immortal Zheng Tuo, before charging forward and using the best tactic to gain the absolute advantage!

Feng Jun was not an idiot, even if he lacked battle experience, he knew that he was in great danger.

He wanted to retreat, it was a wise choice.

In Gu Immortal battles, they fought not only with strength but also with wits!

"Sister has lost it due to her emotions, Hei Cheng is a rank seven Gu Immortal, even if we cooperate, we cannot defeat him. We should join up with the other Gu Immortals, and with Old Immortal Chen Chi at the lead, encircle and kill him!"

Feng Jun thought of this and started to retreat.

He used his immortal killer move, his body moved like a cloud, bringing him and Zhou Min away towards the left.

"What are you doing? Brother, let me kill him, let me kill him!" Zhou Min screamed as she struggled in Feng Jun's arms.

Feng Jun smiled bitterly, he increased the strength he was using on Zhou Min, he pacified her: "Don't move, I am getting some distance to create a chance for your farsight weapon light!"

Zhou Min heard this and shuddered, she said excitedly: "Good idea!"

She concentrated, staring fixedly at Fang Yuan.

With greater distance, farsight weapon light became stronger, Fang Yuan's defense would be under greater pressure.

Fang Yuan looked at the cloud below their feet, he smiled without concern.

He did not chase them, he charged down and landed on the ground, he picked up Zheng Tuo's corpse which was split into two, putting both pieces into his immortal aperture.

"Evil thief! Let go of our brother's corpse!" Zhou Min shouted, her lungs were exploding from anger.

Fang Yuan's actions were truly vile. Not only did he kill Zheng Tuo, he did not even let his corpse off.

How could he let it off?

The dao marks of this rank seven blood path Gu Immortal were an immense boost to Fang Yuan's foundation!

Looking at it, including Zheng Tuo, Fang Yuan had already killed four Gu Immortals, it was hard to annex the immortal aperture as it had strict conditions, but the gain in dao marks was immense.

"Ordinary Gu Immortals would only absorb the dao marks of an enemy of the same path due to the conflict between dao marks. Otherwise, they would get more trouble instead. However, my sovereign immortal body is different, the dao marks do not conflict, this is amazing! I can absorb the dao marks of any enemy I kill and increase my foundation. This seems to be the best way to increase my strength!"

At this moment, Fang Yuan had a new insight.

This sovereign immortal body was created from sovereign immortal fetus Gu, Spectral Soul wanted to revive using it.

If he really succeeded in reviving, the consequences were unthinkable!

Firstly, Spectral Soul had devoured so many souls in the door of life and death, he had countless cultivation experiences. Secondly, all of his paths were great grandmaster and above! Finally, he had the help of Shadow Sect's remnant forces.

With this starting point, he could repeat what he did in his era, killing everyone and everything. He could annex the immortal apertures of Gu Immortals he killed or absorb the dao marks they had. His growth would be at an incredible speed, it would surpass one's imagination!

Unlike Fang Yuan, who only had grandmaster attainment level in four paths, it was hard for him to annex immortal apertures, he could only absorb dao marks in most cases.

Fang Yuan placed Zheng Tuo's corpse in his immortal aperture, Zhou Min looked at with this anger and hatred.

Feng Jun did not speak, he felt aggrieved, but also let out a sigh of relief.

"It seems that Hei Cheng does not have movement methods, or maybe he uses the upper extreme heavenly eagle normally. This immemorial desolate beast has yet to grow fully, it only has rank six battle strength, he did not let it out because he is afraid of farsight weapon light killing it?"

Feng Jun became less worried.

But at the next moment, his mouth opened wide, a shocked expression appeared on his face.

It turned out that Fang Yuan had activated Sword Escape, his body flew into the sky like a sword.

His speed was so fast, Feng Jun and Zhou Min were completely stunned from shock!

"How can he be this fast?" Zhou Min said.

"So this is his real speed!" Feng Jun's heart was about to jump out, his movement method was simply outmatched!

In a few breaths of time, Fang Yuan got close to them again.

His icy killing intent almost froze Feng Jun's heart.

Immortal killer move — Luck Whirlwind!

At the moment of crisis, he had to use his trump card again.

Like what happened earlier, Fang Yuan was sent away again.

"The third time, hehe." Fang Yuan noted, he had been repelled three times, but he felt no dejection.

Zhou Min finally became sober-minded.

She was completely shocked by Fang Yuan's speed, her forehead was full of sweat, her anger dwindled, and fear took over.

"Quickly leave! This person is too strong, let's gather with the rest first!" Zhou Min yelled.

Feng Jun heard this and felt glad at her change of mindset.

With Zhou Min's help, the two rose in speed, they rapidly escaped for their lives.

Fang Yuan chased after them, shooting out with bursts of speed at times.

But every time, Feng Jun's luck whirlwind would ruin his attempt.

After chasing them for some time, two Gu Immortals appeared before them.

They were the two Gu Immortal lone cultivators, they usually lived together, one was called Jiang Ji, the other was Gao Mi.

"Hold on, we're coming!"

The two immortals were flying too, they quickly joined up with Zhou Min and Feng Jun.

Fang Yuan observed their expressions, seeing that they were showing no shock, he knew that Feng Jun and Zhou Min had used a certain information path method to inform these two Gu Immortals along the way.

"Hei Cheng, you are simply too bold, you dare to cause harm to us inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven!"

"Today, you will undoubtedly die!"

Feng Jun and Zhou Min stopped escaping, they went ahead to fight Fang Yuan.

"Young master Hei Cheng, you killed sister Wan Yun?! Did you kill old ancestor as well?" A shrill voice suddenly resounded.

It was Chen Le.

After using the warning, Chen Le went to find Fang Yuan, but at that time, Fang Yuan had already left to find the three immortals including Zheng Tuo.

Chen Le could not find Fang Yuan, she was completely lost and helpless, she did not know what to do.

She did not dare to dispel her immortal killer move, she hid inside the palace for a while, before she received Feng Jun's letter.

The letter stated that Fang Yuan disguised as Chen Le and used an immortal killer move to kill Gu Immortal Zheng Tuo, no matter how stupid Chen Le was, she realized instantly what the situation was.

She quickly went to Chen Chi's place, but where could she find that old ancestor of hers?

Even though Feng Jun was escaping, he had already contacted the remaining immortals, Chen Le also decided to answer his call.

Thus, she appeared on the battlefield at this time.

"Oh, it's you." Fang Yuan looked at Chen Le, smiling cruelly: "You have finally gotten smarter. That's right, be it Chen Chi, Chen Wan Yun, or Chen Li Zhi, even Zheng Tuo died in my hands. All of your rank seven Gu Immortals are dead now, the rest of you should surrender to me, after all, a wise person submits to circumstances."

Chen Le's expression turned pale, her body shook intensely.

Fang Yuan admitted it outright, this was a huge blow to her mental state.

"Why? Why did you do that for?!" Chen Le screamed in a sharp tone, tears were pouring out of her eyes: "Did we do anything wrong to you? Why must you do something so evil and cruel?!"

"Don't be affected by him, Chen Le, let's get into formation!" Zhou Min, who had regained her senses, shouted loudly.

With Fang Yuan in the center, a jade light ball suddenly appeared over a huge surrounding area.

This was a huge battle formation.

With Feng Jun, Zhou Min, Chen Le, and the other two immortals as the formation cores, they assembled an ancient battle formation!

"Hei Cheng, even if you are a rank seven Gu Immortal, you will die here today!"

"That's right, we have already practiced this battle formation many times, we killed over a dozen desolate beasts and eight ancient desolate beasts."

"You cannot escape from here! I will tear our your bones and tendons, and use them as offerings for the innocent souls of our comrades!"

Hei Fan grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals shouted, their morale rose sharply.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, his calm expression did not change at all.

He said slowly and calmly: "Oh, Green City battle formation? Hehehe, it is only a small portion of the ancient battle formation Green City Rampage, do you think I am unaware of it?"

The expressions of the immortals changed, a bad feeling was emerging in them.

Chen Le's expression paled even further, at this moment, she felt utter regret and hatred, she could not live with herself!

Because she was the one who told Fang Yuan about this Green City battle formation.

The Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven had to practice a huge formation in every generation. It was the Green City battle formation, it was used to kill desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts, it had incredible strength.

"I have rank seven cultivation level, while you people are just rank six. Thus, I expected you to use this move. After getting into formation, you won't be able to run, right? Hehehe, when this battle formation is breached, you will all face a backlash, even if you do not die, you will suffer heavy injuries..."

Fang Yuan said in a plain tone.

His tone was very calm, he did not speak loudly, but the immortals could hear him clearly for some reason.

The morale that was raised earlier instantly got cut in several piecees after hearing his words. Before fighting, these Gu Immortals already had wavering determination!

"Now, I will show all of you my true strength."

Fang Yuan called out, his body shook and a loud sound was heard, the aura of Gu worms burst out from within him!

Immortal killer move — Myriad Self!

In an instant, tens of thousands of Fang Yuan phantoms appeared in the space inside the entire battle formation.

They were all strength path phantoms!

And Fang Yuan's true body was hidden among them, acting as one of the phantoms.

The battle commenced at this moment.

From the start, they entered the climax of the battle.

Feng Jun, Zhou Min, and the other Gu Immortals used their respective methods, all sorts of immortal killer moves were unleashed, causing huge damage to the myriad self army.

Fang Yuan's strength path phantoms did not have high defense, but no matter how many were destroyed in battle, more strength path phantoms emerged and replaced them.

Fang Yuan had made ample preparation before the battle.

Even if he did not continue to activate myriad self, he had already stored hundreds of thousands of myriad self phantoms inside his immortal aperture in advance.

He did not lack the immortal essence!

Fang Yuan had a huge storage of green grape immortal essence!

Feng Jun and the rest soon realized that they were in a tough spot.

Without using immortal killer moves, they could not defend against the myriad self army attacking the battle formation. But if they used immortal killer moves, even though they could kill countless phantoms, Fang Yuan would also replenish them, their immortal essence would be wasted.

In this battle of attrition in immortal essence, Fang Yuan completely had the upper hand! Do not forget about the advantage of strength path, that was the minimal consumption of immortal essence. Meanwhile, the advantage of enslavement path was in battles of attrition.

Myriad self killer move combined the effects of both paths, it could display the strengths of both paths at once!

Fang Yuan waited patiently among the myriad self army, observing attentively.

All sorts of information was gathered by him, he committed them to memory.

After fighting for several hours, the Gu Immortals of Hei Fan grotto-heaven were extremely tired, not only were they tired mentally, the immortal essence expenditure was also starting to put a toll on them.

The moment they exposed weakness, Fang Yuan's true body appeared!

"Hahaha, Chen Le, I need to thank you, without your information, how could I have killed Chen Wan Yun and the others?" Fang Yuan laughed loudly.

Chen Le felt like lightning had struck her, the pain in her heart could not be described with words.

Using this opportunities, Fang Yuan went for the killing blow.

Flying sword Immortal Gu!

A flash of light pierced Chen Le's defenses, killing her instantly.

Always pick out the weakest enemy first!

Fang Yuan struck at the crucial moment, immediately killing one immortal on the other side.

Chen Le died on the spot, Green City battle formation became unstable instantly, it started shaking.

The other Gu Immortals quickly tried to stabilize it, succeeding after some effort.

"Next, it is time for the rest of you to die." Fang Yuan smiled sinisterly, he did not attack, instead, he went back into the myriad self army.

The remaining four Gu Immortals had pale expressions, a cold chill was emerging in their hearts.

They were the ones encircling Fang Yuan, but at this very moment, none of these four Gu Immortals felt any joy or excitement.

His victory was assured!

From the start, Fang Yuan had used the most appropriate battle tactics, establishing his current huge advantage.

He was very aware about the methods of these Gu Immortals, but they, on the other hand, did not know about his methods.

Originally, the other party had an advantage.

For example, Chen Le's concealment method, Fang Yuan could do nothing against it.

It was a pity, because Fang Yuan schemed against them, Chen Le joined the battle and formed the Green City battle formation, she gave up her greatest advantage.

In the end, it was because Hei Fan grotto-heaven had been in peace for too long, these Gu Immortals did not lack Immortal Gu or resources, but they truly paled in terms of battle experience.

Even though they sparred during their interactions, the experience gained from fighting on the verge of death could not be gained from friendly battles.

A long while later.

Fang Yuan killed two more Gu Immortals, before breaking apart Green City battle formation.

Feng Jun and Zhou Min escaped in defeat again.

The two immortals had completely lost their courage against Fang Yuan, they did not dare to fight, they escaped towards Immortal Succession Mountain.

Along the way, Fang Yuan killed Zhou Min, as Feng Jun crashed onto the peak of Immortal Succession Mountain with his heavily injured body.

"Heavenly spirit, save me!" He screamed loudly.

This situation was quite ironic, earlier he was still plotting to suppress the heavenly spirit, but now, he had no choice but to seek help from it.

"It is not going to save you." Inside the stone pavilion, Fang Yuan's figure appeared in a flash.

He spoke in a calm tone, he had no injuries on his body, he was still so charming and handsome. It was as if the battle earlier did not occur at all.

Feng Jun saw Fang Yuan and shuddered in fear, he focused his attention on the brass bell heavenly spirit.

The brass bell heavenly spirit had no reaction.

Feng Jun had a look of despair.

"Why?" He muttered.

"Why!" At the next moment, he screamed again, seemingly questioning the heavenly spirit.

But the brass bell heavenly spirit continued to be unmoved.

"Because you are all descendants of criminal immortals. Before Old Ancestor Hei Fan died, he thought of this point when leaving behind his true inheritance. Therefore, he set up this final test. Only by obtaining half of the votes of the Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven could I inherit it. Hehehe, but what if you descendants of the criminal immortals bear hatred to Hei tribe and refuse to let our main tribe's member obtain the true inheritance, what if you cause problems for us intentionally, what will we do?" Fang Yuan extended his hand, lightly touching this stone tablet.

"Then it can only be to kill all of you. After killing you all, I will be the only person left. Then I would also have satisfied the conditions for clearing the final test of Hei Fan's true inheritance."

Fang Yuan spoke lightly, there was even a faint smile on his face.

Feng Jun plopped onto the ground, he had an expression of despair, he was sprawled weakly.

He raised his head and looked up at the sky.

The azure sky which he sought to escape for so long, at the moment before his death, now seemed so endearing to him.

But at the next moment, he heard Fang Yuan's words: "Now, I will give you a chance. As long as you submit to me, and serve me wholeheartedly from now on, I will spare your life."

"What, what did you say?" Feng Jun's body shook, he showed an expression of disbelief.

Fang Yuan repeated his words again, before saying: "You are a smart person, you are not swayed by emotions, you are unlike Zhou Min and Chen Le. I appreciate that aspect of you. Hand over your Immortal Gu and the luck path true inheritance's details, I will spare your life and give you a chance to live."

Feng Jun blinked, he was moved.

"You are not lying to me?" He raised his head and looked at Fang Yuan, anticipation was hidden deep within his gaze.

"Why would I lie to you? Killing you is as easy as breathing to me. But don't even think of bargaining with me now." Fang Yuan's expression changed: "You only have three breaths of time to consider it, will you die, or surrender everything to me and submit, before making an alliance agreement."

"I surrender." At the first breath of time, Feng Jun said without hesitation.

"These are all of the Gu worms that I have." At the second breath of time, Feng Jun handed over everything.

Fang Yuan nodded, stretching out his hand and keeping them, with Feng Jun's cooperation, he suppressed all of them!

"Please make the alliance agreement." Feng Jun breathed in deeply, he was already mentally prepared for an extremely harsh alliance agreement.

Swoosh!

A bloody hole appeared in his forehead.

He had an expression of shock, he stared at Fang Yuan fixedly as he gradually fell onto the ground.

The third breath of time had just passed.

Chapter 1128: Hei Fan's Four Treasures (1/2)

Fang Yuan gathered Feng Jun's corpse.

Together with the Gu Immortal corpses that he had collected earlier, Fang Yuan had a total of nine! And he also had nine corresponding Gu Immortal souls.

"Such gains are truly rare. For Gu Immortals in the outside world, even if they die, they may self-detonate. Among the Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, only Feng Jun has some brains. This person was able to give in when needed, unfortunately, after I gained the upper hand, the situation was firmly within my grasp, he could not do anything. His eventual surrender was out of desperation, too bad for him, his enemy was me."

Fang Yuan sighed as he set aside these thoughts.

He had won.

It was time for the rewards!

He turned around, entering the stone pavilion, he raised his head and looked at the brass bell heavenly spirit on the pillar, he said: "Right now, I am the only Gu Immortal inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, I vote for myself to inherit Hei Fan's true inheritance."

The brass bell heavenly spirit was silent for a moment before shaking, emitting a loud bell sound.

Next, the stone pillars in the pavilion radiated with pure white light.

The white light was not painful to look at, it was very gentle.

As the bright light shone, the stone tablet became more transparent, it turned into a wall of light.

Inside the wall of light, there were several shadowy figures.

And on the surface of the wall, there were several lines of words.

Fang Yuan looked, the words were: the indistinct figures in the stone tablet are the contents of the true inheritance. The inheritor just needs to retrieve them by putting their hands in.

The final line was an instruction by Hei Fan — Descendant of Hei tribe, inheritor of the inheritance, may you achieve great things in life, do not let down the reputation of Hei tribe!

Fang Yuan looked at it and sighed.

Old Ancestor Hei Fan had put in immense effort in setting up this true inheritance, he thought of every aspect.

But a dead person was like an extinguished candle, even a legendary figure like himself could not predict everything in the future.

The incredibly strong Hei tribe had been wiped out, and Hei Fan's true inheritance was taken by an outsider like Fang Yuan.

The world had changed, times were different. New forces prosper while old forces vanish, this was the changing of eras.

Fang Yuan settled his mood, he started acting according to the description on the wall.

He stretched out his left hand, to enter the wall of light.

The white light became brighter, as it shone on his left hand, Fang Yuan's left arm became transparent as well.

Fang Yuan could see his skin, bones, flesh, and even his blood flowing in his vessels.

A small obstruction could be felt ahead.

Fang Yuan's left hand touched the wall of light, it was as if he was touching an icy wall.

At the same time, he noticed: the white light shone on his blood and caused a reaction. His blood moved more quickly, the color also turned from bright red to dark red, before returning back to normal.

Next, the wall in front of his left hand became soft like water. Fang Yuan's left hand easily got through the stone tablet like he was going into water.

Fang Yuan however, felt a chill in his heart, he thought: "So close! This light wall is a test towards my blood. Thankfully, I made ample preparations, I integrated blood asset Immortal Gu into familiar face and modified the killer move to disguise my blood as well. Otherwise, my efforts would have been in vain! This Hei Fan is so hard to deal with."

Fang Yuan regained his cool, he started to assess this wall of light.

From the outside, he could see that there were four shadows in the wall, they were uneven in placement.

The largest shadow was like a ball, it was the size of a basin and was at the most central area of the wall.

On the upper right corner, there was a sharp shadow, it resembled a rock.

On the left side, there was also a shadow, it looked like intertwined threads.

There was also one spot at the bottom, this shadow was the smallest, like a finger.

Fang Yuan had worked so hard to obtain the famous Hei Fan's true inheritance, but the contents seemed to be quite minimal.

Because of where he was standing, Fang Yuan's left hand went to the left of the wall of light, he grabbed towards the shadow closest to him.

He held onto this thread-like shadow.

The shadow had a rough feeling, Fang Yuan felt like he was touching an old tree branch.

Next, Fang Yuan stretched out his hand and pulled out the mysterious shadow.

Once out of the wall, the aura was exposed.

Evidently, these were Gu worms.

These Gu worms were coiled together, they had similar appearance, they were like ginseng roots, or tree roots.

They were not Immortal Gu.

They were just mortal Gu.

But even so, Fang Yuan's eyes shined, his breathing became rougher at once!

Mortal and Immortal Gu were vastly different.

Immortal Gu were unique. Mortal Gu could not compare to Immortal Gu, but there was a huge exception to this rule.

That was lifespan Gu!

That's right, Fang Yuan pulled out a batch of lifespan Gu.

This was expected, yet unexpected.

Earlier, when Old Immortal Chen Chi had asked Fang Yuan for benefits, he mentioned lifespan Gu. Thus, Fang Yuan was mentally prepared for it. But to think there was so many.

"This is indeed a lot of lifespan Gu!"

Fang Yuan began to refine the lifespan Gu.

Mortal Gu could be refined using primeval essence.

Even though the lifespan Gu was not his, Fang Yuan had passed the test, he was the acknowledged inheritor.

As the white light shone, Fang Yuan quickly refined these lifespan Gu successfully.

He found out: "These lifespan Gu grants seven hundred and twenty years of lifespan in total!"

Immense gains!

Old Immortal Chen Chi had thought there would be at least three hundred years worth of lifespan Gu, but Fang Yuan could tell now that he had underestimated it.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven had over twice that amount of years worth of lifespan Gu!

"These lifespan Gu have great value."

"I can use them for myself, who in this world would complain about having longer lifespan?"

"But I still have about eighty years to live, my lifespan is sufficient. Even if I do not use these lifespan Gu, I can use them for transactions."

In transactions between Gu Immortals, immortal essence stones were just basic currency. Lifespan Gu had much greater value than immortal essence stones. No Gu Immortal would not want lifespan Gu! In many high end transactions, immortal essence stones were unusable, Gu Immortals only wanted lifespan Gu.

Lifespan Gu was an absolute hard currency out there!

After a long time of consideration, the lifespan Gu were all refined, becoming Fang Yuan's property.

Fang Yuan placed the handful of lifespan Gu in his sovereign immortal aperture, keeping them securely.

He was not planning to use these lifespan Gu yet.

"Actually, it had been a long time since Hei Fan grotto-heaven was created. It is not strange that so many lifespan Gu were accumulated."

"When can my sovereign immortal aperture produce lifespan Gu as well?"

Fang Yuan was rather fascinated by the prospect.

But he knew that he was far from this goal at this point.

Even though he was earning a lot of profits each month, those were his prior accumulations as an immortal zombie. His immortal aperture's development was still in the basic stage. Only when he gathers enough production in resources to sustain the feeding of all his Immortal Gu could those initial developments be considered complete.

Fang Yuan suddenly thought of Lang Ya blessed land.

"Compared to Lang Ya blessed land, Hei Fan grotto-heaven's existence is very short. Long Hair Ancestor was a person from three hundred thousand years ago, a legendary figure of the Medieval Antiquity Era!"

"Hei Fan grotto-heaven has about seven hundred years of lifespan Gu. Then how many years does Lang Ya blessed land have?"

Thinking about this, Fang Yuan's eyes shined.

"Lang Ya blessed land definitely has much more lifespan Gu. No wonder Lang Ya land spirit can use up some to feed wisdom Gu!"

Fang Yuan could understand Heavenly Court's actions at once.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, Heavenly Court attacked Lang Ya blessed land, even though they sacrificed Feng Jiu Ge, they went ahead without balking.

Lifespan Gu was likely one of the main reasons.

Thinking about it, the geezers in Heavenly Court were lacking lifespan, they could only sustain their lives through sleeping. It was easy to see how much attraction lifespan Gu had towards them!

Fang Yuan's gaze returned to the center of the wall.

This shadow was the largest.

"It is at the center, is this a hint that this is the most precious treasure inside Hei Fan's true inheritance" Fang Yuan's heart jumped.

He stretched out his left hand towards the wall of light, soon, he touched that shadow.

It had an icy feeling, but the shadow was not smooth on the surface, it had many protrusions and holes, it was like a handful of sesame.

Fang Yuan tried to move it.

Very heavy!

Normal human strength could not carry it.

Fang Yuan activated his strength path mortal Gu, after gaining strength, he took it out with one hand.

After seeing this lump of shadow, Fang Yuan had a surprised look on his face.

This was not one entity, it was the combination of countless bodies.

It was a ball of ants.

Black ants, all gathered to fill the size of a basin, that were extremely heavy. Countless black ants were collected in a ball shape, they were extremely compacted and tight.

These ants were not ordinary ants, they were mortal Gu.

The previous item being mortal Gu was fine, because it was lifespan Gu, it had greater value than Immortal Gu from many Gu Immortals' perspectives.

But this was also mortal Gu?

Fang Yuan felt perplexed and a bit confused.

Based on his knowledge, he could not recognize what this Gu worm was.

But forget that, Fang Yuan felt that since it was part of Hei Fan's true inheritance, even as a mortal Gu, it could not be bad.

Thus, he began to refine it.

Mortal Gu could be refined using primeval essence, Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal, he had unlimited primeval essence.

Layers of black ants were refined by him, becoming his property.

Under Fang Yuan's manipulation, the ants split apart, revealing the center of the ball.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's expression changed, his gaze became sharp, because he felt the aura of Immortal Gu.

Actually, at the center of this ball of ants, there was something good! An Immortal Gu!

Ordinary ant mortal Gu were finally completely refined, they landed on the ground, there was only one Gu left in Fang Yuan's hands.

Immortal Gu!

Compared to the other black ant mortal Gu, it was many times larger. It had the form of an ant, it had feelers, small legs, a large abdomen, it looked very chubby.

"Is this the queen of the ant group?" Fang Yuan guessed randomly.

This Immortal Gu had a strong aura, it was at a high level, it was a rank seven Immortal Gu.

As for what it was, Fang Yuan did not know.

He could not recognize it.

But whatever, he was going to refine it first.

Chapter 1129: Hei Fan's Four Treasure (2/2)

Refining Immortal Gu could not be done with primeval essence, he needed immortal essence.

At this time, Fang Yuan took a look at the brass bell heavenly spirit, thinking about it, he directly used his green grape immortal essence to refine this Gu.

The brass bell heavenly spirit had no reaction, on the surface, Fang Yuan could not tell what mentality it had. It was just a bell after all, it had no expressions.

The refinement process was very smooth, the rank seven Immortal Gu resembling an ant queen did not resist, it cooperated with him.

But it was still a rank seven Gu, Fang Yuan's green grape immortal essence was greatly expended.

"Now, my stockpile of green grape immortal essence has dropped again." Fang Yuan reminded himself.

In this trip to obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance, he had consumed a lot of green grape immortal essence. His expenditure was mostly in battle, after all, other than myriad self, Sword Escape and flying sword Immortal Gu were rank seven, his sword path killer moves used rank seven Immortal Gu as the cores.

Even though the battles were not intense, his green grape immortal essence consumption was huge.

"After going back, I need to stock up on immortal essence, otherwise, I can't feel safe."

A moment later, Fang Yuan refined this rank seven Immortal Gu and kept it in his immortal aperture.

There were only two shadows left in the wall of light.

The shadow at the bottom had the smallest size, Fang Yuan left it to the end.

He stretched his hand in and grabbed the shadow at the top right corner.

This shadow was like a rock, but when Fang Yuan touched it for the first time, it reacted.

This shadow was very cold.

Fang Yuan took it out, it was indeed a piece of ice.

The upper portion of the ice was sealing a Gu worm.

Naturally, Fang Yuan's attention was drawn to it.

Even though it was sealed in ice without any aura leaking.

But Fang Yuan's eyes shone, he could recognize this was an Immortal Gu — "Year".

Year Gu!

It was like a ladybug, thumb size and black in color, there were golden markings on its shell.

The golden markings were bright and shining, they showed images of a fierce beast growling, the sharp and menacing teeth left a deep impression. As for what beast it was, it was unclear.

"Oh, year Gu..." Fang Yuan sighed.

This was a famous Gu among time path Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan had a deep impression towards it.

Because it was very unique.

When Gu Immortals expend immortal materials, they could parallel refine a year Gu continuously.

Normal refinement and reverse refinement were mainstream in refinement path, parallel refinement was very rare.

Gu worms that could be parallel refined were very rare.

Year Gu was one of them.

Mortal level year Gu were less than ten years. There was one year Gu, two year Gu, five year Gu, and others.

When the year Gu rises to rank six, it would become an Immortal Gu, unique in the world. Rank six year Gu were at least ten years.

A ten year immortal level year Gu could be parallel refined using immortal materials, to make it twenty year Gu, thirty-eight year Gu, or at its highest, ninety-nine year Gu.

Hundred year Gu was rank seven, to refine a ten year Gu to hundred year Gu, it was not parallel refinement but normal refinement to increase rank instead.

Refinement in this case was tens to hundreds of times as difficult as parallel refinement, with equally low success rate.

Thousand year Gu was rank eight, in theory, ten thousand year Gu would be rank nine. but in history, there had never been a ten thousand year Gu.

But rank eight thousand year Gu had existed before.

The use of year Gu was very unique.

Corresponding to the usage by the Gu Immortal, the number of years would fall continuously. For example, a fifty year Gu might become a twenty year Gu after one use.

There was a specification when using year Gu, that it should not go overboard. For example, if a thousand year Gu is used and becomes nine hundred year Gu, it would fall from rank eight to rank seven. To increase its rank again through refinement, it would be troublesome and risky.

Strictly speaking, year Gu was a consumable Immortal Gu.

But it was not a one time consumable Gu like sovereign immortal fetus Gu.

It could be expended but replenished again.

This was a very special case among Gu worms.

"So Hei Fan had the Immortal Gu 'Year' in his possession. One good thing about year Gu is that it has no issues in terms of food. It has the same food as Spring Autumn Cicada, they both consume the water of the River of Time. However, how can I refine it?" Fang Yuan was unsure.

The year Gu in front of him was sealed by almost transparent ice.

Fang Yuan looked at this ice, he felt that this ice was quite special too.

Its effect was similar to fossilization or amber, it sealed the year Immortal Gu inside ice, so that it hibernated without leaking its aura.

"Why, why did Hei Fan seal year Gu? Wait, this is?" While observing, Fang Yuan had a new discovery.

He realized that there was some flowing water sealed at the bottom of the ice.

"This is water?"

Fang Yuan shook it, he could clearly see that there was water flowing, he could even hear a soft sound.

Water was sealed in ice, it was really quite strange.

Fang Yuan's attention had been drawn to year Gu earlier. In comparison, the flowing water was not eye-catching.

At this moment, when Fang Yuan inspected it again, he realized: this ice was huge, year Gu only occupied a small portion, the flowing water took more than half of the space below. It gave a feeling that the ice was not sealing year Gu, but the water instead!

"To be given such treatment, is this flowing water a rank nine immortal material that surpasses rank eight?" Fang Yuan had a bold guess.

Rank nine immortal material, it could be used to refine rank nine Immortal Gu!

In this world, they were rare, having immense value.

A portion of rank nine immortal material being sealed like this was understandable.

Fang Yuan could not find a way to remove the ice, he could only set it aside, he held it with his right hand as his left hand entered the wall of light again.

This time, he went to the final shadow.

Taking it out, it was a rank five information path mortal Gu.

The details recorded inside were about Hei Fan's true inheritance, it had immense value!

Firstly, the introduction to the Gu worms.

Fang Yuan took his first glance and saw the information about the ant ball.

"So the rank seven Immortal Gu at the center of the ant ball is the time path Immortal Gu, After!" [1. After sounds the same as ant queen if you read it in Chinese.]

Rank seven after Immortal Gu.

The recorded information noted the specifications of feeding after Immortal Gu.

The feeding of after Immortal Gu was quite unique.

This Immortal Gu could eat anything.

The feeding style was very unique too.

It produced black ant mortal Gu on its own, it sent them out to feed on all sorts of immortal materials before using these nutrients on itself.

"Any sort of immortal material can feed after Immortal Gu. The point is not about the immortal materials, but in preserving these black ant mortal Gu."

These black ant mortal Gu were tough and could devour immortal materials, digesting them and retaining the nutrients.

But they were just mortal Gu.

Once too many of them were destroyed, the Immortal Gu, After, would starve. Even though the Immortal Gu could produce black ant mortal Gu, it could only produce one every month. If there were too few black ant mortal Gu, and after Immortal Gu could not be fed, it would die of hunger.

After all, this Immortal Gu, After, could not feed itself.

Fang Yuan felt enlightened, he continued reading, about the information on the ice.

The ice itself was a newly created type of rank eight immortal material, it was created by Immortal Bing Ren. The latter was invited by Hei Fan and went ahead to seal his two Immortal Gu.

One Immortal Gu was year Gu, it was only rank six. Fang Yuan had recognized it already.

The other Immortal Gu was the flowing water.

This was the greatest treasure within Hei Fan's true inheritance!

It was named Years Flow Like Water, it was rank eight!

Rank eight time path Immortal Gu, Years Flow Like Water.

Rank eight Gu Immortals were rare, rank eight Immortal Gu were rarer, and had very great value. Many rank eight Gu Immortals did not even have a single rank eight Immortal Gu, they could not find one even after endless searching.

Hei Fan was a legendary character, the formidable champion who led Hei tribe to a domineering state, but in his life, he only had one rank eight Immortal Gu — Years Flow Like Water.

Fang Yuan's situation was quite special.

As of now, he was a rank six Gu Immortal, but he already had three rank eight Immortal Gu.

One was attitude Gu, one was wisdom sword Gu, and now the third was Years Flow Like Water.

Ordinary Gu Immortals usually had a lack of Immortal Gu. Fang Yuan's problem instead was that he had too many, and could not use them all optimally. Looking at some of his Immortal Gu like Wisdom Sword, he had not even started to use them yet.

This rank eight Immortal Gu, Years Flow Like Water, had one effect, that was to produce year Gu.

The more immortal essence expended by the Gu Immortal, the more year Gu produced, they could even produce immortal level year Gu.

Of course, the rule of Immortal Gu being unique still holds!

Right now, this rank six year Gu was around, unless Fang Yuan used and expended it, he could not create an immortal level year Gu from Years Flow Like Water.

If year Immortal Gu still existed, no matter how much immortal essence Fang Yuan used, he could only get mortal year Gu.

Fang Yuan continued to read.

Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water had two good points.

One was that it had a low usage requirement, even rank six Gu Immortals could use it. As long as they used green grape immortal essence, they would receive year Gu, even though the quantity was less than when using rank seven or eight immortal essence.

The second point was that Years Flow Like Water was easy to feed. It also fed on the water of the River of Time, just like year Gu and Spring Autumn Cicada.

This solved Fang Yuan's greatest problem.

The feeding of rank eight Immortal Gu was a huge burden!

However, Years Flow Like Water had a flaw.

This was clearly listed in the information path Gu worm.

Once the seal of Years Flow Like Water was removed, its Immortal Gu aura would leak, year beasts would be lured towards it and would attack.

Year beasts, a type of special fierce beast that were rare even in the five regions and nine heavens, yet commonly seen in the River of Time. In terms of battle strength, there were desolate beast, ancient desolate beast, and immemorial desolate beast level year beasts.

The food of year beasts was year Gu.

The River of Time was the paradise of time path Gu worms, there were a vast number of wild time path Gu worms in it.

Year beasts were one of them, they ate year Gu as food.

The higher the rank of the year Gu, the more year beasts would be attracted to hunt them.

In fact, immortal level year Gu could also lure year beasts to attack. Even placing the immortal level year Gu inside the immortal aperture would not work.

Because in ordinary immortal apertures, there was a tributary of the River of Time. When year beasts smell the year Gu, they would travel into the tributary from the River of Time, and directly appear in the immortal aperture.

Immortal level year Gu had a huge attraction to the year beasts, Years Flow Like Water, which could endlessly produce year Gu, had hundreds or thousands of times as much attraction as immortal level year Gu for the year beasts!

Precisely because of this, when Hei Fan set up the true inheritance, he sealed year Gu and Years Flow Like Water, not exposing a trace of their auras.

At this point, Fang Yuan had completely understood what Gu worms he had obtained.

Next were the following important details.

Or more accurately, the immortal killer moves!

Chapter 1130: Usage of Hei Fan's Gu

The introductions of countless immortal killer moves were displayed before Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan restrained his excitement, he inspected carefully.

There were immortal killer moves that encompassed offense, defense, movement, healing, and other aspects.

These were all time path immortal killer moves, the cores used were mostly year Gu and after Gu. Few of the immortal killer moves used the Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water as a core. Using a rank eight Immortal Gu as a core of an immortal killer move would naturally produce incredible effects.

In this regard, Fang Yuan had personal experience.

He had familiar face, it was a legendary method that used the rank eight attitude Gu as the core.

Of course, with Fang Yuan's rank six cultivation level, his green grape immortal essence could not activate Years Flow Like Water. It was unlike attitude Gu, which only needed mental energy to use.

"Attitude Gu is the legendary Immortal Gu recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, in terms of ease of use, Years Flow Like Water cannot compare to it. However, thinking about it, didn't Hei Fan give attitude Gu away to Hei Feng Yue..."

These immortal killer moves were truly eye-opening to Fang Yuan.

Many theories were involved, the coordination of Gu worms was stated clearly, he only took a look, but he felt that he had already benefited greatly from the knowledge gained.

There were more than thirty immortal killer moves, some of the immortal killer moves were split between rank six, seven, and eight levels, in some of their descriptions, Hei Fan had also left behind his insight and experiences when creating and using them in the past.

"Bountiful year?" Fang Yuan's gaze was fixed.

He discovered a rather interesting immortal killer move.

Bountiful year.

This was the name of an immortal killer move.

The core Immortal Gu used was immortal level year Gu.

There were tens of thousands of supplementary mortal Gu. It was a tough process to activate the move, Hei Fan had left behind his experience in using it. Even for a legendary figure like him, when using this immortal killer move himself, he would need two or three days of preparation to execute it!

The expenditure of immortal essence was huge, but bountiful year's effect was that for the next year, starting right from the moment of successful activation of the killer move, all of the resources inside the immortal aperture would be produced at a higher rate!

This was an immortal killer move used to develop the immortal aperture.

It was a very rare move, but it had great use and value. Hei Fan also praised this immortal killer move greatly.

According to the description, he was not the creator of this immortal killer move, he had exchanged for it with a person called Pill Immortal.

Fang Yuan took a closer look, bountiful year needed to use many mortal Gu, if he wanted to prepare for it, he would need to buy them from treasure yellow heaven.

He was definitely going to use this killer move.

But not only did he need a lot of immortal essence, there was a lot of expenditure in terms of year Gu as well.

"The year Gu that I have is only a little over the hundred year level. I need to parallel refine it until I can use bountiful year. Otherwise, if it falls to to the level of a mortal Gu, that would be a severe loss."

Fang Yuan continued to read.

Among these killer moves, some had incredible power, some were extremely wondrous, but to Fang Yuan, they were not especially important.

Fang Yuan had never forgotten about his true goal all along.

That was to find a method to delay the calamities and tribulations in his immortal aperture.

"Days pass like years!" His eyes flashed, he saw his target.

This immortal killer move also used immortal level year Gu as the core, with a huge number of supplementary day Gu. Once used, it could slow down the time in the immortal aperture.

Simply from the name itself, the effect was that one day in the immortal aperture would be extended to the length of a year.

However, Hei Fan had noted with great caution: extending one day into the equivalent of a year was purely theoretical. The actual effect varied greatly based on circumstances.

For example, a strength path Gu Immortal with primarily strength path dao marks would receive much lower effect when using this time path killer move.

If a time path Gu Immortal used it on themselves, like Hei Fan, the effect would be amplified by the Gu Immortal's time path dao marks, the effect would be much better.

And also, using the same killer move on a low grade blessed land and a high grade blessed land would produce different results.

"Months pass like years."

Fang Yuan continued to read, there was another immortal killer move that was very similar to days pass like years.

It could also slow the rate of time in the immortal aperture, it could turn what would be one month in the immortal aperture into the duration of a year. The core Gu was still immortal level year Gu, but the supplementary Gu were month Gu now.

Day Gu, month Gu, year Gu.

These were all time path Gu worms that were closely related.

Other than days pass like years and months pass like years, there were also two other immortal killer moves, they were called years pass like months and years pass like days.

The former two were used to slow the time in the immortal aperture, the latter two were used to accelerate the time in the immortal aperture.

Slowing the rate of time in the immortal aperture meant that the calamities and tribulations would be further apart. For example in Fang Yuan's case, he had to undergo tribulation every two months in the outside world's time. After using days pass like years, he would only need to undergo the next tribulation in decades or even a century.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan finally let out a sigh of relief.

He felt great joy.

In the first three earthly calamities, he was almost forced to his wits' end, he could only brace himself as he challenged them.

But now he had this immortal killer move, the situation had changed!

From now on, Fang Yuan could decide when to undergo tribulation, he could either delay or hasten it, there was a huge advantage in this.

"But right now, I do not need to slow the time in the immortal aperture. I should undergo tribulations, increasing my dao marks and raising my cultivation level. With Chu Du helping me, there is a high chance of passing." Fang Yuan thought.

Once he slowed the immortal aperture's time, there were flaws.

His resource would grow more slowly, Fang Yuan's cultivation level would also rise more slowly.

"Now, I should prepare these Gu worms, the Immortal Gu are already here, but I need a huge quantity of day Gu and month Gu. Even if I buy them inside treasure yellow heaven, I will need to spend a long time collecting them."

Hei Fan's true inheritance did not leave behind any day Gu, month Gu, and mortal year Gu, Fang Yuan had to purchase these mortal Gu himself.

Even though this task had its difficulties, as long as Fang Yuan was determined, he could achieve it.

"These four immortal killer moves form a set, they are specially used to alter the rate of time in the immortal aperture. Hei Fan, who created these killer moves, had incredible talent."

At the end, Hei Fan even noted: If the inheritor could obtain immortal level day Gu or month Gu, these four immortal killer moves would not need to consume so many mortal day Gu and month Gu, the effect would even rise greatly.

"I was already extremely fortunate to have obtained immortal level year Gu. As for immortal level day Gu and month Gu, I can forget about it." Fang Yuan was clear of the situation.

His goal in this trip had been fulfilled, Fang Yuan was satisfied with it.

He continued to look.

Immortal killer move — Years Grant Strength!

Soon, Fang Yuan saw a very interesting killer move.

This killer move used year Gu as the core, it could grant the Gu Immortal immense physical strength. The more year Gu expended, the greater the strength obtained.

This was Hei Fan's own creation, he used time path Gu worms to achieve a strength path effect.

Immortal killer move — Hundred Years Harmony!

It also used year Gu as the core, with a large number of supplementary information path mortal Gu, to create an alliance agreement that could last for a hundred years.

This was a use of time path Gu worms to unleash the might of information path.

"I can use this with Chu Du, after all, our current alliance agreement was solely handled by him, it is not reliable." Fang Yuan rapidly had an idea.

Immortal killer move — Unlucky Year.

This was an immortal killer move that used Years Flow Like Water as the core. Fang Yuan could not use it now, he could only look on in captivation.

Using time path to achieve the mystical effect of luck path.

This was an offensive killer move, once the enemy was hit, they would experience a huge fall in luck for a year, nothing they do would go smoothly.

"As expected of Hei Fan, an expert even among rank eight Gu Immortals!"

"If he was born in the Central Continent ten great ancient sects, he would definitely be invited into Heavenly Court, he would be an elite among Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals."

To be able to use one's own path to mimic other paths and achieve their mystical effects, this was the symbol of a rank eight expert. Ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals could not reach this stage.

Hei Fan's strength was similar to Heavenly Court's Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord was a rank eight Gu Immortal cultivating wisdom path. But when Bo Qing awakened, and his sword lights were sent out over Central Continent, in order to fix Heaven Overseeing Tower, he actually used wisdom path methods. And the effect was even better than ordinary refinement path methods.

This was using wisdom path to achieve the effects of refinement path.

"Oh, endless trouble? What move is this?"

Towards the end, Fang Yuan saw an immortal killer move.

Its core was after Immortal Gu, once the Gu Immortal activated it, they could delay the current calamity or tribulation to the time of the next one, and face them together.

Fang Yuan's heart jumped.

There was Hei Fan's advice left inside the description of this killer move.

This killer move could not be used excessively, even though the calamity or tribulation would be delayed until the next one, it would anger heaven's will, the following calamities or tribulations would increase greatly in strength.

This immortal killer move was created by Hei Fan, but he only used it once and never again.

To warn his descendants, Hei Fan intentionally gave a name like 'Endless Trouble'.

"I can only use it in emergencies, it is not a standard method, but it is definitely something very useful." Fang Yuan was surprised and joyful to have obtained this.

Anger heaven's will?

He could not care less.

Heaven's will was bent on killing him anyway. Fang Yuan's existence was the biggest cause of heaven's will's anger to begin with.

After spending some time, Fang Yuan finally finished reading the contents of the immortal killer moves.

It was very comprehensive, there were even details about the development of an immortal aperture. In fact, there were even details about the mimicking of other paths' effects.

Even though Hei Fan's true inheritance only had these few Immortal Gu.

But by cooperating with mortal Gu and forming countless immortal killer moves, the Gu Immortal could deal with any situation that arises.

This was the norm in the cultivation world.

Even though Hei Fan was strong, he was not even of one of the ten extreme physiques. Thus, he raised very few Gu worms, they were all time path Gu worms, he could support them.

The number of Gu worms was not crucial, the Gu Immortal who uses them was most important.

Hei Fan was the best example.

Even though he only had three Immortal Gu, his use of Gu could unleash incredible effects.

There was no strongest Immortal Gu, only strongest Gu Immortal. This was what the sentence was referring to.

Chapter 1131: Hei Fan's Gu Refinement

"Compared to Hei Fan, even though I have many Immortal Gu, I am unable to use all of them to this extent." Fang Yuan reflected upon himself.

Hei Fan's true inheritance gave him a lot of insight to his problems, but he did not waver: "It is great that I can raise so many Immortal Gu as well."

Gu Immortals placed great focus on their calamities and tribulations. The more they cultivated, the tougher the calamities and tribulations.

Hei Fan had few Immortal Gu, his burden of feeding them was low, but he had many methods to deal with all sorts of situations. He accumulated his resources, even if he sold them, by storing up immortal essence stones, he could have a huge immortal essence stones stockpile.

And Hei Fan had a tribe, a super force with the Huang Jin bloodline. Hei Fan liked to nurture descendants, he had a lot of Immortal Gu that were not too important, before setting up the true inheritance, he had given them out to Hei tribe's Gu Immortals, or placed them into the treasury and passed them down.

Hei Fan did not have one of the ten extreme physiques, his immortal aperture had limited potential, the resources he could grow also had a limit.

All in all, he fed just a few Immortal Gu and researched many killer moves for them, it was a very wise choice.

But Fang Yuan was different.

Different situations needed to be analyzed in depth.

The first difference was his sovereign immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture had immense potential, feeding Gu was a burden, feeding Immortal Gu was a greater burden. But Fang Yuan could afford to do so, easily in fact.

The second difference was that Fang Yuan was alone.

He was alone, he only had to care for himself! He did not need to worry for a tribe, or give any attention to his descendants.

This was the advantage of being a loner.

The advantage of a tribe was shared resources and helping each other. But at Hei Fan's level, he was the one giving the tribe benefits.

But Hei Fan had never thought of leaving the tribe.

He had grown up in this tribal environment, during his growth, he had received a lot of help from the tribe, relationships, friendships, and kinship, he had all of them. He cared about the tribe, and his descendants.

The environment that a person grows up in has a huge influence on them.

And Fang Yuan was free and unrestrained, he had almost zero burden in this aspect. Even though he joined Lang Ya Sect, he was just making use of them.

The third difference was that Fang Yuan had huge pressure in survival.

He needed a lot of Immortal Gu. Immortal Gu were unique, with a greater number of them in all aspects, they could deal with many situations. For example, he could use flying sword Immortal Gu to attack, and sword escape Immortal Gu to retreat.

Even without killer moves, Fang Yuan could use Immortal Gu to deal with many situations.

In fact, having many Immortal Gu was useful and helpful to the construction of immortal killer moves.

Immortal killer moves used core Immortal Gu and supplementary mortal Gu. For example, Fang Yuan's sword marks targeting death, a sword path immortal killer move, used flying sword Immortal Gu as the core, and a small number of supplementary sword path mortal Gu.

If Fang Yuan did not have flying sword Immortal Gu, and only had sword escape Immortal Gu, how would he use Sword Escape in place of Flying Sword to unleash sword marks targeting death?

Sword Escape replacing Flying Sword was possible. Because the two were sword path Immortal Gu, they were interchangeable on this basis.

But the entire killer move, sword marks targeting death, would need to be heavily altered.

Flying Sword was used as an attacking Immortal Gu, it was easy to construct an offensive killer move with it.

But Sword Escape was a movement Immortal Gu, if it were to replace Flying Sword, the mortal Gu used for sword marks targeting death would need to be changed, and increased drastically in number. This way, when using sword marks targeting death, the process would be more lengthy and difficult, the failure rate would be higher, and it would have less feasibility as a whole.

Looking at it overall, Hei Fan's development method suited most people, but it did not suit Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's Gu raising method was the most optimal for himself. But if other Gu Immortals mimicked him, they would be courting death.

Fang Yuan continued to read.

After the immortal killer moves, Hei Fan's true inheritance talked about mortal killer moves.

There was an even greater number of these killer moves, a large portion of them were time path, but Fang Yuan basically had no need for them anymore.

Immortal and mortal was vastly different. Maybe in the future, Fang Yuan could use these methods to probe other Gu Immortals in battle, but they had little use, because Fang Yuan already had a good number of exemplary mortal killer moves.

He already had numerous blood path and strength path killer moves.

These mortal killer moves might only have one use in the end, to be the foundation for deductions.

After the mortal killer moves, there were some incomplete killer moves, including both immortal and mortal killer moves.

The completion rate varied, some were even simply inspired ideas or guesses.

These were things that Hei Fan had never completed even upon his death.

Deducing killer moves was unavoidable and essential in a Gu Immortal's cultivation journey.

Fang Yuan took a look, nothing really caught his eye.

His time path attainment level was too low, and he could not use wisdom Gu. Furthermore, Fang Yuan already had many useful methods, they were sufficient.

As a result, his browsing of killer moves ended.

"After returning, I will need to spend a lot of time practising these killer moves." Fang Yuan planned.

The usage of killer moves could end in failure.

If during an intense battle, the activation fails, the Gu Immortal would suffer a backlash. If it was during a critical moment in battle, that would be terrible. One killer move's success or failure could directly affect the outcome of the battle, or even determine life and death itself.

Thus, one had to be extremely familiar and proficient with their killer moves!

This would use some funds as well.

The supplementary mortal Gu that made up the killer moves needed to be purchased. When practising, activating immortal killer moves would expend immortal essence. And practising would definitely occur more than once.

All of these required money, money, money!

Thus, the development of a Gu Immortal's immortal aperture was extremely important in their cultivation.

Finances were the foundation for military might.

Fighting was dangerous, and with the threat of calamities and tribulations, unless huge benefits or conflicts were involved, Gu Immortals usually preferred to live in peace instead.

"To practise so many killer moves, I need a lot of funds." Fang Yuan frowned, he felt both joy and worry.

Of course, this was simply a blissful worry.

Large numbers of immortal killer moves, even more mortal killer moves and incomplete killer moves. After looking at them, Fang Yuan moved onto Gu recipes.

Immortal Gu recipes!

Among which, the first was the parallel refinement method of immortal level year Gu.

There were quite a few parallel refinement Gu recipes.

There were a total of five, they could achieve parallel refinement and elevate year Gu.

At the back, Hei Fan even noted his experiences, he talked about the advantages and disadvantages of all five methods, and some tips when undergoing parallel refinement. Just the methods recorded here was incredibly insightful for Fang Yuan.

Out of the five parallel refinement Immortal Gu recipes, the one Hei Fan used the most was the final one.

This Immortal Gu recipe was created by Hei Fan in his later years. It used the least ingredients and had the highest success rate, it expended the least amount of time and mental energy as well. Overall, it used a large number of mortal level year Gu and added them into the immortal level year Gu, thus the effect was great.

After developing this, Hei Fan almost abandoned the first four Gu recipes, he used this parallel refinement method solely.

But because of the comprehensive nature of Hei Fan's true inheritance, he recorded the four recipes into it regardless.

"Rank eight Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water can produce countless mortal year Gu, these year Gu can be used to parallel refine immortal level year Gu, it is so convenient."

Fang Yuan sighed as he continued looking.

Next was the Immortal Gu recipe of refining after Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan already had this Immortal Gu, he only took one glance at it.

Overall, the number of Immortal Gu recipes was quite shocking.

There were nearly a hundred!

And all of them were fully completed Immortal Gu recipes.

Most were rank six, some were rank seven, and there were only two or three rank eight Immortal Gu recipes.

In terms of path, most were time path, but there were also other paths like fire path and luck path.

Compared to the immortal killer moves, these Immortal Gu recipes were more disorganized. There were recently created Immortal Gu recipes, there were also ancient recipes with extinct immortal materials, they could not be used anymore.

Among all of the Immortal Gu recipes, Hei Fan placed the greatest emphasis on Years Flow Like Water.

The rank eight Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water was actually the creation of Hei Fan!

His inspiration was obtained by constantly parallel refining year Gu.

Hei Fan had described the entire process of refining Years Flow Like Water in great detail. In order to get enough immortal materials, he had expended the entire Hei tribe treasury, and used up a lot of favors and paid a huge price to ask two refinement path great experts to help. In the end, he was still in a lot of debt.

To refine Years Flow Like Water, Hei Fan had placed all of his effort into it. During the refinement process, he had suffered failure after failure, there was several times he wanted to give up.

Hei Fan had recorded all of these mental states down, he was not afraid of his descendants laughing at him. This showed that Hei Fan had truly put his heart and soul into creating this true inheritance.

In the end, because of his relatively good luck, after nine failures, he finally succeeded.

In his words, all of the difficulties and risks that Hei Fan faced when refining the rank eight Immortal Gu was expressed in detail.

Even after succeeding, Hei Fan did not recoup his losses for many years to come.

He solemnly warned his inheritor to treasure the fruits of his predecessor's hard work greatly. If they cultivate to rank eight in the future, when refining rank eight Immortal Gu, they had to be extremely careful.

Fang Yuan saw this and thought of Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Right now, this old fellow was also refining a rank eight Immortal Gu.

And this Immortal Gu was extremely precious, it was fortune rivalling heaven Gu! According to what Lang Ya land spirit said, this Immortal Gu was created in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's later years using the essence of luck path.

Refining rank eight was a huge gamble.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu had Ma Hong Yun as the main ingredient, it saved him a lot of costs. But even so, when gathering immortal materials, he had discarded his reputation, he went personally to Zombie Alliance to steal immortal zombie corpses, he even went to Hei tribe's treasury and looted it. The entire Snowy Mountain blessed land was in chaos because of his actions, everyone was worried.

Yao Huang was also trying to refine resurrection from the dead Immortal Gu. According to the rumors in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, this Immortal Gu was also rank eight.

Actually, everyone knew about the risks of refining a rank eight Immortal Gu.

But why did they still try?

As a matter of fact, having a rank eight Immortal Gu and not having one meant two completely different states.

Rank eight Gu Immortals had to undergo tribulations as well, they usually had low lifespan, many times, they had no choice but to take a risk.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was doing this for his tribulation, while Yao Huang was trying to prolong his life. Calamities and tribulations could not hinder Hei Fan, but he had limited lifespan, he eventually died.

"Tribulations and lifespan." Fang Yuan knew that in his quest for eternal life, he had to get through these two tough problems.

Chapter 1132: Taking Over Hei Fan Grotto-Heaven

After the Immortal Gu recipes, there were mortal Gu recipes.

There were many mortal Gu recipes, Fang Yuan felt a little shocked seeing all of them.

The ones worth looking at were the mortal Gu recipes of day, month, and year Gu.

In accordance with these mortal Gu recipes, Fang Yuan could buy his mortal materials and refine his own mortal level day Gu, month Gu, and year Gu.

"This way, not only can I buy these mortal Gu in treasure yellow heaven, I can also refine them myself. This would no doubt greatly reduce my preparation. But it is a waste for me to do the refinement myself, I should ask the hairy men in Lang Ya Sect to do it."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan frowned uncontrollably.

His relationship with Lang Ya Sect had already turned cold, he would need to improve their relationship if he were to ask them for help.

Forget about these for now, Fang Yuan continued to look at Hei Fan's true inheritance.

After Immortal Gu recipes and mortal Gu recipes, there were some incomplete Gu recipes.

They had varying completion rates, some were ninety percent, stuck at a crucial step. Some were at ten to twenty percent, they were at the initial stages of creation.

"Immortal Gu 'Before'?" Fang Yuan's gaze halted.

Among the incomplete Immortal Gu recipes, the before Immortal Gu recipe was only fifty-seven percent complete.

Before Immortal Gu, after Immortal Gu, they were related Immortal Gu.

Evidently, in Hei Fan's lifetime, after obtaining after Immortal Gu, he had greatly desired before Immortal Gu.

Unfortunately, even until his death, he did not succeed.

Next was Hei Fan's recorded experiences in deducing these Gu recipes. He talked about the difficulties of deduction, he told his inheritor not to be afraid of difficulty and to persevere. At the same time, he talked about the importance of inspiration.

Thus, behind this, Hei Fan wrote about some tricks and tips. Like using wisdom path inspiration Gu, and light path a flash of inspiration Gu, to help him with the deduction.

Looking at this, Fang Yuan smiled.

He was a wisdom path grandmaster, he had obtained Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path true inheritance, he dominated Hei Fan in this aspect. Hei Fan's experiences in this aspect were quite shallow from Fang Yuan's perspective.

Everyone had their own field of expertise, even though Hei Fan was skilled, he had his weak points too.

Like how Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable looked to Long Hair Ancestor for help to refine Immortal Gu.

After killer moves and Gu recipes, there were Hei Fan's own cultivation experiences.

Among this, there were maps, including the five regions and even white heaven and black heaven, they had huge value in terms of reference.

Of course, Northern Plains' map was the most detailed, the other four regions were more simple.

Fang Yuan placed the most attention on the maps of white heaven and black heaven, this had broadened his horizons.

Some strong rank seven Gu Immortals and all rank eight Gu Immortals would often explore black heaven and white heaven, scavenging for resources within.

As an expert among rank eights, Hei Fan was no exception.

After the maps, there were lots of secrets regarding the Gu Immortal world.

Like Imperial Court blessed land and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there was the most information about these. But they were useless now.

And Hei Fan's own conjectures.

What attracted Fang Yuan the most was one of them.

Hei Fan was suspicious that a time path Gu Immortal had inherited Red Lotus' true inheritance.

From this record, Fang Yuan could sense that Hei Fan had a huge desire towards Red Lotus' true inheritance.

This was expected.

He was a time path great expert, he naturally sought out and looked up to the number one time path true inheritance in the world.

The final important point was Hei Fan's own ideas and experimentation on the development of an immortal aperture.

Using his own situation as an example, he clearly stated how calamities and tribulations, dao marks, and immortal aperture helped each other in an intrinsic relationship, and how to modify the immortal aperture's environment, like how to alter the rate of time inside. There was also the management of the immortal aperture, and the selling of resources. The important point here was year Gu.

Back then, after Hei Fan refined rank eight Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water, he started selling mortal level year Gu, it became his most lucrative business.

In just a few months, he became the biggest year Gu vendor in the world, he was earning huge profits.

With this rank eight Immortal Gu, he had an unceasing gold mine!

However, Hei Fan had also stated the possibility of the attack of year beasts. How to deal with the year beast attacks, how to capture year beasts, how to dissect year beasts, and how to sell year beasts. There was also the relationship between year beasts and the immortal aperture and others.

Fang Yuan looked on with a frown.

In Hei Fan's immortal aperture, because of Years Flow Like Water, immemorial level year beasts had once went in.

They had rank eight battle strength!

Hei Fan spent a lot of effort in killing them. Because he fought in his immortal aperture, the result was immense losses. Many times, Hei Fan felt pain due to his losses.

After a painful lesson, Hei Fan started to research on how to seal Years Flow Like Water, and conceal its aura when not using it.

He found and invented many methods, that were all recorded in the true inheritance.

He had made great achievements.

However, Hei Fan warned the inheritor to be careful on something, that was to use Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water carefully when in battle.

Once they fought against a strong foe and lured an immemorial year beast over to attack their immortal aperture, they would be in deep trouble.

"It seems that I need to be very careful when using Years Flow Like Water. If I am careless and heaven's will uses this opportunity to lure immemorial year beasts to me, I would die!"

Fang Yuan was only rank six, he could not fight against a rank eight level existence.

With a huge difference in strength, there would be no unexpected lucky circumstances that could save him.

His consciousness returned from the mortal letter Gu, Fang Yuan let out a breath.

"Hei Fan's true inheritance is truly the work of a time path great expert, he lives up to his name!" Fang Yuan praised: "But the difficulty to inherit this is too high."

Precisely because of the difficulty, Hei tribe's descendants worked hard but did not succeed. In the end, Fang Yuan took advantage of it and obtained the fruits of his labor.

Don't look at how easy of a time Fang Yuan had, it had many preconditions. Like attitude Gu and familiar face, he even had Chu Du's help to obtain the heavenly crystal eagle nest.

"However, according to the logic of the Gu Immortal world, the inheritances left behind by people of Hei Fan's level are usually this difficult."

For example, Nian Er tribe's Nian Er Sword Saint true inheritance. An inheritor would only appear every few hundred years, the current one was Nian Er Ping Zhi.

Hei Fan and Nian Er Sword Saint were people who left their names in history, they were prideful people, they were unwilling to have their inheritances obtained by useless people that would tarnish their reputation, they set difficult requirements to choose a worthy successor, it was normal.

"Next, I have to take over this Hei Fan grotto-heaven." Fang Yuan looked at the brass bell heavenly spirit, signalling to it.

At the next moment, the brass bell heavenly spirit slowly flew towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled.

When he inherited Hei Fan's true inheritance, he became the owner of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he could naturally command this brass bell heavenly spirit.

The regretful thing was, Hei Fan grotto-heaven had absorbed the immemorial azure heaven fragment, it made the brass bell heavenly spirit mindless and unresponsive, Fang Yuan could not manipulate it easily, it was hard to communicate, it was worse than Hu Immortal land spirit.

Fang Yuan first looked at Immortal Succession Mountain.

This mountain had many pavilions on it. Each one had an inheritance in it. Some of the inheritances were mortal level, while some were left by Gu Immortals.

The Gu Immortals originally in Hei Fan grotto-heaven had ascended Immortal Succession Mountain when they were mortals, after getting the inheritances, they slowly cultivated their way up.

Unfortunately, their generations of development were in vain, Fang Yuan killed all of them on this day.

Fang Yuan inspected and realized that Immortal Succession Mountain had a few inheritances left. Most of the stone pavilions were empty already.

He kept all of these inheritances.

He was the owner of the grotto-heaven now, everything inside was his. These inheritances were no different.

However, these inheritances were mostly mortal inheritances, there were only three Gu Immortal inheritances. Among which, two of them did not have any Immortal Gu, but they had a few Immortal Gu recipes. The last Gu Immortal inheritance had one Immortal Gu left, it was called Bone Spike, it was a bone path offensive Gu worm.

After ransacking Immortal Succession Mountain, Fang Yuan looked at the huge world in this place.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven had countless resources, the map in the true inheritance had talked about Hei Fan grotto-heaven's resource distribution, but after so many years, and after nurturing so many Gu Immortals, the resource map was no longer applicable to its current state.

And the brass bell heavenly spirit could not communicate.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan had captives.

Even though he killed all of the Gu Immortals, he had preserved their souls, right now, all of them were locked up in his immortal aperture.

Soul search.

A while later, Fang Yuan knew Hei Fan grotto-heaven like the back of his hand. Other than a few areas that ancient desolate beasts and ancient desolate plants were living in, there were some forbidden grounds.

These Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven were locals, after tens of generations, how could they know nothing about Hei Fan grotto-heaven?

In the process of soul searching, Fang Yuan also learned about the inheritances and cultivation experiences of these Gu Immortals.

"Blood light spirit suppression? Hehe, heaven's will..."

Fang Yuan inspected Zheng Tuo, Zhou Min, and Feng Jun's souls, he realized their scheme.

Fang Yuan was glad that he struck quickly, otherwise, if he waited, these three immortals might have actually succeeded.

Chu Du snatched the heavenly crystal eagle nest away, while Fang Yuan had attitude Gu and familiar face, heaven's will knew about all these.

Most importantly, Hei Fan grotto-heaven had absorbed a piece of an immemorial azure heaven fragment, heaven's will could look into the grotto-heaven.

The immortal killer move blood light spirit suppression that Feng Jun had suddenly created was quite suspicious. Fang Yuan assumed that this was likely heaven's will's influence!

Thankfully, Fang Yuan took action after getting the heavenly crystal eagle nest, he went to obtain Hei Fan true inheritance in the shortest time possible.

"I have to move away all of the resources inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, and put them in my immortal aperture. This place is not safe!"

"As for Hei Fan grotto-heaven, I will give it to Chu Du. The value of the grotto-heaven itself is already thirty percent of Hei Fan true inheritance's value."

As for what heaven's will would do to Chu Du, Fang Yuan could not care less.

He had already given the method of self will Gu to Chu Du, he did not have to worry about heaven's will influencing Chu Du's thoughts.

In the next few days, Fang Yuan went through a thorough inspection.

The entire distribution of living habitats, the cooperation and co-existence between resources, some complemented each other while others restrained each other, these were all precious knowledge that Fang Yuan could learn in order to manage his own immortal aperture.

He was lacking in this aspect.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, he had low aptitude, blood path Gu Immortals were skilled in fighting, but were not good in immortal aperture management. Especially large immortal apertures, Fang Yuan had no experience in managing them. Not to mention the sovereign immortal aperture.

Right now, Hei Fan grotto-heaven was like an encyclopedia placed in front of him!

Chapter 1133: Ransacking the Entire Grotto-heaven

In the next few days, Fang Yuan went around almost the entirety of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

His consciousness was covering the surroundings, observing as he researched.

Sometimes, Fang Yuan felt that it was as if Hei Fan was teaching him personally across time and space.

There was an incredibly detailed explanation in Hei Fan's true inheritance, the Hei Fan grotto-heaven in front of him was a real life example, he could interact with and excavate information from it, he could also observe it. If there were any differences, Fang Yuan would soul search those captive Gu Immortals, this made him understand the process and secrets of the prosperity and dwindling of species in a long span of time.

Hei Fan's talent made Fang Yuan feel deep admiration, he had benefited greatly from it. Regarding the development of the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan now had many new bold ideas.

When Fang Yuan was certain that he had already understood the structure of the entirety of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he started to move resources.

First were the heavenly crystals.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven's first forbidden ground was the heavenly crystal storage pool.

This pool was built in the sky, it covered an enormous area, and was surrounded in layers of Gu formations. But the heavenly crystals only occupied the small area at the center.

The heavenly crystals produced in Hei Fan grotto-heaven were light azure in color.

Heavenly crystals had different colors depends on where they were produced.

Fang Yuan placed this storage pool into Mini Azure Heaven.

"It is a pity that this storage pool can only produce heavenly crystals in a grotto-heaven. My sovereign immortal aperture is only a blessed land, it cannot do anything inside here. However, the light azure heavenly crystals in the storage pool and that heavenly crystal eagle nest should last five to six years for me."

Fang Yuan assessed, with the addition of these crystals, he would have no problems in feeding the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

Heavenly crystals were not easy to buy in treasure yellow heaven.

The second forbidden area was underground.

This was a huge cave.

There was stalactites growing in the cave, the most valuable one were the hibiscus stalactites, it was rare in the outside world, but a lot were growing here.

Fang Yuan spent some effort, digging out the entire cave and transplanting it into Mini Southern Border.

Thankfully, he had pulling mountain Immortal Gu, otherwise, this second forbidden area would be hard to deal with.

"But after I do this, when the stalactites grow, they would need to absorb the earth qi inside the sovereign immortal aperture, it would increase the sovereign immortal aperture's earth qi expenditure. Once in a while, I will need to place down the immortal aperture and replenish earth qi."

Other than these natural resources, there were ancient desolate beasts and ancient desolate plants.

Among the ancient desolate plants, there was one walking meat tree.

This tree was a rare strength path plant, it usually grew in black heaven.

In order to cultivate it, Hei Fan specially enclosed a portion of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, creating a condition of darkness.

Around the walking meat tree, Hei Fan specially created a habitat that suited its growth.

The walking meat tree's branches were very peculiar, they were like soft and thick octopus tentacles. With a light whip, they could send desolate beasts flying.

Fang Yuan had once seen one in Starry Sky grotto-heaven, this was his second encounter, he sighed.

He had once wished he could get a walking meat tree, because he could use eat strength Immortal Gu to increase his strength path dao marks. But now, he had the walking meat tree, but eat strength Immortal Gu was destroyed, it was truly untimely.

Fang Yuan placed the walking meat tree into Mini Black Heaven within the sovereign immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture's advantage was starting to show. Hei Fan had to make meticulous arrangements to plant the walking meat tree. Fang Yuan did not need to do this, because Mini Black Heaven's environment was close to the real immemorial black heaven, the walking meat tree was very pleased after the relocation, it stretched out its branches comfortably.

Because Hei Fan had specialized methods, Fang Yuan had an easy time relocating these ancient desolate plants.

The same went for the other desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts living in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Using methods in Hei Fan's true inheritance, Fang Yuan could lure these desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts into his immortal aperture with no trouble.

What was worth mentioning was that among the ancient desolate beasts in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, there were three remnant heavenly dogs.

Unfortunately, Fang Yuan needed dog desolate beasts, not ancient desolate beasts. He needed their faeces to feed the rank six dog shit luck Immortal Gu.

But these three remnant heavenly dogs were not useless.

In the future, if Fang Yuan raised dog shit luck Immortal Gu to rank seven, its food would change drastically. At that time, the remnant heavenly dog's faeces would be useful.

Fang Yuan's relocation was very efficient, in the entire process, the brass bell heavenly spirit followed beside him.

Fang Yuan was the grotto-heaven's owner, the heavenly spirit would cooperate with everything he did without resistance.

After half a month, Fang Yuan finally emptied Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Even the empty Immortal Succession Mountain was not left alone, Fang Yuan moved it into Mini Southern Border.

Originally, there were large numbers of Gu Masters and mortals living in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

They were all the descendants of Hei tribe's criminal immortals.

Fang Yuan killed all of them, collecting their souls, planning to feed them to Dang Hun Mountain.

What made Fang Yuan feel slight regret was, Hei Fan grotto-heaven did not have any variant humans.

When grotto-heavens or blessed lands reach a certain stage, the Gu Immortals would start rearing variant humans inside. Even though Hei Fan could do this, he did not.

Even though there were no variant humans, and most of the common cultivation resources were expended by the Gu Immortals inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan still had immense gains!

All of the resources in Hei Fan grotto-heaven were placed into the sovereign immortal aperture, from a desolate state, it was starting to gain life.

"This is a huge breakthrough!"

"If I were to work at it myself, to get the sovereign immortal aperture to this stage of development, I would need six hundred years! And that is the best case scenario. Now after taking in Hei Fan grotto-heaven's resources, I have directly reached this stage."

Hei Fan grotto-heaven had existed for a long time, it had accumulated a great amount of resources! After all, this was the accumulation of a rank eight Gu Immortal's wealth.

Even though a lot was used up, and it was not at its prime, Fang Yuan still benefited greatly.

For example, the sovereign immortal aperture previously was like a pauper, even the Immortal Gu were starving. But now, he had inherited the wealth of a billionaire, he turned into a billionaire instantly!

"Now, the resources inside the sovereign immortal aperture definitely surpasses most rank seven Gu Immortals in terms of value! Even by the standards of rank eight Gu Immortals, I might barely be able to reach them."

"Of course, a lot of the resources have just been moved into the sovereign immortal aperture, with a change in environment and a fall in time path dao marks, their production would greatly reduce, they might even wither and die."

"The beasts and plants need to adapt to the new environment, and my sovereign immortal aperture also needs to assimilate them slowly."

"Among which, I can't use some of the resources, I should sell them and exchange for the things I need."

Moving all of the resources was just the start.

Next, Fang Yuan was going to get busy with his development and management.

A few days later, Fang Yuan brought Chu Du into Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

"After getting your letter, I came here immediately. This is Hei Fan grotto-heaven? Hm, why is it so barren?" Chu Du had just arrived in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he looked around with a surprised and disappointed look.

There was almost nothing in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Even the grasslands were dug up by Fang Yuan, it was literally empty. There were no trees as well, of course.

And the rivers and pools were all moved into the sovereign immortal aperture using pulling water Immortal Gu as well.

The scenic Hei Fan grotto-heaven had become desolate as ever, when winds blew, sand flew into the air, it was a dismal sight.

Chu Du looked at Fang Yuan with a flickering gaze.

His expression seemed to be saying: Brother, isn't your appetite too big? I rushed here to see this?

Fang Yuan smiled, pointing at the sky: "Brother Chu, according to our alliance agreement, I will pay you thirty percent of my gains. Hei Fan grotto-heaven is yours now."

Chu Du heard this and his expression changed, he looked at Fang Yuan in shock: "Are you serious?"

"Of course." Fang Yuan nodded.

Chu Du was greatly enticed!

Even though the resources inside the grotto-heaven were taken by Fang Yuan, this was still a grotto-heaven!

Resources and grotto-heaven were like eggs and the chicken respectively.

Fang Yuan took the eggs, he left the chicken to Chu Du.

Chu Du squinted, his eyes were flickering with sharp light.

He could not reject it!

The reason?

Because controlling this grotto-heaven was an immense help to Chu Du's cultivation.

Even though Chu Du also had an immortal aperture, it was only a blessed land, be it time path or space path resources, they could not compare to a grotto-heaven. And this was Hei Fan's grotto-heaven!

Chu Du's blessed land also had lots of cultivation resources, But it was not safe to place his resources there.

Because of calamities and tribulations.

Calamities and tribulations would destroy the immortal aperture's resources when targeting the Gu Immortals as well.

Chu Du had rank seven cultivation level, he had passed many calamities and tribulations, he knew the trouble and pain of getting his resources destroyed by calamities and tribulations.

He did not have the Great Strength True Martial Physique, his blessed land's space was limited. It was unlike Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, it was too big, even after taking in Hei Fan's resources, there was still a lot of space left. Fang Yuan could freely choose a place inside it with no resources to undergo his tribulation, but Chu Du could not.

"Hei Fan grotto-heaven has no calamities and tribulations, because this immortal aperture has absorbed a fragment of immemorial azure heaven. I can place my resources inside here, of course, there are few strength path dao marks here, I will need to decide this carefully in the future." Chu Du assessed.

"Liu Guan Yi handed over Hei Fan grotto-heaven to me, other than completing our agreement, it is also because this grotto-heaven itself is a problem."

Chu Du was not stupid, he quickly realized: He had taken the heavenly crystal eagle nest, everyone knew that Hei Fan true inheritance was in his hands.

In truth, the one who obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance was Fang Yuan. Except that he was in the background, while Chu Du occupied the grotto-heaven. If anything happened in the future, Fang Yuan would not be in trouble, but Chu Du would.

"Even if Heavenly Lord Bai Zu attacks, I will take over Hei Fan grotto-heaven. How can I, the great Domination Immortal, be afraid of a small risk?"

Thinking of this, Chu Du spoke, agreeing.

"Good, as expected of the Domination Immortal!" Fang Yuan clapped, praising.

But next, when handing over Hei Fan grotto-heaven, there was a tiny problem.

The brass bell heavenly spirit was unwilling to.

It was because Chu Du did not have Hei tribe's bloodline.

"Ignorant thing." Fang Yuan smiled sinisterly, destroying the defenseless brass bell heavenly spirit with one hit.

The problem was immediately solved!

Chapter 1134: Battling Falling Star Hound

After the transaction, Hei Fan grotto-heaven changed owners.

Even though Chu Du asked him to stay, Fang Yuan was insistent on leaving.

He had stayed in Hei Fan grotto-heaven for too long, Fang Yuan had to start preparing for his fourth earthly calamity.

Of course, before leaving, he used the immortal killer move hundred years harmony to create a new alliance agreement with Chu Du.

Fang Yuan left quickly, Chu Du was left behind, feeling a huge headache looking at the barren Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Traveling back, he returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

"Oh, look, Fang Yuan is back." A hairy man Gu Immortal who was inside Lang Ya blessed land saw Fang Yuan who was flying in the sky.

"Does it matter if he is back?"

"That's right, there is no difference if Lang Ya Sect has him or not."

"He is a human Gu Immortal after all, he is not one of us."

"Ignore him, let's continue planning on how to take down that falling star hound!"

Soon, these hairy man Gu Immortals lowered their heads, continuing to discuss their tactic.

Fang Yuan looked down, his gaze sweeping past these hairy man Gu Immortals. Even though they were far away, Fang Yuan had investigative methods, he heard what they were saying.

At once, Fang Yuan's gaze turned eerie.

He had spent a lot of time searching for Hei Fan's true inheritance, the fourth earthly calamity was close.

Fang Yuan was planning to undergo this earthly calamity himself.

Even though getting Chu Du's help was safer, Reckless Savage's true meaning would also be split.

Fang Yuan would definitely want to take the benefits for himself if possible! Only when he is unable to do so would he think of other ways.

And just now, he obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, his strength rose greatly, he was confident in dealing with the fourth earthly calamity alone!

"But to undergo tribulation, I need Lang Ya Sect's immortal tribulation tempering aperture, I will need to borrow Immortal Gu and mortal Gu from Lang Ya land spirit."

"With my current relationship with Lang Ya land spirit, he will not lend it to me, unless I provide a huge gain like selling Dang Hun Mountain."

"Looking at it, I should use my remaining time to complete that sect mission of taking down the falling star hound. Firstly, it can improve our relationship, secondly, I can gain a lot of sect contribution points, to pay for borrowing Gu."

Fang Yuan did not return to his cloud city, he flew straight to the first cloud city.

There, he met with Lang Ya land spirit.

"Oh, you still remembered to come back?" Lang Ya land spirit did not speak in a pleasant tone, he had a cold attitude.

Fang Yuan sighed, he showed a bitter expression: "Please understand, first supreme elder, I had my reasons. Earlier, I was not ignoring it, I simply had no time or effort. After going out this time, I resolved my crisis. The moment I returned, I heard the supreme elders taking about taking down the falling star hound, I rushed here to get this mission from you, first supreme elder, at the first moment."

"Oh?" Lang Ya land spirit heard this and stopped frowning: "This means you are going to do it?"

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly again: "I have been wanting to accept the mission, I am a member of Lang Ya Sect after all. But the circumstances did not allow me to, I had no choice. Now that I can spare the effort, I want to do something for the sect."

His acting skills with attitude Gu immediately took effect, Lang Ya land spirit felt that Fang Yuan was speaking the truth, he was sincere and apologetic.

Lang Ya land spirit's expression soothed, he was about to agree, but he quickly changed his words: "It will be troublesome if you want to accept this mission. Earlier, Twelfth Hair and the rest have already coordinated, they are going to strike. Last time, even though they failed, they had gained great experience, both sides had suffered a loss. They are likely going to succeed now. If you want to take this mission, regardless of whether you succeed, you will conflict with them first."

Fang Yuan was only an outsider, Twelfth Hair and the rest were true hairy man Gu Immortals, they were part of the hairy men.

Lang Ya land spirit naturally would side with Twelfth Hair and the rest.

Fang Yuan nodded: "So that's it. How about this, let them take the mission first, if they cannot complete it, I will help out, is that okay?"

Lang Ya land spirit thought about it, nodding: "Okay."

Fang Yuan said again: "I hope first supreme elder can announce this."

Lang Ya land spirit did as he said.

Once he announced it, there was a commotion in Lang Ya Sect.

"That Fang Yuan is finally going to fight?"

"Hmph, he sees that we are succeeding, so he wants to attempt it."

"Despicable scoundrel!"

"Disregarding the fact that he is despicable, the reward for taking down the falling star hound has risen to over a thousand! Whoever completes it will gain the greatest benefit."

"Oh Twelfth, you must succeed, don't let that Fang Yuan take advantage!"

The hairy man Gu Immortals had mutual animosity towards him.

Twelfth Hair nodded, subconsciously clenching his fists, thinking: "I must succeed, we prepared amply, I will not let everyone down!"

His previous fight gave the hairy men lots of confidence.

Twelfth Hair was prepared to attack in two days' time. But because of this matter, he decided to be more safe, and prepare himself better.

Seven days later, Fang Yuan received notification that Twelfth Hair and the rest were about to attack.

He went uninvited, gathering with Twelfth Hair and the rest.

"Elder Fang Yuan." Sixth Hair went ahead and spoke to Fang Yuan in a strange tone.

His true identity was Shadow Sect's spy, but even if Fang Yuan exposed him, nobody would believe it. Because he had made a deal with Fang Yuan, they were in the same boat, he was fearless.

Last time, he was ordered to represent Ying Wu Xie in transacting with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had the upper hand, he had suffered immensely.

Fang Yuan did not go and challenge the falling star hound, Sixth Hair managed to stir up the hairy men and direct their attention to it, causing their relationship with Fang Yuan to worsen.

"Elder Fang Yuan, I know why you are here, but this time, you will be disappointed." Twelfth Hair walked forward, puffing his chest, he was filled with confidence.

He spoke in a normal tone, he was frank and upright unlike the underhanded Sixth Hair.

Fang Yuan looked at Twelfth Hair, he saw that this hairy man Gu Immortal had evidently changed. He was more confident and secure than before.

Fang Yuan assessed: "Twelfth Hair cultivates refinement path along with enslavement path. This time, to deal with the falling star hound, he had been the leader. He was heavily injured before and had to rest in bed for some time. After these obstacles, he has improved drastically, his mental state has also become much more developed."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan smiled as he replied: "Then I will await brother Twelfth's victory."

"Hmph, hypocrite."

"He seems to have given up on the surface, but he must be anxious on the inside right? Hehe."

The other hairy man Gu Immortals could not stand Fang Yuan's words, they were muttering.

Fang Yuan heard their words and ignored it.

The group was standing in the center of the main formation.

The hairy men were standing close together, Fang Yuan was the only outcast.

"Stay alert, I am about to activate the Gu formation." Twelfth Hair said, he took a glance at Fang Yuan: With one more person, the immortal essence expenditure is definitely going to be higher.

The hairy man Gu Immortals had calm expressions, they had already used this teleportation Gu formation many times, they were used to it.

The Gu formation gradually activated, it gave off dazzling lights.

Fang Yuan watched silently.

The teleportation sub formation in Tai Qiu was placed by him, Fang Yuan had returned to Lang Ya blessed land using the teleportation Gu formation.

When he used it alone, it was easy, but he could see that these hairy man Gu Immortals had much more trouble in activating it.

Twelfth Hair continued to expend immortal essence, after a long while, the Gu formation finally activated.

Dazzling lights blinded everyone's vision, with a huge mystical force, it reacted!

In the blink of an eye, the immortals looked around and realized they were in Tai Qiu.

Fang Yuan turned around, the huge elephant corpse was indeed behind him.

"The immortal essence expenditure did not increase by a lot, it seems that Fang Yuan does not have a deep dao mark foundation. He is probably more experienced than us in battle techniques only." Twelfth Hair glanced at Fang Yuan, showing some disdain in his gaze.

"We can only win this time, we cannot lose! Let's go!" Twelfth Hair waved, shouting loudly.

The hairy man Gu Immortals responded, they had high morale.

They started their journey, Fang Yuan tailed behind them. In order to not cause conflicts, Fang Yuan purposely stayed behind, not getting close to these hairy man Gu Immortals.

Before they advanced by a lot, Fang Yuan found his target.

"A falling star hound that has not reached maturity?" Fang Yuan was slightly surprised, he saw that the hairy man Gu Immortals were charging towards it.

"Dog, we will definitely beat you!" Twelfth Hair shouted loudly, battle intent surging in him.

The falling star hound howled, it lowered his body as its hill-like body burst forward with incredible speed.

The hairy man Gu Immortals were scattered by this attack.

Twelfth Hair was in a very difficult state, he shouted in anger: "Beast, you dare to sneak attack us! Come, let's battle for three hundred rounds."

Saying this, Twelfth Hair clapped his hands as a blue light expanded from his hands, forming a blue lake in the sky.

From the lake, water spewed out, as three desolate beasts came out from the bottom of the lake.

One yak, one tiger, and one bear.

It was a chestnut yak, a golden-white tiger, and a diamond bear.

The three desolate beasts went towards the falling star hound, engaging in an intense battle on the giant grass.

This was a deep area of Tai Qiu, the giant grass was extremely tall, even the falling star hound and diamond bear was not as tall as the strands of giant grass.

Twelfth Hair controlled the three desolate beasts, drawing the falling star hound's attention. The other hairy man Gu Immortals were hiding in the giant grass, attacking the falling star hound from a distance.

Fang Yuan watched from an even greater distance.

He could evidently see many traces of intense battle in this battlefield.

The hairy man Gu Immortals' performance was quite impressive. They were skillful and had improved from earlier. Even though it was still quite bad, their improvement was very apparent.

The falling star hound had not reached maturity, but it could fight with these hairy man Gu Immortals evenly.

Fang Yuan smiled, looking at the sky.

He thought to himself: "I am here, heaven's will, how will you deal with me this time?"

Chapter 1135: Don't Be A Disturbance

Boom!

With a loud boom, the falling star hound crashed into the diamond bear.

The diamond bear was only a desolate beast, but it had a robust body, it blocked the falling star hound like a wall.

It was hit by the falling star hound, it moved back five or six steps, but it still stood firmly. The falling star hound moved back by a huge step, its head was spinning.

It shook his head, clearing its mind.

During this period of time, five or six killer moves shot out from the giant grass, impacting on the falling star hound's body.

The falling star hound cried out in pain, its flesh was cut open from the attacks.

Fang Yuan watched coldly from the side.

"It seems that not just Twelfth Hair, the other hairy man Gu Immortals have also learned to use their immortal killer moves."

"But these immortal killer moves mostly only have one core Immortal Gu, they are at rank six level."

After the falling star hound was attacked for a long time, even though its flesh was torn open, it was only lightly injured.

It was an ancient desolate beast, even as an infant which had not reached maturity, it still had incredible defense and recovery abilities.

"I cannot fail this time, Fang Yuan will see me as a joke!" Twelfth Hair concentrated, he was filled with unprecedented determination.

The three desolate beasts seemed to be able to sense their master's feelings, they were filled with battle intent.

Under Twelfth Hair's manipulation, the diamond bear with the sturdiest body resisted attacks, while the golden-white tiger assisted it. As for the chestnut yak, even though it was very weak, it could cause some interferences on the side.

"Twelfth Hair is directing the desolate beasts, he seems to be having an easy time. But this situation is quite stagnant, the falling star hound is attacking fiercely, he has not sent out a fourth desolate beast yet. I am afraid he only has three desolate beasts after all."

Fang Yuan calmly analyzed.

He even had to use a desolate beast like the chestnut yak, Fang Yuan's guess was very likely to be true.

"After treasure yellow heaven opened, Twelfth Hair bought a diamond bear and a golden-white tiger. But his choice is quite questionable, the diamond bear itself is sufficient. Golden-white tiger is a metal path desolate beast with strong defenses as well, he might as well get a flying desolate beast, it would pose a greater threat. That way, the falling star hound would be distracted more and act more warily, it would have weaker attacks when trying to defend itself. Hmm?"

Fang Yuan was thinking about this, when Twelfth Hair made a mistake, the diamond bear left a gap open after moving away.

"Damn it!" Twelfth Hair stared with furious eyes, he immediately moved the chestnut yak to fill the gap.

"You have to hang on!" Twelfth Hair bellowed in his mind.

The falling star hound growled, slamming the chestnut yak away.

Next, the falling star hound broke away from the encirclement and charged into the grass.

As a result, the hairy man Gu Immortals hiding in the grass screamed in terror.

"Quick, use that move!" Seeing that he was about to be hit by the falling star hound, an unlucky hairy man Gu Immortal shouted in fear.

Swoosh.

At the next moment, he vanished on the spot, appearing beside another hairy man a thousand steps away from him.

"Thanks, thanks. You acted quickly, otherwise, I would have died." The hairy man Gu Immortal who was saved still felt lingering fear.

The one who saved him was Sixth Hair.

He patted the hairy man Gu Immortal's shoulder: "Relax, relax, don't forget the outsider is here, don't make our Lang Ya Sect lose face."

Even now, he was still trying to sow discord.

The hairy man Gu Immortal who was saved quickly concealed his expression, but his body was still shaking slightly.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, killing intent was hidden in his gaze as he looked at Sixth Hair.

"I will slaughter this fellow one day! But we are members of Lang Ya Sect now, the information path alliance agreement prevents us from killing each other. So to kill him, I need to get rid of this Lang Ya Sect alliance agreement secretly first."

Fang Yuan wanted to make use of Lang Ya Sect's strength, Sixth Hair was a severe obstacle.

Sixth Hair played a big role in causing Fang Yuan and Lang Ya Sect's relationship to turn so sour.

In Lang Ya Sect, Fang Yuan and Sixth Hair both had ulterior motives. Their relationship was not simple either.

Because they had made transactions, they had a hold on each other.

Fang Yuan had Lang Ya Sect's alliance agreement, he could not do things that harmed Lang Ya Sect. Of course, he could think and talk about them. Sixth Hair was a member of Lang Ya Sect, because of this, if Sixth Hair was in fatal danger, Fang Yuan had to save him! Of course, it depended on the situation. If Sixth Hair tried to suicidally put himself in danger and lure an ancient desolate beast in order to entrap Fang Yuan, he would not have to save him in that situation.

Since Fang Yuan joined Lang Ya Sect and went under an alliance agreement, he was not going to be restricted so easily.

And Sixth Hair only wanted to get rid of Fang Yuan and obtain his body. He had insufficient strength, and Fang Yuan had a hold on him, because of Shadow Sect's plan, he was the final spy left in Lang Ya blessed land, he had to stay hidden.

Both sides had their own reservations, they were wary of each other.

As if he had sensed Fang Yuan's gaze, Sixth Hair turned around and smiled sinisterly.

He was a split soul of Spectral Soul, he had rich battle experience. This was why he could save the hairy man Gu Immortal before anyone else reacted.

He was trying to unite the hairy man Gu Immortals and ostracize Fang Yuan, limiting his growth.

The battle continued.

The falling star hound did not kill the hairy man Gu Immortal, the diamond bear and golden-white tiger quickly diverted it. Soon, the chestnut yak arrived as well, forming an encirclement again.

The hairy man Gu Immortals also continued their long range attacks.

But Twelfth Hair continued to make flaws in the battle due to unexpected circumstances, even though he was performing above his usual abilities.

After getting out of the encirclement, the falling star hound attempted to kill the other hairy man Gu Immortals.

But these hairy man Gu Immortals seemed to have the same immortal killer move. Whenever one was targeted, the rest would be able to teleport them away to another comrade's side.

"This immortal killer move is quite interesting." Fang Yuan watched silently, he subconsciously placed himself in the falling star hound's position, what would he do to resolve the killer move?

Soon, Fang Yuan had an answer.

It was difficult to resolve this killer move. Because with just this little bit of information, he could not analyze anything.

He did not even know the name of the killer move.

In this short period of time, the killer move did not seem to have any flaws.

"Even if I cannot break it, it is very easy to kill these hairy man Gu Immortals. My movement speed far exceeds them, sword marks targeting death and dark assassination can cause many deaths to them already. In fact, just flying sword Immortal Gu alone can kill them. Of course, Sixth Hair is hiding his strength, that is another issue. The actual situation would depend on how the fight develops."

"I am about to succeed! This time, I will truly defeat the falling star hound!" Twelfth Hair got more and more excited, the light of victory could be seen in his eyes.

This time, he performed better than usual, seven to eight hairy man Gu Immortals along with three desolate beasts were fighting against an infant falling star hound. With the proper tactics, victory was favoring these hairy man Gu Immortals.

"Fang Yuan, are you seeing this? Even without you, we can take down the falling star hound and obtain true victory!" Twelfth Hair cried out in his mind.

He loved his home, he was extremely loyal to Lang Ya Sect. Earlier, when Lang Ya Sect was facing trouble with developing in Tai Qiu, Fang Yuan watched on the side, Twelfth Hair had a lot of grudge towards Fang Yuan.

When he was injured and bedridden, Fang Yuan went to visit him, but he did not even want to meet, he sent a mortal Gu Master to reject Fang Yuan's entry into the cloud city.

This victory had incredible meaning for him.

Being able to obtain victory in front of Fang Yuan, Twelfth Hair felt great pride and joy!

As time passed, the battle situation was becoming obvious.

Falling star hound was gradually unable to hold on, the hairy man Gu Immortals felt that their pressure was lifting.

They unavoidably became excited, some of them could even see victory ahead, their eyes were red from excitement, they were trembling slightly.

It was not easy!

With their horrible battle strength, fighting against the falling star hound resulted in repeated setbacks.

They had put in so much blood and sweat, coming up with a tactic to deal with the falling star hound, they had spent countless sleepless nights practising, they were finally going to succeed today!

Even though they were tired and their immortal essence was depleted, the hairy man Gu Immortals felt revitalized, they were having an adrenaline rush.

"Kill, kill this dog!"

"That's right, tear its skin and hang it above the cloud cities, let everyone see our victory!"

"Hahaha, we finally defeated it."

"Fang Yuan, are you seeing this? I know you are unwilling, but so what?"

"Today, we will teach you a lesson, the hairy man Gu Immortals are not powerless. Lang Ya Sect belongs to us hairy men, it is not for a human like you!"

The hairy man Gu Immortals shouted and screamed in excitement.

Fang Yuan smiled plainly, as if he did not hear them.

His attitude made the hairy man Gu Immortals disappointed, some of them even felt disgust and anger.

"He is just concealing his emotions, what can he do?" A hairy man Gu Immortal sneered.

However, a change occurred right at this moment!

An eagle hound suddenly appeared in the center of the battlefield, with one swipe of its claws, the diamond bear fell! With one peck from its beak, chestnut yak went blind! With a flap of its wings, intense winds blew, the golden-white tiger flew back by dozens of steps. The falling star hound curled up into a ball, whimpering in fear.

"What, where did this ancient desolate beast come from?" The hairy man Gu Immortals were shocked.

"Not, not just one!" Soon, five eagle hounds appeared from the grass, and three were flying in the sky.

Out of nowhere, eagle hounds had completely encircled the hairy man Gu Immortals.

"How, how did this happen?" Twelfth Hair's pupils shrunk to pin size, he was completely stunned!

He had just experienced going from heaven to hell.

A moment ago, he was still a high and mighty victor, at the next moment, his life was on the line, this was a desperate situation!

"Oh? Heaven's will, this is your ambush huh... incredible indeed." Fang Yuan laughed in his mind.

The eagle hounds did not make a noise, while the hairy man Gu Immortals were shocked beyond words, there was silence.

"Oh Twelfth Hair, it seems that you have all failed. According to our earlier agreement, it is time for me to act." Amidst the silence, Fang Yuan's plain words could be heard.

For some reason, Twelfth Hair felt his heart jump, intense rage was burning inside him, he screamed at Fang Yuan: "You, are you making a mistake! What are you talking about? Open your damned eyes and see the situation we are in, okay?!"

Fang Yuan's lips curled slightly.

Bam!!

A strength path giant hand appeared out of nowhere, it slammed the eagle hound closest to Fang Yuan to the ground.

Dust and smoke rose.

The eagle hounds' attention was drawn away, towards Fang Yuan, they were wary of this strong enemy.

Within the dust cloud, Fang Yuan's voice could be heard: "Alright, I will accept this present, can everyone please go far away, don't be a disturbance to me."

Chapter 1136: Eagle Hounds

Eagle hounds!

They had the body of a wolf and head of an eagle, with a pair of eagle wings on their backs. Their head, neck and wings were covered in black feathers, while their canine bodies and four limbs were covered in grey wolf fur. The dao marks on their bodies were mostly of dark path.

This was a rather special beast.

Normal desolate beasts, ancient desolate beasts and so on reproduced through males and females mating. Eagle hounds, however, were different.

The reproduction of eagle hound was through infection.

The poison of an eagle hound could influence any species of dog or eagle. When this influence reached a certain degree, the dog or eagle beast infected with the eagle hound's poison would gradually transform into an eagle hound.

As a result, the individual strength of eagle hounds varied greatly.

Some eagle hounds were transformed from desolate beasts, so they would be desolate beast level. Some transformed from ancient desolate beasts, thus would be ancient eagle hounds. Immemorial eagle hounds were rarely seen, even in white heaven and black heaven.

Everything was clear.

The moment the first eagle hound appeared, Fang Yuan had already realized how the falling star hound and these eagle hounds were related.

This group of eagle hounds had been eyeing this falling star hound. It was thrown down from the sky and confined in Tai Qiu to grow.

When the falling star hound matured, it would be a true ancient desolate beast. At that time, the eagle hound group would use poison to turn this falling star hound into an ancient eagle hound.

As for why this falling star hound was roaming near the teleportation Gu formation, the answer was clear — heaven's will!

"Two ancient eagle hounds, while the rest are all desolate beast eagle hounds." Fang Yuan's gaze coldly focused on the two ancient desolate beasts.

He did not sense auras of Immortal Gu on the eagle hounds.

This gave him even greater assurance in this battle!

Having and not having Immortal Gu would lead to Fang Yuan adopting two completely different battle tactics.

"The, the eagle hound was killed in one strike..."

"It has not died, it is only unconscious."

"What was that move just now?"

"It was like a huge hand!"

The hairy man Gu Immortals reacted only now, and they were extremely shocked.

Just now, the eagle hound that was beaten unconscious by one giant hand was naturally a desolate beast level. Strength path giant hand had rank seven battle strength, creating such an outcome was not strange. If it were against an ancient eagle hound, however, it would be a different result.

Twelfth Hair had never seen Fang Yuan fight seriously.

He had always thought the battle strength Fang Yuan showed when instructing him was Fang Yuan's true strength.

Twelfth Hair forcibly calmed down, thinking: "Although Fang Yuan beat one eagle hound unconscious, there are still a lot more remaining! Even if he is powerful, what can just one person do? This battle bodes ill, it is better to retreat! Ahh!"

Just as he was thinking of this, Twelfth Hair suddenly could not help crying out in shock.

Fang Yuan's confrontation with the eagle hound group lasted a very short time. Almost the next instant after beating the eagle hound unconscious, he began his attack.

Sword escape Immortal Gu.

Whoosh!

Fang Yuan left behind an afterimage on his original spot.

Within an instant, Fang Yuan had penetrated from the edge of the battlefield into the center.

"This, what level of speed is this?!" The hairy man Gu Immortals were shocked.

Even Sixth Hair's pupils shrunk, he gritted his teeth. He guessed Fang Yuan used sword escape Immortal Gu, this was Bo Qing's Immortal Gu!

Fang Yuan floated in the air, looking down at the giant beast below.

This was an ancient eagle hound, when it had just appeared, it had knocked down the diamond bear, sent the golden-white tiger flying and pecked the chestnut yak blind.

This ancient eagle hound was stepping on the diamond bear, not letting it budge. The infant falling star hound behind it was curled up into a ball, shivering.

He was close to it!

The distance between Fang Yuan and this ancient eagle hound was less than a hundred steps.

Images of each other were clearly reflected in both their eyes.

Fang Yuan suddenly disappeared and appeared right before the eagle hound's eyes, giving it a scare and causing it to take a step back subconsciously.

But soon, its fierce nature was agitated, as it opened its beak wide and screeched furiously. Its wings flapped rapidly and energy transferred from its rear limbs, as it charged ferociously at Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan sneered, shouting: "Beast, lie down."

Boom!

A strength path giant hand appeared and descended from the sky, slamming on the ground like a jar lid.

The giant hand collided with the ancient eagle hound; the ancient eagle hound was full of ferocity, but was still unable to match the giant hand's power as it was pushed down.

The giant hand also was sent back from the collision.

But soon, under Fang Yuan's control and replenishment, the giant hand once again pushed down fiercely, as if it was bringing down a storm.

The giant hand struck the ancient eagle hound's head, immediately causing it to bow down, its four limbs bent exaggeratedly and its claws that were fiercely supporting its body left four pits on the ground.

The strength path giant hand was again flung up a distance from the vibration of the clash, thinning during the process.

But the next moment, the giant hand once again condensed as it slammed down.

The ancient eagle hound refused to give in and lifted its head, but at the next moment it saw the giant hand covering the entirety of its vision.

Boom!

There was a huge sound as the ancient eagle hound's head was fiercely slammed down to the ground.

The thick and sharp eagle beak was firmly embedded into the ground.

Its feathers chaotically flew in the air, while its four limbs also sunk into the ground.

The ancient eagle hound fell into an extremely furious state, when had it ever received such humiliation. It wanted to strike back, energy flowed through its limbs, its muscles bulged and the next moment, it was about to lift up its head!

Boom!

The giant hand was quicker, however, slamming down on its head and back.

The eagle hound's skeleton gave fracturing sounds at the extremely heavy burden. Its head was shaking intensely and it was seeing stars, the strength it had accumulated just moments ago completely dissipated.

But Fang Yuan's momentum was unforgiving, bang bang bang, another three slams, and this ancient eagle hound was almost completely buried into the ground.

It was motionless, the surrounding soil was gradually turning red from the blood.

The hairy man Gu Immortals were all struck speechless!

After Fang Yuan had made a desolate beast eagle hound faint, he charged into the center of the eagle hounds without being afraid of the enemy's numerical advantage.

Facing the ancient eagle hound, he sent out ten or so giant hands and struck it to death like slamming bread dough!

The hairy man Gu Immortals had never seen such a terrifying display, and were extremely frightened.

In fact, not only the hairy man Gu Immortals, even the other eagle hounds were dazed.

By the time they reacted, one of their leaders had been wiped out.

Deathly silence hung in the air, with not even the sound of wind.

Under everyone's gazes, Fang Yuan slowly lifted his head and gazed at the sky.

There were quite a few eagle hounds hovering in the air, among them was the second ancient desolate beast.

"It's your turn now." Fang Yuan's tone was light, as he charged towards the sky the very next moment!

The eagle hounds in the sky immediately let out ear-piercing cries, breaking up in an uproar as they retreated in every direction.

Twelfth Hair and the group still had their mouths wide open as they looked at Fang Yuan charging to the sky, driving the eagle hounds away like they were sparrows or pigeons.

Were these still eagle hounds?

A mighty ancient desolate beast, where is your imposing might!

Twelfth Hair felt like he was in a dream.

Pursuing good fortune and avoiding disaster, protecting oneself and seeking long life was every living being's instinct. Wild beasts pushing aside the weak and fearing the strong was also normal.

With the eagle hounds dispersing, Fang Yuan could do nothing.

In terms of speed, eagle hounds were outstanding, regardless of whether they were desolate beasts or ancient desolate beasts.

Fang Yuan's gaze continued to stare at that ancient eagle hound.

"Will you be able to escape..." As Fang Yuan mumbled, he suddenly sped up!

The next instance, his figure appeared behind the ancient eagle hound.

Myriad self first style, giant hand!

The giant hand slammed down with such a loud sound, the hairy men shivered and the eagle hounds felt their hair standing on end.

The hairy men saw that ancient eagle hound being slammed down from the air by Fang Yuan like a ball, colliding heavily with the ground.

Sword escape Immortal Gu combined with giant hand gave an outstanding result.

Strength path giant hand's speed was rather slow, if it struck out from afar towards the eagle hound, this eagle hound would probably be able to escape before it reached it.

But Fang Yuan personally moved, using his speed to make up for this weakness of the giant hand.

Of course, this battle tactic also had a weakness, it could easily make Fang Yuan fall into a dangerous situation.

So, Fang Yuan had activated bloodstained conqueror's robe before he used this tactic.

There was also another condition, Fang Yuan did not sense any wild Immortal Gu on these two ancient eagle hounds. If there were wild Immortal Gu, without probing out the details, Fang Yuan would not use this battle tactic.

Giant grass grew all over Tai Qiu, the eagle hound's fall was greatly mitigated by these strands of grass.

Even though ancient eagle hounds specialized in speed, they were all of ancient desolate level, and had sturdy bodies. Fang Yuan would not be able to kill it without using ten or so strength path giant hands.

However, just as Fang Yuan was about to take the chance to chase it, his expression suddenly changed.

In his eyes flashed a scene of the future —

While he charged down, suddenly a third ancient eagle hound appeared and ambushed him.

Fang Yuan was caught unprepared and was clawed fiercely by the wolf claws, smashing to the ground. Blood flowed out of his seven orifices and all his bones were fractured, his bloodstained conqueror's robe was broken and even blood asset Immortal Gu was injured, unable to be used again.

The image flashed in an instant, however Fang Yuan fully trusted it.

Because this was the result of his pre-activated immortal killer move — Three Breaths Future Vision!

It was a time path investigative killer move from Hei Fan true inheritance, 'three breaths future vision' used after Immortal Gu as the core and could allow the Gu Immortal to see their future situation. And this future situation would manifest within three breaths of time.

Fang Yuan did not lose his head, instead his eyes shined with satisfaction.

"Sure enough, heaven's will's arrangement wouldn't be so simple, there was actually an ambush!"

"My bloodstained conqueror's robe is an immortal level defensive move, but its core Immortal Gu is only the rank six Blood Asset. It is still slightly weak when facing an ancient desolate beast."

Since he knew about the ambush, the ambush naturally would be useless.

Sword marks targeting death!

Fang Yuan suddenly shot out sharp sword light towards a certain location in the air.

Right as the hairy man Gu Immortals were feeling puzzled, sword marks targeting death struck that hidden ancient eagle hound.

Ding!

There was a sharp and clear sound, the ancient eagle hound was intercepted by sword marks targeting death.

The hairy man Gu Immortals shouted in shock.

"There was actually a third ancient eagle hound hiding in ambush!"

"Unimaginable, if it had sneak attacked any of us hairy man Gu Immortals, it would probably have gotten its way."

"Fang Yuan could actually sense it?"

Fang Yuan slightly raised his eyebrows, staring at the third ancient eagle hound which had suffered no damage.

"Being able to block sword marks targeting death, this ancient eagle hound seems to have wild Immortal Gu on it?"

Chapter 1137: Transformation Path Gu Immortal

The third ancient eagle hound had Immortal Gu.

If not for this, how could it block Fang Yuan's immortal killer move, sword marks targeting death?

Fang Yuan's heart burned with eagerness.

Times had changed.

If it were before he inherited Hei Fan's true inheritance, Fang Yuan would have avoided this eagle group, but now, with his strength having increased sharply, his mindset had changed.

He intended to take down all these eagle hounds!

"My sovereign immortal aperture is very big!" Fang Yuan's lips curled up.

"As for the wild Immortal Gu on the ancient eagle hound, I will take it as well. Being able to block sword marks targeting death, let me see what kind of exemplary defensive Immortal Gu it is."

In an instant, thoughts surged in Fang Yuan's mind, he determined his battle tactics.

Blood path killer moves like blood torrent and so on were not suitable to be used in front of the hairy man Gu Immortals.

These hairy man Gu Immortals could connect to treasure yellow heaven and knew the terror of blood path. They were not like that group of ignorant Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Although he could use Hei Fan true inheritance's immortal killer moves, he had to be prudent. After all, he still had not practised them to proficiency, rashly using them could likely result in failure and cause backlash.

Therefore —

Fang Yuan clapped, choosing his personal creation, which was also the offensive method he was most skilled in.

Convergence of enslavement and strength path — Myriad Self!

At the next instant, large amounts of strength path phantoms filled the sky.

"Ahh!" The hairy man Gu Immortals were all struck speechless.

Sixth Hair also had a stupefied look, but inwardly was not surprised.

He already knew about myriad self, this was old news.

But soon, Sixth Hair's pupils shrunk as he blurted out: "He va... vanished?!"

In his perception, Fang Yuan had suddenly vanished, and only the dense group of strength path phantoms remained in the sky.

Fang Yuan had used familiar face to disguise himself as an ordinary strength path phantom, mixing in within the myriad self army.

Charge!

The myriad self army cried out together and like a torrent falling from the sky, charged towards the third eagle hound.

The eagle hound's eyes flashed with sharp light, suddenly the wings on its back flapped, bringing forth a layer of dark wing shadows.

Its speed increased sharply, and it actually retreated!

This response was somewhat out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

Clearly, this eagle hound had a second wild Immortal Gu. That layer of wing shadows was the effect of that Immortal Gu.

"It actually has another wild Immortal Gu!" The desire in Fang Yuan intensified.

He commanded the myriad self army to continue charging towards the ancient eagle hound.

Along the way, the strength path phantoms suddenly dispersed, like a blooming flower, or a giant beast's maw, as they pounced at the ancient eagle hound.

The ancient eagle hound gave a sharp cry, as it suddenly rose up.

It was actually retreating again.

Fang Yuan had already calculated its retreat routes, the myriad self army, which had charged ahead like a flood dragon with its mouth open, swung its tail. The strength path phantoms at the rear pounced at the ancient eagle hound.

The ancient eagle hound that was retreating backwards suddenly leaned towards the right, its wings flapped and its whole body drew an inclining arc through the sky, perfectly dodging the myriad self army's offensive route.

The hairy man Gu Immortals were in an agitated state watching all these moves.

Compared to the eagle hound, they naturally wanted Fang Yuan to win.

But this third ancient eagle hound seemed to be extremely cunning, Fang Yuan had encircled it several times but was still unable to succeed.

"The ancient eagle hound's speed is much faster than these 'Fang Yuans'. How could they catch up to it?" Twelfth Hair attentively observed, feeling dejected as Fang Yuan continued to make no progress.

Sixth Hair however had a bright gaze, thinking: 'Fang Yuan's enslavement path attainment seems to have increased slightly. It is going to end soon! This ancient eagle hound might be fast, but it is concerned about the other eagle hounds, and has only been flying around the battlefield, it will soon be captured by Fang Yuan.'

A battlefield formed in the sky.

Almost all the eagle hounds flew up and were battling with the myriad self army.

Fang Yuan's focus was completely on the third ancient eagle hound.

"There is something odd about this ancient eagle hound!"

Fang Yuan had discovered that the other eagle hounds could be easily dealt with. As long as he used a few strength path phantoms, the eagle hounds could be pinned down. Only this third ancient eagle hound was rather crafty and could see through the tactics of the myriad self army, it was able to retreat and advance at will.

Finally, Fang Yuan was able to succeed, several groups of the myriad self army besieged the third eagle hound from the front, back, above and below.

"He actually surrounded it!" Twelfth Hair and the group cried out in joy.

The ancient eagle hound let out a sharp screech, as it flapped its wings wildly and clawed everywhere, destroying many of the strength path phantoms.

Within just a few moments of being encircled, the ancient eagle hound seemed to be about to break through the siege.

But this did not matter.

Because Fang Yuan's true body, hidden among the strength path phantoms, had already approached the ancient eagle hound.

When he was close enough, he decisively used his sword path killer move — Dark Assassination!

This killer move's specialty was that no Immortal Gu aura would leak out when it was activated, it was extremely stealthy.

The ancient eagle hound let out a miserable shriek as it was struck by Fang Yuan.

A bloody hole appeared on its neck, blood spurted out like a fountain.

But in the blink of an eye, the blood lessened, and the bloody hole disappeared, the injury had healed and feathers grew once again on the surface.

At the same moment, the ancient eagle hound turned berserk, its whole body was covered by a layer of dark shadows, its speed increased by multiple times as it attacked wildly, bringing forth afterimages of its wings and claws.

Crash crash crash!

Countless strength path phantoms were destroyed directly by the ancient eagle hound without putting up resistance.

Even Fang Yuan's true body was discovered and was sent flying.

But with bloodstained conqueror's robe, there was not much injury.

"How, how could this be?"

"There are disorderly auras of so many Gu worms appearing on this ancient eagle hound!"

Twelfth Hair and the rest blurted out in shock.

Sixth Hair's eyes also widened at this, as he incredulously said: "Impossible! It can actually use an immortal killer move?"

Such a strong result and the complex aura of Gu worms indicated this ancient eagle hound had actually used an immortal killer move just now.

This no doubt went against the common knowledge of the immortal world.

A wild beast actually had enough intelligence to activate immortal killer move?!

Wind whistled past Fang Yuan's ears, he was sent flying. Although he had avoided the frontal attack, it had still brushed past him and was enough to send him flying away.

He gazed at the ancient eagle hound, his eyes brightly flashing: "So it was like this, no wonder I had felt it was so peculiar! This ancient eagle hound was originally a Gu Immortal!"

It was impossible for wild beasts to be so smart to the extent of using immortal killer moves!

Sixth Hair did not realize this because he did not cultivate transformation path.

Fang Yuan had plenty of understanding regarding transformation path, immediately thinking of this most likely possibility.

A transformation path Gu Immortal who cultivated an eagle hound transformation, but because of transforming too many times or being in transformation state for too long, they were unable to turn back, losing their wisdom and memories, turning into a special ancient eagle hound.

Like when refining Gu, the Gu Immortals cultivating transformation path would have to face the risks when transforming into other forms!

In history, such cases were not rare.

The following battle proved Fang Yuan's guess.

This ancient eagle hound still had some battle instincts of the transformation path Gu Immortal. As a result, its performance was much more cunning than normal ancient eagle hounds, and it understood when to advance and retreat.

But in the end, it was not a Gu Immortal, it did not have human wisdom, it could not grasp opportunities in the battle and could not carry out any battle tactics.

When in battle, it mainly used Immortal Gu. When it was the juncture of life and death, its instincts would be stimulated and it subconsciously used its most familiar immortal killer move from the past.

Just before, Fang Yuan had used dark assassination to pierce through its head, but in the moment of crisis, it had dodged and the attack struck its neck.

Then, the wild shadows it erupted with that sent Fang Yuan's true body flying were from it using an immortal killer move.

The fight instantly fell into a stalemate.

If it were ordinary eagle hounds, Fang Yuan would have captured all of them by now. But it was a different situation with this ancient eagle hound, it was much more troublesome than ordinary ancient eagle hounds.

Whenever Fang Yuan sneak attacked, the ancient eagle hound was always able to avoid the fatal points. Perhaps it was because this transformation path Gu Immortal had experienced many battles, or maybe it was because of the support of an unique Immortal Gu, a more likely possibility was the help of heaven's will.

In short, Fang Yuan's intention to finish the battle quickly had been thwarted.

The sky was chaotic, loud sounds reverberated unceasingly as the strength path phantoms were destroyed at every moment.

But with Fang Yuan's replenishment, the myriad self army was unending.

Their quality might not be up to par, but their quantity held the absolute upper hand!

From time to time, eagle hounds covered by strength path phantoms would fall down from the sky and smash into the ground.

"Upper hand! Fang Yuan... Elder Fang Yuan has the upper hand facing all these eagle hounds."

"An individual's strength can actually reach such a level!"

"Elder Fang Yuan is actually so powerful."

The hairy man Gu Immortals had already retreated to the edge of the battlefield, and as they looked at the battle, they had, without noticing, started to address Fang Yuan as an elder.

Twelfth Hair's expression was filled with shock as well as bitterness.

He felt it even deeper than others.

Fang Yuan's enslavement path attainment of easily commanding the myriad self army, made him have a feeling of how shallow and minute he was!

Although the ancient eagle hound was somewhat troublesome, from the beginning, Fang Yuan occupied the dominant position and the eagle hounds could not do anything to him.

"Since it is like this, then I should change my battle tactics." Fang Yuan's true body put off attacking, and suddenly retreated to the side.

He began to gather his concentration to activate another immortal killer move.

By now, he had already been constantly maintaining bloodstained conqueror's robe, familiar face and three breaths future vision. He was floating in the air and also activating Gu worms, and occasionally replenishing the myriad self army. All these used up his focus.

And this immortal killer move was rather complicated and he had yet to practice it to proficiency, thus he had to give up on attacking and move to a safer environment, to gather almost all his concentration and activate this move.

Rank seven year Gu was first activated, followed by the supplementary mortal Gu one after the other.

Immortal killer move — Year Beast Summoning.

"Come out, my ancient year beast!"

Splash splash splash.

In mid-air, a phantom image of the River of Time manifested.

Waves were surging endlessly in the river, and from these waves, an enormous bestial figure jumped out!

Cluck cluck.

The year beast unfurled its wings and descended to the battlefield!

Chapter 1138: End of Battle

"This, what is this?"

"Such a large chicken!"

Seeing an ancient year beast suddenly entering the battlefield, the hairy man Gu Immortals were shocked.

"According to the contents of Hei Fan's true inheritance, there are twelve different forms of year beasts. This time, I was pretty lucky to be able to summon a chicken year beast." Fang Yuan sized up this year beast, while appraising it inwardly.

This year beast was as large as a hill.

When it unfurled its wings, it cast a huge shadow on the ground.

It was valiant and spirited, with awe-inspiring might. Its feathers were bright and colorful while its claws were sharp as blades.

It quickly swept its gaze around the battlefield, before fixing on Fang Yuan.

No one else had more appeal to it than Fang Yuan, because it smelled the scent of year Gu from Fang Yuan.

Year Gu!

This was the food of year beasts. The higher the rank of the year Gu, the more enticing it was to year beasts.

The immortal killer move, year beast summoning, was formed from this principle. Its creator, Hei Fan, had invented this killer move long before refining Years Flow Like Water.

"This is for you." Fang Yuan chuckled, as he waved his hand, sending out large amounts of mortal year Gu.

The chicken year beast was joyous, as it raised its head and inhaled.

Immediately, an enormous air current was created and like a dragon swallowing water, the chicken year beast inhaled all the mortal year Gu.

"Kill it and I will give you a lot more." Fang Yuan pointed at that crucial ancient eagle hound.

The chicken year beast's gaze sharpened, as it quickly turned its head towards the target.

The ancient eagle hound felt goosebumps all over its body, revealing its sharp claws as it felt a strong threat from the chicken year beast.

The ancient eagle hound formed a clear contrast with the chicken year beast, even if it stood up like a human, it would not reach half the height of the chicken year beast.

Cluck cluck!

The chicken year beast flapped its wings, charging towards its target. The speed it erupted with was actually faster than the ancient eagle hound.

Bam.

The two collided fiercely, the chicken year beast was sent back seventy to eighty steps, while the ancient eagle hound was directly sent flying.

The chicken year beast let out a sharp cry, as it chased after the ancient eagle hound.

The ancient eagle hound was indeed crafty, after suffering a loss, it no longer confronted the chicken year beast head-on, instead it moved left and right, dodging the chicken year beast.

Fang Yuan looked on for a while before he relaxed.

This chicken year beast had no Immortal Gu, but its physical constitution was much stronger than the ancient eagle hound.

Year beasts, even in the River of Time, were very rare beasts!

Of course, if the ancient eagle hound activated Immortal Gu, the chicken year beast would fall into a disadvantage. Once or twice would not matter, but if it continued on, the chicken year beast would also be defeated.

The side which had Immortal Gu would naturally obtain a huge boost in their battle strength.

"Hei Fan warned in the true inheritance that the summoned year beast is not a slave and the summoner does not have very much control over it. If the enemy is too powerful, it won't battle at all. Even if it battles, it might retreat after a short period of time and demand even more year Gu from the summoning Gu Immortal."

As he thought of this, Fang Yuan knew he did not have much time left.

He did not choose to pincer attack the ancient eagle hound with the chicken year beast.

Because the chicken year beast was not under his control and he was only able to barely communicate with it using the method left behind by Hei Fan, reaching a collaboration.

Fang Yuan's true body, which was hidden amidst the myriad self army, quietly approached a desolate beast eagle hound.

The eagle hounds were still fighting with the myriad self army in the air.

Occasionally, some eagle hounds would be beaten down by Fang Yuan's strength path phantoms, but shortly afterwards, these eagle hounds would fly to the air again, continuing to fight.

Although there were many strength path phantoms, their offensive prowess was clearly weak when facing against desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts. They were only able to disrupt and expend the eagle hounds' energy.

Strength path giant hand!

Suddenly, Fang Yuan attacked, a strength path giant hand appeared out of nowhere, slamming down towards an eagle hound.

Fang Yuan's position was extremely good, the eagle hound was caught unprepared and was struck by the hand, immediately letting out a miserable cry before it fainted.

The eagle hound began to fall down, but Fang Yuan activated another giant hand and was waiting below.

The second giant hand grabbed this unconscious eagle hound, and carefully placed it on the ground.

Fang Yuan's true body disappeared amongst the myriad self army once again.

But soon, he appeared in another area of the battlefield, strength path giant hand attacked quickly and sent another eagle hound fainting.

He then did the same as before, placing this eagle hound on the ground, beside the first eagle hound.

The hairy man Gu Immortals were all struck speechless!

"Elder Fang Yuan seems to be..."

"Right, he intends to capture these eagle hounds alive!"

"A skilled person is truly courageous."

The hairy man Gu Immortals sighed. These eagle hounds, which were deadly opponents to them, seemed to be no more than wealth from Fang Yuan's perspective.

One after the other, eagle hounds were plotted against by Fang Yuan, struck unconscious, and piled up together.

Soon, these unconscious eagle hounds piled up to form a hill, making for quite a grand sight.

The ancient eagle hound saw this scene and gave a furious cry. But it was pinned down by the chicken year beast and was unable to go rescue its brethren.

The chicken year beast was also slightly in a slightly miserable state, its whole body was filled with injuries and it seemed to be having the intent to retreat.

After all, Hei Fan was a time path Gu Immortal, being able to create an immortal killer move that imitated enslavement path was already extremely amazing.

"It seems that year beast summoning is ideal for use in a favorable battle. If used to fight in a disadvantageous situation during a life or death battle, the result won't be outstanding." Fang Yuan engraved this information in his mind. Only when one used immortal killer moves in practice would they obtain deeper experience.

Fang Yuan firmly held the initiative in the battle.

He paid attention to the battle between the chicken year beast and the ancient eagle hound all along.

Before the chicken year beast retreated, Fang Yuan dealt with the remaining eagle hounds.

The unconscious eagle hounds numbered to eight, while the rest were struck to death. After all, giant hand was not a capturing method, it was not easy for Fang Yuan to use it to imitate this effect.

"Die!"

Fang Yuan flew to the sky and flanked the ancient eagle hound with the chicken year beast.

After fighting for several rounds, the result was indeed not good.

Fang Yuan called out to the chicken year beast to retreat and guard those unconscious eagle hounds.

The chicken year beast already had low battle intent, and after receiving Fang Yuan's instruction, it did not immediately move, but instead quietly retreated a distance before opening its beak as it gazed at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan understood its intention, and threw out a large batch of year Gu.

The chicken year beast had its fill, only then did it turn around and move towards the ground, to guard the unconscious eagle hounds.

Fang Yuan and the ancient eagle hound battled once again.

But this time, the situation was different from before.

The ancient eagle hound was anxious to save those unconscious comrades, as it charged in all directions.

"What a pity. A grand Gu Immortal falling down to such a level! Thinking it is an actual eagle hound." Fang Yuan was lot more relaxed now than before.

The ancient eagle hound flew fast and with Immortal Gu on it, at the crucial times, it could arouse its survival instincts and activate the previous immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan changed his battle tactic.

His previous tactic of charging in and using giant hand was too risky. Bloodstained conqueror's robe's defense was nothing prominent in front of this ancient eagle hound.

Fang Yuan started using sword path killer moves to attack the ancient eagle hound from afar.

But the ancient eagle hound's defensive method was outstanding, Fang Yuan did not know which Immortal Gu it was specifically. He estimated this transformation path Gu Immortal, when alive, felt the defense of an eagle hound was rather low, thus intentionally strengthening this aspect.

Fang Yuan fought for a long time but still had no upper hand, the ancient eagle hound also could not rescue its comrades, while the chicken year beast sat in position to fight a defensive battle.

The injuries on the ancient eagle hound slowly accumulated.

"This is truly troublesome. Giant hand's speed is slow, it cannot hit. Sword path killer moves can hit, but the effect is not that good. Using poison spit is simply wasting immortal essence. Ancient eagle hounds are extremely resistant to poison!"

Fang Yuan was without other options.

Similarly, after this transformation path Gu Immortal completely transformed into the ancient eagle hound, they obtained the intuition of wild beasts, and with the remaining battle instincts, this ancient eagle hound became much more difficult to handle.

Facing it, Fang Yuan found himself at a loss as to what to do.

A transformation path Gu Immortal's advantage was that after the transformation succeeds, their body's constitution would be extremely high. Like this ancient eagle hound, just its flying speed could match Sword Escape in short range. Let alone when it activates its Immortal Gu.

At the moment, Fang Yuan could only choose to fight a battle of attrition.

When this ancient eagle hound uses up all its immortal essence, and is no longer able to activate its Immortal Gu, that would be his victory.

Or when its injuries accumulate to a certain degree and it exposes a flaw which Fang Yuan could use!

Fang Yuan felt helpless, but the spectators did not have this feeling.

The hairy man Gu Immortals were staring blankly.

Strength!

In the competitive, cruel world of Gu Immortals, the most important thing was the Gu Immortal's strength.

The strength Fang Yuan displayed shocked all the hairy men.

Even Sixth Hair was not an exception.

"This guy, how could he increase his battle strength so much in such a short time?! He can actually summon a year beast, how did he get a hold of this method? He clearly only went out for a short period of time..."

Sixth Hair felt heaviness in his mind.

Fang Yuan's growth speed caused him to feel stifled and breathless.

After some more time fighting, the ancient eagle hound suddenly rose up.

"Eh? You want to escape!" Fang Yuan thought before quickly giving chase.

The ancient eagle hound's injuries had accumulated to a certain state, whether it be its offensive prowess or flying speed, both had clearly fallen.

No matter how talented in battle the Gu Immortal was when they were alive, the wild beast's instinct of evading danger still made it choose to retreat.

As for those unconscious 'comrades', they could only be abandoned.

Fang Yuan inwardly cursed at this, he had already anticipated this situation, it was just that it happened earlier than his expectation.

Fang Yuan activated sword escape Immortal Gu to give chase, but the distance between them was shrinking very slowly.

The ancient eagle hound was escaping for its life with an astonishing speed.

Immortal killer move — Luck Whirlwind!

Fang Yuan was without other options and could only activate this killer move.

Success!

The ancient eagle hound directly returned to the previous position, Fang Yuan caught up to it and both sides engaged in fierce battle again.

After a few rounds of fighting, the ancient eagle hound escaped again.

Fang Yuan could only give chase.

Luck whirlwind!

Success.

Both sides battled again, while the hairy man Gu Immortals watched on from afar.

But soon, the ancient eagle hound gave up on Fang Yuan, it crazily flapped its wings as it retreated for a third time, its attitude more firm than before.

Fang Yuan was helpless, he was unable to break the eagle's wings.

Luck whirlwind!

Unfortunately, he failed this time and immediately spurted out some blood.

It took him a few breaths to stabilize himself, the ancient eagle hound had already flown to the horizon by this time.

Fang Yuan had no choice but to stop.

Heaven's will was paying attention all along, Tai Qiu was perilous, and there were already vague signs of a beast tide forming.

Chapter 1139: Deadly Situation

"There was not much time to practice luck whirlwind properly." Fang Yuan thought as he sighed.

If luck whirlwind was activated on its own, the success rate of its activation was eighty to ninety percent.

But when put in real battle, it was a different situation.

For instance, Fang Yuan had to maintain bloodstained conqueror's robe, familiar face, three breaths future vision, and other immortal killer moves, these killer moves involved large numbers of Gu worms and needed enormous mental energy.

In this situation, activating 'luck whirlwind' which he was not proficient in, and being able to activate it twice successfully already showed Fang Yuan's luck was quite good.

Immortal killer moves had outstanding effects, but their expenditure of mental energy was very high. Let alone in life and death battle, where one had to maintain their attention on the enemy, consider battle tactics as well as making appropriate responses in time.

As a result, it was not the case that the more immortal killer moves activated in battle, the better.

If the mind was burdened over the limit, one might not be able to give a correct response to an enemy's sudden attack or might not even be able to react in time, leading to their defeat and death. That would truly be laughable.

In fact, there were countless such laughable ends in the history of Gu Immortals.

Examples of extremely powerful killer moves failing in activation and causing the Gu Immortal to die were not few.

"To resolve this issue, I can only raise my battle strength even further!"

"Besides adding in more practice and modifying the immortal killer moves to make them simpler, wisdom path can be used to solve it."

Immortal killer moves were created from the combination of countless Gu worms.

Activating each Gu worm expended at least one thought of the Gu Immortal. Successfully activating one immortal killer move would expend thousands or even tens of thousands of the Gu Immortal's thoughts!

Wisdom path was a path that was specialised in solving this issue.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals were often able to use a greater number of and more complex immortal killer moves than Gu Immortals of other paths.

"Among the wisdom path inheritances I have obtained, the most important one is still Dong Fang Chang Fan's Wisdom Star true inheritance. It is specialized in deducing and is not specialized in controlling Gu worms and activating killer moves. But I am now a wisdom path grandmaster, I can fully use this foundation to develop on this aspect and make a breakthrough."

After Fang Yuan sent the ancient eagle hound escaping away, he examined his own shortcomings while returning, and decided he had to progress on wisdom path next.

Descending on the ground, Fang Yuan patted his stomach and opened the entrance to his immortal aperture.

The entrance opened, revealing a part of the landscape in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Sixth Hair stared fixedly, but how could he be able to see properly from outside the entrance?

He only saw a desolate icy plain.

That was Mini Northern Plains of Sovereign blessed land.

Sixth Hair let out a sigh of relief at this.

'It seems he focused on raising his battle strength, while the management of the immortal aperture has fallen. It's no wonder, after all this sovereign immortal aperture faces calamity once every two months.'

Sixth Hair simply did not know Fang Yuan had completely plundered Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he thought Fang Yuan was still a pauper, little did he know that the other areas of Sovereign blessed land were beautiful mountains and rivers, lush forests, and shocking amounts of rich resources.

"Regardless, this is genuine rank seven battle strength.' Sixth Hair's eyes twitched as he gazed at the chicken year beast: 'Fang Yuan might only be rank six, but he already holds rank seven strength. Adding on to another rank seven battle strength... this, I definitely need to report this matter to Lord Ying Wu Xie!"

The chicken year beast clucked in happiness.

Fang Yuan fed it large numbers of year Gu, making it extremely satisfied.

Finally, it flapped its wings and jumped into the River of Time, slowly disappearing from sight.

Taking in the eagle hounds one after the other into his immortal aperture, along with the falling star hound, and after sending away the chicken year beast, Fang Yuan turned around and faced the hairy man Gu Immortals.

"This mission should be considered done by me, right?" Fang Yuan lightly smiled, using an inquiring tone to ask these hairy men.

The hairy man Gu Immortals nodded, their expressions were more or less filled with reluctance, helplessness and embarrassment.

This was the fact.

Without Fang Yuan making a move, their lives would have been in danger.

Twelfth Hair opened his mouth as if to say something, but even after moving his mouth multiple times, he did not manage to say a word.

He thought of his meager performance and how he had an exaggerated opinion of his own abilities, he could not help feeling ashamed.

Sixth Hair was observing the others' expressions, and spoke with a sinister smile: "Elder Fang Yuan, you are truly amazing, you were able to defeat the eagle hound group by yourself! If we had not seen it personally, none of us would have believed it. If you had made a move earlier, the falling star hound or whatever would have been nothing difficult, right?"

The hairy man Gu Immortals heard this and their expressions changed slightly, feeling even more complicated.

"I have my own problems, I don't want to explain to you. First supreme elder knows about them." Fang Yuan chuckled, he then gazed at everyone before looking at Twelfth Hair: "Alright. This matter is over now, let us return."

With the teleportation Gu formation, everyone returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

After hearing everyone's report, Lang Ya land spirit's attitude softened by a lot.

He was not very shocked at Fang Yuan's battle strength.

Because he knew Fang Yuan had once possessed Spring Autumn Cicada and had reborn. A rank six possessing rank seven battle strength was rare, but for Fang Yuan, it was not hard to understand.

Having eased his relationship with Lang Ya land spirit, and obtaining the thousand contribution points from completing the falling star hound mission, Fang Yuan was able to smoothly borrow Gu worms to use immortal tribulation tempering aperture.

Over the following days, Fang Yuan cultivated in peace.

He mainly cultivated his soul using Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley, secretly trained the new killer moves like luck whirlwind, and in his free time, he looked after the newly obtained infant falling star hound and the group of eagle hounds.

Regarding these desolate beasts and the ancient eagle hound, they only needed to slightly adapt to the new environment and could live in peace.

Regardless of where they lived, they were still living, right?

This was the behavior of those without intelligence.

As for the countless resources moved over from Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan placed most of them in Mini Southern Border.

Because Mini Southern Border's environment was rather similar to Hei Fan grotto-heaven's.

Despite this, because the dao marks of Fang Yuan's immortal aperture could not compare to Hei Fan grotto-heaven, many resources had reduced production and some were even on the verge of dying.

As a result, Fang Yuan still had a concern, which was to quickly sell these resources that he could not grow.

Besides transacting with Lang Ya land spirit, the focus was on treasure yellow heaven.

In a short period of time, Fang Yuan accumulated a large number of immortal essence stones. After using a portion of the resources, the slightly insufficient immortal essence reserve was no longer a worry, and now it had become Fang Yuan's strong point.

"So much green grape immortal essence! I don't have to worry even if I activate triple layered sword wave a hundred times."

Fang Yuan had never possessed so much green grape immortal essence.

This made him even more confident for his fourth earthly calamity.

Time passed, finally it was time for Fang Yuan to pass another earthly calamity again.

He left Lang Ya blessed land and came to the northern icy plain.

After choosing an area, he placed down his immortal aperture and opened its entrance, absorbing heaven and earth qi.

This time, the duration of the absorption of heaven and earth qi was tens of times as long as before!

The reason was that the resources inside Fang Yuan's immortal aperture had increased by hundreds of times, expending large amounts of heaven and earth qi of the immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan then arranged immortal tribulation tempering aperture.

Everything was handled with ease.

After finishing the preparations, Fang Yuan closed the blessed land's entrance, and welcomed the fourth earthly calamity.

It was still at Mini Northern Plains.

Fang Yuan encountered endless flying frost.

"This is... profound white flying salt calamity?"

Fang Yuan was stunned, before recognizing it.

He was slightly surprised.

This calamity was not strong, instead it was the type which could be passed rather easily.

Yellowish clouds started forming in the sky.

Large amounts of frost salt slowly fell down from the sky. The whole process was silent, the salt was like snow and there was not any wind.

The endless salt fell down on the ground, and melted the ice and snow on the ground.

Some cold-resistant wild grasses and flowers that had grown on the snow were submerged by the salt, and were wilting rapidly before completely dying.

"It is trying to destroy Mini Northern Plains' ecology?" Fang Yuan was slightly perplexed. For the moment, he did not move and only looked on from the side.

Although there were some losses, most of his resources were currently gathered in Mini Southern Border.

Mini Northern Plains was the area Fang Yuan had been using to pass tribulations, Fang Yuan could completely bear these losses before, let alone now when he had harvested Hei Fan grotto-heaven's accumulation, and had become extremely wealthy.

After a while, snowmen started to appear from the endless salt and frost.

This was the influence of Reckless Savage's true meaning.

So long as Fang Yuan killed these snowmen, he could obtain Reckless Savage's true meaning, rapidly raising his transformation path and strength path attainment levels.

This time was not like the previous time where he shared with Chu Du, Fang Yuan was going to enjoy it all by himself.

Fang Yuan quickly made a move.

These snowmen had just appeared when they were melted by the flying salt. The intention of heaven's will manifested at this moment, it wanted to reduce Fang Yuan's benefits from the earthly calamity, as much as possible.

Fang Yuan and heaven's will raced to strike at the snowmen.

Myriad self was activated, eliminating these snowmen. Naturally, there were also other methods used.

These had to be done by Fang Yuan himself.

Other existences, whether they be Gu Immortal or desolate beasts, whoever killed the snowmen would be the one to obtain Reckless Savage's true meaning.

Waves of Reckless Savage's true meaning entered Fang Yuan's mind, quickly raising his attainment level.

As for the profound white flying salt, they were inexorable and not something Fang Yuan could directly get rid of.

This fourth earthly calamity continued for a long time. Even when the duration of the previous three earthly calamities were added, they would not even be one-tenth of this earthly calamity.

Three days later, profound white flying salt's scale began to slightly decrease.

"Is this a battle of attrition?" Fang Yuan frowned, somewhat puzzled.

Several days went by again, the profound white flying salt calamity finally stopped.

Fang Yuan gazed at the frost salt that had covered the land, the doubt in his mind intensifying.

According to his previous deduction, the fourth earthly calamity should have been even more strong and even more difficult to handle. But the reality was, the profound white flying salt calamity had been mild from start to finish, it descended gradually; Fang Yuan did not feel any pressure at all.

He was even able to destroy almost all of the snowmen, not wasting much of Reckless Savage's true meaning. His gains were plentiful.

It was as if heaven's will was letting him go.

"Previously, I used some time path killer moves in Tai Qiu, it was also to test heaven's will's deduction ability and to see how it deals with me afterwards. The result was the profound white flying salt calamity."

"No matter what, the fourth earthly calamity is now over."

"I can let the land of salt remain, after cleansing it with self will, I can treat it as a special environment."

This earthly calamity was unimaginably easy. Fang Yuan did not suffer even a small injury.

Fang Yuan retrieved his immortal aperture and was about to return to Lang Ya blessed land.

But right at this moment!

The surroundings suddenly changed, Fang Yuan entered a battlefield killer move.

Nine Gu Immortals appeared around him, along with an enormous dragon shaped beast whose aura was majestic and boundless, staring at Fang Yuan with hostility.

Immemorial desolate beast!

Fang Yuan's heart immediately sank to rock bottom, he immediately comprehended: "Human calamity! So heaven's will was intentionally extending the duration of my tribulation to set up this deadly situation for me!"

In an instant, Fang Yuan had fallen deep into a predicament.

Chapter 1140: The Sliver of Hope to Survive

The surrounding area was frost white in color.

Countless grey clouds, the size of carriages, hovered around Fang Yuan.

Although Fang Yuan did not feel any wind, these clouds coiled around him swiftly, like hunting sharks or a pack of starving wolves.

"This is a battlefield immortal killer move! And one which I have not seen before. It seems to be mostly formed of cloud path..."

Fang Yuan was fully vigilant, and after the brief shock, his mind worked rapidly, analyzing the situation.

"Forget about the battlefield immortal killer move, the main point is there are actually nine Gu Immortals and a dragon immemorial desolate beast!" Fang Yuan observed the nine figures.

These mysterious Gu Immortals were covered in a layer of grey clouds, covering their true appearances, only revealing their eyes.

As for the Gu Immortals' auras, the clouds could not hide them, they were leaked.

That dragon beast was also covered in a thick layer of grey cloud as it hovered, facing Fang Yuan. It was completely releasing its majestically shocking aura! In Fang Yuan's perception, the dragon was like a lofty mountain, while he himself was like an ant at the base of the mountain.

Fang Yuan was shocked.

This group was too powerful! He could not even think of being their match.

"Strange! How could there be so many people lying in ambush?" Besides shock, Fang Yuan also felt an enormous doubt.

The northern icy plain rarely had humans, as there were almost no resources in it.

This was a desolate land created by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, the only wealth to be found was Reckless Savage's true meaning which Chu Du desired very much.

As a result, Gu Immortals rarely came here.

Moreover, before each earthly calamity, Fang Yuan would gather intel about any movements regarding Northern Plains' righteous forces, through treasure yellow heaven, Lang Ya Sect and even Chu Du.

There was no commotion from Northern Plains' super forces.

Because of Hei tribe's extermination, everyone was absorbing their gains, and adapting to the completely new power structure of forces.

Almost all of these righteous forces had territories in Northern Plains which were guarded by Gu Immortals. In fact, it was difficult for Huang Jin tribes to mobilize three or four Gu Immortals at once, unless something big happened.

While demonic path and lone immortals might be free, they usually moved alone, how could they suddenly gather into one group?

"Moreover, I have been holed up inside Lang Ya blessed land for almost all the time, avoiding wisdom path Gu Immortals' deductions. I am also protected by Dark Limit and other methods. It is almost impossible for my traces to be deduced so clearly! Where did these Gu Immortals come from? Could they be from Central Continent?"

Previously, to investigate the truth of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Central Continent's ten great ancient sects had allied and built a team of Gu Immortals to send to Northern Plains.

Currently, Heavenly Court was trying every means possible to deal with Shadow Sect and Fang Yuan, it would not be strange if they sent out another group.

However!

Central Continent's Gu Immortals, especially from the ten great ancient sects or Heavenly Court, did things openly and in a grand style. How could they act so evasively like now?

These Gu Immortals' appearances were hidden, even the immemorial desolate beast was the same, and only their vague figures could be seen.

"Maybe this is only an illusion created by the battlefield killer move?" Fang Yuan quickly speculated.

From the time he put away his immortal aperture and prepared to return, to being ambushed, falling into the trap and his current analysis of countermeasures, only a short few moments had passed.

The mental capability of the body from the sovereign immortal fetus was excellent by itself, and with wisdom path methods to support him, Fang Yuan had already reacted!

If it truly was such a terrifying formation, Fang Yuan did not have any hope.

But!

He felt the probability of this being an illusion was huge, because the origins of these Gu Immortals could not be explained at all.

A sharp light blossomed in Fang Yuan's eyes, at the next moment he decisively activated sword escape Immortal Gu and charged towards the Gu Immortals.

The nine Gu Immortals did not react as if they were stupefied.

Fang Yuan flew nearer before stopping, three breaths future vision and bloodstained conqueror's robe were already activated as he pointed, sword light shot out.

Immortal killer move — Sword Marks Targeting Death.

A Gu Immortal with rank six aura moved.

But a rank seven female Gu Immortal to the side grabbed their shoulder: "You can't take on this move, let me."

Her voice had just sounded out, when she pointed with a finger, an ice mirror immediately appeared in the air.

The sword light condensed by sword marks targeting death shot at the ice mirror, but it did not pierce through, instead it was reflected away.

"She is able to change the direction of my immortal killer move!" Fang Yuan's heart chilled, as he quickly maneuvered sword marks targeting death back to the original direction.

His sword marks targeting death's direction could be controlled by the mind once it was activated.

It was just that this killer move was extremely fast and was not easy to manipulate.

Sword marks targeting death returned to its proper path with difficulty, but suddenly there was another ice mirror in front.

Fang Yuan could only helplessly look as sword marks targeting death derailed once again.

Then, there were the third, fourth, and following ice mirrors, surrounding sword marks targeting death, actually making it go around in a circle.

"This is bad! This Gu Immortal's method counters my sword marks targeting death." Fang Yuan's heart sank.

A second rank seven Gu Immortal suddenly took a step forward and gave a deep bellow, an ice spear immediately condensing in his hand.

He then pulled back his arm, like drawing a bow, and after stretching to the limit, he threw the spear towards Fang Yuan.

The ice spear produced a heart-shaking screech as it pierced through the air. Cold air overflowed and vapor was frozen along the way, turning into beautiful frost that floated in the air.

The breathtaking scene, however, carried intense killing intent.

"This is an immortal killer move formed with rank seven Immortal Gu as the core!" Fang Yuan quickly jumped backed to dodge the spear.

But this ice spear was like sword marks targeting death, its direction could be controlled.

Fang Yuan could not dodge, gritting his teeth inwardly, he knew just bloodstained conqueror's robe could not block this move, so he sent out strength path giant hand.

The giant hand suddenly appeared and created a barrier, it blocked in front of Fang Yuan.

The ice spear reached the giant hand, immediately piercing through it and striking Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was sent flying backwards, thick ice condensed on his whole body and even the blood which he spurted out condensed into blocks of ice. His blood asset Immortal Gu also suffered damage.

If he continued to activate it, blood asset Immortal Gu might be seriously injured or even destroyed.

But in this situation, how could Fang Yuan care about this?

He could only crazily use blood asset Immortal Gu to barely maintain bloodstained conqueror's robe.

"The two rank seven Gu Immortals are not illusions. What about the others then?" Fang Yuan swallowed his blood and clapped, using the killer move myriad self.

In an instant, large numbers of strength path phantoms surged out and covered everyone's sight.

These mysterious Gu Immortals looked stunned.

The third rank seven Gu Immortal smiled and called out: "Let me."

He raised his arms and puffed his cheeks, before fiercely blowing.

Spiralling wind shot out of his mouth.

Within the blink of an eye, the wind enlarged to an enormous tornado.

The tornado was as high as thirty meters, its two ends were wide while the middle part was thinner, and was dark green in color. It spiralled frantically, sharp as blades as it engulfed all the strength path phantoms in its path and easily ripped them into pieces.

The size of the myriad self army sharply reduced by more than half in a short period of time.

Fang Yuan quickly replenished the numbers.

"Brother, I will lend you a hand." The fourth rank seven Gu Immortal spoke in a muffled voice.

He pointed with his index finger, targeting the tornado.

Instantaneously, a certain mysterious immortal killer move was activated, the tornado split into two, before turning into four. Within moments, four enormous tornadoes ravaged the battlefield! Their power had increased by four times!

"This!!" Fang Yuan's mind shook once again, feeling the situation was far from good.

Since the battle started, he had suffered light injuries, blood asset Immortal Gu was injured and was in a danger of dying if it was continued to be used.

While at the enemy's side, that immemorial desolate beast had yet to move, among the nine Gu Immortals, four rank sevens had each activated an immortal killer move, which were either mysterious and awe-inspiring, or profound and exquisite.

"Could it be... this is not an illusion?" As if he had fallen into an abyss, Fang Yuan's heart sank.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Wind whistled crazily, in a few short moments, the myriad self army was going to be completely destroyed even if Fang Yuan continuously replenished them.

The quality of the strength path phantoms was too low, their numbers could not be put to good use in front of rank seven killer moves.

Myriad self, which had always been successful, now was in an awkward place, and was not able to change the situation for Fang Yuan.

"No, there is still an advantage of myriad self, it can at least expend the enemy's immortal essence, I have a strong point in this aspect. But there are a lot of enemies, while I am alone, this advantage is as good as nothing. What can I do!?"

The difference in strength between the two sides was so great that any battle tactic looked useless.

In fact, these mysterious Gu Immortals did not work together at once. Every time they made a move, they took turns. If this immortal level battlefield killer move was not entrapping him, perhaps Fang Yuan could make his getaway.

Unfortunately, the enemy had already prepared amply, Fang Yuan also lacked space path methods, escaping itself was a problem, not to mention he still had to face four rank seven and five rank six Gu Immortals, as well as that immemorial desolate beast. This was an extremely dangerous peril!

This situation was simply the worst.

Compared to his first life where he was besieged by righteous path Gu Immortals, this was innumerably more dangerous.

After all, at that time, there had not been an immemorial desolate beast to control the situation!

Fang Yuan probed these Gu Immortals, but regarding the immemorial desolate beast, he did not even have a thought of probing it.

Fang Yuan was relying on continuously activating myriad self to survive in this worsening situation.

One after the other, the Gu Immortals made moves, strength path phantoms were almost annihilated. The myriad self army, which had always until now been surging with overwhelming momentum, simply could not form a large scale.

"Am I going to die here today?" An intense sensation of incoming death shrouded Fang Yuan's mind.

Requesting for reinforcements would not work, within this battlefield killer move, Fang Yuan could not even connect to treasure yellow heaven.

However, he had still not given up.

His thoughts moved like lightning, and he suddenly remembered: "No, I still have a chance of survival!"

This chance of survival was not Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada was filled with heaven's will, heaven's will was trying all methods possible to eradicate Fang Yuan. Using Spring Autumn Cicada was courting death.

This chance of survival was in the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

If it was before Fang Yuan obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, his death would be certain at this moment. But it was different now, he still had one hope left.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was also an immemorial desolate beast, it was just that it was only an infant currently with desolate beast level strength.

However, Hei Fan's true inheritance naturally had time path immortal killer moves that could speed up the upper extreme heavenly eagle's aging and push it to grow in a short period of time!

With this, Fang Yuan would have rank eight battle strength.

Coincidentally, the upper extreme heavenly eagle was also a space path immemorial desolate beast that could enter and exit grotto-heavens and the immemorial nine heavens, there was a huge chance it could pierce through this battlefield killer move!

"Persevere! I need to persevere until the upper extreme heavenly eagle reaches rank eight!!" When he thought of this, Fang Yuan immediately changed his battle tactics.

Chapter 1141: Refusal to Listen or Believe

The time path immortal killer move was already quietly activated inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was affected by the killer move, its body's time was rapidly quickened by countless times, making it mature quickly.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle cried out, feeling extremely unwell.

On one hand, it was because its body was growing rapidly, while on the other hand, it was hungry!

It required many heavenly crystals to fill its stomach every day. Right now, in just one breath, a day had passed for its body, and with its body growing continuously, how could it not feel hungry?

Naturally, Hei Fan had considered this situation as well, so there was another immortal killer move which was used specially to make up for this flaw.

At the same time, the upper extreme heavenly eagle huddled up in the heavenly crystal eagle nest and began to eat madly.

Only such a two-pronged approach could sustain its growth.

This was a quick growth method and had a lot of flaws. The upper extreme heavenly eagle had been in contact with Fang Yuan for a very short time, now with its strength suddenly increasing, it would become more bestial and would not be easy to control. Moreover, the upper extreme heavenly eagle's growth rate was sped up too much, and there was no way for it to adapt and get familiar with its growth, so it might not be able to use even thirty percent of its strength.

However, Fang Yuan had no other choice!

He was in a desperate situation and this was his only hope to get out of this predicament.

He was like a drowning man who was firmly grasping onto the sole life saving straw.

Myriad self was continuously activated, the once-powerful killer move had now become the only reliance for Fang Yuan to stall for time.

He had used familiar face to disguise himself and mixed in among the strength path phantoms, the enemy Gu Immortals had not discovered him since the start.

The tornadoes wreaked havoc, during which the enemy Gu Immortals had each made their moves, their powerful killer moves shrouding the entire battlefield.

Fang Yuan's strength path phantoms could only last about one or two breaths of time before they were destroyed.

He had never activated myriad self as frequently as now!

Fortunately, myriad self was created by him, and by now, he was so proficient with it that it had turned into an instinct and there had yet to be failure when activating it.

However, his green grape immortal essence reserve was rapidly dwindling.

Regarding immortal essence reserves, Fang Yuan was completely in a disadvantage, he naturally had no way to compare with the nine enemy Gu Immortals.

"This guy's concealment skill is quite amazing." An enemy Gu Immortal praised.

"Relax, as long as this battlefield killer move, grey cloud battle puppet, is here, we don't have to worry about him escaping." Another Gu Immortal replied.

"Hmph, rat like thing, come out. The earlier you die, the earlier you can be free from suffering."

The four rank seven Gu Immortals did not speak, but the other five rank six Gu Immortals yelled, vainly attempting to shake Fang Yuan's will.

But could Fang Yuan waver so easily?

His will was firmer than steel, even when he was in danger, he would not give up trying until the very last moment.

Since he was using a stalling tactic, Fang Yuan would never reveal himself.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was growing rapidly, it already gave a trace of an ancient desolate beast's aura. As for the heavenly crystal eagle nest, it was already eaten by over half.

But this growth rate was still far from enough.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was the key for this battle!

"The enemy has the numerical advantage, their immortal killer moves also seem to be endless. Once I take out the upper extreme heavenly eagle, if my breakthrough attempt fails, I will probably be immediately dealt with the next moment. I won't have any second chance! I must succeed in one try!!"

Just as he thought of it, Fang Yuan suddenly heard a chuckle by his ear.

"Heehee, found you."

This was a female Gu Immortal's voice.

At that instant, Fang Yuan's hair stood on end, and without caring about exposing his true self, he activated sword escape Immortal Gu!

He flew towards the sky!

Almost at the same time, frost condensed on his original spot, quickly forming into thick ice the size of a pavilion.

"He's quite fast." A rank six Gu Immortal said in surprise. Her voice was the same voice that had sounded by Fang Yuan's ear.

"Xue Er, you succeeded. Not bad." A rank seven Gu Immortal praised.

"Thank you, great-grandma." The female Gu Immortal seemed to be happy, "Although I cannot break through his disguise, every time he activates his killer move to create those phantoms, the aura of the killer move will leak out. He might be heavily concealed, but it is of no use. As the frequency increased, I discovered him."

"Good! Let me see where you can escape!" Another rank seven Gu Immortal shouted, directly charging towards Fang Yuan.

He was extremely fast.

Shortly afterwards, he reached Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan recognized this Gu Immortal, this person was the one who had shot the ice spear before.

"Die!" The rank seven Gu Immortal clenched his fists, instantly two ice spears condensed in his hands.

"A close combat Gu Immortal?!" A sharp light flashed past Fang Yuan's eyes, and he quickly retreated.

However, Sword Escape was actually unable to throw the enemy off.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk slightly as he noticed his body was covered in a layer of thin grey clouds.

It was the cause of his reduction in speed.

While on the other side, the rank seven Gu Immortal's speed seemed to have been increased.

"If I let you escape freely, would not it make me look incompetent?" The Gu Immortal controlling the battlefield killer move was standing straight, with his hands folded in front of his chest, watching the battle situation from afar.

Fang Yuan was forced to engage in close combat.

This rank seven Gu Immortal was very powerful with outstanding fighting skill.

Within several moves, Fang Yuan's left arm and stomach were pierced.

Blood asset Immortal Gu was heavily injured!

Large amounts of fragmentary ice and snow path dao marks were engraved on Fang Yuan's wounds, making them difficult to heal. Cold air entered his limbs and bones, further lowering his speed.

The sovereign immortal body's disadvantage appeared for the first time!

There were no conflicts between dao marks, causing Fang Yuan to be easily injured.

Previously, Fang Yuan was defending and painstakingly dodging around. But at this moment, he had no choice but to face the consequences of this weakness.

"Die!" The enemy's offense was extremely fierce. He thrusted the ice spear in his right hand towards Fang Yuan's forehead, while quietly moving the ice spear in his left hand towards Fang Yuan's heart.

Blood torrent!

Fang Yuan suddenly changed his killer move, bizarrely curving around and dodging the enemy's attack.

"Blood path!" A rank six among the Gu Immortals blurted in shock.

"He is indeed an unforgivable sinner! He actually cultivates blood path!!"

"We can be considered to be eliminating an evil, helping the people of the world."

"I had been somewhat suspicious of that defensive killer move earlier. So it was like this."

The Gu Immortal dual wielding spears, was filled with even more killing intent, as he pounced over again.

Giant hand!

Fang Yuan suddenly slammed, a strength path giant hand flew out.

In such a short distance, the Gu Immortal with dual spears was unable to dodge.

But he had not even thought of dodging.

Head-on!

He pierced the giant hand with his two spears, and continued to chase Fang Yuan.

Since he could fight in close range, he naturally had extremely outstanding defensive methods. If not for this, how could he dare to take the risk?

The two spears in his hands intertwined into dense spear shadows, fully displaying the advantage of a close combat Gu Immortal's attack speed.

Close combat Gu Immortals were few in numbers, they had once flourished in ancient times, but were now almost extinct.

However, if such a Gu Immortal manages to get near to the opponent, they would become an extreme threat.

Fang Yuan was constantly in a life and death situation, he had to pay close attention to the enemy's movements, and slight negligence could result in him dying.

Fang Yuan possessed many immortal killer moves, but in close combat, in most cases, he could only concentrate on dodging. Because there was no time to use any complicated immortal killer moves, and once his response was delayed, it could be his death.

Fang Yuan's momentum was already destroyed, he was barely able to continue for a while before the enemy finally found a gap and pierced a spear through his heart.

"It is over." At this moment, the enemy's expression was slightly relaxed.

Man as Before!

As Fang Yuan erupted, he used man as before Immortal Gu to restore the fatal injuries.

Then using dark assassination, he shot towards the enemy's head.

In an instant, Fang Yuan had established his victory!

He had been concealing Man as Before, waiting for this battle opportunity.

Sounds of shock rose, but the Gu Immortals were not angry.

At the next instant, Fang Yuan saw a strange sight: The enemy's head was not made of blood and flesh, and was completely formed from grey clouds.

The grey clouds scattered before condensing, and the dual spear wielding Gu Immortal shook his newly formed head, laughing: "Not bad! You could actually destroy my head, hmph! Human Gu Immortals are so crafty, if it were normal times, I would have already died. Unfortunately, this is within grey cloud battle puppet, an immortal level battlefield."

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk to pin-size.

He suffered a loss.

Not knowing the mechanism of this battlefield killer move led to an error in judgment.

"Although this is the first time I have heard of grey cloud battle puppet, it is truly a fierce battlefield killer move." Fang Yuan let out a breath, his whole body was filled with injuries.

He had intentionally concealed Man as Before and used it at the crucial time, but his painstaking plan had been thwarted by grey cloud battle puppet.

"That goes without saying, this was created by Lady Earth Mother!" The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal spoke with pride.

Fang Yuan took the chance to look at his immortal aperture, the upper extreme heavenly eagle had already grown into an immemorial desolate beast.

However!

It was near death.

The heavenly crystals were already finished, and it was now starving to death.

Fang Yuan quickly dispelled the effect of the immortal killer move on the upper extreme heavenly eagle and attempted to feed other things to it.

However, the upper extreme heavenly eagle kept its mouth closed.

"Damn it! Earlier, I was too busy dealing with the enemy, I simply had no time to be concerned about the upper extreme heavenly eagle's situation." Fang Yuan's heart sank to rock bottom.

His final trace of hope was gone.

In this battlefield killer move, the enemies could not die, Fang Yuan did not have any strategy to ensure his victory. Dealing with just one rank seven Gu Immortal was difficult, not to mention there was also the dragon immemorial desolate beast that had not moved from the start.

What now?

Death was already approaching close.

"Young man, leave your name. You are a worthy adversary, after this life of mine, my battle with you shall be remembered as a glory by my descendants." The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal pressed on forward.

The atmosphere was solemn, other Gu Immortals did not speak anything to stop him, seemingly approving of the dual spear wielding Gu Immortal's words.

Fang Yuan, however, revealed a confident smile: "My name is not important, what is important is my status. I am a supreme elder of Lang Ya blessed land, a member of a variant human force. In the current situation of the world, we variant humans should not take up arms against each other, isn't that the case? Snowmen, rockmen and hairy men should help each other, not have internal fights which will instead please enemies!"

"How do you know..." The dual wielding Gu Immortal was extremely surprised.

"He actually knows of our identities!"

"Quick, kill him!"

"Human Gu Immortals have always been crafty, don't listen to his misleading words!"

The other Gu Immortals cried out, almost screaming.

"What Lang Ya blessed land! Also, you are clearly a human, what hairy man? Do you think I am blind?!" The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal furiously pierced forward with his spears.

Fang Yuan exposed their identities, but they simply did not listen to or believe Fang Yuan's words.

Chapter 1142: Bluffing, Deceiving

The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal rushed towards Fang Yuan.

"Variant humans... are indeed stubborn? Or is this the influence of heaven's will? Hmph!" Fang Yuan's gaze turned dark, he looked at the dual spear wielding Gu Immortal charging at him, but he did not dodge or retreat.

Boom!

At the next moment, he opened the entrance to his sovereign immortal aperture and released a gigantic beast.

"Ahh! This, this is!!!" The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal felt a majestic aura that instantly overwhelmed his body and mind.

His momentum stopped abruptly, and his battle intent had dispersed at that very instant.

What Fang Yuan released was none other than the upper extreme heavenly eagle that had now matured to immemorial level!

A truly mature upper extreme heavenly eagle was extremely huge, multiple times the size of a whale, it did not lose out even when compared to that immemorial dragon desolate beast.

The immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle was a terrifying rank eight level battle force!

Shock!

Instantly, the enemy immortals were all shocked and dumbstruck. They had never expected Fang Yuan to still be holding such a card in reserve.

This trump card was too strong!

The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal was almost trembling from fear.

The atmosphere of the whole battlefield had instantly transformed completely.

Fang Yuan stood proudly on the upper extreme heavenly eagle's head, and coldly snorted: "Why do you think I was fearless since the start? Even if your battlefield killer move is powerful, could it obstruct my upper extreme heavenly eagle?"

The enemy immortals' bodies jolted upon hearing this.

"Upper extreme heavenly eagle!"

"According to legends, this eagle is a space path immemorial desolate beast that can avoid the heavenly wind qi wall and enter the immemorial nine heavens."

"Not only this. It can also pierce through space and enter grotto-heavens. Our battlefield killer move cannot trap it!"

The group of immortals communicated in fluster.

Fang Yuan had a confident smile on his face: "Even if you use that dragon immemorial desolate beast, I am confident of escaping. But what I said before is all true! I simply don't need to deceive you, and even if I wanted to deceive you, such a shoddy lie could easily be exposed. Why would I waste my time?"

The enemy immortals fell into silence.

The mountain-like upper extreme heavenly eagle was the best evidence of Fang Yuan's words.

The dual spear wielding Gu Immortal was the nearest, the upper extreme heavenly eagle filled his whole vision. Despite the upper extreme heavenly eagle slightly closing its eyes, the cold light leaking out of the crack of its eyes still made him feel like he had fallen into an icy abyss.

"Did you verify it? Is it real or not?" The Gu Immortals secretly transmitted their voices.

It was rather ironic.

Just before, when Fang Yuan was ambushed and saw this terrifying battle formation, the first thing he felt was doubt at whether this was real or an illusion.

Now, after Fang Yuan released the upper extreme heavenly eagle, these Gu Immortals were experiencing the same thing.

"It is real!" That rank six Gu Immortal called Xue Er spoke with shock, "Moreover, that upper extreme heavenly eagle's vitality is extremely flourishing, don't be fooled by its unmoving and harmless look! Once it attacks, it would definitely be earth-shaking!"

Soon, the rank seven Gu Immortals confirmed one after the other.

"This! He only has a blessed land, how could he store an immemorial desolate beast!"

"Although it is unimaginable, it is the truth."

"What should we do? He can use an immemorial desolate beast, could it be that we also have to send out the immemorial rock dragon?"

In fact, the dragon beast in grey cloud battle puppet was not as intimidating as it appeared. Although the aura was real, it could not fully display its rank eight battle strength.

There were many reasons.

Grey cloud battle puppet did not have a core rank eight Immortal Gu, and was not suitable for use on rank eight level existences.

Another reason was, the snowman and rockman Gu Immortals' main bodies were far below underground. They put in their respective Gu worms and immortal essence in this grey cloud battle puppet, forming battle puppets that were not weaker than the main bodies.

That is to say the power of grey cloud battle puppet originated from the remote control of the Gu Immortals, and the immortal essence along with Gu worms concealed in the battle puppets.

The battlefield killer move could form a grey cloud battle puppet corresponding to the immemorial rock dragon, but the immemorial rock dragon did not have a Gu Immortal's intelligence, let alone remote controlling the puppet, it could not even freely use Immortal Gu, as such it was unable to manifest its strength.

That was the reason for this rank eight battle strength to not move even the slightest since the start of the battle.

It was instead Fang Yuan who was cautious and did not dare to even risk probing it.

Naturally, this was common sense.

Just like now, the dual spear wielding Gu Immortal was stunned and did not dare to attack the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

When Fang Yuan released the upper extreme heavenly eagle, the situation completely transformed.

The rank eight battle strength on the variant human Gu Immortals' side was only a facade, while they were unaware of the details regarding Fang Yuan, and thought they were on the weaker side.

And Fang Yuan?

He was also not clear of the variant human Gu Immortals, and also did not know if the immemorial dragon beast was only there for show. He also felt his strength was on the weaker side.

As far as the truth was concerned, Fang Yuan's judgment was correct.

Right now, Fang Yuan was feeling rather tense.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was about to die from hunger, and he had to use blood path methods to disguise it to look like it had flourishing vitality. Once it was attacked, this disguise would fail.

However, the other side did not dare to attack.

The reason?

Once they attacked, if they could not kill their enemy and let him escape, that would be a very troublesome situation.

Even if they summoned the immemorial rock dragon from the deep underground, if the upper extreme heavenly eagle wanted to escape, they would not be able to stop it!

Since Fang Yuan exposed their identities, he also knew of their misgivings.

Their identities!

Once their identities of the snowmen and rockmen were exposed to Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, it would immediately lead to invasion from the righteous path, demonic path and lone cultivators.

Human forces were strong and had killed on their path to reach this age since the immemorial antiquity era, they absolutely would not let such a huge variant human super force to exist beside them!

Thus, when the variant human Gu Immortals ambushed Fang Yuan, they had concealed their appearances.

The variant human Gu Immortals had even mobilized nine Gu Immortals and moved out an immemorial desolate beast to suppress the situation, just to handle Fang Yuan, one person.

It was to make sure there was no mishap.

But even in such a foolproof plan, there were many mishaps because of Fang Yuan alone. Finally, he even brought out an immemorial desolate beast, upper extreme heavenly eagle.

If they had known this earlier, how could the variant human Gu Immortals still lay an ambush, and end up in this current awkward situation of not knowing what to do!

Fang Yuan waited for a while, the variant human Gu Immortals did not speak.

He shook his head and gave a helpless smile: "Alright, I have already said this, why are you still not believing me? Could it be that you really want us to fight to the death? Naturally, I won't be the one to die."

"How could we trust you, a human!" A rank seven Gu Immortal said with anger.

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh of relief inwardly, since the other side spoke, that means they had been deceived. He got the opportunity, now it would depend on his performance.

Thereupon, Fang Yuan activated familiar face.

Immortal killer move's aura spread everywhere, the variant human Gu Immortals immediately became vigilant, the dual spear wielding Gu Immortal even retreated far away.

However, what came next shocked the variant human Gu Immortals, as they looked on with wide eyes at Fang Yuan transforming into a hairy man, with no flaws.

"I am a transformation path Gu Immortal, and I inherited a portion of the true inheritance of Ren Wang. I could easily deceive you all by transforming into a hairy man, but why did I not do so?" Fang Yuan spoke in sincere fashion as he spread his arms and turned back to his previous appearance.

The variant human Gu Immortals quietly looked at him.

Fang Yuan continued to bullshit: "I did it as an act of sincerity to you! Since I realized your identities just moments ago, then we can be considered people on the same side. Although I am a human Gu Immortal, I am truly a member of Lang Ya blessed land. Lang Ya blessed land's origin is Long Hair Ancestor. Currently, under Lang Ya land spirit's lead, Lang Ya Sect has been created and I am one of the supreme elders of the sect. If you believe me, then open up the battlefield killer move, and I will send a message to inform the sect of this matter."

The variant human Gu Immortals looked at each other but nobody moved.

Both sides were at a stalemate.

Fang Yuan did not dare to let their minds wander.

After all, heaven's will was influencing them.

To dispel heaven's will's influence, Fang Yuan had to continue to talk and change their minds.

Heaven's will was not fake will, and its influence over variant human Gu Immortals was not high. After all, the intelligence of variant humans was second to only humans. It was because of this that Fang Yuan had hope.

"Alright, I will show my sincerity first." Fang Yuan suddenly sighed, and opened his immortal aperture, placing the upper extreme heavenly eagle inside.

This move shocked all the variant human Gu Immortals.

"Careful. Although the upper extreme heavenly eagle has been placed inside, it can rely on its power to come out of the aperture and make a move at any time."

"Enough, dispel grey cloud battle puppet."

"Leader..."

"Could it be that you still think grey cloud battle puppet can trap him?"

The other variant human Gu Immortals were unable to reply.

From what they saw, the truth was indeed like that.

Amidst the stifling silence, the killer move grey cloud battle puppet was slowly dispelled, Fang Yuan's vision was once again filled with the sight of the bright landscape of Northern Plains.

He strongly endured the impulse of making an immediate getaway, speaking to these variant human Gu Immortals: "Good! Friends are often made after a fight. I will immediately notify Lang Ya Sect, staying here and waiting for the sect to send Gu Immortals."

Fang Yuan's joyful attitude was naturally a disguise.

But with his acting along with attitude Gu, there was no flaw at all.

At least, these variant human Gu Immortals did not notice any flaw.

Adding on that Fang Yuan did not run away, it gave even more proof of the truth of his words.

"Then we shall invite you to make a visit underground as a guest. Here." The other grey clouds had all dispersed, while only a rockman Gu Immortal's physical body was remaining. He was the person controlling grey cloud battle puppet.

"Hahaha, please lead the way." Fang Yuan followed this rockman Gu Immortal into the underground part of this icy plain.

The facts proved that heaven's will's influence towards Gu Immortals was not remarkable. At least, Fang Yuan was able to use words to dispel this influence.

Naturally, it was on the basis of the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

It was because of the existence of the immemorial desolate beast that these variant human Gu Immortals changed their minds.

After all, heaven's will could not destroy these Gu Immortals' rationality, challenging an immemorial desolate beast would be looking for death.

In the depths below the icy plain, there was a scenic and beautiful world of its own.

Fang Yuan was vaguely encircled by several Gu Immortals as they led him, while he looked at the underground scenery absentmindedly.

The variant human Gu Immortals were also in the same situation.

Until Lang Ya Sect sent a group of hairy man Gu Immortals to this place.

Twelfth Hair and Sixth Hair were among them.

Chapter 1143: I Am... Rejoicing!

Northern icy plain, deep underground.

Within a large hall, stone chairs and tables were arranged in a circle, thick vines grew on the walls and grass grew between the cracks of the rocks.

Three bonfires were burning high at the center of the hall.

It is said that this was a tradition passed down from the Olden Antiquity Era. When variant humans attend to esteemed guests, they would set up a banquet and burn three bonfires.

Snowman, rockman and hairy man Gu Immortals, as well as Fang Yuan, were seated inside the hall.

The fire shone on every person's face and their smiles could be seen.

All kinds of fruits were laid in front of everyone, and soon, rockman servants served each person a large bowl of wine.

"This is our rockman tribe's lip fish wine, have a taste!" Shi Zong stood up from his seat and called out while holding the wine bowl.

Shi Zong was this rockman tribe's first supreme elder, he had not joined the battle to kill Fang Yuan.

His whole body shone with many colors from the countless gold, silver and pearl ornaments inlaid on him.

This was the style of rockman tribes.

Rockman bodies were made completely of rocks and in their long period of life, all kinds of gold, silver, iron and steel ores would grow on their bodies. Rockmen took this as a symbol of good looks and honor, the higher the position of the rockman, the more extravagant ornaments they would have on them.

Not only Shi Zong, several other rockman Gu Immortals present on the scene were the same.

Since Shi Zong had invited it, all the immortals held up their wine bowls in response.

Shi Zong and the other immortals took big gulps of the wine, the hairy men did the same, only Fang Yuan took a small sip.

After Shi Zong had finished drinking, he put down the bowl which did not even have a drop of wine remaining.

Cheers broke out.

Other Gu Immortals also imitated him, and drank down all the wine in their bowls.

The immortals laughed, the calm atmosphere became lively.

Only Fang Yuan put down the wine bowl, having only drunken a bit of the lip fish wine.

The snowman and rockman Gu Immortals turned a blind eye to this.

Instead, the dissension rose from within the hairy man Gu Immortals, Sixth Hair criticized Fang Yuan: "Elder Fang Yuan, what are you doing? Don't you know your action is impolite? The host finished the wine, you, as a guest, should also follow and not leave behind any wine in your bowl, this is respect towards the host. Ah, I forgot you are a human and not one of us variant humans, no wonder you don't know this tradition passed down from the Remote Antiquity Era."

Sixth Hair was a spy placed in Lang Ya Sect by Shadow Sect, he took advantage of every chance to cause trouble for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan sneered, his gaze scanned around before he spoke leisurely: "How would I not know of this tradition? It is just that this lip fish wine is the saliva left behind by underground rockfish, I don't like drinking it."

"You..." Sixth Hair's expression looked dark, but he was happy inwardly. Fang Yuan's words were no doubt offending the other side, which was what he intended.

In Fang Yuan's letter to Lang Ya Sect to notify the land spirit, he had naturally not mentioned everything, and only explained the matter roughly. Sixth Hair and the others did not know that Fang Yuan had brought out an immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle in the life and death battle with the snowmen and rockmen, before he could make the other side compromise.

In fact, when Fang Yuan had joined Lang Ya Sect, Lang Ya land spirit had issued a mission to find variant human allies.

Since Fang Yuan had found them, he naturally completed this mission and was sure to receive rewards from Lang Ya Sect.

As a member of Shadow Sect, Sixth Hair did not want to see Fang Yuan obtain benefits and develop. Right now, he spoke up to try and suppress Fang Yuan.

"Haha, since Elder Fang Yuan does not like this wine, then we shall change to another one. Bring out the ice wolf wine from my winery." A snowman Gu Immortal laughed.

Snowmen had snow-white skin, ice blue pupils and aqua blue hair.

This snowman Gu Immortal was robust and strong, his upper body was bare, revealing a dark blue tattoo on his chest. His aqua blue hair was tied up, revealing a firm and dauntless face.

This person's name was Bing Zhuo, he was that dual spear wielding Gu Immortal who had made Fang Yuan struggle bitterly.

Soon, a snowman servant brought the wine.

This was a wine bowl made from ice, the wine inside was almost frozen and released cold air.

"To tell the truth, I myself don't like drinking lip fish wine, so I brewed this wine, how about giving it a taste." Bing Zhuo passionately spoke.

Fang Yuan swept his gaze at the wine and intentionally spoke without proper respect: "Let me taste it then, let's see if it is to my taste or not."

"Please." Bing Zhuo laughed.

Fang Yuan drank a gulp, the first instance this wine entered his mouth, it was icy cold, but when it entered his throat, it became hot like fire. The feeling of ice and fire immediately made Fang Yuan's eyes brighten as he spoke: "Good wine."

"Hahaha." Bing Zhuo laughed loudly, "Since you like it, then please drink some more."

He had just finished speaking, when the immortals saw Fang Yuan lift the whole bowl and drink it down in one gulp.

The immortals were dazed for a moment, before applauding and cheering loudly.

Fang Yuan discreetly glanced at Sixth Hair while laughing internally.

He had already known Sixth Hair's intention.

Sixth Hair would not let any mishaps happen to Fang Yuan. Because after Shadow Sect saves Spectral Soul's main body, their next target would be Fang Yuan. Because of this, Sixth Hair would not harm Fang Yuan's life.

Sixth Hair could only suppress Fang Yuan at most, and delay his growth to make it easier for Shadow Sect in the future.

Sixth Hair had already done this before, making Fang Yuan's relation with Lang Ya Sect turn cold.

However, how could he have ever expected Fang Yuan to have an immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle and moreover, that he had used it to successfully awe the snowmen and rockmen.

An immemorial level battle strength, these variant human Gu Immortals had no choice but to give respect to it!

This was strength!

In their hearts, no matter how Sixth Hair provoked or smeared, Fang Yuan's importance was much greater than all the hairy man Gu Immortals combined.

In fact, variant humans very strongly revered strength. This was one of the characteristics of variant humans that had passed down since the Immemorial Antiquity Era.

Because be it the era of eating raw flesh and drinking blood, or the period of war between different races, or the era when they were slaughtered by humans, great strength had always brought more space to survive and opportunities to these variant humans.

It was instead the humans who, after becoming the overlord of the five regions and having an unshakable position, stopped having as much reverence for strength as before, it could not compare to these variant humans who were barely surviving at some isolated parts of the world.

Fang Yuan had intentionally made things difficult, and as far as these variant human Gu Immortals were concerned, it was normal.

What expert did not have some attitude?

If Fang Yuan did not display it, they would instead feel uneasy.

Fang Yuan knew the mentality of these variant human Gu Immortals very well, naturally he also had another reason for it, that was to probe their intentions.

Now, Fang Yuan was basically completely confident that he was safe.

"What's going on?" Looking at the variant human Gu Immortals' smiling expressions, Sixth Hair was greatly shocked.

Next, almost all snowman and rockman Gu Immortals approached Fang Yuan, while leaving aside the hairy man Gu Immortals.

"Elder Fang Yuan, here, I will toast you."

"Elder Fang Yuan sure is a great drinker!"

Fang Yuan did not refuse them, he drank each time.

The hairy man Gu Immortals looked at each other in confusion.

Sixth Hair was extremely bewildered: "What magic bewitchment has Fang Yuan used, he is actually so greatly welcomed?"

If Fang Yuan had turned into a hairy man's appearance, they maybe it could make sense. But he was in his original form, which was a genuine human.

"Elder Fang Yuan, I, Xue Er, shall pour wine for you." During the feast, a beautiful female snowman Gu Immortal actually walked over to Fang Yuan and took up the work of a servant, pouring the ice wolf wine for Fang Yuan.

The other hairy man Gu Immortals looked on with wide eyes.

Sixth Hair almost shouted out: "What the hell are you all doing! Are you even variant humans? Fang Yuan is clearly a human Gu Immortal! Human! The humans who had slaughtered and marginalized you variant humans!!"

"Xue Er, you are that snowman who discovered my true body?" Fang Yuan brazenly sized up this female snowman immortal, and asked.

The female snowman lowered her head and gave a coy smile: "I am only good at some investigative methods, Elder Fang Yuan is the true hero."

Twelfth Hair had been drinking wine, but when he heard these words, he could not help spurting out the wine.

Sixth Hair looked like he was about to fly into a rage, almost cursing at the female Gu Immortal: "What is your intention? Hey hey! Why is your face red? What are you doing by lowering your head and acting shy? Still taking sneaky glances at Fang Yuan, you think I can't see your expression? Damn it! Are you a snowman or not! Pay attention to your identity!"

"I don't deserve the title of hero." Fang Yuan laughed half-heartedly. Even he himself was somewhat surprised. The attitude of these variant human Gu Immortals seemed to have changed a little too much.

Bing Zhuo walked over at this moment while holding his wine bowl: "If Elder Fang Yuan is not a hero, then who can still claim to be a hero?"

Xue Er gave a timely introduction: "This is Brother Bing Zhuo. He is the strongest in our tribe, normally he is cold and extremely prideful. Only when talking with Elder Fang Yuan is he this passionate."

Fang Yuan stood up and assessed this Gu Immortal: "If I am not wrong, you are the person who dual wielded spears and fought with me for dozens of rounds?"

Bing Zhuo laughed, giving a thumbs up: "Elder Fang Yuan, you have a good eye for detail!"

Fang Yuan did not continue gossiping, and directly chugged down the wine.

Bing Zhuo was overjoyed, and also chugged down his wine.

Cheers rose up once again, while Xue Er clapped from the side: "Heroes attract heroes."

The hairy man Gu Immortals looked on, dumbfounded, no one was paying attention to them. The other side's Gu Immortals were all looking at Fang Yuan.

Sixth Hair almost slammed the table.

Bing Zhuo's attitude was making him feel worse.

He mentally screamed: "What in the world are you guys doing?! Forget about that female Gu Immortal named Xue Er, Fang Yuan's current appearance is quite handsome. What are you, a man, being so excited for! Look at your laughing expression, you look like you want to be sworn brothers with Fang Yuan, what are you thinking? The strongest in your tribe and also a hero? Being this close with a human Gu Immortal, you want to betray your tribe?!"

Bing Zhuo sighed: "Compared to Elder Fang Yuan, how could I be considered a hero? Elder Fang Yuan possesses an immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle. If Elder Fang Yuan was not on the same side as us, we might have provoked a disaster for our tribes."

"Wha... what? Immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle!" In an instant, the hairy man Gu Immortals looked at each other in shock.

"Elder Fang Yuan, I didn't hear wrongly, right? You actually have an immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle?!" Sixth Hair finally could not endure it, he stood up suddenly and stared fixedly at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan rubbed his nose, and said with a slightly embarrassed expression: "Not long ago, I allied with Chu Du to get to Hei Fan grotto-heaven and take Hei Fan's true inheritance. This upper extreme heavenly eagle is one of the gains."

"What?!" The hairy man Gu Immortals exclaimed in shock.

Meanwhile, the snowman and rockman Gu Immortals also exchanged looks with each other.

Sixth Hair took a step back unconsciously, staring at Fang Yuan incredulously, and then looking at the other Gu Immortals.

In that instant, he finally realized and understood why these variant human Gu Immortals gave so much importance to Fang Yuan!

Immemorial desolate beast, rank eight battle strength!!

Plop.

Sixth Hair could not bear such a huge impact, his legs gave way and he sat down again on the stone chair.

"I did not have the time to inform all of you. Come, let us Lang Ya Sect members have a drink, this calls for a celebration." Fang Yuan smiled and raised his wine bowl.

The hairy man Gu Immortals reacted, revealing joyous expressions.

"Our Lang Ya Sect also has rank eight battle strength now!"

"Elder Fang Yuan, you are truly unfathomable, simply amazing!"

"Elder Fang Yuan, it was my mistake in the incident earlier, I had eyes but failed to recognize Tian Ti Mountain."

The hairy man Gu Immortals all had looks of 'acceptance'.

This was the prestige of rank eight battle strength!

Sixth Hair also rose his wine bowl with a smile, while inwardly, he was spurting blood from anger.

Fang Yuan glanced at him, smiling: "Elder Sixth Hair, why are your hands trembling?"

Sixth Hair smiled towards him, he indeed was a spy who had lurked for many years, his expression did not show any flaws, it was just his voice that had turned somewhat hoarse: "This is because I am extremely excited for you, Elder Fang Yuan, and for Lang Ya Sect, I am... rejoicing."

Chapter 1144: Refining Gu, Grand Commotion

Snow descended slowly and quietly.

There was no wind.

A series of snowy mountain peaks formed a range.

A couple were snuggling each other near the window, looking outside at the snowy landscape.

There was a warm atmosphere in the room.

The wife was neat and graceful, some white color was already beginning to show in her hair. She leaned on her husband's arm and spoke with nostalgia: "It has been so long since I watched the snowy landscape with you this serenely..."

Her husband already looked old but was in good health, he comfortingly patted his wife's arm with his aged hand, and spoke slowly: "I would like to stay with you always and watch the snowflakes fall quietly. Do you still remember the time we first met?"

His wife chuckled, the joyous memory seemed to be resurfacing in front of her eyes: "That was also a snowy day, you were still hotheaded, wanting to become stronger and stronger."

"I wanted to become stronger, wasn't it for the sake of becoming worthy of you? Back then, you said you would marry me when I cultivate to rank eight. Hehe." The old man laughed, his laughter had some craftiness as well as some pride.

His wife's smile, however, shrank slightly, and her brows furrowed: "To tell the truth, I regret it a little. I would rather your cultivation be slightly lower."

"To be your husband, how could I have lower cultivation level? Rest assured, as long as we refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, I have confidence in passing this myriad tribulation, then our future will be boundless as the sea and sky, and I can stay with you forever." As he said this, the old man's sight slowly became sharper, revealing an extraordinarily powerful aura.

His aura went from weak to strong, continuously growing stronger. As time passed, it actually flowed outside, causing the surrounding snowflakes to stop falling, and float in front of him.

His wife slowly moved away from him, quietly looking at the snowy landscape as a firm will emerged in her eyes.

"Let us begin." After a long while, the old man spoke, breaking the silence.

His wife only replied with one word: "Okay."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou began refining fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu!

On this day, gorgeous lights shot out to the sky from Snowy Mountain blessed land, unable to be hidden or concealed!

Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world had yet to recover from the commotion of Hei tribe's annihilation, but now, it fell into upheaval once again.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu had begun refining rank eight fortune rivalling heaven Gu!

This news was like a whirlwind that engulfed the whole Northern Plains Gu Immortal world.

Feng Xian grotto-heaven.

"Such a grand show, as if he is afraid others won't come to wreck his plan. But this is indeed Old Xue Hu's style." Prince Feng Xian chuckled indifferently at the news.

"Lord, if we let Old Ancestor Xue Hu successfully refine the rank eight Immortal Gu, I am afraid he would just get much stronger." Gu Immortal You Lan spoke from beside Prince Feng Xian.

"Even without fortune rivalling heaven Gu, he is still the number one expert of Northern Plains. Our current task is to capture Fang Yuan. We have already obtained news from that side, Heavenly Court has deduced and confirmed Fang Yuan is in Northern Plains!" Prince Feng Xian laughed, his eyes shining with cold light.

His hatred towards Fang Yuan was deep.

The reason?

Because Prince Feng Xian's original task had been to infiltrate Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. But the grand plan was destroyed by Fang Yuan, causing his many years of waiting to go down the drain.

Could he not feel hatred?

Bai Zu grotto-heaven.

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu has been fiddling around for these years, he finally decided to act?" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu mumbled, then shook his head.

After that battle with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was even more aware of the other side's strength.

"Just I alone am absolutely not Old Ancestor Xue Hu's opponent. Also, wrecking his refinement plan would mean I will be an irreconcilable enemy of him. But I have now established Bai Zu tribe, this is the result of many years of planning and arduous work, I cannot make a move lightly."

"Unless Yao Huang and some other people want to make a move... before they show any signs, I should concentrate on invading that Hei Fan grotto-heaven instead."

Yao Huang grotto-heaven.

A large cauldron was floating in front of Yao Huang.

It was made from cauldron strength Immortal Gu.

Inside the cauldron were countless immortal materials, the blazing fire below it was constantly melting these immortal materials into liquid and fusing them.

When he heard the news of Old Ancestor Xue Hu's Gu refinement, the fire heating the cauldron trembled.

Yao Huang sighed and mumbled to himself: "Fighting with Old Xue Hu is not wise. Instead, I just need to concentrate on refining this resurrection from the dead Immortal Gu, and I will also possess a rank eight Immortal Gu, and solve the issue of lifespan."

Longevity Heaven.

"Look at those lights soaring to the sky, hmph! Old Ancestor Xue Hu has really started refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu!"

"Even if he is a rank eight Gu Immortal, he is too audacious, to dare to covet Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's Immortal Gu!!"

Longevity Heaven was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's grotto-heaven, the Gu Immortals who lived inside were descendants of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable with the closest bloodline connection to him.

They naturally did not want to see fortune rivalling heaven Gu falling into an outsider's hands.

However!

They were unable to make a move.

Because of one person — Five Elements Grandmaster!

...

"Elder Fang Yuan, please come in, this is our tribe's sacred land — Earth Mother Altar!" Shi Shi Cheng respectfully guided Fang Yuan.

This rockman Gu Immortal was only rank six, but he controlled the immortal battlefield killer move, grey cloud battle puppet, he was clearly a character representing the next generation of the rockmen.

Following with him was also the rank six female Gu Immortal from the snowman tribe, Xue Er.

Right now, some days had already passed since the banquet.

The allied tribes of snowmen and rockmen living here treated Fang Yuan and the hairy man Gu Immortals with utmost cordiality.

According to Lang Ya land spirit's arrangement, Sixth Hair and the others were responsible for negotiating about cooperation and alliance between both sides. As for Fang Yuan, he was accompanied to tour around and view the scenery, becoming familiar with the lifestyle of these variant humans.

Over these last few days, Fang Yuan had deep insight.

These snowmen and rockmen were living in hiding below the northern icy plain, but they were filled with awareness of crisis and were extremely strict in the upbringing of their later generations, almost to the point of cruelty.

This led to generations after generations of powerful variant human Gu Immortals.

Compared to them, Hei Fan grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals formed an extremely clear contrast.

"Elder Fang Yuan, didn't you ask me yesterday why there is such earth and soil below the northern icy plain? You will know once you enter." Xue Er giggled.

"Okay." Fang Yuan nodded, being somewhat curious.

When he entered Earth Mother Altar and saw two statues enshrined at the center, he was left staring.

"This is..."

He was shocked.

Because he saw a female human immortal hugging a rockman Gu Immortal's arm. The two were looking into the distance with blissful expressions, looking like they had lived a charmed life together.

"This is the twenty-seventh first supreme elder of my tribe, Shi Mu, the one beside him is his wife, my tribe's most respected Lady Earth Mother. Of course, as you can see, Lady Earth Mother is a human Gu Immortal." Shi Shi Cheng introduced.

This was somewhat unthinkable.

A female human immortal actually fell in love with a rockman Gu Immortal, and was enshrined and respected by the later generations of rockmen to this degree.

Xue Er continued: "Lady Earth Mother was kind and benevolent, her love transcends race. She was deeply saddened that the rockman tribe did not have land for survival, and not long after Lord Shi Mu passed away, she also died of her own accord to be with her love. For the sake of the later generations, her dao marks and blessed land turned into this underground land, allowing rockmen to have a foundation for survival."

Fang Yuan firmly stared at this couple's statues.

His mind was surging frantically.

Because this Earth Mother, whom the rockmen and snowmen respected and revered, he actually knew her!

Naturally, he and Earth Mother were not people of the same time period, there would normally not have been any link between them. The reason why Fang Yuan could recognize Earth Mother's identity was because he had soul searched Hei Cheng.

Because Earth Mother was the missing Hei Feng Yue of Hei tribe, Old Ancestor Hei Fan's most beloved granddaughter!

"Who could have expected that Hei Feng Yue disappeared as a result of hiding her own identity. She fell in love with a rockman Gu Immortal, this definitely would not have been accepted by the tribe, and even more so, would not have been accepted by the human Gu Immortals in Northern Plains."

"As for why she fell in love and stayed with a rockman Gu Immortal, there definitely must have been a hidden story."

Fang Yuan was expressionless, but was inwardly sighing.

No matter what the truth of the past was, he had no intention to excavate it.

Every person had their own life to lead, their own loved and hated enemies. Right?

Xue Er had been secretly observing Fang Yuan, and seeing Fang Yuan having no expression of disgust or anger, her whole heart felt joyous.

She then looked at the statues of Shi Mu and Earth Mother dazedly, speaking with certain intent: "I won't hide it from Elder Fang Yuan, from my perspective, love has no boundaries! Whether it be rockmen or humans, both have the possibility of existing together and the right to love each other!"

Fang Yuan went absent-minded.

A beautiful white figure flashed across his eyes.

But it disappeared shortly afterwards.

"The five hundred years of my first life..." His gaze turned deep and serene.

He slightly realized now.

Why this group of snowmen and rockmen accepted him so easily after knowing Fang Yuan was on the same side.

From a certain aspect, Fang Yuan could also be considered to have received Earth Mother's help.

"Actually, we were compelled by the situation to fight with Elder Fang Yuan. Elder Fang Yuan must also be clear on how the northern icy plain was formed. This was previously a pure icy land, only with Lady Earth Mother's profound methods, did this area start gathering earth qi and form this soil."

Shi Shi Cheng earnestly continued: "However, when a Gu Immortal faces their tribulation in the northern icy plain, it would draw in and consume heaven and earth qi. Every time the earth qi is weakened, the northern icy plain will get more unstable, and the land we can live on will decrease by a portion in area."

Fang Yuan nodded, he already knew of this reason during the banquet, now his understanding had become even deeper.

"This is my fault. If I had known this before, I would not have undergone my calamity in the northern icy plain!" Fang Yuan earnestly spoke.

Shi Shi Cheng and Xue Er's face brightened.

"If misunderstandings can be solved, that is for the best." Shi Shi Cheng spoke.

Right at this time, Shi Shi Cheng's expression changed, shortly afterwards Xue Er's expression also changed.

"What's wrong?" Fang Yuan quickly asked.

"Lights are soaring to the sky from Snowy Mountain blessed land, our information claims that Old Ancestor Xue Hu has begun refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu." Shi Shi Cheng spoke in a heavy tone.

Any human growing stronger was grievous news to variant humans.

Xue Er's eyes shifted to Fang Yuan: "Elder Fang Yuan, you used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth and are an otherworldly demon, you even destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building by your own hands. I would like to ask if Old Ancestor Xue Hu succeeds in refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu in the future?"

Chapter 1145: Rank Eight Determines The Situation

A number of days had passed since the hairy man Gu Immortals from Lang Ya Sect came in touch and started discussing with this group of snowmen and rockmen.

The more they talked, the more they found common topics between each other.

This was decided by the external factors.

Human forces were incomparably big, while the variant human tribes could only barely survive in isolated parts of the world, like this place. They were naturally inclined towards allying.

Although Sixth Hair was a spy inserted by Shadow Sect into Lang Ya Sect, he did not oppose the alliance of the two sides, instead even working hard for it.

On one hand, Sixth Hair knew very well that just by himself, he could not make the two sides turn hostile to each other.

On another hand, Sixth Hair also took this chance to show his skills and obtain more contribution points, letting Lang Ya land spirit put more trust in him and increasing his status.

Finally, Shadow Sect's goal was Spectral Soul's goal. Although the Demon Venerable had died, his aspirations were already beyond the boundaries of race.

Both sides discussed, each understanding more about the other. Sixth Hair even sold almost all the intel about Fang Yuan to get more trust from the other side.

Thus, snowmen and rockmen knew how special Fang Yuan's status was.

Fang Yuan once possessed Spring Autumn Cicada and was a person who had been reborn.

He was also an otherworldly demon who came from a foreign world.

He was also the main culprit for the destruction of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Imperial Court blessed land.

It was worth mentioning that the last point made the variant human Gu Immortals feel even closer to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, greatly weakening the human forces of Northern Plains, which was an extremely good thing to variant human forces. They were so joyous that, in the past, when they heard about Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's destruction, this allied group of snowmen and rockmen even had a banquet for three days and three nights.

Inside Earth Mother Altar, hearing Xue Er ask about the future, Fang Yuan replied with a bitter smile, having already prepared beforehand: "Although I had Spring Autumn Cicada, I have already lost this mystical Gu. After I was reborn, there have been many changes in the world. You also know that I made Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapse, right?"

"Yes, Elder Fang Yuan, you are truly amazing." Xue Er said with bright eyes.

"I also feel extreme admiration towards you about this." Shi Shi Cheng also added.

Fang Yuan rubbed his nose and sighed: "I am a person who had been reborn, and knew some secrets. Although I am not of the Huang Jin bloodline, I participated in the fight for Imperial Court to get some benefits from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. My original plan was to visit time after time to get unending benefits. But plans can't keep up with changes, some accidents happened and I could only adapt to the circumstances, finally causing the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

Xue Er and Shi Shi Cheng revealed joyous smiles.

Shi Shi Cheng said: "Elder Fang Yuan's words make sense."

Fang Yuan shook his head in helpless fashion: "Who wants to be chased by all the Gu Immortals in the world? That was truly an accident."

Xue Er smiled: "From what I see, Elder Fang Yuan, you are a natural hero, although you destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building accidentally, if it were someone else, would they be able to do it?"

"It is because of this I had no choice but to hide in Lang Ya blessed land, later on, things happened and I joined Lang Ya Sect. While living over there, I slowly discovered that the traits of variant humans were actually not weaker than humans. Their sincerity, trust and loyalty and so on far surpass the humans who always try to deceive each other. Although the five regions are vast, the survival space of variant humans is shrinking by the day, this is not right. Heaven's will permits all living beings to exist, variant humans and humans should indeed co-exist."

Fang Yuan's face did not show shame in the slightest when he said this.

He even brought up heaven's will, which was trying every way possible to eradicate him.

Fang Yuan had a sincere expression, so vivid that it could not be more realistic, Xue Er's eyes even reddened from hearing these words.

Shi Shi Cheng was extremely moved: "If other human Gu Immortals were all as understanding and knowledgeable as Lord Fang Yuan, the world would be much better!"

In his words, he had already raised Fang Yuan from elder to lord, even speaking to him respectfully.

Indeed, Fang Yuan's words were extremely politically correct as far as variant humans were concerned, inciting resonance and approval with their minds.

"But Elder Fang Yuan, you have yet to answer my question." Xue Er was intelligent and not easy to deceive.

"I was just getting there." Fang Yuan coughed, "Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's destruction was not my intention. In fact, before I had reborn, it had never fallen!"

"Ah? Is that so." Xue Er and Shi Shi Cheng looked at each other.

"Northern Plains' situation has changed too much because of me. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was destroyed, Ma Hong Yun was kidnapped and his possession of fortune rivalling heaven Gu was exposed so quickly, with him being bought by Old Ancestor Xue Hu. Before I was reborn, there was simply no event of Old Ancestor Xue Hu trying to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu." Fang Yuan added.

These words were all true.

Xue Er and Shi Shi Cheng both chose to believe them.

The former slightly pursed her lips: "Then doesn't it mean it is difficult to deduce the result? If we really let Old Ancestor Xue Hu refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu, the strength of Northern Plains' human Gu Immortals will rise by another level."

Fang Yuan's thoughts turned, questioning: "Could it be that you want to stop it?"

He had no choice but to admit this allied group of snowmen and rockmen had the power to interfere in this matter.

Because they had an immemorial rock dragon, this was a genuine rank eight battle strength.

Moreover, it was an existence which was very hard to deal with among rank eight battle strengths.

The immemorial rock dragon's might was recorded and emphasized heavily in the historical records.

"Of course not!" Shi Shi Cheng shook his head, "We absolutely cannot interfere in this."

"Yes. We have been living peacefully here, why would we expose ourselves and go offend a rank eight expert? Moreover this rank eight expert controls Snowy Mountain blessed land, with large numbers of demonic path experts under him." Xue Er also shook her head.

They were very aware of the situation.

Even if they seized fortune rivalling heaven Gu for their own use, they would be exposing themselves, attracting the joint pursuit of the whole of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

All the human forces would come rushing over, at that time, forget fortune rivalling heaven Gu, even if there were several more immemorial rock dragons, they would be unable to stop the humans.

Fang Yuan nodded and did not say anything, while inwardly pondering.

"These variant humans are indeed not ordinary, I have seen all the variant human Gu Immortals over these days, each of them is an elite. Whether it be their battle strength or foresight, they are outstanding in both. Even among the Northern Plains' human Gu Immortal circle, they would be excellent. When compared to them, Hei Fan grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals would be way behind. Fortunately, I had rank eight battle strength with me!"

So what if he was an otherworldly demon?

So what if he had Spring Autumn Cicada and was a reborn person?

These statuses and mysteries, when they were stacked on his rank eight battle strength as foundation, they become a part of a glorious halo, and not a source of trouble.

When one had great strength, who would dare to find trouble?

Rank eight battle strength!

With just a flick of their finger, they could crush others like ants.

This was the reason the snowmen and rockmen not only did not dare to find trouble with Fang Yuan, they also expressed cordial stances and attempted to rope him in.

Anyone of rank eight battle strength was of sufficient value for others to rope in.

In the absence of rank nine, rank eights were the overlords. This was already among the peak battle strength in the world.

"In fact, the whole of Northern Plains' situation and structure is a result of rank eight Gu Immortals conflicting with each other. The politics of a world having individuals with great strength is always dictated by the strongest people!"

Fang Yuan was well aware of this.

"But if they know my upper extreme heavenly eagle is already dead, I wonder what kind of expressions these people will have?" Fang Yuan found it somewhat funny as he thought of this.

He forcibly sped up the growth of the upper extreme heavenly eagle, using time path killer moves, but with insufficient heavenly crystals, it was on the verge of dying from hunger.

He then used blood path methods to raise its vitality when he let it out, and successfully shook the variant human immortals. Relying on his bluffs and deception, he was able to survive, and change the situation.

However, the upper extreme heavenly eagle was like the last radiance of the setting sun. After Fang Yuan placed it in his immortal aperture, it died at almost the very next moment.

An immemorial desolate beast dying of hunger, this life of the upper extreme heavenly eagle was indeed somewhat depressing.

But!

That might not be the case in its next life.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle's amazing trait was that it would produce an egg after its death. When the egg hatches, it would once again be reborn.

It was true that Fang Yuan lost the immemorial desolate beast upper extreme heavenly eagle, but similarly, he obtained an upper extreme heavenly eagle's egg, and also the immemorial desolate beast's giant corpse.

He could completely accept this result!

Because first of all, Fang Yuan was not satisfied with this upper extreme heavenly eagle. He had to disguise as a person of Hei tribe's bloodline to command it.

Secondly, many flaws appeared after the upper extreme heavenly eagle was forcefully grown. With rank eight battle strength, how could such a grand being let Fang Yuan, a rank six Gu Immortal, control it? Let alone when the upper extreme heavenly eagle was an extremely prideful beast. It was certain that the upper extreme heavenly eagle would not listen when it was forcefully grown into being of rank eight battle strength, there was even a huge possibility of it rebelling and turning against Fang Yuan because of its strong pride in itself.

As a result, the upper extreme heavenly eagle dying was not bad news to Fang Yuan.

As for the new egg, Fang Yuan could rely on the contents of Hei Fan's true inheritance to change it, tampering with its memories and so on, such that when it hatches, it would directly obey Fang Yuan.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was openly refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu, the refinement path Gu formation's light even shot up to the heavens, shining brightly for seven days and seven nights before it gradually dissipated.

This matter caused strong turbulence in the whole of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

However.

After the shock, the Gu Immortal world of Northern Plains strangely quietened down.

This was because Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, Yao Huang, Five Elements Grandmaster and Prince Feng Xian had not responded yet. Without these rank eight Gu Immortals speaking up, even if the other rank six and rank sevens clamored, it would be of no use.

Being able to battle a rank eight existence with rank seven cultivation, within the last few thousand years of the five regions, only Feng Jiu Ge could do it.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu did matters rampantly and tyrannically, but one had to say he not only had brawn but also brains, picking up such an extremely opportune time.

This group of variant humans under the northern icy plain also chose to watch by the sidelines.

As for Fang Yuan himself, he similarly had no thoughts of participating in this matter.

This matter was too big, it concerned the rank eight great expert Old Ancestor Xue Hu, although Fang Yuan currently was stronger than before, if he interfered in this matter, he would easily be turned into mush.

Chapter 1146: Four Races Alliance

Three days went by.

Underground of the icy plain, Earth Mother Altar.

Four incense sticks were lit and the smoke coiled up to the air, Gu Immortals were standing by a side with solemn expressions, the four camps clearly differentiated.

Fang Yuan was also among them, the people beside him were Lang Ya Sect's hairy man Gu Immortals.

A melodious bugle call resounded, and then the drums roared.

Shi Zong took a large step ahead during the drum sounds, speaking in a loud voice: "I, Gu Immortal Shi Zong of the rockman tribe, am willing to join the four races alliance. From today onwards, the four races shall be united, we shall share fortune and woe together."

He then activated his immortal essence, causing some changes in the Earth Mother Altar.

The smoke that was curling up in the air surged towards Shi Zong, and after coiling around for a dozen breaths, they completely merged into Shi Zong's body.

"Adding on information path dao marks! It seems to be an ancient method..." Fang Yuan inwardly pondered.

Originally, the hairy men were discussing about an alliance with the allied group of snowman and rockman tribes.

But the matter went unexpectedly smoothly, as both sides were increasingly in agreement with the alliance. The hairy men's side even took the initiative to mention bringing Inkman City in too.

After the allied group of snowmen and rockmen understood the details, they agreed to it.

Long Hair Ancestor and Immortal Yi Yan were publicly known to be bosom friends in history. Long Hair Ancestor left Lang Ya blessed land behind while Immortal Yi Yan founded Inkman City. The inkmen and hairy men from these places thus always had close relations.

Since the hairy men's side vouched for the inkmen, the allied rockmen and snowmen tribes also chose to believe them.

As a result, the discussion between the three sides became one involving four variant human races.

Finally, the three sides reached a consensus and were willing to form an alliance, sharing hardships together and assisting each other from now on.

The current scene was a result of that.

The three sides used an ancient information path method to officially form an alliance.

Gu Immortals took turns to go forward and accept the effect of the information path dao marks. As such, they became members of the four races alliance.

Time passed, Fang Yuan gradually understood some of the mechanics.

"This does not seem to be an orthodox information path method, but instead earth path is used to get the effect of information path. Just like my time path immortal killer move — Hundred Years Harmony."

Fang Yuan's heart sank as he thought of this.

It was going to be troublesome if he wanted to break this alliance agreement in the future. Because it did not seem likely that he could resolve it using information path. Most probably, it needed to be resolved with earth path methods.

"Elder Fang Yuan, it's your turn." At this time, Twelfth Hair reminded softly from the side in a warm tone.

Speaking of which, ever since the matter of the falling star hound was resolved and the news of Fang Yuan obtaining an immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle was known, the hairy man Gu Immortals' attitudes towards Fang Yuan had a complete change, becoming reverential, forming a stark contrast from before.

Fang Yuan nodded and walked to the front without hesitation, and just like what the rockman Gu Immortal Shi Zong did, he allowed the incense smoke to imprint on his body.

His every action was being observed by the immortals present on the scene.

Seeing that he had truly joined the alliance, the group of immortals slightly relaxed, letting go of another layer of worry. The smile on Xue Er became even more lovely.

Little could they imagine that Fang Yuan was already thinking of how to break the restrictions of the alliance agreement.

He naturally could not follow along with the aims and mindsets of these variant humans.

Even entering Lang Ya Sect was to make it more convenient to use Lang Ya blessed land's strength.

Similarly, joining this four races alliance was because Fang Yuan was forced by the situation and also because it would be easier for him to borrow the strength of the alliance to help in his cultivation.

"To truly have me be of the same faction as variant humans and resist humans, that is impossible!"

"Humans have absolute dominance, even if these four variant human tribes have allied, what can they do?"

"However, this strength also cannot be underestimated. In my first life, did these four groups really ally?"

Fang Yuan's thoughts had started to drift as he pondered.

He did not know the answer to this question.

In his first life, he had been a rank six blood path Gu Immortal. In matters regarding the Northern Plains Gu Immortal world, he did not have enough understanding. Especially these kinds of behind the scenes details, even Northern Plains' Gu Immortals might not be aware.

"But I do know there had been no news of these snowman and rockman tribes in my first life, maybe they were annihilated or maybe they were still living, hiding from the world. Lang Ya blessed land had also not established a sect, and was finally destroyed by Heavenly Court. On the contrary, the inkman tribe did surprisingly well."

As he thought of this, Fang Yuan sneaked a glance at Mo Tan Sang.

This person only had rank six cultivation and cultivated qi path. Qi path had much longer history than strength path, but was similarly a declining Gu cultivation path.

Mo Tan Sang had a middle-aged appearance, he had black skin and thick white hair. He appeared quite dignified when he did not smile, and when he smiled, he gave people a feeling of great closeness.

"This person is also a formidable character." Fang Yuan inwardly appraised.

He remembered that in the five regions chaotic war, this Mo Tan Sang took advantage of the lack of attention paid to him due to the human tribes being too busy in their internal conflicts, to develop rapidly, greatly expanding the inkman forces.

When the Northern Plains human forces wanted to suppress him, he actually disregarded his dignity as the king and threw himself to Liu tribe. He took a servant's rite to Liu tribe's supreme elder and became a servant to him.

Liu tribe was one of the super forces, thus the inkman forces were protected. The inkman forces grew stably under this layer of protection.

Later, when Liu tribe weakened, the Inkman King immediately gave up on Liu tribe to collaborate with Ma Hong Yun on equal terms.

Before Fang Yuan self-detonated, the inkmen had hundreds of cities and occupied one-third of northern plains' lands. If Fang Yuan were to talk of such a scale and force, no one would believe him.

In this four races alliance, the inkman tribe was undoubtedly the weakest.

But in Fang Yuan's first life, it was the inkmen who were thriving.

Mo Tan Sang knew when to advance and when to yield, he was a spiritual figure representing the rise of the inkman tribe. At the same time, it was also because of the external environment. In the five regions chaotic war, all order collapsed, opportunities and risks were everywhere.

As if sensing Fang Yuan's gaze, Mo Tan Sang turned back to look at Fang Yuan, immediately smiling, expressing sincerity and kindness.

This kindness was so deep and clear that when he smiled, he was almost bowing, even giving the feeling of some flattery.

Fang Yuan snorted inwardly, while returning the smile on the surface.

Mo Tan Sang's expression changed slightly, showing a feeling of excitement at being recognized by an important person.

If it were others, they would have probably felt a sense of superiority and smugness at this moment.

"Truly formidable." Fang Yuan's own acting skills were beyond ordinary, but this Mo Tan Sang before him was on par with him.

"The world is big, experts and talents emerge every generation, I absolutely cannot look down on these champions." Fang Yuan inwardly reminded himself, his mind remaining cool without any fluctuations.

Northern Plains' situation could be described as going through one wave after another.

The storm of Hei tribe's collapse and takeover by Bai Zu tribe had yet to settle down. Old Ancestor Xue Hu began refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu, attracting the gazes of the whole of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

And behind their backs, at an unknown, secluded area, four variant human races - hairy men, snowmen, rockmen and inkmen - had quietly formed an alliance.

Although variant humans were absolutely in a weaker position, this alliance could not be looked down upon. Because it possessed a rank eight battle strength immemorial rock dragon. Of course, in the minds of the other alliance members, there was also Fang Yuan's upper extreme heavenly eagle.

Fang Yuan was forced to join them.

But what made him feel slightly at ease was there were no wisdom path Gu Immortal among these four tribes.

After the alliance was formed, Fang Yuan's loss was obvious.

That was, from now on, he could not undergo tribulation in the northern icy plain.

This no doubt would influence Fang Yuan greatly.

But he had no choice.

Undergoing tribulation here meant consuming earth qi, which was the greatest damage to the rockmen's home. This was the reason why these rockmen and snowmen did not stint on cost to set up the battlefield killer move, grey cloud battle puppet, to kill Fang Yuan.

But besides loss, Fang Yuan also had gains.

He cleared the way for trading with the rockman and snowman tribes, letting his monthly earnings reach a new level.

Leaving aside the snowmen, the main point were the rockmen, their desire towards guts Gu was higher than humans!

The reason?

It was obvious, when one considered the time Fang Yuan used guts Gu to increase the population of rockmen in Hu Immortal blessed land.

Guts Gu was the best way to grow and develop rockman tribes.

Besides this, Fang Yuan also sold some resources he obtained from Hei Fan grotto-heaven to the rockmen, snowmen and inkmen, making great profits, causing Sixth Hair to worry and rage on the inside.

"Fang Yuan's gains are so huge! What should I do? How can we restrain him in the future?!"

It was time to bid farewell!

"Elder Fang Yuan, you really need to leave so soon? You could stay for another day or two." Xue Er attempted to persuade Fang Yuan to stay.

Fang Yuan shook his head, saying with a warm smile: "We have formed an alliance, this matter is too important, I need to personally return to report to Lang Ya land spirit. You can rest assured, I will be back. We can be considered to be friends made from fighting and I feel quite fond of this place."

Fang Yuan was interested in the snowman Gu Immortals' ice and snow path Immortal Gu, as well as their killer moves.

These two were very suitable for him.

After all, in terms of dao marks, the highest quantity in his body were currently ice and snow path dao marks.

As per the relation between him and the snowman tribe currently, along with rank eight battle strength publicly, he could exchange Immortal Gu. But Fang Yuan did not plan to give up any of his Immortal Gu, he had a better plan.

For instance, some day in the future, when a certain variant human Gu Immortal cannot pass their tribulation and required his time path immortal killer move to slow the time in their immortal aperture.

At that time, Fang Yuan could take the chance to demand Immortal Gu.

In the past, Hei Fan did this many times and obtained a sizable number of Immortal Gu.

Xue Er naturally did not know this handsome young man in front of her was harboring evil intent with his mind full of schemes. She lowered her head as she saw Fang Yuan was intent on leaving, revealing hesitation and a struggling expression.

But soon, her eyes revealed firm intent as she raised her head and handed an item in her hand to Fang Yuan.

"Elder Fang Yuan, take this as my farewell gift to you." Xue Er tried to keep a calm exterior as she spoke, but her voice was still shaking.

Fang Yuan glanced at the item, it was an ice tear drop!

Chapter 1147: Making Chu Du Change Sides?

Ice tears were not an immortal material but was still precious, widely loved by both Gu Masters and Gu Immortals.

Ice tears originated from snowmen.

Snowmen survived in icy environments. Snowmen normally did not cry or laugh, so their tears were very rare. The majority of the snowmen would never experience crying from joy or pain in their lives. But if they shed tears, the tears would immediately condense into ice tears.

Snowmen could shed tears at most three times in their lives and the number would not surpass sixty drops. Every time they shed tears, the snowman's lifespan and life essence would decrease by a huge amount. If the snowman shed too many tears, they would rapidly age, quickening their death.

So ice tears were rare as well.

Transactions of ice tears had always been flourishing in treasure yellow heaven. Long ago, Xue Song Zi had particularly engaged in selling snowmen, supplying them to other Gu Immortals to torment and get the ice tears.

As far as human Gu Immortals were concerned, ice tears were a precious Gu refinement material.

But to snowmen, ice tears had another significant meaning.

That was — a token of love!

That's right!

Snowmen, this race had male and female genders, unlike rockmen who were purely male.

During the marriage of snowmen, they would often exchange ice tears. This action had extremely huge meaning to snowmen.

"This is an ice tear." Fang Yuan's eyes brightened, holding it in front of his eyes and making detailed observation.

"Don't, don't look at it like that, quickly place it down..." Xue Er's voice was soft and anxious. There were many people present, holding the ice tear like that in public was sure to be noticed!

Sure enough, the next moment, Xue Er heard those Gu Immortals' surprised sounds.

Xue Er quickly lowered her head, her face flushing red with shyness.

She handed the ice tear to Fang Yuan, which was as good as expressing her love. Although she had mustered her courage before, now that so many people were looking at her, she was truly, truly embarrassed!

"Speaking of it, I have heard of this strange Gu material long ago. I have now finally seen it personally. Thank you Xue Er, this gift is pretty good. Maybe I should refine it into some Gu worm?" Fang Yuan cheerfully spoke.

Xue Er's body visibly shook.

Fang Yuan turned a blind eye to it, continuing: "But a drop of ice tear is still too little, it would be good if there were some more. Why are there no transactions of ice tears? It is truly regretful."

As Xue Er listened, the shy redness in her face had already dissipated, replaced by pale white. Her head was lowered even more, her sight turning blurry as tears started to form in them.

"This, this fool!" Bing Zhuo could not see it continue, as he inwardly cursed and walked over.

The other variant human Gu Immortals were tongue-tied, not knowing what to say.

Xue Er suddenly raised her head, her back facing Fang Yuan as she called out to Bing Zhuo: "Brother Bing Zhuo!"

Bing Zhuo gritted his teeth, an intense pity rose up in his heart as he saw Xue Er's pale white expression. He knew Xue Er was shy, it had already taken a lot of her courage to hand over the ice tear just now, maybe she had also felt an impulsive urge in her mind. Fang Yuan did not know the meaning of the ice tear, if he criticized Fang Yuan now in front of everyone, would it not put Xue Er in an even more embarrassing situation?

Thinking of this, Bing Zhuo could only swallow the words that were in his mouth, saying something else: "Elder Fang Yuan, I had many gains from battling you. Next time, we should spar properly again!"

When he mentioned sparring, he intentionally made his voice heavier, along with some gnashing noise.

Xue Er was young and beautiful, her talent was outstanding and her cultivation was high, she had all along been receiving the attention and favor of the tribe. It was just that there was no man in the same generation worthy of her.

This time, she felt feelings for Fang Yuan, although he was a human Gu Immortal, the snowman Gu Immortals felt they could accept him.

Rockmen had their Earth Mother, could our snowmen not have a Snow Father?

If Xue Er could marry Fang Yuan, the snowman tribe would possess the backing of an immemorial desolate beast.

But who could have thought Fang Yuan to not be aware of the tradition of these variant humans, treating the ice tear as a common Gu material, making the whole situation awkward. Even Xue Er was put on the spot.

Fang Yuan smiled and patted Bing Zhuo's shoulder: "Alright, I promise you if there is an opportunity in the future, we will spar again. Okay, everyone, I am taking my leave. No need to send me off, we shall meet again in the future. Hahaha."

Fang Yuan laughed heartily and walked away. Adorned in a white robe with long black hair, he looked handsome and extremely carefree.

Xue Er's gaze even turned somewhat dazed.

Bing Zhuo, however, gnashed his teeth, wanting nothing more than to chop this kid Fang Yuan into pieces.

"This can't do! When he has gone far enough, I need to send him a letter, telling him the meaning of the ice tear properly!"

The journey back to Lang Ya blessed land was smooth and without any obstacles.

Seeing Lang Ya land spirit again, the attitude of the first supreme elder of Lang Ya Sect towards Fang Yuan had underwent a huge change.

"You truly inherited Hei Fan's true inheritance? You possess methods to slow the time of an immortal aperture? Also, you actually have an immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle, quickly take it out!" Lang Ya land spirit excitedly asked.

Fang Yuan shook his head bitterly, and took out the corpse of the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

Lang Ya land spirit was stunned on the spot.

Fang Yuan informed Lang Ya land spirit of the whole event.

"A grand immemorial desolate beast was actually starved to death by you?! You... but fortunately, you still have the egg, that's good, that's good, the upper extreme heavenly eagle's special point is this."

Lang Ya land spirit came back to his senses, and looked at Fang Yuan with a burning gaze: "Sell this upper extreme heavenly eagle's egg to me, we can make a deal!"

Fang Yuan laughed: "I can sell this egg!"

Lang Ya land spirit was joyous.

Fang Yuan continued: "But I am afraid you don't have any heavenly crystals to raise it. Even treasure yellow heaven has very few transactions of heavenly crystals."

"Naturally. Heavenly crystals can only be produced in grotto-heavens or the immemorial nine heavens. This is a very precious and rare rank eight immortal material! Right now, only black heaven and white heaven remain from the immemorial nine heavens while the number of rank eight Gu Immortals have always been few. Moreover, among these rank eight Gu Immortals, some are unable to produce heavenly crystals."

As he spoke until here, Lang Ya land spirit shifted his words: "But you don't have to worry about this. My Lang Ya blessed land was once Lang Ya grotto-heaven, it had once produced heavenly crystals, besides this, in the past, my main body had also hoarded a large batch of heavenly crystals from the immemorial nine heavens."

"Ah, since that is the case, I can rest at ease. I will sell it to you." Fang Yuan nodded.

Lang Ya land spirit laughed heartily: "Fang Yuan, since you are one of us, I absolutely won't let you suffer a loss. Luck path true inheritance, Thieving Heaven true inheritance or Long Hair true inheritance, choose as you please."

Fang Yuan's tone sank: "What? I am not too interested in these things. Moreover, isn't this price somewhat low to exchange for a rank eight battle strength?"

Lang Ya land spirit's smile stiffened, he thought for a bit and nodded: "It is indeed so. Then... how about exchanging with my Luo Po Valley?"

Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley were secluded domains of heaven and earth, unique in the whole world. But compared to rank eight battle strength, Lang Ya land spirit would not hesitate to give up on the former and choose the latter!

"Price is too low, not selling, not selling." Fang Yuan refused.

Lang Ya land spirit scratched his head: "How about this, I am willing to give up Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus as well as the incomplete Immortal Gu House Refinement Cauldron in exchange for your upper extreme heavenly eagle!"

Fang Yuan's heart jumped but he still shook his head: "It is still not enough, not selling."

Lang Ya land spirit was furious: "Then give me a price, how much will you sell it for?"

Fang Yuan smiled, emphasizing: "This is of rank eight battle strength!"

Lang Ya land spirit naturally was not foolish, as he retorted: "It is indeed of rank eight battle strength, but it needs to be fed. Do you have heavenly crystals? Also, even if you raise the upper extreme heavenly eagle, will it listen to you? To tell you the truth, you were really lucky this time, starving the upper extreme heavenly eagle to death. If not for this, according to my understanding, this upper extreme heavenly eagle only needs to have some strength left to directly crush you, an ant who tried to enslave it, to death."

Fang Yuan smiled: "If so I am willing to use sect contribution points to exchange for heavenly crystals to raise the upper extreme heavenly eagle. Anyway, I am a supreme elder of Lang Ya Sect and also one of the members of the four races alliance. In the future, if the sect needs me, I will naturally appear."

Lang Ya land spirit was stumped, pondering upon it before he pointed at Fang Yuan's nose and scolded: "Good brat! You had no intent to sell it in the first place and were just making things difficult for me!"

Fang Yuan immediately showed a serious expression, speaking earnestly: "How could I easily give up a rank eight battle strength? But making things difficult for first supreme elder, how could I have such thoughts! It is just that the price is indeed too low."

As he said this, he suddenly thought of another intention of Hei Fan.

Even if Hei Fan's true inheritance was inherited by one of the Gu Immortals in the grotto-heaven, Hei Fan had left the upper extreme heavenly eagle in Iron Eagle blessed land.

With this immemorial desolate beast, even if there was not an inheritor, it would be an extremely huge gain to the tribe!

Lang Ya land spirit sighed, knowing well that Fang Yuan was not wrong, so he stopped persisting on buying.

On one hand, the upper extreme heavenly eagle had already become an egg, making him greatly disappointed. On the other hand, Fang Yuan was not only bound by Lang Ya's alliance agreement, he had also joined the four races alliance, which put Lang Ya land spirit at ease. Finally, he, more or less, knew Fang Yuan's nature.

"Such an ambitious and audacious guy like you absolutely won't easily give up on a rank eight battle strength! But if you want to use sect contribution points to exchange for Lang Ya Sect's heavenly crystals, it won't be easy! Heavenly crystals are rank eight immortal materials, the contribution points you have are many, but you would still not be able to afford them." Lang Ya land spirit's mood became better as he said this.

With heavenly crystals at hand, he could entice Fang Yuan to work for Lang Ya Sect.

By now, Lang Ya land spirit had no choice but to admit Fang Yuan was strong and resourceful, much more useful than other hairy man Gu Immortals!

"Then I will exchange for some first. We can slowly go about this." Fang Yuan intentionally revealed a distressed expression.

Fang Yuan's current sect contribution points were indeed a lot.

He had solved the matter with the falling star hound, earning a thousand sect contribution points at once. And this time, he had discovered the allied tribes of snowmen and rockmen, and succeeded in spurring the four races alliance, the sect contribution points for this were also nearly a thousand!

As such, Fang Yuan's Lang Ya Sect contribution points numbered over two thousand points.

But calculating it, two thousand contribution points were still too little to exchange for the rank eight immortal material, heavenly crystals.

At this moment, Lang Ya land spirit suggested another mission for Fang Yuan: "Aren't you familiar with Domination Immortal Chu Du? Rope him in to our Lang Ya Sect, make him rebel against the humans and become one of us. I can give you another thousand sect contribution points if you do this!"

Chapter 1148: Temporary Rest

Fang Yuan's divine sense was roaming in treasure yellow heaven.

"Oh?" His divine sense stopped for a moment.

A Gu Immortal's will was at the side, with a mountain of goods behind him.

"These are all slippery soil?" Fang Yuan took the initiative and asked.

Han Yu's Gu Immortal will awakened from slumber, seeing a customer, he quickly said: "These are all slippery soil!"

After reporting the price, he asked: "Sir, how much are you buying?"

Slippery soil was a type of rank five material, the soil was very fertile.

Fang Yuan nodded mentally, this was a very appropriate price, it was even lower than the normal market price. He needed this soil anyway, he said: "I'll take them all."

Han Yu's will shook: "Everything? I have a huge stock."

Fang Yuan confirmed: "Yes, everything. Two hundred and two immortal essence stones, that is the price, right?"

Han Yu's will quickly nodded: "Yes, yes."

Inside treasure yellow heaven, any form of goods would have treasure light emitting from them.

Fang Yuan could estimate the price by looking at the treasure light and the goods themselves.

He was a wisdom path grandmaster, after all.

"Let's trade." Fang Yuan said quickly.

"Alright, alright." Han Yu's will quickly nodded and responded.

The situation was out of his expectations.

He was only a rank six Gu Immortal who had passed one heavenly tribulation, he was trying hard in developing his blessed land. He wanted to sell the slippery soil in his blessed land, and because of his past experiences, he even lowered the price by a little, to think that it was going to be sold out so quickly!

This was great news to him.

Han Yu's will carried two hundred and two immortal essence stones, the entire will's body was shaking, he was very excited.

"In my previous life, I was just like this." Fang Yuan saw this and sighed internally.

Han Yu was the norm among most rank six Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan, during his previous life, had even been inferior, because he was a blood path Gu Immortal.

But it was different now!

Just the guts Gu trade, which was a monopoly, was bringing him immense profits.

After taking the resources of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan's own wealth had reached an unprecedented level. Not just two hundred immortal essence stones, he could take out two thousand without batting an eyelid.

All in all, Fang Yuan's financial situation was quite good now.

After buying the slippery soil, Fang Yuan moved his divine sense around and went to buy several types of soil.

After reaching his goal, Fang Yuan withdrew his divine sense and brought the soils back to the sovereign immortal aperture.

He controlled the strength path immortal zombies, they scattered the soils into different areas of Mini Southern Border in the sovereign immortal aperture.

The scenery in Mini Southern Border had already drastically changed.

Forests were everywhere, causing greenery to overwhelm the lands. Tall ancient trees and pine trees, the straight cottonwood, the short shrubs, and an uncountable number of grass and flowers made Mini Southern Border vivid and full of life all of a sudden.

These were just ordinary plants, there were lots of high grade resources mixed in among them.

Like the musical trees, they were in the greatest quantity!

This type of tree had curvy branches, they were quite unique. There were birds on the branches, mostly qi death birds, they had distinct calls and chirped loudly.

Originally, Mini Southern Border was completely empty, but it was quite lively now.

Other than birds, there were lots of deer, squirrels, monkeys, snakes, tigers, and other animals, they formed into a proper ecological cycle.

Originally, Mini Southern Border only had a few mounds.

But now, there were more than ten mountains here.

These mountains were all moved in by Fang Yuan from Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Ordinary Gu Immortals could not move mountains, but his pulling mountain Immortal Gu could be used for this.

Right now, among the mountains, the tallest one was Immortal Succession Mountain.

The stone pavilions were still on the mountain, Fang Yuan did not remove them, but the inheritances inside were all taken away.

After a long time, Fang Yuan finally finished controlling all of the immortal zombies to scatter the soil at their proper locations.

Fang Yuan observed for a while, before stopping in satisfaction.

"With these soils, these plants would be able to grow well for some time."

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had few earth path dao marks, the space was also very big, it had five regions and nine heavens, Mini Southern Border could not have many earth path dao marks after they were distributed.

With few earth path dao marks, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture would not have mountains forming, the soil would not be thick or fertile.

The vegetation in Mini Southern Border was almost completely from Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, these plants and trees were growing well, they were dense and green.

But after moving into Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, because of the sparse earth path dao marks, they were drying out, and appeared to be lacking nutrients.

Fang Yuan could only buy lots of fertile soil, like slippery soil, to scatter them in Mini Southern Border, resolving the problem.

"But this does not solve the underlying issue!"

"These different soils will turn into ordinary soil after some time, the earth path dao marks in them would dissipate."

These soils were just mortal Gu materials, they had fragmented earth path dao marks in them. After the grass and trees absorb the nutrients, these scattered earth path dao marks would mostly vanish.

"Only by undergoing tribulation or absorbing the dao marks of an earth path Gu Immortal, to increase the earth path dao marks in the immortal aperture, can I resolve the problem." Fang Yuan knew this clearly.

Fang Yuan could not undergo the fifth earthly calamity in the northern icy plain anymore. This time, he could choose to go Southern Border, or any place with rich earth path dao marks for his tribulation, hoping to encounter an earth path earthly calamity.

Once he encountered an earth path earthly calamity, after going through it, Fang Yuan's problem would be alleviated.

As for killing an earth path Gu Immortal to absorb their dao marks, it was not easy.

Earth path Gu Immortals with low cultivation level did not have many earth path dao marks. And those with high cultivation level were too strong, there was too great of a risk for Fang Yuan to deal with them.

Until now, Fang Yuan had already gone through four earthly calamities.

The first was the snow monster calamity, there were iron crown eagles, ruin bats and others. The second was the wind flowers and snow moons calamity, the third was the spring dawn jade orioles and giant disaster blazing trees, the fourth was the profound white flying salt calamity.

Because the sovereign immortal aperture surpassed the ten extreme physiques combined, heaven's will was wary of it, during each earthly calamity, it would increase the strength of the earthly calamity to the greatest limit allowed.

Earthly calamities of such difficulty greatly surpassed other Gu Immortals, by several or even over a dozen times.

Thus, Fang Yuan also made incredible gains, he obtained more than a dozen times the dao marks each tribulation!

As a result, Fang Yuan had the highest number of ice and snow path dao marks, followed by transformation path, strength path, qi path, rule path, there were also some from luck path, blood path, and others.

The entire sovereign immortal aperture had improved drastically after obtaining Hei Fan grotto-heaven's resources.

Because the space was huge, at the moment, only Mini Southern Border was quite lively, even though the other areas had some resources, they did not have such a complete ecosystem as Mini Southern Border.

There were many desolate beasts, giant horned sheep, shark fin wolves, dragonfish, eagle hounds and others. In terms of ancient desolate beasts, he had remnant heavenly dogs and a falling star hound (infant). He also had an immemorial desolate beast, that was the upper extreme heavenly eagle, but it had turned into an egg already.

There were some desolate plants too, he even had an ancient desolate plant, that was the walking meat tree.

All in all, Fang Yuan's accumulated resources currently matched Gu Immortals at the peak of rank seven. Chu Du was probably similar to Fang Yuan now. As for Feng Jiu Ge, he was heavily nurtured by a super force, Fang Yuan was still inferior to him.

After scattering the soil, Fang Yuan's concentration returned to soul searching the captive Gu Immortals' souls.

Fang Yuan's immortal aperture had many Gu Immortal captives, in fact.

There were many Gu Immortal souls.

The focus of his soul search this time was on the nine Gu Immortal souls in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Feng Jun's luck path true inheritance and Chen Le's concealment method were quite impressive, Fang Yuan was interested in them.

"You are not Hei Cheng! Who are you?"

"You unscrupulous scoundrel, kill me if you dare!"

"Spare me, please spare me, as long as you resurrect me, I will be your most loyal servant!"

Among these Gu Immortal souls, some questioned him, some cursed him and wanted to die, while some wanted to survive.

Fang Yuan did not conceal himself as Hei Cheng anymore, after all, familiar face also needed to consume immortal essence, and attitude Gu needed to use his mental energy.

Towards these Gu Immortals' cries, Fang Yuan ignored them, he soul searched them without pause.

Every day, he would soul search them for a period of time.

"In about three days, I will be done searching the memories of these souls, I would know everything about them."

After his soul searching, Fang Yuan collated his gains, retracting his mind.

He left the cloud city, moving towards Luo Po Valley.

There, his soul went out of his body, as he underwent tough soul path cultivation.

Fang Yuan had already used Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley for some time, his soul foundation had already reached dozens of times as before!

However, he was still not confident of placing his soul into his original body.

"This problem is the most troublesome."

"Even if my soul foundation increases, it is still hard to avoid Shadow Sect's possible hidden methods."

"Who knows, Ying Wu Xie's arrangements might become stronger if my soul has greater foundation. Perhaps the stronger my soul, the deeper Shadow Sect's trap."

"Ying Wu Xie knows I have Luo Po Valley and Dang Hun Mountain, when setting the trap, there is no way he did not consider these details."

His daily soul cultivation ended, Fang Yuan's soul returned to his body, he stood up shakily.

He had a grim expression.

As long as he could use wisdom Gu, his strength would increase at an explosive rate!

Many development problems he was facing now were related to wisdom Gu.

As long as he could use wisdom Gu, many problems would be resolved instantly.

"I have wisdom Gu, and the strength path immortal zombie body, I just need that final key!" Fang Yuan mentally sighed helplessly.

Just like this, Fang Yuan stayed in Lang Ya blessed land for seven days.

He cultivated unceasingly, he did not relax for even a minute.

His soul foundation grew again, he completely searched the souls of the nine Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan also used half of his Lang Ya Sect contribution points to trade for some heavenly crystals and even put up some Gu refinement missions.

Self will Gu, year Gu, month Gu, day Gu, as well as all the other mortal Gu, he needed a huge quantity of them.

He would rather spend sect contribution points to get these mortal Gu, getting the hairy man Gu Masters and Gu Immortals to refine them for him. This could save him a lot of time and energy.

Seven days later, he left Lang Ya blessed land, heading for Eastern Sea!

Chapter 1149: Desiring the Information Path Inheritance

The great winds blew, carrying the salty flavor of the sea water.

Fang Yuan sat on top of a cloud, he traveled quickly while splitting his attention towards the information path mortal Gu in his hand.

This mortal Gu was from Bing Zhuo.

The snowman Gu Immortal who dual wielded spears and was skilled at close combat, he told Fang Yuan in the letter: the ice tear had significant meaning to the snowman tribe, it was not just a Gu refinement material, it was the token of one's love.

"Hmph." Fang Yuan smiled coldly, he crushed that information path mortal Gu in his hands.

Pure white clouds carried him on his journey. The wind caused his hair to flutter in the sky, he had a fair face like jade, he was extremely handsome, almost enchanting, his dark abyss-like eyes looked down at the deep blue sea, showing traces of cold flickering light.

How could Fang Yuan not know about the meaning of the ice tear to the snowmen?

Don't forget, he was someone who had lived for five hundred years, even though his cultivation level was not high, his knowledge was definitely vast.

Not just the ice tear, Fang Yuan had deep knowledge regarding the wine culture of variant humans.

During the earlier banquet, Sixth Hair accused Fang Yuan of not knowing about the variant human drinking culture. In fact, Fang Yuan was just pretending to not know, he was probing the attitude of the snowmen and rockmen.

Sometimes, acting ignorant allows someone to have more options.

The matter of the ice tear was like this. Fang Yuan pretended to be unaware, but he knew it clearly on the inside.

Accepting the ice tear was accepting Xue Er's love. But if he did not accept it, he would ruin the cooperative relationship between himself and the snowmen and rockmen.

Getting together with Xue Er?

The disadvantages were greater than the advantages!

The snowman tribe was after Fang Yuan's rank eight battle strength, from the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

Disregarding how much benefits Fang Yuan could gain from the snowman tribe, just this point alone, he could not fulfill it.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle had already become an egg.

Even though Fang Yuan spent a portion of his Lang Ya Sect contribution points to get some heavenly crystals, the amount was not enough. He could not hatch the upper extreme heavenly eagle egg yet.

"Marrying Xue Er would tie me closely to the snowman tribe. We would be sure to establish a marriage agreement. Right now, I already have Lang Ya Sect's agreement and Chu Du's alliance agreement, there is also the alliance agreement of the four races, my freedom is greatly limited now. If I add in the marriage agreement, aren't I just finding problems for myself?"

While Fang Yuan benefited from these alliance agreements, he also had to undergo missions for them in return.

For example, if Lang Ya blessed land was attacked by enemies, Fang Yuan would have to reinforce them and fight to his death if needed.

Lang Ya land spirit followed the rules, because the land spirit was not crafty like humans, it followed the rules of Lang Ya Sect closely and did not restrict Fang Yuan.

But the snowman tribe was different.

They were variant humans, their intelligence was lower than humans. But after being suppressed for so many years, and living pitifully in the northern icy plain, the immense pressure for survival had honed their strong battle strength and keen perception.

If Fang Yuan wanted to marry a snowman, the snowman tribe would do everything they could to squeeze out Fang Yuan's value!

By then, Fang Yuan would unable to help himself.

"The snowmen and rockmen live under the northern icy plain. The rockmen have the immemorial rock dragon, it has rank eight battle strength, but the snowmen do not. Thus, they want me to marry Xue Er, so that they can also have rank eight battle strength and contest evenly with the rockman tribe."

Do not look at how cohesive the rockmen and snowmen were when attending to Fang Yuan.

Were they really living in such harmony?

The two sides were living under the icy plain, sharing a tiny area together, how could there not be conflicts? They were two different races after all.

But because of the big picture, they maintained reason and tolerated each other.

One could imagine that the rockman tribe with the immemorial rock dragon would usually win when there were conflicts. The snowmen must have suffered many losses, but they endured it all along.

The rockman tribe had greater status after all.

This could be seen from many small details during the alliance.

For example, the Gu Immortal Shi Zong usually was the first to speak, instead of the snowman Gu Immortals.

"If I marry Xue Er, no, even if I just accept her feelings, it would mean that I am siding with the snowmen. Unavoidably, I would be involved in the conflict between both the rockmen and snowmen."

Once there were internal conflicts, Xue Er would find Fang Yuan and hope that he would mediate their conflicts, as an ally, he could not reject them.

But the rockman tribe gave Fang Yuan more benefits.

After all, they were trading guts Gu.

How could Fang Yuan ruin his relationship with the rockmen just because of a woman, and cause his gains to be smaller?

These last days, not just Bing Zhuo's letter, he had also obtain letters from other inkman, snowman, and rockman Gu Immortals.

Including Xue Er.

Their intent was to rope in Fang Yuan.

Rank eight battle strength was simply too alluring!

The reason why Fang Yuan left Northern Plains and went to Eastern Sea was to avoid these Gu Immortals. It also meant that he could avoid many problems in the future.

"I am purely making use of these variant humans. But our relationship is uncontrollably deepening. Once any mishaps happen, I will die along with them. I need to leave and gain freedom, so that I can retreat with ease." Fang Yuan was well aware of the situation.

Furthermore, Lang Ya land spirit was showing the intention of recruiting Chu Du, this made Fang Yuan feel great threat.

Should Chu Du join, it would greatly affect Fang Yuan's status in Lang Ya Sect.

The reason why Lang Ya land spirit wanted to recruit Chu Du was also worth considering.

Even though Lang Ya land spirit gave him this mission, Fang Yuan decided to stall it. He was not going to be so stupid as to wholeheartedly try recruiting Chu Du.

"Eastern Sea information path inheritance..." Fang Yuan thought to himself.

This was one of the reasons why he was in Eastern Sea.

If Fang Yuan could obtain a method from this information path inheritance to get rid of the restrictions of the alliance agreements, that would be best.

Fang Yuan would gain the complete initiative within his alliances.

However, this information path inheritance was only his secondary objective, Fang Yuan had another primary goal.

Several days later.

Eastern Sea, turbulent flow sea area.

"Spare me, I surrender!" Liu Qing Yu was kneeling on the ground, he was covered in injuries, he had no will to fight.

He was a rank seven lone immortal, he even collaborated with with three rank six comrades just now.

To think that they would be ambushed in this turbulent flow sea area, the three rank six Gu Immortals that he invited were already dead.

Their enemies were four mysterious Gu Immortals.

Liu Qing Yu was considerably knowledgeable, but he had never heard of these four strong experts in the entire Eastern Sea Gu Immortal world!

These four were all very unique.

The one with the highest cultivation level had rank seven aura, but he was a rockman Gu Immortal.

The other three were rank six Gu Immortals, one was a beautiful and bold female immortal, one was a kindly old man, and one was an ordinary looking immortal zombie.

No matter which one, they were formidable Gu Immortal experts. But the strange thing to Liu Qing Yu was, their leader was not the rockman Gu Immortal or the bold female immortal or the old man, it was the ordinary rank six immortal zombie!

"Oh? Surrendering, hehe, you know your place." The rank six immortal zombie rubbed his chin, saying as he chuckled.

If Fang Yuan were here, he would know who this person was.

That's right, it was Ying Wu Xie!

"Hmph, a spineless coward, no wonder he was not my match. We should kill him and give Shi Nu some earth path dao marks." Hei Lou Lan was covered in orange flames.

The rockman Gu Immortal Shi Nu had no expression, he looked at Ying Wu Xie as he said slowly: "I will listen to master."

"No, no!" Liu Qing Yu quickly shouted, he had a frantic and helpless expression: "Even though I am a rank seven Gu Immortal, my Immortal Gu are only rank six. However, fairy, you have rank seven Immortal Gu and even so many fire path killer moves, it was no wonder I could not defeat you!"

Ying Wu Xie laughed, waving his hand: "Right now, my Shadow Sect needs members, I will give you a chance to live. Do not resist, I will use an immortal killer move to make the alliance agreement!"

"Thank you lord for sparing my life, thank you lord for sparing my life!" Liu Qing Yu was overjoyed, he was crying as he kowtowed continuously.

Ying Wu Xie's alliance agreement was extremely strict. But Liu Qing Yu wanted to survive, everything else was secondary.

"It is a soul path method indeed..." Hei Lou Lan observed on the side, Ying Wu Xie used a soul path method to achieve the effects of information path. It was like Fang Yuan's hundred years harmony, it could unleash the effects of another path.

"From now on, you are a member of Shadow Sect, get up." After making the alliance agreement, Ying Wu Xie smiled.

"Lord, I am willing to offer my Immortal Gu." Liu Qing Yu did not get up, he held his two rank six Immortal Gu above his head.

Ying Wu Xie laughed: "I do not care for these two Immortal Gu, you can keep them, in the future, if you perform well, I can grant you rank seven Immortal Gu or even true inheritances, that is not a problem."

"Thank you, lord, for your kindness!" Liu Qing Yu was overjoyed with tears.

"Speaking of which, this place is so remote, and there are many islands around us, why are you here at this island?" Ying Wu Xie asked, he was suspicious that his movements were exposed.

Liu Qing Yu heard this and smiled bitterly: "Lord, this is all a misunderstanding. I was just trying to find a place to rest. Sigh, I will have to explain from the start. In this turbulent flow sea area, I found the clues to an information path true inheritance..."

It turned out that back then, Liu Qing Yu chased after the blood path demonic immortal, wanting to get his information path inheritance clues. In the end, he killed this person and had no gains, the two other rank seven Gu Immortals became suspicious of him instead.

Thinking about it, he felt that Fang Yuan was the most suspicious, the information path true inheritance clues were likely in his hands.

Liu Qing Yu could not let it go, he brought a group of Gu Immortals and entered turbulent flow sea area secretly, attempting to find the clues or wait for Fang Yuan to arrive.

After hearing Liu Qing Yu's story, Hei Lou Lan, Ying Wu Xie, and the others smiled.

This Liu Qing Yu was simply too unlucky.

He wanted to find a place to rest, but he ended up going towards Shadow Sect's secret base instead.

Ying Wu Xie's expression suddenly changed: "Wait, the Gu Immortal who you were suspicious of earlier, what was his appearance?"

Chapter 1150: Turbulent Flow Sea Battle (1/2)

Liu Qing Yu repeated his words from before.

Ying Wu Xie's expression turned grim very quickly.

Fang Yuan had used familiar face when traveling from Southern Border to Northern Plains, he had concealed his appearance. But familiar face could not conceal Immortal Gu effects or immortal killer moves.

When he was in Eastern Sea, Fang Yuan had fought with Liu Qing Yu, Tang Song, and Zhou Li, he unavoidably revealed some methods.

Even though Ying Wu Xie did not know Fang Yuan's appearance at that time, from Liu Qing Yu's description, he felt a sense of familiarity.

Following his intuition, he probed, and Liu Qing Yu described this opponent in greater detail.

"Flying sword Immortal Gu, sword escape Immortal Gu..." Ying Wu Xie thought to himself.

"Looking at the timing, it matched perfectly." Ying Wu Xie felt that the Gu Immortal who Liu Qing Yu fought was very likely to be Fang Yuan!

"It is quite coincidental, I actually got information about Fang Yuan like this. Hehe, heaven's will!" Ying Wu Xie raised his head, looking at the sky.

The turbulent flow sea area's sky was covered in clouds and fog the entire time.

At this moment, Ying Wu Xie could feel that beyond these clouds, heaven's will was looking at him closely!

For heaven's will, be it Fang Yuan, who has the sovereign immortal aperture, or Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, who is attempting to defy fate by reviving and reaching the apex again, they were targets to suppress and eliminate.

Of course, in the past, Spectral Soul was the biggest target, but now, Fang Yuan was the one who attracted its attention the most.

But currently, heaven's will was making an arrangement, attempting to lure Fang Yuan and Ying Wu Xie together, so that they would fight each other. This was a method that killed two birds with one stone, it was a plan that saved a lot of effort.

Ying Wu Xie assessed this as he transmitted secretly to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was slightly dazed.

She did not find anything wrong earlier because she was not familiar with Flying Sword and Sword Escape.

After reacting, she was a little shocked.

"Ying Wu Xie discovered something so significant, he is actually discussing with me?"

But soon, Hei Lou Lan realized, if she were in Ying Wu Xie's position, she would do the same thing herself to analyze the situation.

Until now, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was still kept in the dark, Shi Nu had absolute loyalty but he was a variant human, he could not think as flexibly.

She herself had the Shadow Sect alliance agreement, she was bound to Ying Wu Xie, she had no choice but to plot together with him.

"Dealing with Fang Yuan..." Hei Lou Lan had complex emotions.

She had a rather complex relationship with Fang Yuan.

They were enemies at first, before becoming allies, but now with a twist of fate, they were enemies again!

Even Hei Lou Lan had to admit it herself, Fang Yuan was a huge help and had great influence on her.

But soon, Hei Lou Lan calmed down and transmitted: "Your analysis makes sense, but you only guessed Fang Yuan's identity, how can you be sure he will come here? Just because of the information path true inheritance? Not only is the information path inheritance's crucial clue gone, even if he obtained it, what does that have to do with us? He might not come here and encounter us."

Ying Wu Xie smiled coldly: "That is because you don't understand heaven's will. Earlier, to obstruct Fang Yuan, heaven's will made a plan, that was to lure Fang Yuan with the information path true inheritance. But Fang Yuan is crafty and vigilant, he did not fall into the trap. He went to Northern Plains without stopping, this was a wise decision. Heaven's will's arrangements inside the turbulent flow sea area were completely wasted."

Ying Wu Xie's understanding was a little off.

The truth was, Fang Yuan did not sense the information path true inheritance's clues back then. After all, the clue was concealed in flying sword Immortal Gu.

Of course, even if Fang Yuan found them, with his personality, it would not have slowed down his return to Lang Ya blessed land.

"Right now, Fang Yuan obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance and has gained immense strength. But he is in Lang Ya Sect, and has recently been added to the four races alliance, he also has an alliance agreement with Chu Du, he has huge needs in the information path aspect. Thus, he is likely to come here, following the true inheritance's clues to obtain this information path inheritance." Ying Wu Xie continued.

Undoubtedly, suffering and setbacks were of value in life.

Ying Wu Xie had gone through many difficulties, his mind was sharper and more vigilant now, he had the demeanor of an expert.

Hei Lou Lan was quite familiar with Fang Yuan's situation.

The intel that Fang Yuan had exposed reached Ying Wu Xie through Sixth Hair.

In order to draw out Hei Lou Lan's hatred towards Fang Yuan, Ying Wu Xie had told her a portion of the information.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes burst out with brilliance, she had an understanding: "You mean to say, Liu Qing Yu is a reminder to us from heaven's will?"

"That's right. Liu Qing Yu might have chosen this place by coincidence, but he was actually subconsciously influenced by heaven's will. He purposely chose our island, it is too much of a coincidence. Heaven's will probably thinks that the trap earlier can no longer affect Fang Yuan, who has gotten much stronger, thus, it wants to make use of us to deal with Fang Yuan!" Ying Wu Xie looked at the sky, showing a cold smile.

Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated.

Shadow Sect had opposed heaven's will for so many years, Ying Wu Xie was naturally aware about heaven's will's goals and schemes.

"Then, we can use this chance to ambush Fang Yuan. Aren't you trying to get back the sovereign immortal body?" Hei Lou Lan transmitted.

Ying Wu Xie turned around, looking at Hei Lou Lan.

The two were secretly transmitting to each other. They did not talk for long, the other three immortals only saw Ying Wu Xie looking at the sky for a while, before he turned around and walked back.

Ying Wu Xie did not speak, he took huge steps, leading the way.

Behind him, Shi Nu, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and Hei Lou Lan followed after.

"Ah." Liu Qing Yu who was kneeling on the ground was dazed, he quickly got up and followed behind them closely.

"Hei Lou Lan." Ying Wu Xie suddenly transmitted: "If we can capture Fang Yuan this time, I will grant you freedom."

Hei Lou Lan's body and mind shook!

But soon, she reacted, replying: "Only a child would be fooled by that, would you willingly let go of my battle strength?"

"Hahaha, you truly know me well, Lou Lan." Ying Wu Xie laughed, admitting it openly.

"How will you deal with Fang Yuan? He has rank eight battle strength." Hei Lou Lan asked.

Ying Wu Xie's smile faded, he sighed, Hei Lou Lan could hear the helplessness in his tone.

Next, she heard Ying Wu Xie: "I am not going to deal with him, the immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle is very hard to deal with."

"No, we can. If we use that secluded domain of heaven and earth, can't we succeed?" Hei Lou Lan asked.

"You really want him to die? I remember that you have gone through thick and thin before."

"Hmph, every man for himself, if he dies or is defeated, there are only advantages to me, there are no disadvantages." Hei Lou Lan showed a cold killing intent.

Ying Wu Xie rejected this alluring suggestion: "Even if we use that place, my goal cannot be achieved. I need to capture Fang Yuan alive, the material needs to be fresh. If we use that place, we can only make the upper extreme heavenly eagle lose its threat temporarily."

"Furthermore, even if we could, I would not do it." Ying Wu Xie smiled.

Hei Lou Lan: "Why?"

"Not considering the big picture is simply shortsighted. Like how Fang Yuan did not take the information path inheritance earlier, as long as we save my main body, we will have a great advantage. My memories are limited, if we fight with Fang Yuan now, we will be falling into heaven's will's trap. We will leave Eastern Sea! However... before leaving, we can leave behind some arrangements as a present for Fang Yuan. Hehehe." Ying Wu Xie transmitted a laugh.

A day later.

"I am finally here... turbulent flow sea area." Fang Yuan stood on a cloud, he looked at this sea area as he sighed.

Rumors said that there was an intense battle between Gu Immortals here.

There were no rank eight experts among the participating Gu Immortals, but there were many rank six and seven Gu Immortals.

Because their battle was too intense, the dao marks carved in this area caused a change in the environment, in the end, a unique place in Eastern Sea, turbulent flow sea area, was created.

Because of this reason, there were many Gu Immortal inheritances hidden inside the turbulent flow sea area, or their wealth left behind after death.

In history, there were lucky people who obtained Gu Immortal inheritances inside the turbulent flow sea area. Even though the lucky people were few, these rumors caused many people to be attracted to this sea area.

Many Eastern Sea Gu Immortals as well as Gu Immortals of Central Continent, Northern Plains and Southern Border would often come to the turbulent flow sea area to search for fortuitous encounters.

Fang Yuan's gaze swept across the sea water.

The turbulent flow sea area's water was very unique, the surface was calm, but there were many undercurrents below.

These currents were of all types and forms. They interlinked with one another, they moved in this sea area with absolutely no rhythm or pattern.

Precisely because of this, Gu Immortals called this the turbulent flow sea area.

Fang Yuan looked at the sky again.

The sky had many white clouds, shrouding his vision, he could not see any starlight. Even when the sun was blazing, the sunlight could not penetrate the cloud layers, it only made the place brighter.

When Gu Immortals entered the turbulent flow sea area, they often lost their sense of direction. These cloud layers were one of the causes, because of the clouds, Gu Immortals could not determine their precise location.

It was impossible to get rid of these clouds.

To do that, one was contesting against heaven and earth. Gu Immortals with such abilities were at least rank eight great experts, they were very rare. Paying a huge price to destroy these clouds would also destroy the turbulent flow sea area. To them, it was not worth the effort at all.

Breathing in deeply, Fang Yuan's aura surged as Immortal Gu aura burst out from within him.

Immortal investigative killer move — Qi Luck Sensation!

This move was obtained from Feng Jun's inheritance, it used qi luck Immortal Gu as the core, it could sense people who were closely connected by luck to the Gu Immortal user. The closer the distance, the clearer the effects.

"Oh? They are nearby! They are in the turbulent flow sea area?"

Chapter 1151: Turbulent Flow Sea Battle (2/2)

Five Gu Immortals were moving along the surface of the sea.

"Hehehe, with the appropriate arrangement, as long as Fang Yuan falls for it, he will suffer. Even if we cannot trap him, we can greatly delay his growth." Ying Wu Xie felt a little smug.

Fang Yuan's development was too fast, it was terrifying!

Heaven's will was trying all means possible to kill him, it even used the snowmen and rockmen.

They had to suppress him.

Earlier, Fang Yuan was in Lang Ya blessed land, Ying Wu Xie could not do anything. Now that he was coming over, they were going to teach him a lesson.

Of course, they could not act personally.

They had a huge responsibility, he had the most important task to rebuild Shadow Sect!

"This is good, we can suppress Fang Yuan while not falling into heaven's will's trap. Hmm?!" Suddenly, Ying Wu Xie's gaze froze.

"Be careful, there is a desolate beast in the sea, it is moving rapidly, it is very strange!" Ying Wu Xie frowned, reminding them.

"Merely a desolate beast." Rank seven Gu Immortal Shi Nu attacked.

Boom!

Huge ripples and waves appeared on the water surface, as Fang Yuan emerged and showed himself.

"I finally found you... Ying Wu Xie!" Fang Yuan's mouth opened, revealing a ruthless smile.

The five immortals were stunned, this was the first time they were seeing Fang Yuan. Because Fang Yuan was vigilant, before setting off on this trip, he had already changed his appearance.

"You are?" Suddenly, Ying Wu Xie's body shook.

He used luck inspection Immortal Gu, seeing that Fang Yuan's tall luck was exactly the same as his and Hei Lou Lan's luck.

Connect luck Immortal Gu!

Ying Wu Xie had used Connect Luck on Hei Lou Lan. And Hei Lou Lan was luck connected to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's appearance could change, but his luck was unconcealed.

Seeing his luck, Ying Wu Xie realized that this was Fang Yuan!

"Quick, the ancient battle formation!" He shouted loudly, panicking.

The other three immortals had coordination, they subconsciously acted, using the ancient battle formation, Omni-directional Travel.

Swoosh, the four immortals disappeared completely.

Only one person was left behind.

Liu Qing Yu: "..."

Fang Yuan: "..."

The two looked at each other, falling into silence.

Ancient battle formation — Omni-directional Travel.

It could allow Ying Wu Xie and the rest to escape from Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, it naturally had incredible effect.

Fang Yuan was seeing it for the first time as well.

Thus, he was speechless.

Even though he had some guesses, after seeing it personally, he still felt quite shocked.

"This method might be strong, but as long as I have qi luck sensation, I will be able to find them. Now, I should kill this person first!"

Fang Yuan thought as his attention went over to Liu Qing Yu.

Liu Qing Yu: "..."

Seeing Fang Yuan's cold gaze filled with killing intent, he subconsciously flew backwards.

His mood was even worse than Fang Yuan!

He had tried so hard to obtain the information path inheritance, yet it got snatched away.

After killing the blood path demonic immortal, the crucial clue was lost.

He returned to the turbulent flow sea area to wait, but he encountered Ying Wu Xie, his helpers were all killed, and he had to surrender.

So be it if he surrendered, so be it if the alliance agreement was overbearing, he admitted his loss! So be it if he had to call Ying Wu Xie his boss! For his life, Liu Qing Yu was determined to become a core member of this group called Shadow Sect.

However, when leaving Eastern Sea, a person suddenly appeared!

And next, Ying Wu Xie ran away!

He ran!!

Not only did he run, the other three Gu Immortals also ran.

And they ran so quickly!

In literally one moment, they vanished without a trace!

"This is absurd!" Liu Qing Yu really wanted to swear.

But he could not.

He was under the alliance agreement, he had to be polite to Ying Wu Xie at all times.

If he cursed, he would face the backlash of the information path dao marks.

Liu Qing Yu's current mood was simply terrible, it was at rock bottom!

He did not recognize Fang Yuan, because Fang Yuan was only rank six now. But Liu Qing Yu sensed that Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal that was rank six as well.

This time, Fang Yuan had casually changed his appearance, in terms of aura, he did not conceal anything. His main goal was to kill Ying Wu Xie and the rest. Everyone knew each other and their cultivation level, his aura was not too important.

This caused Liu Qing Yu to feel deeply aggrieved.

"Against a rank six Gu Immortal, why are you running?!"

"Running for what?!"

"We have two rank sevens and three rank sixes, we are all experts! Why are you running?"

"Ah! Why did you run?"

Liu Qing Yu screamed internally, furious.

But he could not get any answers.

He had joined Shadow Sect for too short of a time, Ying Wu Xie did not expect Fang Yuan to come so quickly, he did not tell Liu Qing Yu some details.

If Ying Wu Xie told Liu Qing Yu that the reason why they fled was because Fang Yuan had the rank eight battle strength — upper extreme heavenly eagle!

Then Liu Qing Yu would not scream like this internally, he would definitely flee more quickly than Ying Wu Xie and Hei Lou Lan.

Oh, no.

He could not outrun them.

But in terms of effort, he would definitely exceed them.

Rank eight battle strength was no joke, killing them was as easy as killing an ant!

"This is the deterrence of rank eight." At this time, Fang Yuan had a lot of insight.

Ying Wu Xie and the rest fled, they were wise and resolute. If their positions were reversed, Fang Yuan would escape too.

Earlier in the northern icy plain, he did not flee, that was because Fang Yuan could not begin to escape! It was not that he did not want to.

There was no shame in running away.

For an old demon like Fang Yuan, temporary retreat was a brilliant tactic in battle.

However, Ying Wu Xie and the rest did not know that the upper extreme heavenly eagle had died already, it had returned to being an unhatched egg.

Even though Fang Yuan told this to Lang Ya land spirit, he had asked him to not leak out this secret.

Thus, Sixth Hair only obtained intel about the earlier part, he could not tell Ying Wu Xie about the most crucial intel that was kept secret.

At this moment, Ying Wu Xie and the rest left, only Liu Qing Yu was left.

This situation was very good for Fang Yuan.

Originally, Fang Yuan was a bit concerned in chasing after them, after all, they had an advantage in numbers, there were two rank seven Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan recognized Liu Qing Yu, but this was the first time he saw Shi Nu.

Now, once Fang Yuan's identity was exposed, Ying Wu Xie ran away, only Liu Qing Yu stayed.

It was correct to escape.

Trying to probe a rank eight was courting death. During the grey cloud battle puppet killer move, Fang Yuan did not dare to probe the immemorial rock dragon as well.

Right now, Fang Yuan was considering killing Liu Qing Yu first.

Eliminating him would weaken their combined strength, this was a good chance to take them down, if Fang Yuan could not make use of it, he would definitely get hit by lightning.

"After killing him, I would be able to use soul search and obtain intel regarding Ying Wu Xie and the rest!" Thinking of this, Fang Yuan attacked.

Sword mark targeting death!

At once, he used an extraordinary sword path killer move.

Even though Liu Qing Yu was screaming internally, he was still filled with immense wariness.

The logic was simple, he was something who made Ying Wu Xie and the rest so fearful, even though he was a rank six Gu Immortal, he was definitely dangerous.

Liu Qing Yu was already completely focused against this huge foe.

At this moment, sword light flew out, Liu Qing Yu quickly moved, dodging Fang Yuan's attack.

"Sure enough, this guy is also a rank six Gu Immortal with rank seven Immortal Gu. Sword path?" Liu Qing Yu thought bitterly, he only had two rank six Immortal Gu, he had lost to Hei Lou Lan earlier because of this.

After some rounds of fighting, Liu Qing Yu was in a disadvantaged position.

He was a lone cultivator, even though his cultivation level was higher, with rank seven cultivation level, he had only two rank six Immortal Gu, his immortal killer moves were also deduced by himself, they were not exemplary, and few in number too.

After another dozen rounds, Fang Yuan had almost completely understood Liu Qing Yu's methods.

He only used the same few moves over and over again, how could he not learn everything?

Liu Qing Yu was covered in sweat, he was in a sad state.

Even though Fang Yuan could not use blood asset Immortal Gu temporarily, he had other time path defensive methods, he could easily attack or defend, he had an easy time.

His strength had grown too quickly!

In the past, Liu Qing Yu chased Fang Yuan and caused him to run, but now, Fang Yuan was suppressing him instead.

Even though he had rank six cultivation level, in terms of battle strength, he far surpassed Liu Qing Yu.

"No wonder Ying Wu Xie ran, this is a monster! He is unbelievably powerful, and by the looks of it, he has not used his full strength yet." Liu Qing Yu lost his motivation as he fought.

He really wanted to surrender.

But now was different, he had Shadow Sect's alliance agreement, he could not surrender to the enemy.

He had only one option left, that was to fight to the death!

"Follow me if you dare." Liu Qing Yu desperately avoided Fang Yuan's attack as he turned into a green rainbow, escaping towards the turbulent flow sea area.

"Too naive." Fang Yuan sneered, he pointed at Liu Qing Yu's escape route.

Immortal killer move — Year Beast Summoning!

A snake year beast tore through space, suddenly appearing and blocking Liu Qing Yu.

Liu Qing Yu was obstructed and could not escape anymore.

Fang Yuan used sword escape Immortal Gu behind him and easily caught up to him, attacking.

Liu Qing Yu was struck, his life was over, his body self-detonated as his soul broke into several pieces.

Fang Yuan quickly acted, but he only salvaged a portion.

Liu Qing Yu's immortal aperture also fell into the sea, sinking, as the heaven and earth qi surged into it, a blessed land was formed.

His remnant soul was dissipating, it seemed to be Shadow Sect's method, Fang Yuan tried several methods but did not seem to be able to stop the soul from self-destructing.

Fang Yuan quickly soul searched.

Dozens of memory fragments were seen by him.

Fang Yuan was quite lucky, he saw the scene of Liu Qing Yu and Ying Wu Xie setting up the trap.

"Oh? It seems that after Ying Wu Xie found out I have rank eight battle strength, he knew he could not fight me, so he set up a trap to harm me. He has truly grown."

The other fragments were useless.

Soon, these remnant soul fragments dissipated completely.

Liu Qing Yu's body also turned into pulp, it was hard to collect it. Already, all of his dao marks had returned to his immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan let out a sigh.

He wanted to absorb Liu Qing Yu's dao marks into himself.

But Gu Immortals in the five regions were not so easy to loot.

After some commotion, a blessed land was completely formed from the immortal aperture.

The entrance opened.

This was a rare chance to enter the blessed land!

If he missed it, to enter it later, there would be much greater obstacles.

In the past, when Fang Yuan placed Star Form blessed land and Ge Pi blessed land, he also used these chances to enter the blessed land.

Chapter 1152: Obtaining Five Light Mountain

Quack, quack!

Inside Liu Qing Yu's blessed land, there was a dorky duck calling out to Fang Yuan.

This was the land spirit that was formed using heavenly power after Liu Qing Yu's death.

Appearances of land spirits differed drastically, a duck land spirit was nothing peculiar.

Fang Yuan listened attentively.

Even though all he heard was the duck quacking, in his mind, it was translated into words that Fang Yuan could understand the meaning of.

In fact, Hei Fan's heavenly spirit was a brass bell, but it could communicate with people as well. Unfortunately, before Hei Fan died, he had allowed his immortal aperture to absorb a fragment of immemorial azure heaven, it caused heaven's will to enter and caused his heavenly spirit to lose intelligence.

"The condition of inheriting this Qing Yu blessed land and becoming its owner is actually this..." Fang Yuan's eyes flashed, he showed a look of joy and surprise.

Even though Liu Qing Yu was killed by Fang Yuan, his obsession was not to find Fang Yuan for revenge. He was not trying to locate Ying Wu Xie and find trouble with him either.

It was — the whereabouts of the crucial clue to the information path inheritance.

"The clue to the information path inheritance is carved in flying sword Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan took out flying sword Immortal Gu, showing it to the duck land spirit, explaining the situation to it.

A moment later, the duck land spirit circled around Fang Yuan, using its beak to peck Fang Yuan's white shoes, it was very fond of him.

Fang Yuan was now the owner of the blessed land!

However, this blessed land was quite desolate.

It was not that Liu Qing Yu had poor foundation, but after he joined Shadow Sect, the resources inside his immortal aperture were all taken away by Ying Wu Xie.

Ying Wu Xie did not take Liu Qing Yu's two Immortal Gu, that was because he wanted to preserve his battle strength and make him work like a slave.

But Ying Wu Xie took away his cultivation resources, this was leaving him no way out, in the future, when Liu Qing Yu wanted to continue cultivating, he would lack resources, he could only rely on Shadow Sect.

Fang Yuan only had to think for a bit before understanding this.

As for Liu Qing Yu's Gu worms, they had already been destroyed.

This applied to the two Immortal Gu and the mortal Gu, nothing was left for Fang Yuan.

"What is left in this blessed land?" Fang Yuan looked around, asking the land spirit as he frowned.

Qing Yu blessed land was completely ransacked, it was left in a state similar to Hei Fan grotto-heaven when Fang Yuan took over it.

At this moment, Fang Yuan could somewhat feel what Chu Du had gone through at that time.

The duck land spirit: "Quack, quack, quack!"

Fang Yuan turned around: "Bring me there."

The duck land spirit could not teleport, it brought Fang Yuan to the destination.

A rainbow colored mountain which was neither tall nor short was displayed before Fang Yuan.

The mountain rocks were giving off green, red, yellow, blue, and white lights. There were no trees on the mountain, but there were many different types of grass. These types of grass had ten colors, they shone together, they were more beautiful than a sea of flowers, it was a dazzling sight.

"Five Light Mountain, ten colored grass." Fang Yuan muttered.

These were resources that light path Gu Immortals often cultivated.

The special environment would cause this mountain to produce large numbers of light path mortal Gu.

Evidently, this Five Light Mountain was heavily developed by Liu Qing Yu, it was quite big.

"Ying Wu Xie does not have pulling mountain Immortal Gu, he had no methods to move this mountain, he could only leave this here." Fang Yuan guessed the truth.

Trees had tree roots, mountains had mountain roots too.

Mountains were not easy to move, using brute strength would only cause the mountain to collapse.

And methods to move mountains were very rare in the world.

Back then, when Fang Yuan was able to move Luo Po Valley, even the rank eight Gu Immortal Prince Feng Xian was shocked.

Even though Ying Wu Xie inherited a portion of Shadow Sect's wealth, he lacked a method to move Five Light Mountain.

He originally had pulling mountain Immortal Gu, but in those transactions, it was sold to Fang Yuan.

When he saw this Five Light Mountain and could not move it, he must have felt annoyed.

All in all, this Five Light Mountain was now Fang Yuan's property.

Without hesitation, Fang Yuan used pulling mountain Immortal Gu and moved this Five Light Mountain into his own sovereign immortal aperture.

He placed this mountain into Mini Southern Border.

Mini Southern Border had many mountains, it was a place with rich earth path dao marks to begin with. With the addition of Five Light Mountain, all of the mountains from Hei Fan grotto-heaven were outmatched, Immortal Succession Mountain could only become the second tallest mountain.

After all, Immortal Succession Mountain was used as an inheritance ground, the inheritances were all gone now. Five Light Mountain was now the biggest mountain in Mini Southern Border.

"I had some gains at last." Fang Yuan let out a breath of air.

If he did not have Five Light Mountain, his losses would be severe.

Even though he won this battle, from Fang Yuan's perspective, victory had no value, the loot after winning did.

It was a pity, even after taking Five Light Mountain, Fang Yuan concluded that in this battle against Liu Qing Yu, he still made losses.

It could not be helped.

He was using green grape immortal essence, and most of his Immortal Gu were rank seven, he also had to use many immortal killer moves.

In every battle, his green grape immortal essence expenditure was severe!

Of course, blessed lands could annex each other.

However, Liu Qing Yu cultivated light path, this blessed land was a light path blessed land. Fang Yuan's light path attainment level was only ordinary, this was a rank seven blessed land, he could not annex it.

In the following period, Fang Yuan asked the duck land spirit, he obtained a lot of intel.

The duck land spirit still remembered many details from when it was alive, this allowed Fang Yuan to become quite aware of the trap that Ying Wu Xie set.

And also regarding the information path true inheritance, Fang Yuan also obtained some information.

After obtaining the intel, Fang Yuan left behind some mortal Gu for the duck land spirit, and ordered that without his permission, it was never to open the blessed land's entrance. If any enemies attacked, it had to inform Fang Yuan using treasure yellow heaven immediately.

Liu Qing Yu's rank seven red date immortal essence was still left behind, Fang Yuan did not take them, he gave them to the duck land spirit.

"Quack, quack." The duck land spirit had tears in its eyes, it flapped one wing, saying goodbye to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not look back, he left the blessed land.

The blessed land's entrance closed after he left.

"This rank seven blessed land, as long as the entrance is shut and it is hidden well, it should not be discovered."

"However, if heaven's will wants to harm me, it will have many ways of dealing with this blessed land."

"It would be great if I can keep this rank seven blessed land, but even if I can't, it is fine. It has too little value anyway."

Fang Yuan did not have the time to raise his light path attainment level, and his cultivation level was still far from reaching rank seven.

To continue to pursue Ying Wu Xie?

Fang Yuan was hesitant.

From the duck land spirit, he had obtained a lot of information, he had a clearer understanding of their strength.

Ying Wu Xie had four Gu Immortals including himself. A rank seven Gu rockman Gu Immortal named Shi Nu, he cultivated earth path. Hei Lou Lan was now a strength and fire path cultivator. Tai Bai Yun Sheng had lost his time path Immortal Gu, but he now had cloud path Immortal Gu, he had originally been secondarily cultivating cloud path.

As for Ying Wu Xie, he still had a strength path immortal zombie body. He still used soul path Immortal Gu, he had the lowest cultivation level, but his battle strength was likely to be the highest or second highest.

If Fang Yuan had the immemorial upper extreme heavenly eagle, he would pursue them immediately!

But now, the upper extreme heavenly eagle was just an egg, even though Fang Yuan had many Immortal Gu, looking at it, with his strength and intelligence, against Ying Wu Xie's group, it was difficult to predict the winner.

"How long has it been! Ying Wu Xie and the rest have already gained so much strength, it is truly out of my expectations."

Fang Yuan's growth shocked Ying Wu Xie and the rest. But Ying Wu Xie and the rest also grew at a rate that shocked Fang Yuan.

He had originally thought that Ying Wu Xie and the others had suffered a huge setback after the transactions. To think that not long after, they had already recovered.

Shadow Sect was already in shambles, but it was still not to be underestimated.

Ying Wu Xie and the others were truly huge threats from Fang Yuan's perspective!

Because of sovereign immortal fetus Gu, Shadow Sect and Fang Yuan had an unresolvable conflict.

Ying Wu Xie was not dealing with Fang Yuan now, it was because saving his main body was more important, he was making a wise decision.

Fang Yuan did not deal with Ying Wu Xie earlier because he had insufficient strength, he needed to deal with the earthly calamities and try to develop his sovereign immortal aperture.

Now that he had Hei Fan's true inheritance, with enough strength, he came to find Ying Wu Xie straight away.

Once Ying Wu Xie saved his main body, Fang Yuan knew that he would no longer have any chance of victory. Because the other party was one of the ten venerables, even though he had died before, Fang Yuan was not his match.

Of course, there was still a crucial point.

That was wisdom Gu.

Wisdom Gu was not lost, it was currently in Lang Ya blessed land. Fang Yuan regained his former strength path immortal zombie body, there was just one key point, he was afraid that inside this immortal zombie body, there was a trap set by Ying Wu Xie which targeted his soul.

Fang Yuan did not dare to act rashly.

He had thought of using other Gu Immortals' souls and putting them inside the immortal zombie body to test it out.

But there were many flaws with this.

Firstly, he had to undergo such experiments secretly, he could not take out his immortal zombie body openly, this would reveal many secrets to Lang Ya land spirit.

Secondly, even if he used Gu Immortal souls to test it, they were unreliable. Because Fang Yuan was not clear if Ying Wu Xie had set up traps that targeted weak or strong souls, or was it a trap specifically targeting otherworldly demons?

The problem of using wisdom Gu was the greatest restriction towards Fang Yuan's development.

Thus, Fang Yuan thought of the plan in Eastern Sea.

His main objective was to deal with Ying Wu Xie.

If he succeeded, he might be able to check from Ying Wu Xie whether this immortal zombie body had any traps. If there was a trap, how would he resolve it?

Ying Wu Xie wanted to suppress Fang Yuan's growth speed, but Fang Yuan was also afraid that Ying Wu Xie would grow too quickly and save his main body.

Thus, when he came to Eastern Sea now, the information path inheritance was secondary.

He went straight for the main objective.

Ying Wu Xie was his main goal!

Chapter 1153: Fighting Across Vast Distance

Ahead was a deep blue veil, it completely covered the visions of Ying Wu Xie and the others.

Blue water regional wall!

Between the five regions, there were regional walls, they were like thin membrane which shielded the region.

Blue water regional wall was the protective membrane of Eastern Sea.

The turbulent flow sea area was very close to blue water regional wall to begin with, precisely because of this, when Fang Yuan was on the journey from Southern Border to Northern Plains, when he got close to the turbulent flow sea area, he encountered Liu Qing Yu and the rest.

Ying Wu Xie and the other immortals used Omni-directional Travel to directly reach this place.

"Are we leaving again?" Hei Lou Lan sighed.

"Who was that person earlier?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng questioned.

"An enemy, a strong enemy, an irreconcilable enemy! Don't look at his rank six cultivation level, he has rank eight battle strength." Ying Wu Xie looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, choosing to expose some information to him.

Hearing this Tai Bai Yun Sheng breathed in sharply, he shouted in disbelief: "Rank eight battle strength?!"

Hei Lou Lan pretended to be shocked too: "No wonder we had to retreat."

Shi Nu had no expression.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng suddenly thought of something, he showed sadness on his face: "Sigh! Since he has rank eight battle strength, Liu Qing Yu is finished. It is a pity."

"Dying for Shadow Sect is his greatest honor." Shi Nu snorted, saying in disdain.

"Let's go, since he can chase us, we should increase our distance. That upper extreme heavenly eagle is an immemorial desolate beast that can roam the nine heavens, it is likely to be a life form from the immemorial nine heavens, it can travel in the five regional walls freely." Hei Lou Lan transmitted secretly, reminding Ying Wu Xie.

Ying Wu Xie looked at her deeply, replying: "Don't worry, I have already checked the historical records in Northern Plains. Fang Yuan's upper extreme heavenly eagle came from Hei Fan, and the upper extreme heavenly eagle that Hei Fan had was raised in Northern Plains. If it enters the five regional walls, it would face suppression as well. We are quite safe now at the border of the regional wall."

"Is that so?" Hei Lou Lan was stunned, before showing an expression of relief.

"Where are we going now? We cannot go to Central Continent, are we going to Southern Border to work on the rescue?" Hei Lou Lan asked.

Ying Wu Xie smiled, he did not enter the blue water regional wall, instead, he used his immortal essence as aura of Gu worms burst out from within.

His entire body was floating in the air, he turned around and looked in the direction of the turbulent flow sea area.

Ripples appeared below his feet, making a soft sound.

The cold and wet sea breeze blew on the four Gu Immortals' faces.

"Wait." Ying Wu Xie said one word in reply to Hei Lou Lan.

"Wait for what?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was confused.

"Wait for the enemy." Ying Wu Xie said.

The rest of the three Gu Immortals looked at each other, not understanding why.

Since they retreated earlier, why were they waiting for him now? That person had rank eight battle strength, why were they waiting for him? Waiting for him to kill them?

Hei Lou Lan's expression changed: "I see!"

"See what?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly asked, he was extremely lost.

Shi Nu was expressionless, but his gaze also revealed curiosity.

Hei Lou Lan smiled: "Don't you find it strange? How did he know our location? When chasing us, why did he have such precise knowledge of our whereabouts?"

This time, even Shi Nu's expression changed.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tone became lower: "Hei Lou Lan, you mean to say, we have a traitor? impossible, how can the four of us... unless, that Liu Qing Yu is a spy? Wait! He went under an alliance agreement to join us, could the alliance agreement be exploited?"

"The probability of a traitor is small." Ying Wu Xie shook his head, replying.

He looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Even though Tai Bai Yun Sheng was kept in the dark, he was also under an alliance agreement from Ying Wu Xie, he could not become a traitor.

"The most probable reason is, he has an investigative method that can track our locations." Ying Wu Xie said.

"These last days, we have been staying in our base, we rarely went out." Tai Bai Yun Sheng frowned.

Hei Lou Lan smiled: "Gu Immortal methods are unfathomably vast in number, some are incredibly brilliant, how much do we actually know?"

"That's true." Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded.

Hei Lou Lan continued: "If we cannot find a way to counter it, no matter where we go, that enemy will find us, it is only a matter of time."

"Thus, lord decided to stay here and not enter the regional wall. Lord is waiting for the other party to use his investigative killer move. I see!" Shi Nu suddenly realized.

Actually, a lot of information was only known to Ying Wu Xie.

At this moment, countless thoughts were forming and colliding in Ying Wu Xie's mind.

Even though he was a strength path immortal zombie and could not think well, he had lots of methods to bypass this flaw.

Ying Wu Xie was rapidly thinking now!

"What method is Fang Yuan using to find my location?"

"I came to Eastern Sea secretly, how did the intel leak? Is he able to find my location in Northern Plains, across two regional walls?"

"That is impossible! Even Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals could not deduce anything after I used my Gu formation to conceal my traces."

"No matter what is inside Hei Fan's true inheritance, he would not be able to do this."

Heaven's will!

Ying Wu Xie had an answer in his mind.

"Since I can be plotted against by heaven's will, gaining its reminder regarding Fang Yuan's intel, would Fang Yuan also receive the same information about me?"

This was very possible.

But Ying Wu Xie was not satisfied with this answer.

"If at this time, the person in my situation is not me but Fang Yuan, what would he do? What would he consider?"

"He would consider the worst possible situation."

"And what was the worst possible situation?"

Ying Wu Xie asked himself, and had answer — "The other party has an investigative killer move that can pass regional walls to confirm my location."

Ying Wu Xie smiled, how could that be possible?

But suddenly, his smile froze.

He thought of a possibility!

Luck path!

Fang Yuan had the most important clue all along. It was that their lucks were all interconnected.

Connect luck Immortal Gu!

Back then, Ying Wu Xie had no choice, he could only sell this Immortal Gu in treasure yellow heaven.

After transacting with Fang Yuan, Ying Wu Xie obtained the Gu refinement materials he needed, when treasure yellow heaven opened, he took back connect luck Immortal Gu.

Even though Fang Yuan had a new body, Connect Luck's effect also targeted his soul. Thus, his luck connection to Hei Lou Lan and the rest was still in effect.

Ying Wu Xie gained a lot of information from Shadow Sect regarding how to resist heaven's will, there was one point — Fate is hard to defy, but luck can be exploited.

Using luck, one could deal with heaven's will effectively.

Who had better luck?

Undoubtedly, it was Fang Yuan who owned dog shit luck Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan had Dog Shit Luck, Ying Wu Xie knew this clearly. Sixth Hair, who was in Lang Ya Sect, was not to be forgotten.

Thus, Ying Wu Xie used Connect Luck and connected his own luck with Hei Lou Lan.

Even though Hei Lou Lan was unwilling to, she could not resist.

This way, Ying Wu Xie and Fang Yuan truly had their luck connected.

"If he realizes this relationship and uses a luck path method, even if we are in two separate regions, he can still sense me, that is possible."

"Is it luck path?"

Right at this moment, Ying Wu Xie's body shook.

He saw it!

Using luck inspection Immortal Gu, he saw that at this moment, the luck above him and Hei Lou Lan's head was shaking slightly.

"As expected... a luck path method. Impressive, Fang Yuan. To think that you even made use of the fact that we have Connect Luck, and found your way to us. It is a pity, I have understood your method already."

Ying Wu Xie's eyes flickered brightly.

Even though he knew about Fang Yuan's method, Ying Wu Xie could not break the luck connection.

He did not have break luck Immortal Gu.

However, he had a lot of soul path methods, he could influence and interfere with the luck.

He tried them one by one, but the effect was not good.

The luck was still shaking.

In fact, even if he was concealed, there was still Hei Lou Lan.

Unlike Liu Qing Yu, Hei Lou Lan could not be thrown away easily.

She had huge value, once they lost her, they could not even use the ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel. Thus, Ying Wu Xie quickly gave up this thought.

"Then, enter an immortal aperture?"

Ying Wu Xie entered Shi Nu's immortal aperture, and he was surprised to find out that in conjunction with his soul path methods, the luck on top of his head stopped shaking.

He ordered Hei Lou Lan to enter Shi Nu's immortal aperture as well.

Next, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Shi Nu entered the blue water regional wall, quickly vanishing from sight.

Fang Yuan had just come out of Qing Yu blessed land.

Luck path investigative killer move — Qi Luck Sensation!

He activated his immortal killer move, at once, he sensed several locations.

Eastern Sea, Western Desert, Southern Border.

Among which, Eastern Sea had the clearest sensation and highest number of people.

Qi luck sensation had a huge investigative range, but the effect was not very outstanding. If not for Connect Luck, Fang Yuan could not pass regions in investigation.

"They are at the border of blue water regional wall, this ancient battle formation is actually so amazing?"

"Hmph! Even if victory is hard to obtain, I will pursue you, even if I cannot kill you, I will weaken you. As long as I prevent you from saving Spectral Soul's main body, I would be victorious."

"Strange, why did they stop?"

"Hmm?!"

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's expression changed, he showed shock.

In his senses, two people had suddenly vanished.

"Oh? He sensed it so quickly?" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

This way, he could not pursue them.

"But as long as your luck is connected, you will be threatened by my killer move. I have the initiative, I can use this killer move from time to time, and check your location. But you need to be wary of me at all times, you will have to pay a bigger price than me."

"This will cause a battle of attrition between us, but if you break the luck connection, hehe, isn't that just what I want?"

"Forget it, I should get the good stuff inside the turbulent flow sea area first."

Chapter 1154: Immortal Hua Die

Since he could not locate them, Fang Yuan wisely chose to give up on pursuing them.

Ever since reviving, this was the second time Fang Yuan was up against Shadow Sect. The first time, Ying Wu Xie had no choice but to undergo transactions with Fang Yuan, in the end, Fang Yuan took great advantage of it.

In the second contest, Fang Yuan only had a slight edge. Even though Fang Yuan's strength had grown immensely due to Hei Fan's true inheritance, in the end, he did not achieve his goals, he only killed one member of Shadow Sect, he slightly weakened Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

Fang Yuan was growing fast, but Ying Wu Xie was also increasing in strength!

And Fang Yuan's growth was uncertain and unstable. After all, benefits like Hei Fan's true inheritance were once in a thousand year encounters, they were not easy to get.

Conversely, Ying Wu Xie's growth in strength was very steady.

Because he could go and obtain Shadow Sect's inheritances in all five regions, these originally belonged to him, they were reliable and predictable.

Based on this point, it was wise of Fang Yuan to kill them preemptively.

If he did not use this chance to act, the disparity between them would grow more obvious. Once Spectral Soul was successfully rescued, Fang Yuan's doomsday would arrive.

Ying Wu Xie's immediate retreat was shameless, but it was the wisest and most resolute choice.

For Ying Wu Xie, as long as he continued to gather Shadow Sect's remnant forces, he would grow rapidly in strength. Accumulating them, he eventually would grow to become quite powerful!

In the turbulent sea area, even though both sides did not fight, they had competed against each other across a vast distance.

Fang Yuan obtained a lot of information regarding Ying Wu Xie and the rest, he even saw the ancient battle formation, Omni-directional Travel, as well as Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, and the others' situations.

Meanwhile, Ying Wu Xie identified Fang Yuan's investigative killer move, even though he only resolved it temporarily, and did not solve the problem, his advancement was not halted, his plan could still continue smoothly.

Fang Yuan and Ying Wu Xie were bound to engage in a battle of life and death.

But now was not the time, Ying Wu Xie chose to retreat.

One day, between Fang Yuan and Ying Wu Xie, one would die. Their enmity was far from resolved.

Fang Yuan turned around, going back to the turbulent flow sea area.

Vast clouds and turbulent sea water, it was a chaotic sight.

Fang Yuan was about to go in, when a female immortal suddenly came from the west, calling out: "Please wait."

Fang Yuan turned around, only to see that this woman was dressed in a raiment, her sleeves were fluttering, she wore light pink. Her eyes were clear and shiny, she was extremely beautiful.

Immediately, Fang Yuan stopped moving, his eyebrows raised as he waited for the female immortal to arrive: "So it is Immortal Hua Die. I wonder why you called out to me?"

Immortal Hua Die smiled, her tender pink lips parted to show her pearl-like teeth: "I am ashamed, you know my name but I am unaware of your name?"

"I am Chu Ying." Fang Yuan casually said a name, his current appearance was disguised as well.

Chu Ying, it sounded like remove shadow[1].

Even though Fang Yuan's goal was not achieved this time, Fang Yuan was determined to eliminate Shadow Sect, with a firmer attitude now.

"Chu Ying, I saw that you were about to enter the turbulent flow sea area, I have a suggestion, if it works, it will benefit you too." Immortal Hua Die said.

"Please speak." Fang Yuan smiled, having a warm attitude.

In his mind, he was thinking: If he killed this Immortal Hua Die, would the chances of success be high?

She was a beautiful woman, but to Fang Yuan's heart, she was better off as part of his dao mark accumulation.

Fang Yuan knew a bit about Immortal Hua Die's information. She was a transformation path Gu Immortal from Eastern Sea, she had rank six cultivation level and had passed two heavenly tribulations.

In terms of battle strength, looking at her records, she was at the peak of rank six.

For Fang Yuan, that was not a problem.

Transformation path!

The important thing was this.

Currently, Fang Yuan was a transformation path grandmaster, he had quite a few transformation path dao marks, but there was nothing wrong with accumulating more.

Immortal Hua Die smiled too.

She felt that even though Fang Yuan had an unimpressive appearance, he behaved gently and politely, he was not a frenzied demonic path Gu Immortal, he was likely to be a lone immortal like herself.

If she knew what Fang Yuan was thinking, who knew how she would feel.

"Even though I cannot set up a battlefield killer move, my battle strength should be superior to her's. But Immortal Hua Die has a close relationship with Miao Ming Shen, how confident am I in killing her?" Fang Yuan was considering the possibility.

Miao Ming Shen was a rank seven expert in Eastern Sea, his status was similar to that of Qin Bai Sheng before awakening his memories.

Most importantly, Miao Ming Shen was a space path Gu Immortal who had a method to expand the size of immortal apertures. As a result, many Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, especially lone immortals, sought his help.

After all, the space of an immortal aperture was limited, many Gu Immortals had to choose carefully when cultivating resources. Miao Ming Shen could expand the immortal aperture, it could provide a lot of convenience and help to these Gu Immortals.

And Miao Ming Shen himself was an ambitious person, he was very good at building relationships, he had a lot of charisma. Thus, around him, there were a group of Gu Immortals with common interests.

This group had four people. With Miao Ming Shen as the core, and Immortal Hua Die, Feng Jiang, and Gui Qi Ye as his followers.

Among them, Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang had rank six cultivation level, Gui Qi Ye and Miao Ming Shen were rank seven, but the latter had the greatest battle strength.

If Fang Yuan killed Immortal Hua Die, he would become enemies with the other three.

Miao Ming Shen had a huge network and knew many people, a lot of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals wanted to be friendly with him. Even super forces refused to offend him. After all, they might need his help one day.

If Miao Ming Shen and Fang Yuan were enemies, he would fully use his network and call upon lots of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals to push aside Fang Yuan.

But so what?

Fang Yuan had familiar face, he could freely change his identity, so what if it was Miao Ming Shen!

As long as it was not a rank eight Gu Immortal.

"However, if I kill Immortal Hua Die, familiar face cannot defend me from wisdom path deductions, my identity might get exposed."

Familiar face was not all-powerful.

In the past, when Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable used this method to deceive two rank eight Gu Immortals, he had ensured that they did not have investigative methods against it.

Even though this was an amazing story, it made others alert, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could not replicate this glorious event in the future.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan and Ying Wu Xie had met.

Ying Wu Xie used luck inspection Immortal Gu to observe Fang Yuan's luck and discern his identity, before retreating immediately.

Just rank six luck inspection Immortal Gu could make familiar face ineffective. It seemed peculiar, but it was not.

The world was balanced, all living beings had their food and natural predators. The same went for Immortal Gu, the essence of immortal killer moves was the use of a combination of Gu worms, it could not escape this principle.

This was why, there was no strongest Gu worm, only strongest Gu Immortal.

"But I am a wisdom path grandmaster, as long as I elevate my wisdom path methods and conceal my true identity, when I use familiar face to conceal myself, who would be able to find my true identity?"

Especially with his sovereign immortal body, he could travel through regional walls easily, he could even completely alter his aura and become a local.

He was unlike Hei Lou Lan and the rest, they had Northern Plains aura, it was still fine in Eastern Sea. But when they got to Southern Border, Western Desert, or Central Continent, they would face strong ostracism from the locals.

"However... I remember that this Miao Ming Shen had a method to find that immemorial desolate beast blue dragon whale, he had once rallied more than ten Eastern Sea lone immortals to find it. Should I build a relationship with him, so that I can use this relationship to take a share of the profits from entering the blue dragon whale as well?"

Taking this into consideration, the blue dragon whale was naturally more important than merely Immortal Hua Die, Fang Yuan dispelled the thought of killing her.

There was another advantage in becoming friendly with Miao Ming Shen.

Eastern Sea had the most cultivation resources among the five regions. Eastern Sea Gu Immortals often held meet-ups to exchange resources between each other. These resources were very precious, they had great value, lifespan Gu were used for transactions. In comparison, treasure yellow heaven was an open market, it was not a private auction location.

Miao Ming Shen was a common guest in these private auctions. With his approval, Fang Yuan would be able to enter these events as well.

Immortal Hua Die did not know that she had just barely escaped death, because of her relationship with Miao Ming Shen, she narrowly avoided a terrible fate.

She smiled lightly as she said: "Chu Ying, since you know about me, you must know about Lord Miao Ming Shen as well. Lord Miao Ming Shen has observed the turbulent flow sea area for years, he wants to find a tributary of the River of Time among these chaotic currents. If you have the opportunity to find that tributary of the River of Time, I hope that you can locate it and inform us, we will definitely thank you for it."

As for why a space path Gu Immortal like Miao Ming Shen was searching for a tributary of the River of Time, Immortal Hua Die was not going to explain it.

"So that's it." Fang Yuan agreed: "I have long since heard of Lord Miao Ming Shen. I would not ask for a great reward, I would simply like to be on good terms with both of you."

Fang Yuan was so tactful, Immortal Hua Die's smile became even wider.

Fang Yuan was not the first person she had talked to, in fact, Immortal Hua Die, Gui Qi Ye, and Feng Jiang would guard the turbulent flow sea area in turns at regular intervals. When they see any Gu Immortals approaching the turbulent flow sea area, they would talk to them and ask for their help.

Some rejected, but most people would agree.

The reason was naturally Miao Ming Shen's method to expand immortal apertures.

Thus, Fairy Hua Die was not surprised that Fang Yuan agreed.

"Then I will wish you good luck, friend." Immortal Hua Die turned around and was about to leave, she did not think highly of Chu Ying.

Because she had never heard of this person before.

Of course, Eastern Sea had no lack of hidden cultivators. But Immortal Hua Die had many connections, Chu Ying was someone who was completely unknown, and he only had rank six cultivation level, how strong could he be?

"Lord Miao Ming Shen is searching for the tributary of the River of Time, it does not require cultivation level, but luck instead. Maybe this Chu Ying might be able to find it? Oh, I have such thoughts each time. But more than ten years have passed, we have not even seen a trace of that tributary."

Immortal Hua Die sighed internally, saying goodbye to Fang Yuan.

However, a while after leaving, Immortal Hua Die used an information path mortal Gu and transmitted to him.

"I almost forgot to tell you. A blood path demonic immortal, Ding Qi, has recently come to the turbulent flow sea area. This person's younger brother, Ding Yan, had once held the clues to an information path inheritance, he was attacked by Liu Qing Yu, Zhou Li, and Tang Song. Ding Yan is dead, Ding Qi wants revenge, because he heard that Liu Qing Yu had come to the turbulent flow sea area, as if to obtain the information path inheritance, he rushed here. Blood path demonic immortals are ruthless and crazy, they are unlike us, their minds are completely insane. When they see a Gu Immortal, they would first think about whether they should kill that person to increase their own strength. If you encounter him, you should be careful."

Fang Yuan kept the information path mortal Gu, rubbing his nose.

Immortal Hua Die gave him some friendly advice, she was a kind person. But she did not know that the person she was talking to was a blood path demonic overlord, a person bearing great sins, he had once casually slaughtered countless lives in Central Continent!

[1] The name he used is Chu Ying (楚瀛), which sounds similar to 'chu ying' (除影), meaning remove shadow Back

Chapter 1155: Snatching Oyster

The conversation with Immortal Hua Die was only a short intermission.

Fang Yuan finally went into the turbulent flow sea area.

The sea water moved randomly, like intertwined ropes, or completely messy balls of string, filling Fang Yuan's vision.

Strength path giant hand!

Seeing nobody around, Fang Yuan used his immortal killer move.

The giant hand smashed more than ten currents, causing the sea water to become chaotic.

Fang Yuan charged towards a certain direction.

This was at the fringe of the turbulent flow sea area, he could forcefully make his way in.

But a moment later, a huge current of light yellow water blocked Fang Yuan's path.

"This is yellow spring water."

Fang Yuan stopped his steps, this current was huge, strength path giant hand could not smash it, in fact, he might even get injured.

Yellow spring water came from the yellow spring sea area.

That was the territory of Zombie Alliance's headquarters.

As the largest zombie farming area in the five regions, the yellow spring sea area was filled with zombie corpses. At the bottom of the sea, there was decomposed coral and between them, there were strands of seaweed drifting with the flowing water.

Yellow spring water contained dao marks, it was a type of Gu refinement material.

Fang Yuan activated his defensive method, entering it.

This yellow spring water current flowed in one direction, but it was not the one Fang Yuan wanted. He could only charge through this current, using his Immortal Gu and consuming immortal essence.

A while later, he broke through the yellow spring water current, arriving at another current.

This water was pale white, after entering it, Fang Yuan felt like he was moving inside clouds.

Illusory scenes were displayed before him.

Thousand illusion water, it came from Eastern Sea's thousand illusion sea area.

Fang Yuan used wisdom path methods, easily blocking the interference of these illusions, after spending some effort, he got into the third current.

Magma current.

This current was not from Eastern Sea, it came from Western Desert's largest pit — blazing glory pit.

It was extremely deep and was linked to the underground, every hundred years, magma would burst out from the earth veins, the hot magma would fill the entire pit, even oozing out and changing the terrain of the surrounding area.

Magma current, it came from a deep part of the magma, it was very hot.

Once Fang Yuan entered it, he would need a defensive immortal killer move, ordinary rank six Gu Immortals without an immortal level defensive method could only avoid this.

His immortal essence expenditure was multiple times that of the two earlier currents!

Thankfully, this magma current was not big, Fang Yuan got through in a few dozen breaths of time.

This time, he did not encounter another current, he went into an empty space.

Other than Fang Yuan, there was nothing.

Looking back, the magma current was still flowing behind him.

On his front-left side, there was deep darkness, waves were crashing inside, resembling thousands of vengeful souls. This black soul water came from the black soul sea area, it contained soul path and dark path dao marks.

On his right, there was a third current. It was golden and shiny, like countless gold fragments mixed together, moving forward together in a dazzling manner.

Fang Yuan saw this and was surprised: "If I am not wrong, this is a gold fragment current. Rumors say that immemorial yellow heaven has a lot of metallic heavenly rivers. After immemorial yellow heaven broke, most of the metallic heavenly rivers were destroyed. This gold fragment current is likely from a certain immemorial yellow heaven fragment world. Because of the nature of the turbulent flow sea area, by gathering all the different currents in the world, I am able to witness it."

Magma current, black soul current, and gold fragment current.

These three currents contested against each other, they reached a mystical balance, a completely empty space was created between them.

This was where Fang Yuan was at now, as if he was in the eye of the cyclone, he could not stay here for long, but it gave him precious time to rest.

Fang Yuan did not rest, his strength had grown drastically, he had a lot of immortal essence, he had not reached his limit yet.

After finding his direction, he shot out into the gold fragment current at lightning speed.

He faced a lot of obstructions, more than ten times of the magma current, but his immortal essence expenditure had decreased instead.

The magma current was too hot.

Fang Yuan crossed the entire gold fragment current.

During this process, he collected up to five hundred kilograms of gold fragments.

On Earth, this would be a huge amount of wealth. But in this world, it was merely a common Gu material.

Other than gold fragments, the gold fragment current also had a large number of Gu worms.

They were mostly metal path.

There was golden dragon Gu, it looked like an earthworm, but it had claws and a head, it resembled a miniature dragon.

There was also golden aurora Gu, it could allow a Gu Master to fly.

And a rare mortal Gu that could make all mortal Gu Masters go crazy — polished gold Gu, it was a one time consumable Gu that could increase a Gu Master's aptitude!

For Fang Yuan, this polished gold Gu had little use.

He casually collected some.

After getting out of the gold fragment current, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture gained a new small gold fragment river.

Fang Yuan placed this river in Mini Yellow Heaven, it was just to add to the scenery. With this tiny gold fragment river, it could not give him any benefits.

Gu Masters might treat it like a treasure, for Fang Yuan and other Gu Immortals, it was worthless.

Fang Yuan got through many currents, gradually getting towards the center of the turbulent flow sea area from the fringe.

A moment later, a huge current blocked Fang Yuan's path.

The huge current was deep blue, every drop of water flickered with electricity, it caused the entire current to be eye-catching and bright.

Fang Yuan let out a breath, he knew that this was a lightning water current.

When lightning accumulates to a degree, it would become liquid. The destructive force would convert in a water of vitality that could draw out potential.

Lightning path Gu Immortals often built lightning pools, storing this lightning water inside.

Lightning path Gu Immortals would use these lightning pools to nurture large numbers of lightning path mortal Gu.

The significance of a lightning pool to lightning path Gu Immortals was like Five Light Mountain to light path Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan had already reached the center of the turbulent flow sea area.

With his strength, he could not go into currents rashly anymore. The strength of the currents had gotten stronger, if Fang Yuan went in, he would be swept away.

In this situation, to get to his destination, it depended on luck.

With good luck, a random current would bring him to his destination, Fang Yuan would be able to travel smoothly.

If he was unlucky, even after dozens of currents, he might still be going in circles.

This was the special characteristic of the turbulent flow sea area.

Fang Yuan entered the lightning water current.

This current was huge, it was as if Fang Yuan was a small rabbit which had entered a large river.

Thankfully, the lightning water was very calm. Only the ripples at the top would create lightning, with destructive force that would destroy whatever touched it.

Fang Yuan only had to sink to the bottom of the lightning water, the immortal essence expenditure was low, it was calm and smooth.

He traveled along with this current.

A while later, Fang Yuan got to the end of the lightning water current.

At the end, there was another current with the same size as the lightning water current.

Fang Yuan entered it as the water carried him along.

He was quite lucky.

Even though there were some hurdles, in the end, he still moved closer to his target destination.

A day and a night later, Fang Yuan got to an empty space with no currents.

This was the twelve one he had seen during this trip.

"This space has just formed, the surroundings currents won't change for now, I should rest first." Fang Yuan wanted to rest here.

Because now, even he felt a little tired. The expenditure of immortal essence was not small.

But after resting for a while, there was some commotion from the current above his head.

Soon, a giant oyster came out of the current.

This oyster was the size of four elephants, it gave off the aura of an ancient desolate beast, the surface was entirely white-gold.

After seeing Fang Yuan, this oyster moved in a stunned manner.

Soon after, a voice came from the oyster: "Eh? There's someone here, you are just a rank six Gu Immortal, how can you reach here?"

Fang Yuan did not speak.

The oyster's shell opened, as its pinkish flesh was exposed.

This flesh was like a bed, with three people lying on it.

Two mortals female, considerably beautiful, were lying on a male Gu Immortal's body with their clothing undone.

This male Gu Immortal had a young man appearance, he was thin and had a sharp gaze, he looked at Fang Yuan with an overbearing gaze, he analyzed as he said with curiosity: "Strange, strange, you really have rank six cultivation level, quickly tell me your name."

Fang Yuan was silent, his gaze went from the male Gu Immortal to the oyster.

The male Gu Immortal was angry: "Hey, I am talking to you, are you deaf or mute?"

Fang Yuan asked instead: "This is the rumored precious beast — hidden room oyster?"

The male Gu Immortal immediately felt praised, he laughed: "You have quite some knowledge, I had asked for this from my grandpa after much work. My grandfather is the famous enslavement path Gu Immortal in Eastern Sea, Ren Xiu Ping!'

Fang Yuan nodded, saying plainly: "I know about Ren Xiu Ping, he is an expert at the peak of rank seven, not long ago, he found his blood related grandson, and spent a lot of effort to get him to ascend to immortal, that is you, right?"

"Hahaha." The male Gu Immortal laughed: "That's right, that's right, You are not bad, your foresight is good."

"Mm. Hand over the hidden room oyster, and I will spare your life." Fang Yuan said plainly.

"What?!" The male Gu Immortal thought he was hearing things.

His expression froze, he laughed out of pure anger, he pointed at Fang Yuan: "Good, good! I praised you wrongly, you have foresight but you are blind, you offended the wrong person! You are truly courting death! Then I shall — Ah!"

The male Gu Immortal was still talking, when he suddenly gasped.

Fang Yuan had already attacked.

The strength path giant hand grabbed the hidden room oyster fiercely.

The male Gu Immortal had a fearful expression, because he realized that the hidden room oyster was currently being squeezed by the giant hand, the two shells were making cracking noises under the pressure.

"Misunderstanding, it is a misunderstanding." He screamed: "I am Ren Xiu Ping's grandson, who are you, we might be friends!"

"Who is friends with you? I can let you go, just hand over the Gu worm that controls the hidden room oyster." Fang Yuan sneered: "Otherwise, you will die here."

"You are a demonic path Gu Immortal! You cannot do this, my grandfather will not let you off, think about it clearly!"

"It's just Ren Xiu Ping, so what." Fang Yuan smiled, aura surged out of his body, going from rank six to the peak of rank seven.

The young Gu Immortal had an ashen expression, the two mortal female beauties were completely shocked, they were shrinking away in a corner, shivering.

Chapter 1156: Immortal Gu Perceivable Dao

A moment later, Fang Yuan controlled the hidden room oyster, becoming its new master.

Pat pat pat.

He patted the young Gu Immortal's face: "Wise choice, lad."

The young Gu Immortal had a stiff expression, he did not dare to move, but his eyes were burning with embarrassment and hatred.

Fang Yuan ignored it.

Next, he jumped up into the hidden room oyster, sitting in the young Gu Immortal's former spot as he left.

Before leaving, he even said: "My name is Chu Ying, I took your hidden room oyster, remember to tell your grandfather."

Looking at the hidden room oyster which had closed its shell and vanished into the currents, the young Gu Immortal said with a forceful tone: "Good, Chu Ying? Don't worry, I have already transmitted your appearance to my grandfather!"

"Young master, what do we do now?" The two beauties were crying, they were tugging the young Gu Immortal's sleeves.

The young Gu Immortal's expression froze, the surrounding space was shrinking, the currents were about to form, his expression sank.

With his strength, he could not enter this place, he got here thanks to the hidden room oyster.

"Don't worry, even though the hidden room oyster is lost, I have my grandfather's traveling son Gu, I can return to the doting mother Gu, which is with my grandfather." The young Gu Immortal gritted his teeth.

"That's great, we are saved!" The two girls were overjoyed.

Boom boom!

With two sounds, the two beautiful girls looked with shocked gazes, one looked at the bloody hole in her chest while the other looked at the young Gu Immortal: "Young master, you..."

The young Gu Immortal had a grim expression: "Both of you witnessed everything, hmph!"

Immediately after, he showed a look of pity.

He stretched out of arm, touching the two beauties' faces: "It is a pity, they are quite beautiful, it is all Chu Ying's fault."

As he said that, he threw these two corpses into the current.

Without the defensive methods of a Gu Immortal, the mortal corpses were torn to shreds in the currents instantly.

Seeing that this space was about to collapse, the young Gu Immortal gritted his teeth, using traveling son Immortal Gu.

This turbulent flow sea area had very chaotic dao marks, the same applied to space path, Gu Immortals could not use space path Immortal Gu easily, the safest way was to travel normally.

But the young Gu Immortal was not using a space path Immortal Gu now, but emotion path instead.

Emotion path was a path originating from wisdom path. Wisdom path had three elements, thoughts, wills, emotions.

Traveling son Gu and doting mother Gu were a set of famous Immortal Gu in emotion path.

When the turbulent flow sea area was formed, emotion path had not been created yet, thus, at this moment, the young Gu Immortal could use traveling son Gu without any danger.

The young Gu Immortal allowed the power of traveling son Gu to send him away.

He seemed to have entered a long river, he felt groggy and dazed. A few minutes later, he regained his senses, realizing that he was inside Ren Xiu Ping's blessed land.

"Grandfather, I..." The young Gu Immortal showed fear and unrest.

"Hmph, while I was placing my immortal aperture to absorb heaven and earth qi and stabilize my blessed land, you sneaked out to have fun. If I knew this, I would not have given you the hidden room oyster for protection." Ren Xiu Ping chided.

"Grandfather, the hidden room oyster was taken away." The young Gu Immortal said in a distressed tone: "I met a demon, he stole my hidden room oyster and killed my two servants!"

"Oh?" Ren Xiu Ping's eyebrows rose: "Tell me the details."

The young Gu Immortal added lots of inflammatory details as he explained.

"Chu Ying..." Ren Xiu Ping muttered, frowning.

He had never heard of this name before. The two mortal girls were nothing, but a rank seven Gu Immortal approached and took away the hidden room oyster, this was the act of a demonic scoundrel. But why did he leave his name behind?

Was he not Chu Ying but someone else? Trying to frame him?

What ulterior motives did he have?

But regardless, Ren Xiu Ping memorized the name of Chu Ying.

He had a cold expression as he lectured his grandson: "Now, do you know about the cruelty of the Gu Immortal world? Up until now, you have been around me, all you saw were immortals I was on good terms with, they had a warm attitude towards you, or even flattered you because of me. Now, you have to learn a lesson, I will punish you to ten years of secluded cultivation. For the next ten years, you have to stay in my immortal aperture and will not leave."

"What?" The young Gu Immortal was shocked.

"Scram." Ren Xiu Ping billowed his sleeve, the young Gu Immortal's vision changed, he was inside a cave instantly.

"A jade cannot become refined without polishing, grandson, I cannot let you mess around anymore. Otherwise, even with my protection, there are many people in Eastern Sea who would not give me face. As for this Chu Ying, I will deal with him one day!" Thinking of this, Ren Xiu Ping's eyes flashed with ruthlessness.

...

"Since I am trying to befriend Miao Ming Shen, I might as well offend Ren Xiu Ping."

"Speaking of which, this hidden room oyster is quite useful, it is easy to use for transport. As long as the current isn't too strong, I can rest inside and regain my strength."

Fang Yuan sat inside the hidden room oyster as it flowed along with the currents.

Just like this, he got closer to his destination.

But in the turbulent flow sea area, distance did not relate to time from destination.

After taking the hidden room oyster, Fang Yuan's luck started to fall, he encountered several bad currents and went in bad directions. He had to make many detours.

After a long trip, a day later, he finally reached the central area of the turbulent flow sea area.

The currents here were massive, Fang Yuan entered them like an ant jumping into a river.

Ordinary currents would change directions or locations once in a while.

But the central area of the turbulent flow sea area was too big, because of its size, it was hard to shift, even though it changed at every moment, the extent was small, it was actually quite stable.

And in these currents, there were many bubbles.

There were big and small bubbles, from the size of a human head to a mountain.

These bubbles were formed during the huge battle, it was unknown which great expert's immortal killer move did it.

In the bubbles, there were carcasses and inheritances. Most bubbles contained sea water and small sized islands.

"Found it, it's this!" Fang Yuan looked for his target, he approached it with difficulty before entering it.

The bubble's surface was torn open, but it soon was restored, only some water went in, it was not a problem.

Fang Yuan's vision changed.

There was a green sea with a calm surface.

The sky was pure white, like an egg in color.

It was simply another world!

At the center of the sea, there was an island, there was wild grass on the island, and in the grass, there were many tall stone pillars.

Some people said that the worlds inside the bubbles were actually portions of the turbulent flow sea area originally, but after the battle, space was torn into pieces.

Some also said that these were the fragment worlds of the great expert's immortal aperture, because of a unique immortal killer move, these bubbles were formed.

Fang Yuan did not care about the reason why there were bubbles.

He came to the stone pillar and took out flying sword Immortal Gu.

Seemingly having sensed the information path insignia on flying sword Immortal Gu, these stone pillars started to shine in red light, soon after, they started to move slowly.

When they slowed down, space of around a vat's size opened, as a skeleton fell out.

Fang Yuan carefully inspected it.

This skeleton was full of bone path dao marks, it was a quasi rank eight immortal material.

The skeleton's right hand was holding a dark green lump.

Fang Yuan took out this dark green lump, after inspecting it, he burst it and several sleeping Gu worms were revealed.

Two Immortal Gu, and five mortal Gu.

Unfortunately, most of them were dead, only a corpse was left. When the wind blew, they turned to ash.

Countless years had passed, the Gu worm preservation method was not very good, it was no wonder that time prevailed.

Eventually, only one rank six Immortal Gu was left.

Fang Yuan quickly saved it, as it barely hung onto life.

"What Gu worm is this?" Fang Yuan was perplexed, he did not recognize it.

Looking at the skeleton, there was nothing left.

"This is that so called information path inheritance." Fang Yuan sighed.

An ordinary Gu Immortal would be joyous. But Fang Yuan, who had just obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, felt quite unsatisfied.

Inspecting the corpse, Fang Yuan discovered that in the skull of this skeleton, there were many thoughts sealed.

The thoughts were fragmented, but Fang Yuan was a wisdom path grandmaster, he could barely excavate some details from them.

The name of the Gu Immortal who left behind this inheritance could not be found. Fang Yuan only knew that he had barely survived that intense battle with his last breath, he managed to enter this bubble and set up his inheritance.

It was indeed an information path inheritance, but most of the information was lost.

But Fang Yuan was not leaving empty handed.

He knew the name of the Immortal Gu he saved — Perceivable Dao.

Perceivable dao Immortal Gu was an information path investigative Immortal Gu. It had a very niche effect, it could help the Gu Immortal see clearly what types of dao marks the target had and their quantity as well.

As for the origin of this skeleton, it was not the inheritance's creator, but an enemy killed by the information path Gu Immortal.

In the thoughts, the information path Gu Immortal who left this inheritance said that this skeleton could be used as immortal material directly. Because the enemy's dao marks were all left inside this skeleton.

This made Fang Yuan feel some surprise.

Because after a Gu Immortal dies, their dao marks usually go back to the immortal aperture. Unless it was an immortal zombie, without a normal immortal aperture, their dao marks would remain in the body.

"This information path Gu Immortal has amazing methods, he could gather all of the Gu Immortal's dao marks into their skeleton and preserve them. Unfortunately, the inheritance's information is too lacking, and it cannot be restored."

Fang Yuan felt it was a great pity.

He was hoping that this information path inheritance could allow him to obtain a method to break his alliance agreements.

Unfortunately, most things in the world do not proceed as one hopes.

What he obtained was only perceivable dao Immortal Gu.

Keeping the Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture, Fang Yuan prepared to leave.

"Murderer, where are you going!" At this moment, a blood-red figure charged into this huge bubble.

His bloodshot eyes were staring at Fang Yuan fiercely!

Chapter 1157: Exterminate

The other party had arrived imposingly, staring at Fang Yuan fixedly, he had injuries on his body, his hair was messy and he looked to be in a sorry state.

One thought flashed in Fang Yuan's mind: "Ding Qi."

Some days ago, Immortal Hua Die had told Fang Yuan about the blood path demonic path immortal, Ding Qi, who had come to the turbulent flow sea area. His brother, Ding Yan, was the blood path demonic immortal that had died at Liu Qing Yu's hands.

Now, Fang Yuan saw this person, he naturally had a guess towards his identity.

Next, another group of Gu Immortals appeared as they charged into the bubble.

The two at the front were familiar to Fang Yuan.

One was Tang Song, the other was Zhou Li.

Tang Song shouted: "Ding Qi, where are you trying to go? In exactly one year, it will be the anniversary of your death! It is a pity, your brother is dead, nobody is going to send you offerings, hahaha!"

Ding Qi seemingly did not hear anything, he stared at Fang Yuan, gritting his teeth: "It's you! You just obtained the information path inheritance, my brother found that clue after so much trouble, but it is with you. You are also his murderer!!"

"What?" The Gu Immortals pursuing him heard this and turned to stare at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Interesting. How did you know I took the inheritance?"

Ding Qi smiled coldly: "Because I have blood trace Immortal Gu."

Saying this, he used his Immortal Gu.

Soon, blood colored shadows appeared in the island. The shadows formed a series of movements, it was Fang Yuan who had entered the bubble and took away the information path inheritance.

Zhou Li and Tang Song screamed angrily: "He stole the inheritance!"

"Who are you?"

"Hand over the inheritance!"

Fang Yuan's smile bloomed, he ignored the immortals, he only looked at Ding Qi with curiosity: "Blood trace Immortal Gu, this is the first time I have heard of this."

"This is a blood path Immortal Gu that I created together with my brother. Other than this, we also created the Immortal Gu Blood Oath!" Mentioning his brother, Ding Qi was extremely angry and upset.

Zhou Li, Tang Song, and the other immortals were furious too.

As it turned out, Liu Qing Yu gathered a bunch of people to come to the turbulent flow sea area, it caused Ding Qi to appear.

Information got out, Zhou Li and Tang Song also gathered a group of Gu Immortals to come here. Initially, they were suspicious that Liu Qing Yu had gotten the information path inheritance clue.

They had spent so much effort in getting here, but the immortals met Ding Qi.

Ding Qi had already gotten here long ago, using blood trace Immortal Gu to make some arrangements.

Both sides fought, but Ding Qi was alone, even though he was a blood path demonic immortal, he could not rival so many enemies, he had to escape while fighting.

During which, Fang Yuan came in and obtained the inheritance. Ding Qi felt something and rushed over without caring about anything else, meeting Fang Yuan.

"This is blood trace Immortal Gu? Very interesting indeed." Fang Yuan looked at Ding Qi with a look of appreciation, sighing: "Geniuses are indeed everywhere, they have their own unique talents."

Speaking of blood path, the most famous person was Blood Sea Ancestor.

He was a great demon with seven Blood Sea true inheritances, everyone knew about them, he had left a deep mark in history.

But at present, if blood path experts were listed down, Ding Qi and Ding Yan would definitely have reputable rankings.

These brothers had deeply researched, they created Blood Oath and Blood Trace, these two blood path Immortal Gu. Most importantly, they actually managed to refine them, in terms of blood path, they were truly talented, it was rare.

"What are you sighing about, hand over the inheritance!"

"That's right, the inheritance is mine, you are an outsider, you actually snatched it from us."

Zhou Li and Tang Song screamed.

They had worked so hard and put in so much effort, in the end, an outsider whose name was not even known had taken their rightful gains.

Zhou Li and Tang Song had already regarded this inheritance as their own. Fang Yuan was naturally taking away their food, how could they stand it?!

Zhou Li and Tang Song gave up on their original target, Ding Qi, they turned towards Fang Yuan.

But Ding Qi was even quicker, he directly attacked Fang Yuan: "Murderer, hand over your life!"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "You want my life, but I'm not going to play with you. The inheritance is mine already anyway."

Saying so, he charged out of the bubble, going into the currents.

"Chase!"

"We will catch him, dead or alive!!"

Zhou Li and Tang Song shouted angrily, they refused to give up, especially Fang Yuan's final words, it truly sent their anger over the edge.

A group of Gu Immortals were chasing in the chaotic currents.

In this special environment, Gu Immortals could only move along with the currents. During the process, countless attacks aimed at Fang Yuan were unleashed.

Fang Yuan used his Immortal Gu to defend as he accelerated.

Sword escape Immortal Gu was not to be underestimated, soon, a group of Gu Immortals fell behind, they were too far apart.

"Eh? This person's movement is so familiar!" Zhou Li was perplexed.

Tang Song's eyes opened wide, he wanted to get back his inheritance, he did not think in that aspect at all.

Between the two sides, there was also the blood path demonic immortal Ding Qi.

His eyes were blood red, he was filled with killing intent: "Die, die! My brother died, and you took advantage of it, it was such a regretful death. Death, you deserve death, I will tear you into pieces!!"

Intense rage burned through his rationality, he was in a frenzied state.

Fang Yuan suddenly turned, dodging a huge waves of attacks.

The pursuers were stifled.

Fang Yuan's movements were too slippery, even if some killer moves could chase after the enemy, he destroyed them personally.

The Gu Immortals chased him for so long, but there was no result, they even wasted a lot of immortal essence.

Here was not like other places, the environment was quite unique.

A bubble appeared before them, Fang Yuan thoughts shifted, directly entering it.

"He went in!"

"Quick, quick, encircle it."

"Something is wrong, why did he enter a bubble instead of escaping?"

The immortals surrounded this bubble, but they did not enter, they were filled with suspicion.

A blood-red figure shot into the bubble like an arrow.

It was the blood path demonic immortal Ding Qi, he was more resolute than these Gu Immortals.

The immortals stayed outside the bubble, but they saw no disturbance.

They started to get restless, they could not stand it anymore, Tang Song went in first, followed by Zhou Li, and the rest, all of the Gu Immortals went into the bubble.

"Strange, where is this?"

"A city?"

The Gu Immortals who came in found that they had appeared amidst some houses for some reason.

These houses were designed meticulously, but they had broken walls, as if an earthquake had occurred here.

Furthermore, this place was full of cobwebs and dust, it looked like a city that had been abandoned for many years.

"Strange, strange. There are lots of pans and bowls here, it seems like many people had lived here before."

"On such a large scale, they cannot be Gu Immortals. But mortals actually lived here?"

"Even before the turbulent flow sea area formed, I have never heard of many mortals living here."

The Gu Immortals gathered as they discussed.

"Also, where is that Gu Immortal who ran away?"

"Ding Qi is missing too."

"No, Ding Qi is there, facing Lord Tang Song."

"The Gu Immortal who took the inheritance is really missing, he seems to be hiding inside here."

"Find him and force him to hand over the inheritance!"

The immortals were about to get to work, when they suddenly heard Fang Yuan's voice from the sky, it was loud and grand: "You are all here, good, everyone, enjoy this. It is your final moment before death."

As he said this, the immortals felt the sky turning dark.

They raised their heads and at the next moment, the immortals showed extremely shocked expressions.

Only to see that a huge hand, enormously big, covering the entire sky, pressed down slowly.

The aura was too imposing, it was like the sky was collapsing, everyone felt a strong feeling of weakness and helplessness.

"Impossible! This is an illusion, if he has such strength, how could he be running away from us?" Zhou Li shouted.

The immortals jolted, their morale rose, they felt that Zhou Li was right.

All of the immortals attacked.

Boom!

With a loud sound, the giant hand pressed down, countless houses collapsed, several Gu Immortals died at once, turning into meat paste.

"How can this be?" Zhou Li climbed up from the pit with much difficulty, he opened his eyes and looked around in disbelief.

The entire city was gone, it was a pathetic sight full of ruins.

The Gu Immortals who survived stood up in the rubble, they were all shocked and fearful.

In a contest of strength, they had so many Gu Immortals, but they actually lost.

"Shadow Sect's trap is truly useful. Hehe." Fang Yuan thought as he activated strength path giant hand again.

Thus, in the immortals' eyes, the sky turned dark again, the giant hand crashed down slowly while covering the entire sky.

"It's coming, it's coming again!"

"Hold on, we have to endure it!!"

"At the moment of life and death, forget about the rest, take out your trump cards and survive this trial."

The immortals shouted, they were fearful and uneasy, their attitude was clearly different from before.

Boom!

The giant hand caused the entire ground to lower by several meters, this time, only three people stood up.

Zhou Li, Tang Song, and the blood path demonic immortal Ding Qi.

Giant hand was used for the third time, the three immortals had a look of despair.

"I will not let you have an easy time even if I die!" Ding Qi self-detonated.

Zhou Li and Tang Song resisted but to no avail.

Eventually, they died at Fang Yuan's hands.

"Secluded domain of heaven and earth — City Well, it truly lives up to its reputation!" Fang Yuan praised as he sighed.

Right now, there was a well in front of him.

The well was squarish on the outside, but it was circular on the surface inside.

Fang Yuan stood on the edge of the well, he looked down, seeing a miniature town at the bottom of the well. Right now, it had been completely decimated from his three uses of giant hand.

There were some bloody patches in the rubble, it was the meat paste of Gu Immortals who were killed.

City Well first appeared in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Or more accurately, \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter four, section twenty-three clearly described it.

Chapter 1158: City Well

Legend has it ——

Ren Zu's fourth child, Boundless Forest Samsara, fell from the tree, she did not follow after Ren Zu, instead, she was trapped inside Ordinary Abyss.

One day, when she was sleeping, she met a miniman.

The miniman was crying, Boundless Forest Samsara asked him why.

The miniman spoke while crying: "I am the tallest in my tribe, and I was brave, arrogant and proud because of this. Today, I intended to climb a mountain, but to think that this mountain was really a person. There are actually such giant people like you in the world, this is the first time I've seen someone like you, so I burst into tears!"

Since then, Boundless Forest Samsara and the miniman became good friends, they were inseparable.

"Miniman, oh miniman, where is your father? Do you not have siblings? Why have I never seen your family?" One day, Boundless Forest Samsara asked the miniman.

The miniman directed Boundless Forest Samsara to a well, saying: "Look at this well, my former home is inside."

Boundless Forest Samsara sprawled in front of the well, extending her head to look inside.

Next, she shouted: "Ah, there are so many minimen."

She saw that there were countless minimen inside the well, they were living together.

They built many houses, they lived among each other, there were markets, flowers, it was a harmonious scene, they were very happy.

The minimen in the well also shouted.

"Why did the sky become so dark? It's night time already?"

"There was thunder but no rain, I don't see lightning either!"

The minimen were in panic, they discussed as the entire city went into commotion.

"Your family is here? Why did you go outside the well, you don't want to live with them?" Boundless Forest Samsara asked.

The miniman shook his head: "They were the ones who exiled me, they think I am a monster."

"Oh? Why is that?" Boundless Forest Samsara was curious.

The miniman answered with sadness: "I told them that the world we were living in was just a well. The outside world is very big. But they did not believe me, they told me to stop spouting nonsense."

"I also told them that the mountain at the fringe of our city is a very small mound. But they refuse to believe me, they think that it is the tallest mountain in the world, they told me to stop spreading lies."

"Which mountain is it?" Boundless Forest Samsara asked.

"That's Miniscule Mountain." The miniman pointed.

Boundless Forest Samsara started to giggle: "You call that a mountain? It can fit in my palm!"

Suddenly, Boundless Forest Samsara clapped: "Then let me tell them the truth."

The miniman shook his head: "It is useless."

Boundless Forest Samsara did not believe him, she faced the well as she shouted, the minimen inside started to panic even more.

They felt that today was too strange.

Not only did the sky turn dark, there was thunder rumbling, and it was getting louder and more frequent.

"Heaven is raging, I want to repent, I want to confess!"

"No, it is a monster, a monster ate heaven, it is burping now."

"Save me, this world is getting destroyed!"

Some minimen knelt on the ground and begged, some had despair on their faces, while others were running around crazily.

Boundless Forest Samsara's breathing became a tornado inside the well.

Boundless Forest Samsara's saliva became a huge rainstorm when it went into the well.

Boundless Forest Samsara's words were like rumbling thunder in the minimen's ears, their eardrums almost burst from it.

Boundless Forest Samsara eventually gave up, she sprawled outside the well, exhausted, she said weakly: "Why are these minimen so stupid? Can't they be like you, to get out of the well and see the world?"

The miniman shook his head as he sighed: "They think that they are big enough, they think the sky is round, they think the mountain is only that tall, they think life is just like this."

"Then why did you climb out?" Boundless Forest Samsara opened her eyes wide as she asked with curiosity.

The miniman smiled bitterly: "Because I realized how small and insignificant I was, therefore, I got out to see how big the world is."

...

Fang Yuan walked in a circle around City Well, his eyes were flickering brightly.

This was the third secluded domain of heaven and earth he had encountered.

The first two were Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley.

In order to harm Fang Yuan, Ying Wu Xie had set up a trap, it was by using City Well. But Fang Yuan took him by surprise, he obtained precious information from Liu Qing Yu, and in turn, made use of City Well to kill a bunch of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals instead.

Like what was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, Boundless Forest Samsara's breathing became a tornado, and her saliva became rain. Fang Yuan was outside the well, when he used his immortal killer move, the power was amplified by tens or hundreds of times when it entered the well!

But Fang Yuan had to pay a price.

His immortal essence expenditure was also tens or hundreds of times as high.

Even though Fang Yuan only used three giant hands, the expenditure was around the same as a hundred uses of it.

If an uninformed person entered the bottom of City Well, they would be trapped. But once they realize their situation and know this is City Well, they would be able to escape.

Like what \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> said, once the miniman realized his own insignificance, and wanted to see the world outside, he managed to climb out of City Well.

One could say, leaving City Well was both difficult and easy.

Precisely so, Ying Wu Xie did not use City Well to target Fang Yuan to a great extent.

Firstly, he could not control his strength, what if he killed Fang Yuan, how could he find the immortal material to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu again?

Secondly, Fang Yuan might immediately recognize the truth and escape with the upper extreme heavenly eagle, by then, Ying Wu Xie would not stand a chance.

The bigger reason was the second one.

Because he was uncertain, Ying Wu Xie made this City Well a trap to stall Fang Yuan, instead of using it to kill him.

Fang Yuan wanted to take this City Well for himself.

Because this secluded domain of heaven and earth would be a huge help to him when he develops his immortal aperture.

Pulling mountain Immortal Gu!

Fang Yuan began to try.

But City Well only shook slightly.

Pulling Mountain could pull out mountains, but City Well was not a mountain, although it was on the ground and needed earth qi.

Strength path giant hand!

Fang Yuan tried to dig out City Well.

However, once the giant hand got close to City Well, it rapidly shrank, like a burst bubble, in a few breaths' time, it was completely depleted.

"It seems that even though Shadow Sect has control of this secluded domain of heaven and earth, they cannot relocate it."

Fang Yuan tried a few more times without success. His best attempt was the first time, the result was evident, he used pulling mountain Immortal Gu and managed to make City Well shake slightly.

"In this case, pulling mountain Immortal Gu is actually effective, but just Pulling Mountain alone is not enough, I need to think of an immortal killer move that can relocate this City Well."

Realizing this, Fang Yuan could only give up for now.

He entered the well, when he got to the bottom, his body became very small.

Looting the battlefield.

Only Zhou Li and Tang Song had complete corpses, Fang Yuan put them into the sovereign immortal aperture.

As for the other Gu Immortals, they were all meat paste.

The blood path demonic immortal Ding Qi had self-detonated, but his blood path immortal aperture was left behind.

Other than him, the other Gu Immortals also left behind their immortal apertures.

Soon, the world inside the well started to stir, heaven and earth qi burst out as blessed lands formed one by one.

Fang Yuan spent a lot of time entering these blessed lands and exploring them.

Forget about Immortal Gu.

But there were quite a number of resources that were normally owned by Eastern Sea cultivators.

These Gu Immortals were not as poor as Liu Qing Yu, most of their assets were still around.

Except the blood path demonic immortal Ding Qi, even all of the resources inside his immortal aperture were destroyed. Even so, Fang Yuan was a blood path grandmaster, he had enough attainment level to annex Ding Qi's blessed land and expand the sovereign immortal aperture.

Inside these blessed lands, some had land spirits, some did not.

In the blessed lands without land spirits, Fang Yuan took away all of their resources. Those with land spirits were more troublesome, they needed to acknowledge him as their master, otherwise, Fang Yuan could not take away all of the resources inside.

Of course, it was not impossible to just plunder it, but that was a short term benefit disregarding the long term gains.

Fang Yuan thought about it, he did not use brute force.

After spending some time in the well, he left and started to modify this bubble.

The bubble had a sea and an island, City Well was in the middle of the island. Because of Ying Wu Xie's arrangement, outsiders would directly end up at the bottom of the well when they went in.

But Fang Yuan had Liu Qing Yu's information, he did not fall for it. Instead, he used this trap to kill all the pursuers, he got rid of a lot of trouble.

If Ying Wu Xie knew that his arrangements not only failed to give Fang Yuan problems, they even provided huge help to him, would he spit out blood from anger?

Fang Yuan preserved some of Ying Wu Xie's arrangements, at the same time, he added in some of his own methods, to conceal the bubble even more.

Next, he left the bubble and directed the bubble to a new location.

Not long ago, Ying Wu Xie did the same thing.

This bubble with City Well was not originally here. Ying Wu Xie wanted to harm Fang Yuan, he spent a lot of time and effort to move this bubble here.

Inside the current, Fang Yuan could not control where he went, he was washed away by it.

Thankfully, he had the hidden room oyster, he could rest inside.

Fang Yuan moved back and forth dozens of times before moving this bubble into another current.

He spent more than ten times the amount of immortal essence and time as Ying Wu Xie.

After completing this, Fang Yuan took a detour and went to Ying Wu Xie's former camp.

There, it was another island in a bubble.

Fang Yuan entered deep underground, but Regret Pool was already taken apart by Ying Wu Xie, even the surrounding Gu formations were gone.

The tributary of the River of Time that Shadow Sect had kept here was also missing.

This was the special characteristic of the turbulent flow sea area, every current was constantly changing and moving.

"But with this, it is enough to befriend Miao Ming Shen." Fang Yuan used his information path mortal Gu, sending it through treasure yellow heaven.

Chapter 1159: Development of the Sovereign Immortal Aperture

Several days later, Fang Yuan waited for Immortal Hua Die to arrive.

"There is a trace of the River of Time indeed, it is very recent!" Immortal Hua Die inspected and felt overjoyed. With this clue, she could definitely locate the tributary of the river of time.

"Chu Ying, we have truly troubled you. To think that you really found this tributary of the River of Time, we searched for decades without finding any useful clues!" Immortal Hua Die was very excited, she could finally give Miao Ming Shen good news.

"Go ahead and track it. I do not need any compensation, I might need Lord Miao Ming Shen's help in the future. I will take my leave."

Fang Yuan was understanding and kind, Immortal Hua Die had a good impression of him.

Before leaving, she advised again: "Be careful, blood path demonic immortal Ding Qi has appeared, engaging in battle with Zhou Li and Tang Song. If you meet them, you should avoid them, there is no need to get involved in this."

"Fairy, I will remember your words, thank you." Fang Yuan showed a moved expression.

Immortal Hua Die had no idea: It was this person who had killed Ding Qi, Zhou Li, Tang Song, and everyone else. But the turbulent flow sea area was very complex, it was normal that they all went missing, nobody felt anything strange.

There were often Gu Immortals who went missing for months or years before appearing suddenly again.

Half a month later.

Fang Yuan returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

In this journey to Eastern Sea, even though his goal was not achieved, he had great gains.

In the cloud city's secret room, Fang Yuan quietly sat as his divine sense activated, inspecting his entire sovereign immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture had changed greatly. In the past, it was barren and empty. But now, it had a lot of resources. At a glance, it was no longer so empty and boring.

Actually, all of these resources that Fang Yuan gathered could not fit inside ordinary blessed lands.

But the sovereign immortal aperture was simply too huge, after placing these resources, there was still a lot of space left.

In Mini Northern Plains, half the area was covered in snow and frost. The other half had green grass, on this grassland, Fang Yuan placed a few desolate beasts, like the giant horned sheep and shark fin wolf that he had since long ago.

In Mini Western Desert, there were already eleven eerie fire dragon python dens. Because of his aperture's rate of time being at sixty times, along with Dong Fang tribe's superb method of rearing, the eerie fire dragon pythons were reproducing at a rapid rate.

In Mini Eastern Sea, Fang Yuan had created several artificial lakes, putting dragonfish groups, air bubble fish groups, literature carp groups and others. Now, with more of the common resources obtained from killing the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, he had great gains. Even though they were not particularly precious, the quantity was high, he could develop using this foundation.

In Mini Central Continent, there was a huge area of mirror willows, it had formed a giant forest spanning a hundred li. Speaking of which, Fang Yuan had originally planted mirror willows inside Hu Immortal blessed land, after relocating them, these mirror willows were moved into Mini Central Continent. And because of the sovereign immortal aperture's time flow, although Fang Yuan had never put effort in them, with just their own growth rate, the forest reached this scale.

Other than mirror willows, Mini Central Continent also had a huge underground blood zhi forest, its scale was only slighter smaller than the mirror willows.

Mini Central Continent was too huge, mirror willows and the blood zhi forest had no competitors, they could grow freely.

The most flourishing region was Mini Southern Border, which was overflowing with life.

The resources obtained from Hei Fan grotto-heaven were mostly relocated here.

However, Mini Southern Border was not filled up.

Large numbers of musical trees and tea streams were seen, there were also the qi death bird groups bringing immense vitality to Mini Southern Border.

More than ten mountains had appeared in Mini Southern Border already.

The tallest mountain was Five Light Mountain, it was bright and grand, followed by Immortal Succession Mountain, it had many stone pavilions on it, the scenery was good.

Mini Southern Border's most important resource was the regretful spider group, it had already grown in scale multiple times already.

Above the five regions were the nine heavens.

In Mini Orange Heaven, there were profound lights, they were emitting from the flowing light fruits, this was the result of Fang Yuan's previous effort in farming them.

In Mini Yellow Heaven, there was a gold fragment river, it was not big, but better than nothing.

In Mini Azure Heaven, there was azure fog, it was the pill azure incense that Fang Yuan bought. There was also the storage pool of the heavenly crystals, it was temporarily placed here without any use.

In Mini Blue Heaven, large clouds were floating with star fragment grass and arrow bamboo forests on them, producing star path mortal Gu for Fang Yuan. There was also a young ancient desolate beast falling star hound, it was saved by Fang Yuan and was playing around in Mini Blue Heaven.

In Mini Purple Heaven, the heavenly crystal eagle nest was eaten by the upper extreme heavenly eagle, only an upper extreme heavenly eagle egg was left. There were also some heavenly crystal fragments. These were all exchanged from Lang Ya land spirit.

In Mini Black Heaven, there was a walking meat tree.

In Mini White Heaven, there were three remnant heavenly dogs, and a group of eagle hounds, as well as some multicolored overlord flowers, the light was making the environment quite conducive already. Earlier, because Fang Yuan killed some light path Gu Immortals, the light path dao marks in the immortal aperture had increased.

"Unfortunately, I did not bring back City Well into the sovereign immortal aperture."

Fang Yuan was still thinking about City Well, inside the turbulent flow sea area.

Even though City Well was damaged greatly, Fang Yuan could use Landscape as Before to restore it.

The destroyed buildings could not be repaired, but Miniscule Mountain could definitely be reformed.

It turned out that this legendary mountain had been destroyed during the battle of Yi Tian Mountain when Fairy Li Shan died. However, Fang Yuan thought of a way to restore it.

According to \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, Miniscule Mountain was a part of City Well.

"If I had City Well, I could raise large numbers of variant human groups inside the well. It is a pity..."

There were three stages in managing an immortal aperture.

The initial stage was when the Gu Immortal grows enough resources to fulfill the needs of their Immortal Gu's food.

The middle stage would be to develop more resources in addition to the Immortal Gu's food, to help the Gu Immortal in cultivation while also selling them for immortal essence stones.

The upper stage would be raising variant humans inside the immortal aperture, or even humans. This had huge significance to the Gu Immortal and has many benefits as well.

For example, earlier, Fang Yuan bought hairy man slaves in Hu Immortal blessed land to refine Gu for himself. This saved him a lot of time and effort.

Among the other variant humans, minimen could grow flowers and grass, rockmen could develop underground space, snowmen could produce ice tears and survive in the icy plains...

Pure bred humans had the greatest intelligence, they could reproduce rapidly and create things with their wisdom, large numbers of Gu recipes and killer moves could be created without the Gu Immortal making deductions themselves.

If one developed well, the immortal aperture might even have Gu Immortals or human Gu Immortals. They would be extremely loyal because they grew up in there. This would be a great help for the immortal aperture's owner.

Currently, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture was at the initial stage.

Because he had gained a few more Immortal Gu, and had not fulfilled their feeding needs. Attitude Gu, wisdom sword Immortal Gu, and the other rank eight Immortal Gu were hard to feed. Fang Yuan could only devise a plan, he had solved a portion of them, but these problems were not resolved yet.

However, in terms of the middle stage, he had incredible achievements.

Because he had obtained countless resources from Star Form blessed land, Dong Fang tribe, and Hei Fan grotto-heaven. Most normal resources, like star path mortal Gu, regretful spiders, musical trees and others, they were all sold outside and provided profits.

Not to mention Dang Hun Mountain, guts Gu has always been Fang Yuan's greatest source of profit, it earned him revenue daily.

Horses need extra grass to grow healthy, humans need windfalls to get rich.

What made Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture so wealthy were the countless windfalls that he had obtained.

And these resources were Fang Yuan's great assurance in cultivating.

Without these resources, no matter how high Fang Yuan's battle strength was, he would not feel assured.

Currently, Fang Yuan could not raise variant humans in large numbers.

Of course, he could do the same thing as in Hu Immortal blessed land, buying large numbers of variant humans to work inside the immortal aperture for him. But that was not the proper way.

The true way was to allow these variant humans to grow and reproduce naturally, they would be real members of the immortal aperture, living inside peacefully.

Only like this, they could grow healthily and produce great profits in the future.

If he bought variant human slaves and made them work, Fang Yuan would only incur losses. He had already learned this lesson in Hu Immortal blessed land. Fang Yuan's stone nests had hairy man slaves dying from Gu refinement almost every day. The hairy man slaves had no time to reproduce or rest, their numbers dwindled, Fang Yuan could only make a loss as he continued to buy slaves to replenish them.

However!

If he had City Well, it would be different.

City Well was a special environment isolated from the outside world, it was very suited for raising humans or variant humans. The reproduction and deaths of variant humans inside City Well would also have an effect of nourishing and elevating City Well itself.

Forget about this mystical property for now.

All in all, with City Well, Fang Yuan could instantly start his upper stage developments while still in the initial stage, he would obtain great gains.

This would undoubtedly allow his cultivation journey to be smoother, and his cultivation level would grow many times faster.

Fang Yuan ended his inspection of the sovereign immortal aperture.

There were areas where he was pleased, and areas where he was not satisfied.

What made Fang Yuan satisfied was, the sovereign immortal aperture's dao marks had grown favorably. For example, earth path dao marks, even though they were still lacking, they had improved greatly compared to earlier.

He was not satisfied with the fact that other than Mini Southern Border, the rest of the regions were still quite empty and had little resources. The sovereign immortal aperture was just too big.

Having huge space was a good problem.

The current situation would cause conflict between his resources in the future.

For example, the mirror willows, they were growing rapidly in Mini Central Continent. If another type of plant also grew quickly, and the two types met, an intense conflict would occur.

Conflict between plants was quite mild. But what about beast groups? If two fierce beast groups met, wouldn't they fight to the death?

If the blessed land was small, the Gu Immortal could adjust it quickly. But Fang Yuan's blessed land was too big, by the time he noticed their conflict, his losses would be severe.

To prevent this situation, Fang Yuan could only start planning early with great foresight.

The sovereign immortal aperture was not easy to manage.

Fang Yuan not only had to consider his current gains, he also had to think about the future.

Chapter 1160: Qi Luck Sensation is Ineffective

In conclusion, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had already grown much, but it still needed a lot of development work.

The sovereign immortal aperture had too much potential. It had five regions and nine heavens, even Mini Southern Border, which had taken in all of Hei Fan grotto-heaven's resources, could not be filled up. Nobody would believe this story.

And every layer of the nine heavens had the size of all five regions combined.

Fang Yuan had already noticed that the development of the sovereign immortal aperture would be a vast and unparalleled project.

Up until now, out of a hundred percent, his current developments could barely be considered to make up two percent completion.

"Were it not for me being the person involved and witnessing this myself, how could I possibly believe that such an immortal aperture exists in this world?"

"Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Shadow Sect, and Zombie Alliance planned for a hundred thousand years to obtain this, I took this from them, this conflict is truly irreconcilable."

"Sigh! It is a pity... even though in this trip, I managed to deal a blow to Ying Wu Xie's group, it could not truly shake their foundation."

Fang Yuan sighed when he thought of this.

In the dark secret room, he sat quietly, his hair hung down to his waist, his skin was pure like jade, his eyes were unfathomably dark like an abyss, as cold light flashed in them occasionally.

After adjusting his breathing, Fang Yuan mobilized his immortal essence, using an immortal killer move.

Qi luck sensation!

At once, a feeling spread out from Fang Yuan's body.

If he had luck inspection Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan would be able to see his huge luck shaking above his head.

Fang Yuan started to feel vague spots of sensation appearing one by one.

Western Desert.

The sun was blazing hot, causing steam to rise up from the sandy ground.

A pursuit of life and death was engaging here.

"Rascal, you actually dare to snatch the Gu worm that us bandits want!"

"Don't let me catch you, I will tear you to pieces, and use your skin as a lantern cover!!"

"Surrender, obediently hand over polished gold Gu, and you might have a chance to live."

A large group of Gu Masters with an imposing aura were chasing Han Li, who was running in front of them.

Han Li had extremely great luck, when he was alone, his luck could be low at times, but after it was connected, it had been very stable.

He cultivated for a period of time, he had rank three cultivation level now.

Elder level!

In the Gu Master world, he could already hold his own. He was neither a beginner rank one nor a cannon fodder rank two.

Rank three cultivation level was 'elite' in the Gu Master world.

However, in his current situation, three of the pursuers had rank three cultivation level, the rest were rank two and one.

Han Li could only run.

His primeval essence fell rapidly, his injuries were becoming a burden, blood was oozing out.

With every breath he took, Han Li endured pain that felt like a fire was burning his chest!

But such pain could not make him let go.

Right now, he was holding onto that polished gold Gu.

"My aptitude is not high enough, even though I have fortuitous encounters, in the long term, they are unreliable."

"This polished gold Gu can increase my aptitude, it can grant me a brighter future."

"I need to push on! Only by betting my life on it, can I have a chance to get stronger in the future!"

Han Li breathed roughly, he was extremely tired, but his legs moved like the wind, his running speed did not slow down at all.

His eyes were burning with fire!

Southern Border.

Water flowed down the lush green mountain.

Ye Fan shouted loudly, as his body suddenly grew to twice of his original size, he was tall and extraordinary.

Multi-colored lights were shining out of his muscles and pores, his eyes were radiating with bright light, he was truly grand and elegant.

Under the shocked gaze of his opponent, he punched with both fists like an unstoppable warrior, his aura was incredibly powerful.

Rumble!

Ye Fan took huge steps forward, everywhere he went, light shone as rocks shattered and streams dried, his enemies were forced back by him without any chance of retaliating.

"Cough, cough, Shang clan's Ye Fan, you live up to your reputation. This time, we, the Eighteen Sons of Wine Village admit defeat!" The leader of the enemies spat out blood, even though he wanted to get up, he could not.

The other seventeen Gu Masters were also lying on the ground, some had fainted while others were grunting, even though they could not fight anymore, they stared at Ye Fan with intense hatred.

Ye Fan slowly adjusted his stance, he let out a breath, his huge body shrunk back to its original size.

He looked at his opponents on the ground, saying calmly: "According to the rules, you Eighteen Sons of Wine Village are not to take a step onto this mountain again. This is now Shang clan's territory."

"Hmph, don't worry, we might be lone cultivators, but we lost this contest fair and square, we will keep our word." The leader replied firmly.

Ye Fan nodded, he rubbed his hands together, as jade green light shone on the Eighteen Sons of Wine Village.

They first shook in anxiety, but soon, they found that their injuries were rapidly recovering.

Soon, the Eighteen Sons of Wine Village stood up, they were able to move again.

The Eighteen Sons of Wine Village looked at Ye Fan with more relaxed expressions now.

Ever since Ye Fan accepted Gu Immortal Shang Qing Qing's Gu Master inheritance, his cultivation level might not have risen much, but his overall strength had grown drastically, he had methods in all aspects, and did not have a visible flaw.

When Shang Xin Ci first became clan leader, Shang clan's mortal sector had lots of internal and external problems. It was Ye Fan who stood up and helped Shang Xin Ci resolve her problems. Right now, Ye Fan chased away the Eighteen Sons of Wine Village, he helped Shang clan open up a new trade route and eased her political pressure.

The leader sighed, cupping his fists: "Ye Fan, you are very strong, but you let us off in the end. We brothers will accept this favor, as long as you are in Shang clan, we will not target it. However, if you want to open up the trade route, we are only the third hurdle, you have two more obstacles ahead."

"I understand, any Gu Master in these two rounds would be stronger than all of you combined." Ye Fan nodded expressionlessly.

He had a lot of information, Shang clan was a huge force, Shang Xin Ci would not restrict Ye Fan in this aspect.

But the leader's following words made Ye Fan's expression change: "Hehe! Ye Fan, be careful. These two obstacles have changed, not long ago, White Demon appeared and defeated those lone cultivators. Right now, she has already gathered all the Gu Masters in these two rounds, becoming the mastermind. If you arrived a day later, we would have surrendered to White Demon as well."

"White Demon? You mean, the Black and White Demons?" Ye Fan's eyes shined brightly.

The leader of the Eighteen Sons of Wine Village nodded: "If it were not a famous demonic cultivator like White Demon, why would those lone cultivators submit? She has unfathomable strength, I would advise you to consider it thoroughly."

Shang Xin Ci's image appeared in Ye Fan's mind, before Hei Tu appeared in his mind.

"No!" His body shook with determination, he spoke plainly, with an indisputable tone: "I will go."

Central Continent.

In a nameless cave.

"Don't come here, don't come here!" Hong Yi's clothes were torn, his muscular chest was exposed.

A morbidly obese female Gu Master chuckled as she approached him: "Little sweetheart, can you escape? You have ended up in my hands, accept your fate. Just submit to me, hahaha."

Whoosh.

With a soft sound, Hong Yi's clothes were all stripped away.

The female Gu Master jumped, about to press on him.

"No!" Hong Yi screamed in fear, at the moment of crisis, he unleashed two hundred percent of his potential, he broke the seal on his body and pushed the female Gu Master away.

"Impossible! How could you break the seal I created?" The female Gu Master was startled and angered.

"That is because I am here." A miniman Gu Master appeared on Hong Yi's shoulder.

"You finally came!" Hong Yi was about to cry.

"We got the thing, let's go!" The miniman whispered.

The female Gu Master's expression changed, she sensed something amiss, the muscles on her fat face distorted: "So that's it! You two came here to steal my ecstasy water!"

Hong Yi, Ye Fan, Han Li...

Even though Fang Yuan could not see their experiences, he could sense their locations, and differentiate them.

Because of their relationship from Connect Luck, qi luck sensation could detect them across all five regions.

However, Hei Lou Lan and Ying Wu Xie were nowhere to be found.

From this, Fang Yuan concluded that Ying Wu Xie indeed had a way to conceal his own luck connection.

"Actually, so be it if he does. But Ying Wu Xie as a person is maturing, he will be much more problematic to deal with in the future."

This was why, there was no strongest Immortal Gu, only strongest Gu Immortal.

The Gu Immortal was the core.

Ying Wu Xie's matured mind, in Fang Yuan's opinion, was far scarier than whatever strong Immortal Gu he had.

"The other party can deal with qi luck sensation, then in the future, I can only reduce the number of times I use this immortal killer move."

After all, this was an immortal killer move, it required green grape immortal essence to activate.

Once it was used frequently, even Fang Yuan could not bear the cost.

This trip to Eastern Sea was rather successful, but his green grape immortal essence stockpile had already reduced sharply, he needed to replenish it.

From Fang Yuan's perspective, the best situation was that he could find Ying Wu Xie's location and exert pressure on him, or even kill him to get rid of the threat entirely.

But currently, the situation was not as he wished.

Fang Yuan thought about it, he could only choose the best alternative and focus on raising his strength.

But he knew deeply: "There was only one true inheritance of Hei Fan, but Shadow Sect has remnant forces in all five regions. In this trip to Eastern Sea, I did not get rid of Ying Wu Xie, the next time we meet, they might already greatly surpass me in strength."

Shadow Sect did not lack resources, and they had at least four Gu Immortals on their side.

Right now, Fang Yuan could only do his best and develop, when they met again, hopefully, he would not be left in the dust by Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

Fang Yuan took out perceivable dao Immortal Gu.

This rank six information path Gu worm was now healthy and strong, it gave off an alluring light, it had been saved by Fang Yuan.

Breathing in deeply, Fang Yuan started to activate this Immortal Gu.

Chapter 1161: Testing Perceivable Dao Immortal Gu

Perceivable dao Immortal Gu!

This Immortal Gu had a round head and a black body, it had many segments in its body, once activated, it started to shine in starlight.

Blue starlight reflected on Fang Yuan's entire body.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply and concentrated, he observed meticulously, preventing any accidents from occurring.

When Gu Masters use Gu, it was not safe. Many Gu worms had backlashes or weaknesses.

The same went for Immortal Gu, and because they were powerful, the drawbacks and weaknesses were also larger.

This was the first time Fang Yuan was using perceivable dao Immortal Gu, even though he used wisdom path methods to deduce it already, he still had to be careful.

Initially, starlight only shone on Fang Yuan's body. But after a few breaths of time, starlight accumulated, it covered Fang Yuan's entire body like a thin layer of water.

Starlight gathered into shining water, it got thicker and thicker, accumulating on Fang Yuan's face, limbs, and body.

Afterwards, as time passed, the shining water faded, after more than ten breaths, it vanished.

The starlight around perceivable dao Immortal Gu also vanished, it returned to its black state.

But in Fang Yuan's mind, there was some information, he could see how many dao marks he had in his body.

The greatest number were in snow path and ice path dao marks, reaching a total of sixteen thousand!

Fang Yuan learned this and his heart jumped.

A hundred dao marks meant that an Immortal Gu's effect would increase by ten percent. A thousand dao marks would double its effect. Then sixteen thousand dao marks would result in sixteen times the amplification of effects!

This meant that when Fang Yuan uses an Immortal Gu from ice or snow path, the effect would be very strong. For example, compared to a Gu Immortal without any dao marks using an ice or snow path Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan's might would be seventeen times of this Gu Immortal!

And the most important point was, even though the power was seventeen times as much, Fang Yuan's green grape immortal essence expenditure was the same as the other Gu Immortal.

This was different from City Well, even though the immortal killer move was a hundred times stronger, Fang Yuan's green grape immortal essence expenditure rose by a similar proportion, he also spent a hundred times as much!

This was very fearsome.

Why did the battle strength of Gu Immortals as their cultivation level got higher, this was the reason.

Below ice and snow path, the second highest quantity of dao marks belonged to luck path, it had fifteen thousand!

"My luck path dao marks were basically all absorbed from Feng Jun's accumulation, this person had a deep foundation, he personally ascended Immortal Succession Mountain and succeeded, inheriting a large number of luck path dao marks from it."

"Oh, right. There was an earthly calamity with the giant disaster blazing tree, after passing it, I gained luck path dao marks as well."

Below luck path dao marks were qi path and sound path dao marks.

Both had around thirteen thousand.

"Qi path dao marks mainly come from Qi Zai, he was a rank seven Gu Immortal who cultivated qi path, almost all of his qi path dao marks are absorbed into my body now."

"Sound path dao marks came from Tang Song, this person is also rank seven, he is a supreme elder from a super force of Eastern Sea, Tang clan."

Below that was blood path dao marks, about twelve thousand of them, they were obtained from Hei Fan grotto-heaven's blood path Gu Immortal, Zheng Tuo.

Fang Yuan thought about it, he realized that among his dao marks, the rest of those that reached ten thousand were all from rank seven Gu Immortal corpses.

Among them, rule path dao marks had twelve thousand, they were from Hei Fan grotto-heaven's rule path Gu Immortal, Chen Chi.

Water path dao marks were around eleven thousand, obtained from lone immortal Zhou Li after Fang Yuan absorbed his foundation.

Below that was transformation path and strength path, they summed up to nine thousand in total, close to ten thousand.

Other than that, there was an assortment of other paths, haphazardly mixed in.

For example, there was wind path, wood path, and food path.

"I went through a few earthly calamities, the wind flowers, spring dawn jade orioles, they gave me wood path and wind path dao marks. Food path actually exceeds these two paths, I guess the profound white flying salt calamity gave me food path dao marks."

And fewer than these were earth path, time path, and information path.

"Earlier, I joined the alliance of variant humans, they used an earth path method to attain information path effects. Thus, I gained quite a number of earth path dao marks."

"As for time path, they are probably from the hundred years harmony that I set with Chu Du, similar to the variant human alliance."

"As for information path dao marks, they must be from the alliance agreement of Lang Ya Sect."

The least in quantity, like phantom path, still had a hundred or so. This was the initial number of dao marks that sovereign immortal fetus brought with it.

Fang Yuan considered these numbers, from these, he had a glimpse of the nature of some calamities and tribulations.

He concluded.

Ice and snow path were highest, followed by luck path, qi path, sound path, rule path, water path, and blood path, they all had over ten thousand.

Below these were transformation path and strength path.

And below those were food path, wind path, wood path, earth path, time path, and others.

"I mainly fight with strength path, sword path, and time path methods. Familiar face and blood asset Immortal Gu are supplementary methods."

"My five grandmaster attainments are in wisdom path, strength path, star path, blood path, and transformation path."

Fang Yuan looked at his situation, it was quite awkward.

His paths with more than ten thousand dao marks were almost completely different from his main methods and five highest attainment levels.

According to Fang Yuan's original cultivation plan, his focus was on transformation path.

But now, because he joined the four races alliance, this plan had a lot of barriers. He could not undergo tribulation in the icy plain, Fang Yuan could not draw out Reckless Savage's true meaning. If he could not influence the earthly calamity, he would not gain transformation path dao marks, or even any rise in his attainment level.

Fang Yuan pondered.

"From this, it seems that most rank seven Gu Immortals have about ten thousand or more dao marks of their main path."

"But I have only gone through four earth calamities, and already have sixteen thousand ice and snow path dao marks, while my transformation path and strength path dao marks are close to ten thousand. Looking at my wood path, wind path, and food path dao marks, my total gain from these calamities add up to thirty thousand."

Evidently, this number was abnormal.

Gu Immortals with rank seven cultivation level had undergone up to around forty to fifty earthly calamities, four or five heavenly tribulations, and one or more grand tribulations.

After all these, their main paths only had about ten thousand dao marks.

Fang Yuan had only gone through four earthly calamities, but he had already gained three times the number of dao marks as them!

The stronger the calamities and tribulations, after passing them, the greater number of dao marks the Gu Immortal would obtain.

Ordinary Gu Immortals would have simpler tribulations. When they get to rank seven, they would have about ten thousand dao marks in their main path.

Those with higher aptitude and having high grade blessed lands, or even immortal apertures originating from the ten extreme physiques, would have more resources in their blessed lands, with greater fortune comes greater disaster, they would have stronger calamities and tribulations, and would gain more dao marks after passing them.

Fang Yuan's situation was unique in the entire world!

Even if the sovereign immortal aperture had no resources, it was an immense amount of fortune in itself, the earthly calamity that befalls also reaches the limit of its strength.

And because he was a complete otherworldly demon, heaven's will would try every possible way to kill Fang Yuan, causing his earthly calamity to be elevated to the maximum force allowed.

In his first four earthly calamities, each one was extremely difficult, Fang Yuan passed them with great danger, it was like he was walking on a tightrope. But now it seemed, the risks were great, but his gains were huge as well!

"Even though my current development and my methods don't match, my dao mark growth is real. At this rate, after each earthly calamity and heavenly tribulation, my foundation would rise to a terrifying degree!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan felt that all the difficulty and hard work he had gone through were worth it.

Even his attitude towards the earthly calamities had vaguely changed.

Each earthly calamity could be seen as a great chance to gain more dao marks!

"After a few more earthly calamities, how much would I grow? How much would my foundation grow?" Even Fang Yuan could not estimate this.

The sovereign immortal aperture surpassed the norm by too much.

His growth potential and speed could not be assessed by normal means!

The amount of dao marks Fang Yuan gained from four earthly calamities was multiple times that of an ordinary rank seven Gu Immortal's dao marks in their main path!

After clarifying the number of dao marks in his body, Fang Yuan took out his Immortal Gu, using Perceivable Dao to investigative them.

But unfortunately, even though the starry water covered the surface of the Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan did not get any results.

He realized: "Man is the spirit of all living beings, Gu are the essence of heaven and earth. Mortal Gu have dao marks, while Immortal Gu have fragments of the Great Dao. Perceivable Dao can only investigate dao marks, it is ineffective against Great Dao fragments."

Indeed, when he used perceivable dao Immortal Gu on mortal Gu and checked them, it worked like a charm.

But his tests were far from over.

Next, Fang Yuan took out immortal materials and used perceivable dao Immortal Gu to inspect them.

He realized that even though the dao marks in the immortal materials could be sensed by him, the expenditure of immortal essence rose when the quality and rank of the immortal material was higher.

"Perceivable dao Immortal Gu is an information path Immortal Gu, when looking at purely information path immortal materials, the immortal essence expenditure is lower. Other than that, any other type of immortal materials would have an element of conflicting dao marks. Thus, the immortal essence expenditure is greater."

"As for why using it on me does not cause more immortal essence expenditure, that is because my dao marks are non-conflicting."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan had a stern expression on his face.

The property of non-conflicting dao marks of the sovereign immortal body was both a good thing and bad thing for him.

For ordinary Gu Immortals, when killer moves of other paths land on them, their dao marks would first reduce the might of the attacks, but Fang Yuan would have to face its full force. In fact, when his dao marks are of the same path as the attacking killer move, it might even get amplified!

With just this point, Fang Yuan could not fight at close range.

He was suited for long range battles, after creating some distance, he could amply think and evade attacks.

"Perceivable dao Immortal Gu cannot be used on Immortal Gu, and when using it on immortal materials, there is a conflict of dao marks. All in all, it is not very useful." After Fang Yuan tried using it, he came to a conclusion.

He could only think of three ways to use perceivable dao Immortal Gu currently.

The first was to decipher immortal materials, preventing others from scamming him.

The second was to investigative a Gu Immortal's dao marks, to probe their foundation and strength. But it was quite impractical, the time needed to use it was quite long, and the effect of the starry water was also very obvious, it was easy to take action to counter it.

The third was in refining Immortal Gu.

Investigation using Perceivable Dao could allow him to see the dao marks clearly during the process of refining Immortal Gu, as well as to make a comparison.

However, perceivable dao Immortal Gu was unable to find out the exact location of dao marks or influence them, thus, it had limited use.

At most, it could allow the Gu Immortal to turn from a 'blind man' to a 'man with his eyes shut'.

Chapter 1162: Soul Path Trap

After testing out perceivable dao Immortal Gu, it was time for Fang Yuan to cultivate his soul again.

He flew out of his cloud city, and went to Luo Po Valley.

However, the usage of perceivable dao Immortal Gu was not over.

Fang Yuan multitasked.

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Southern Border.

There were ample forests, it was no longer barren. Ordinary mountains were evenly distributed across Mini Southern Border in different places.

A strength path immortal zombie was controlled by Fang Yuan, carrying some immortal essence and perceivable dao Immortal Gu as it flew in the air.

A moment later, it slowly descended, landing on a small mountain.

Fang Yuan named this mountain Heaven Sealing Mountain.

The name was very grand, but the mountain was short and uninspiring. The mountain peak was being modified by Fang Yuan, there was a huge Gu formation on it, as the interior of the mountain was empty, it was sealing an immortal zombie body.

It was Fang Yuan's original body.

The strength path immortal zombie entered the interior of the mountain and came to the center of the sealing Gu formation.

Fang Yuan's original immortal zombie body was six meters tall, it had a miniature pair of bat wings on its back, it had a green face and sharp fangs, its eyes were shut. Its eight arms were all different, other than his two original arms, there was the asura arm, heavenly demon arm, blood wight arm, nightmare arm, plague arm, and the earth chief arm.

At this moment, the eight arms were spread out like a peacock's tail, their fingers were tightly stabbed into the ground.

Because it was sealed, the immortal zombie's heartbeat was very slow, there was only one beat every few minutes.

Light was emitting from the Gu formation, blowing on the immortal zombie body like a clear breeze, this showed that the sealing Gu formation was working fine.

Fang Yuan manipulated the strength path immortal zombie as he activated perceivable dao Immortal Gu, starlight gathered into flowing water as it covered the body of the immortal zombie.

A moment later, Fang Yuan got his results, he mentally snorted: "Something was done to it after all!"

His caution was truly wise.

Ying Wu Xie had left about ten thousand soul path dao marks in the immortal zombie body, it was more than Fang Yuan's original strength path dao marks inside the body.

After storing away perceivable dao Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan manipulated the strength path immortal zombie, opening a slit in the sealing Gu formation as the strength path immortal zombie pulled something out of its body.

A Gu Immortal's soul shrieked as it was dragged out by the strength path immortal zombie.

"Spare me, spare me!"

"I will acknowledge you as my master, please spare my life!!"

The Gu Immortal's soul struggled intensely, it seemed to have sensed its doomsday.

Fang Yuan manipulated the strength path immortal zombie expressionlessly as his demonic claws controlled the Gu Immortal's soul, preventing it from moving.

In the dark space in the mountain, the sealing Gu formation shone with light, not only did it not bring the warmth of light, it gave the environment a cold eerie feeling.

The Gu Immortal's soul cried out, it made the atmosphere even more creepy.

The strength path immortal zombie moved slowly, pressing the Gu Immortal soul into Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body.

The Gu Immortal soul was unwilling, but Fang Yuan was amply prepared, he forcefully stuffed it into the immortal zombie body.

Soon after, Fang Yuan used the Gu formation, activating the sealing Gu formation.

Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body did not move, it lay on the ground like a statue. But after the Gu Immortal soul entered it, the body started to shake.

Soon, the shaking intensified.

Suddenly, the shaking stopped entirely, Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body stopped moving, he opened his eyes, they were red like blood!

Roar!

He opened his mouth and growled, the loud noise was echoing in the mountain's interior, like the rumbling of thunder.

Fang Yuan sneered, the strength path immortal zombie that he controlled did not move, it looked down at the immortal zombie body.

Indeed, due to the Gu formation's restrictions, and the arrangements done to the Gu Immortal soul earlier, Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body struggled to get up but could not, feeling weakness all over.

"What are you doing, what are you trying to do?" The Gu Immortal soul screamed.

He did not understand Fang Yuan's intentions, he felt an utter wave of fear and horror.

Soon, the Gu Immortal soul screamed in a high pitch tone: "You, what did you do to me? My soul is melting, you have a vicious heart, I only have my soul left, and you still refused to let me off!!"

Fang Yuan controlled the strength path immortal zombie, he watched with concentration, he ignored the Gu Immortal soul's screaming and crying.

"The soul would melt if they enter huh..." Fang Yuan investigated with all sorts of methods.

"Oh, this is an amazing soul path method. This Gu Immortal soul could not even last a short period of time!" Fang Yuan gasped, at his will, the strength path immortal zombie stretched out its right arm, trying to pull out the Gu Immortal soul from the immortal zombie body again.

But at the next moment, a ghost face appeared on the chest of Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body, cackling at Fang Yuan loudly!

An immense strength burst out as the strength path immortal zombie took three steps back.

Looking at it again, the ghost face had vanished.

Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body stopped moving, returning to the state of a statue.

Fang Yuan controlled the strength path immortal zombie, carefully getting closer, Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body did not move at all.

Fang Yuan continued to probe.

The Gu Immortal soul that he stuffed into the immortal zombie body earlier had completely melted, not even a bit of it was left.

"The melting speed is really fast, once the soul goes in, it is like a deep trap. Even if I pull it out, it cannot escape from the trap!"

Fang Yuan analyzed mentally.

Ying Wu Xie's trap was incredibly vicious, the method was extraordinary.

Fang Yuan was glad that he was vigilant, he did not take a risk to enter the body, otherwise, the consequences would be severe.

After several inspections, Fang Yuan used perceivable dao Immortal Gu again, inspecting his immortal zombie body.

"What is going on? The soul path dao marks did not decrease, they even rose by two thousand!" Fang Yuan was shocked.

At this moment, Fang Yuan was completely stunned by Shadow Sect's incredible soul path methods.

Melting the Gu Immortal soul was a huge problem, but Fang Yuan could deal with it.

The simplest and crudest method was to use Gu Immortal souls and constantly stuff them into the immortal zombie body so that the trap would weaken after several activations, before breaking down eventually.

But Ying Wu Xie's trap was not normal!

It not only prevented the soul that entered Fang Yuan's immortal body body from leaving, it even melted the soul and after that, strengthened itself, to replenish its expenditure and become stronger!

"Truly impressive! In this case, my action of sending Gu Immortal souls to probe it is restricted. Unless I have a method that can truly target the soul path dao marks in this body. Otherwise, I would only be making this trap more powerful!"

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth.

Actually, the Eastern Sea information path inheritance would have had many methods that targeted dao marks.

This could be seen from the information path dao mark insignia in flying sword Immortal Gu. Flying sword Immortal Gu was a dao mark fragment of sword path, but information path dao marks were added to it, the conflict between different paths was resolved. It was very difficult to achieve this, even rank eight Gu Immortals might have problems with it.

Furthermore, the quasi rank eight skeleton that Fang Yuan obtained was also clear evidence.

After a Gu Immortal dies, their path's dao marks would go into the immortal aperture as it forms a blessed land outside. If a blessed land did not form, these dao marks would scatter into nothingness and return to the five regions.

But this information path Gu Immortal could actually directly carve this bone path Gu Immortal's dao marks into his skeleton. The method was very special, it was rather unthinkable.

In the end, perceivable dao Immortal Gu even proved that this information path Gu Immortal had special methods that targeted dao marks.

"The complete information path true inheritance might have really had methods against dao marks. It is a pity I obtained this true inheritance too late, most of the Gu worms are dead, and the information path methods are lost."

How could everything be perfect in this world?

Fang Yuan could obtain Hei Fan's complete true inheritance, it was already very lucky.

The Eastern Sea information path inheritance had been there for too long, and the information path Gu Immortal had just killed his enemy, he created the inheritance on the verge of death. The contents of the true inheritance could not be preserved for long.

Even though he obtained perceivable dao Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan still needed to get more information path methods that could prevent him from being restricted by his alliance agreements.

"Searching for an information path Immortal Gu that can break alliance agreements is one way. But I need to keep it a secret, I cannot find Lang Ya Sect for help on this. Let alone getting Lang Ya land spirit to help me refine such an information path Immortal Gu."

Information path inheritances would not be easy to obtain, and Fang Yuan's information path attainment level was at ordinary level, he could not design his own Immortal Gu recipe and innovate.

In this trip to Eastern Sea, even though his gains were not few, Fang Yuan's original goal was not achieved.

He still sought out and lacked information path methods.

As his focus turned away from the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan began to focus on his soul path cultivation.

An hour later, he left Luo Po Valley.

He rigidly stuck to daily soul path cultivation. Because his soul path foundation grew rapidly, Fang Yuan could stay inside Luo Po Valley for a fifty percent longer time now.

However, now that Fang Yuan saw the trap inside his immortal zombie body, he was wavering on his plan of cultivating his soul.

Ying Wu Xie knew that Fang Yuan had Luo Po Valley and Dang Hun Mountain, how could he not consider this? Cultivating his soul was not a wrong decision, but by the time Fang Yuan gained enough soul foundation to resist the trap, a long time would have passed, he would have to put in a huge amount of effort!

And Fang Yuan's time and energy were not unlimited. He needed to spend a lot of time and effort in planning, devising ways to advance his cultivation and development.

"But I have to leave the matter of information path for later. The fifth earthly calamity is coming."

This earthly calamity was different from the previous four.

The last four times, Fang Yuan used immortal tribulation tempering aperture to undergo tribulation in the northern icy plain. But now, Fang Yuan could not stay in the northern icy plain, he had to find a new tribulation location.

What location should he choose?

A few days later, Chu Du sent him a letter, saying that he would help Fang Yuan undergo tribulation, in exchange for Reckless Savage's true meaning.

At once, Fang Yuan was in a situation with his hands tied!

Chapter 1163: Chu Du versus Heavenly Lord Bai Zu

Northern Plains, Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Chu Du stood in the air, the Immortal Gu aura on him was emanating, his immortal essence was being consumed rapidly.

"Open!"

Suddenly, he shouted, his eyes burst with bright light, his body shook intensely.

The ground several meters away from him started to crack open under the power of his immortal killer move.

Suddenly, this opening became larger, it extended out, a hundred feet, a thousand feet, ten thousand feet!

After tens of breaths, Hei Fan grotto-heaven stopped shaking, a huge trench of tens of thousands of feet opened up along the ground.

Chu Du had created an artificial Earth Trench with his strength alone, he was indeed an expert that stood tall and proud in Northern Plains!

He breathed roughly, looking at the trench below him, he frowned.

"It is not perfect yet, even if it is long enough, it is not deep enough. After all, earth path Gu Immortals are most skilled in doing this."

All paths had their own specialties.

Earth path Gu Immortals were particularly skilled at changing the terrain of the ground.

But Chu Du was a famous strength path Gu Immortal.

"There is another way, I can buy many rockman slaves and modify this place. However... forget it, this trench is enough for now."

Thinking of this, Chu Du took out a huge object from his immortal aperture.

This object was huge like a small mountain, it was a red and black meatball, it was hot and round, vibrating weakly.

Chu Du used his strength path hand, carrying this huge thing and slowly placing it into this newly created earth trench.

This huge thing landed in the trench, once it came into contact with the soil, it spread out, becoming flat, spreading across several li.

Next, its color started to change.

Initially, it was black and red, but after spreading out, it took in earth qi, as its color changed. A portion became blue, another became green, part of it resembled jade, while another side was red like fire.

Chu Du watched from above, seeing this color changing scene in the earth trench, it was quite a dazzling sight.

These were multicolored guts!

A rank seven immortal material that came from deep within Earth Trench.

Chu Du acted quickly, taking out dozens of multicolored guts from his immortal aperture, tossing them in.

The earth trench that was empty earlier was completely filled, no more multicolored guts could be put in.

After carefully inspecting it, Chu Du let out a breath, his body slowly ascended into the air.

He looked far away, taking in the view of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

When he took it over from Fang Yuan, it was barren and completely ransacked by Fang Yuan, it was a terrible sight. But now, it had mountains and rivers, the resources were prudently distributed.

Undoubtedly, these resources were all relocated from Chu Du's own immortal aperture.

Even though he was just a lone immortal, his foundation in terms of resources was very deep.

"The initial developments are complete. In the future, Hei Fan grotto-heaven's production will far surpass my own immortal aperture."

"Looking at the time, Liu Guan Yi is about to undergo tribulation. Hmm?!"

Suddenly, Chu Du's expression froze, his sharp gaze pierced through the sky, he saw a twisted figure squeezing into Hei Fan grotto-heaven with much difficulty.

"Who is it? You dare to invade my grotto-heaven!" Chu Du shouted, his body flew over like a gust of wind.

After the figure got into the grotto-heaven, he smiled at Chu Du: "Domination Immortal, as a junior, your talent is quite good. In such a short time, you have already taken ownership of this place."

The invader spoke big words, against the great Northern Plains expert Domination Immortal Chu Du, he regarded himself as a senior.

But Chu Du did not rebuke him, he had a heavy expression: "It is you, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu."

It turned out, the invader of Hei Fan grotto-heaven was none other than one of the rank eight Gu Immortals in Northern Plains, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was originally a lone cultivator, but in recent years, because Fang Yuan destroyed Imperial Court blessed land and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he saw hope in creating a super force.

He had planned this long ago, inside his Bai Zu grotto-heaven, he had countless blood related descendants and even multiple Gu Immortals.

Initially, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang worked together to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, even though they lost, he had obtained Yao Huang's support.

After that, when Hei tribe was exterminated, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu used the chance to take over Hei tribe's Iron Eagle blessed land, and also taking in all of Hei tribe's remnant forces.

Right now, Bai Zu tribe had officially taken over Hei tribe, becoming one of the righteous path super forces publicly recognized in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

However, Northern Plains was different from the other four regions, most of the super forces were of the Huang Jin bloodline. As an outsider, Bai Zu tribe was quite unique. Even though Heavenly Lord Bai Zu knew this and tried to be amicable with the other super forces, giving up most of Hei tribe's resources to satisfy their appetite.

But after he officially created Bai Zu tribe, he realized that the surrounding forces were still targeting him. Because he had rank eight cultivation level, these super forces did not give him problems openly, but they created many small issues indirectly.

In order to defend his hard work, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could only stay to guard there personally. As a result, he wasted a lot of time.

Until not long ago, when the surrounding righteous path Huang Jin tribes realized they could not gain anything anymore, they gave up and Bai Zu tribe's situation became better, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu finally rushed to Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

The four supreme elders of Hei tribe did not know the exact location of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, but they knew which area it was in.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu acted secretly, coming here and spending a lot of effort to find out where Hei Fan grotto-heaven was.

After getting enough information, he took action and started to invade Hei Fan grotto-heaven!

"Chu Du, you are an astute person. If you back off, I will not make it hard for you, I was a lone cultivator myself." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu said calmly, urging Chu Du to give up.

Chu Du's lips curled up, he directly attacked!

Rumble!

With an intense clash, dust and clouds rose.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was destroyed by Chu Du in one move, there was a huge pit in the area he was standing at.

"Sending just an illusion, and you want to take Hei Fan grotto-heaven?" Chu Du snorted, turning his head.

The space behind him suddenly distorted, as a small centipede entered Hei Fan grotto-heaven from the outside.

Soon, the distortion vanished, and the centipede turned into Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's appearance, it was exactly the same as before.

"Nice method." The second Heavenly Lord Bai Zu looked at Chu Du, praising as he commented: "You attacked earlier without any warning, and not a bit of Immortal Gu aura leaked out, is this your immortal killer move formless strength?"

Chu Du did not answer, he asked: "Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, even if you have rank eight cultivation level, to snatch Hei Fan grotto-heaven away from me, it will not be easy. Because I have already developed this place for a while, I have made many arrangements."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu smiled: "No matter how long you have been here, or how many arrangements you have made, I can break all of them with my own strength."

He spoke calmly, but he had an aura of confidence and power.

There was only one reason. He was a rank eight Gu Immortal, while Chu Du was rank seven.

Chu Du did not rebuke him, he nodded and admitted: "You are right, I cannot resist the might of a rank eight. But Hei Fan grotto-heaven is my territory, how can I give it up so easily?"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu shook his head: "Hei Fan grotto-heaven is good, but it is not essential. If the great Domination Immortal dies in my hands because of it, isn't it a waste?"

Chu Du's eyes shined with a cold light: "Hmph! Too much bullshit, if you want to take Hei Fan grotto-heaven, just these small methods will not work. Show your true abilities, I want to see the might of a rank eight."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was silent for a while, before saying: "Fine."

As he said that, around Chu Du, in an enormous surrounding range, countless distorted figures appeared, huge quantities of centipede Gu went into Hei Fan grotto-heaven, turning into Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's appearance.

In an instant, Chu Du was surrounded by over ten thousand figures of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

Event though he was encircled, he was not nervous, he even showed a look of disdain.

"Just illusions, no matter how many, they are useless!" Chu Du raised his right hand, his fingers were spread out, before clenching together, forming a tight fist.

Boom!

A huge strength shot out from all directions, in the blink of an eye, all of the figures of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu were exterminated.

"You made many preparations indeed." Another figure of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu came from afar.

Chu Du's pupils shrunk, the Heavenly Lord Bai Zu in front of him was not the main body either, but it was different from the illusions that Chu Du had destroyed earlier.

Chu Du could sense the aura of Immortal Gu on this Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

"Let's fight in the sky." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was the first to fly up.

Chu Du followed him willingly.

There were lots of resources on the ground, he had placed them with much effort, Chu Du did not want these resources to be destroyed.

This was also Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's concern.

He had taken in Hei tribe, and built Bai Zu tribe, he made great losses. He had already paid a huge price to negotiate with the other four rank eight experts. Even though he took in Hei tribe, most of Hei tribe's resources were distributed to the other forces to satisfy them.

Thus, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had a huge desire towards Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

But when he got here, he saw that the grotto-heaven had far less resources than he had estimated.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu quickly realized that most of the resources were newly added. He naturally thought: Did Chu Du store those resources away already?

Thus, Chu Du became his greatest target.

An intense battle unfolded in the sky of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

One side was the clone of a rank eight great expert, while the other was a famous rank seven expert, the two sides fought like rumbling thunder, the entire world was shaking.

After more than ten rounds of fighting, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone could not take it anymore, it lost.

But soon, a second Heavenly Lord clone appeared and joined the fight, it also brought immortal essence and Immortal Gu with it, it was stronger than the first clone.

Chu Du fought against two enemies, but he got stronger as they fought, after another ten rounds, he had the advantage, he was about to execute the killing blow when a third Heavenly Lord clone appeared.

Chu Du's expression changed, he realized something was amiss!

Chapter 1164: Fifth Earthly Calamity

"Heavenly Lord Bai Zu has a method to invade grotto-heavens, but his main body cannot come in, he can only send clones."

"Hei Fan grotto-heaven has a huge space, and the brass bell heavenly spirit was destroyed by Liu Guan Yi, I cannot see the entire place, I do not know how many Heavenly Lord Bai Zu clones there are at this moment!"

"Every time I am about to kill a clone, new ones come in. This shows that he definitely has more than three, they have already formed and are ready to enter battle. Once I understand their methods and gain the advantage, when I am about to deal the killing blow, they would show up to save the other clones, this is definitely him trying to stall for time!"

Thoughts flashed in Chu Du's mind, he felt a bad sensation.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was stalling for time, he definitely had his motives!

Even though Chu Du could not decipher his true motive, there was one unquestionable point — he could not fight according to the enemy's tempo.

Thinking of this, Chu Du erupted, his body expanded rapidly, turning into a ten meter giant.

Immortal killer move — Battle Strength Transpiration!

His entire body turned red, all of the pores on his body opened up, as his sweat turned into steam, surrounding his body.

Next, he raised his right hand to face the sky palm up, his left hand was facing the ground, he chanted softly: "Try this move — Heaven and Earth Combined Strength."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's three clones could not move, they felt like the entire world was sending an unparalleled strength that restricted them, crushing towards them from all directions.

Chu Du did not feel well either.

The muscles in his entire body were tense, he had used all of his strength. Within the steam, his face was bright red, his eyes were bloodshot, especially his two arms, they were bulging with beings resembling moving earthworms, it was quite terrifying.

His right arm moved down, his left arm moved up, as if two hills were converging towards the center with great difficulty.

In his immortal aperture, red date immortal essence expended rapidly.

As Chu Du did this, the three Heavenly Lord Bai Zu clones felt horrible. They felt that the force around them was increasing, they were almost getting crushed.

Seeing that these three clones were about to explode, at the crucial moment, the fourth, fifth, and sixth clones came to save them.

Boom boom!

With two loud sounds, the first clone and second clone were completely smashed by Chu Du, they were reduced to dust, but their Immortal Gu and immortal essence were missing, they were not destroyed.

"What an amazing killer move, it can attack, defend, and even immobilize multiple targets, it is almost like an incomplete battlefield killer move!" The third clone was saved, but it still felt lingering fear.

"No matter how many clones come, it is useless! I prepared this next move for rank eight existences. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, if you refuse to show up, you will not be able to save these clones." Chu Du shouted, preparing his attack.

He had spread out his arms and legs in a '大' shape, his hands were facing heaven, palms upward, aura of Immortal Gu and mortal Gu were emanating from his body, changing constantly, just the aura alone was far superior than the heaven and earth combined strength earlier, it was truly shocking.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clones all moved back, they used their defensive killer moves, preparing themselves.

Boom boom boom.

At the next moment, the Heavenly Lord clones self-detonated without any warning.

"What move is this?" Outside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body frowned deeply.

Even though his clones were all destroyed, he still had memories of the battle, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could learn about Chu Du's mystical attack.

"This killer move is formless and covers a range. Once one is within range, from within, an internal strength would be produced and detonate the body. Hmm? The area that it covers is actually so huge!"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu frowned deeply.

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Chu Du covered his mysterious strength path killer move over the entirety of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

It caused all of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clones to self-detonate.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu smiled: "Interesting, it seems that I cannot deal with Chu Du unless I enter personally."

Once he said that, he used an immortal killer move.

A profound white centipede figure flew out of his body, it drilled into space, causing a huge distorted shadow to appear in Hei Fan grotto-heaven instantly.

Next, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu took large strides, stepping into the shadow.

"Want to come in?" Chu Du laughed, stomping his feet.

A strength path leg flew out and kicked the distorted shadow, sending Heavenly Lord Bai Zu out.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was stunned, before showing a furious and helpless expression: "This Hei Fan grotto-heaven is easy to defend and hard to attack, I will need twenty breaths of time to enter it. In this process, there is enough time for Chu Du to stop me. If I send clones in, they will instantly self-detonate, they are useless..."

Chu Du was completely defending, hiding inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu felt difficulty against this well defended fortress.

"Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is attacking Hei Fan grotto-heaven?" Fang Yuan held Chu Du's letter of emergency support as he let out a breath of air.

His worry was lifted.

Even though Chu Du was his ally, in order to defend Hei Fan grotto-heaven, using the properties of the grotto-heaven to contest with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, there were great advantages for Fang Yuan in this.

Lang Ya land spirit wanted to recruit Chu Du, it was very difficult. But if it succeeded, and Chu Du joined Lang Ya Sect, it would greatly affect Fang Yuan's current status. If he failed, Fang Yuan's relationship with the variant humans would be exposed, the situation would be unthinkable.

Fang Yuan could only stall it, one day at a time.

Because of the alliance agreement, Fang Yuan could not lie to Chu Du, especially in terms of the tribulation. Fang Yuan could not continue to undergo tribulation in the northern icy plain, this way, Chu Du would make guesses, it would expose the snowmen and rockmen under the northern icy plain. If this was settled poorly, and Chu Du attacked the tribe, Fang Yuan would be trapped in the middle, the situation would be very awkward and dangerous.

Thus, he could not make alliances casually, in fact, most Gu Immortals were very wary when making alliances.

Fang Yuan had originally intended to use his time path killer move to slow the time in his immortal aperture, and inform Chu Du about it.

This was not lying, it was the truth.

Next, Fang Yuan would hasten his immortal aperture's time, before starting his tribulation, he would inform Chu Du that the situation had changed. This way, Chu Du would not make it in time, even though it would ruin his relationship and trust, it was the best way.

Chu Du was very astute, there were no loopholes in his alliance agreement, Fang Yuan could only think of this roundabout way.

This method was very troublesome however, not only would it waste Fang Yuan's immortal essence, it would also cause a rift between Fang Yuan and Chu Du.

All in all, it was troublesome.

But now, Chu Du was forced to defend Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he was engaging Heavenly Lord Bai Zu in battle, he could not leave.

Fang Yuan mentally praised: "Heavenly Lord Bai Zu really came in the nick of time, he solved a huge problem for me!"

"For that to have happened, my luck was pretty good."

Fang Yuan started to reply using the information path mortal Gu.

In the letter, he expressed concern and sympathy for Chu Du's encounter, he showed his intense fury and hatred towards Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's invasion. He said that he would definitely help Chu Du and would not break the alliance agreement. But!

His tribulation was coming, he had to get through this first before helping Chu Du, and getting rid of the huge threat, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

He hoped that Chu Du would understand.

Chu Du quickly replied. He showed his understanding and told Fang Yuan: It was not hard to deal with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's invasion, he had already rallied allies to support him, he hoped that Fang Yuan could settle his problem and quickly help.

Fang Yuan quickly replied: He would do his best, and all that he could, he hoped that Chu Du could hold on!

A few days later.

Fang Yuan left Lang Ya blessed land, using the super Gu formation to teleport out.

Next, he rushed to Earth Trench without stopping, choosing an appropriate location to place his immortal aperture.

The main part of Northern Plains' Earth Trench had seventeen sections, they were managed by Zombie Alliance. But after the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Zombie Alliance was used by Shadow Sect and sacrificed, used to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it caused the Zombie Alliances in all five regions to vanish overnight.

However, Shadow Sect also had their arrangements.

For Northern Plain Zombie Alliance, the headquarters, Dark Flow City, had sunken into Earth Trench, other than the remaining members of Shadow Sect, nobody could find it.

Fang Yuan came to an Earth Trench, it was not the one in Zombie Alliance. There were large numbers of lone immortals and demonic immortals there, they were all trying to look for Dark Flow City. Ying Wu Xie and the rest might have even gone to the secret base there, unless Fang Yuan was a fool, he would not undergo tribulation there.

Most parts of Earth Trench were split up by super forces, or were occupied by Gu Immortal experts.

The part Fang Yuan chose had been completely excavated, nobody wanted it anymore, after countless battles, it was barren and empty, nobody came here anymore.

Fang Yuan chose this place purely because this place had rich earth path dao marks, as well as many dark path dao marks too.

Immortal tribulation tempering aperture!

Fang Yuan successfully activated this immortal killer move.

Next, he opened his immortal aperture's entrance, as heaven and earth qi rushed in.

Soon, the fifth earthly calamity formed.

The sky turned dark, a huge skeletal shadow covered up half of the sky.

The skeleton cackled, opening its mouth and spitting out a dark current that resembled a black python.

The dark current flew rapidly, everywhere it went, the soil became corroded, in an instant, they melted completely and turned into puddles of black rotten water, emitting a foul smell.

Earthly calamity — Corrosive Dark Current!

Fang Yuan recognized the earthly calamity, he quickly dealt with it.

The corrosive dark current was hard to deal with, Fang Yuan did not have any methods that resisted it, he could only fight it using his strong offensive methods.

The skeleton continued to spit, as waves of corrosive dark current rushed towards Fang Yuan like seas of snakes.

Heaven's will had purposely raised the calamity's power to its limit, Fang Yuan was in a difficult state.

This earthly calamity did not have Reckless Savage's true meaning. It was completely controlled by heaven's will, thus, it was multiple times as powerful than before.

However, Fang Yuan had grown drastically in strength, forget about the Eastern Sea information path inheritance, he had also obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, he had many time path immortal killer moves to use. Even though he looked distressed, rushing around frantically, he had been preserving his strength to deal with unexpected situations.

Chapter 1165: Ye Fan versus Bai Ning Bing

"Huff..." Fang Yuan looked at the black rotten ground in front of him as he let out a deep sigh.

"I have finally passed the fifth earthly calamity!"

Fang Yuan spent a lot of effort in dealing with the corrosive dark current, but he had Hei Fan's true inheritance, he did not have obvious weaknesses. After persevering for a while, he passed the tribulation.

The terrain here had completely changed, he needed to spend a lot of effort to get it back to its previous condition.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture was huge enough, this area in Mini Western Desert was originally barren to begin with, Fang Yuan's losses were minimal.

In fact, he could even preserve this area and not modify it.

Fortune and disaster were correlated, there were two sides of the same coin.

This place could not cultivate normal crops, but it was now an extreme environment, many types of special fierce beasts and plants could live and grow here.

Of course, there was heaven's will lingering here, Fang Yuan needed to use a lot of self will Gu to get rid of it.

But it was a small matter.

The important thing was, the fifth earthly calamity was over.

Successfully returning to Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan concluded that even though the fifth earthly calamity was powerful, beyond the first four, it did not greatly surpass his expectations.

There was one crucial reason why he passed it, Fang Yuan's strength had grown far quicker than the growth of the earthly calamity's power.

"It seems that earthly calamities themselves are no longer a problem, they can no longer stop me for now, the problem is human calamities!"

Fang Yuan thought about the fourth earthly calamity, the human calamity was too terrifying, he still felt a chill in his heart.

That human calamity was terrifying, even the immemorial rock dragon had appeared. Its might had greatly exceeded Fang Yuan's limits, thanks to his bluffing, he evaded the danger and survived it.

"That means, heaven's will is conjuring human calamities now because earthly calamities can no longer kill me?"

"Precisely so, heaven's will is plotting and scheming to use human calamities to destroy me."

"In this tribulation, I did not encounter any human calamities. That is because I am a complete otherworldly demon, heaven's will cannot decipher my plans, and because I moved very quickly, it did not have enough time to construct a human calamity!"

Heaven's will was not a fake will, it could not have such an obvious influence. Especially towards the higher cultivation level targets, or human Gu Immortals, having the highest intelligence.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan felt that he should not undergo tribulations at fixed locations.

Constantly undergoing tribulation in the northern icy plain allowed heaven's will a chance to affect many Gu Immortals subconsciously, it nearly killed Fang Yuan.

"But this time, I purposely chose Earth Trench because I wanted an earth path calamity, to increase the number of earth path dao marks in my sovereign immortal aperture. In the end, it was a dark path earthly calamity."

Inside Earth Trench, earth path and dark path dao marks were in the highest quantity.

Fang Yuan successfully activated immortal tribulation tempering aperture, the earthly calamity had to be from these two.

But heaven's will did not want Fang Yuan to get what he wanted, thus, an earth path earthly calamity did not form, it was dark path instead.

Fang Yuan used perceivable dao Immortal Gu to inspect it, he realized that his dark path dao marks had increased, they were very close to ten thousand.

"Earlier, my dark path dao mark foundation was very weak, but in this earthly calamity, I gained at least nine thousand dao marks! I made quite some gains."

Even though Fang Yuan's dark path attainment level was low, he had a dark path Immortal Gu — Dark Limit!

This Immortal Gu was very useful to him, he could conceal himself from heaven's will's perception to an extent. Fairy Jiang Yu had once used this to conceal Hei Lou Lan's ten extreme physique aura completely.

For this tribulation, Fang Yuan only spent a few days.

Over in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, it was still at a deadlock.

Chu Du had rank seven peak battle strength, while Hei Fan grotto-heaven was heavily guarded by him, it was impregnable.

However, Fang Yuan could tell that it was Heavenly Lord Bai Zu who had the upper hand, even though he could not break through and was pushed back repeatedly.

But Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was merely attacking, he could attack or retreat, he could decide completely when he fought or left. Chu Du could only defend using the grotto-heaven, he did not know when Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would attack or what methods he would use. He was in a passive position.

"Chu Du is bound to fail at this rate. But he is still far from reaching his limit." Fang Yuan mentally assessed the situation.

He thought, if Chu Du died in this battle, would he benefit or lose out from it?

After consideration, Fang Yuan concluded: It was better for Chu Du to be alive.

There were several points.

Firstly, Fang Yuan had invested heavily in Chu Du. The first investment was the rank seven Immortal Gu Calamity Beckoning. If Chu Du died, Calamity Beckoning would perish.

Secondly, Chu Du had an alliance agreement with him, he could not abandon him if he requested assistance.

Thirdly, the calamities and tribulations were only going to get stronger from now, Chu Du's Calamity Beckoning could help Fang Yuan divert a lot of the pressure. His existence was useful for Fang Yuan's development.

Fourthly, if he helped Chu Du defend Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan would be able to relocate his storage pool, using Hei Fan grotto-heaven to produce heavenly crystals and hatch the upper extreme heavenly eagle once more.

"It seems that I need to take action and help against Heavenly Lord Bai Zu." Fang Yuan made his decision.

However, he was not in a rush to act.

Chu Du could continue to suffer, he had just undergone tribulation, he needed to rest and restock his green grape immortal essence.

This was a justifiable reason, it did not break the alliance agreement, even if Chu Du knew, he could not blame Fang Yuan.

Southern Border, Sun Crown Mountain.

This mountain was green and lush, it had stood for a long time. During each sunrise, there would be a halo over the mountain peak, resembling a bright crown, thus it was named Sun Crown Mountain.

But now was night time.

The bright moon was radiating over the entire mountain.

"Who else?" Ye Fan stood arrogantly, his arms were crossed in front of his chest, he was standing on a huge rock.

Opposite him, a group of Gu Masters were shivering, hesitating.

They were fearful of Ye Fan!

"Ye Fan, you were chased out by your clan, you are also a lone cultivator. We are also lone cultivators, why are you making life hard for us?" A Gu Master spoke.

Ye Fan sneered: "Before we fought, all of you sought to overwhelm me with numbers, why did you not say that? Also, are you considered lone cultivators? Dominating this mountain and plundering the surroundings, as Gu Masters, you bully the weak and fear the strong, you slaughter and humiliate mortals. You are all vicious fiends, you are demonic cultivators, you are not lone cultivators!"

"We are innocent. The ringleader and main culprit has already died at your hands, we were forced to comply."

"Also, ever since we submitted to boss White Demon, we have stopped committing crimes!"

The Gu Masters cried out.

Ye Fan's expression eased.

According to the intel he obtained, the situation was indeed like this.

Ever since Bai Ning Bing took control of Sun Crown Mountain and Silent Flow Mountain, she had restrained the demons, taking them in, but did not give them any evil orders.

"Hmph, if not for this, you would all be dead now, how could I let you live?" Ye Fan snorted, he continued: "I represent Shang clan, I need to get through Sun Crown and Silent Flow Mountain, I will wait here, get White Demon to come and see me. Otherwise, tomorrow, I will slaughter everyone here!"

Ye Fan was very perceptive, he was not a rash brute.

He knew that Silent Flow Mountain's defense was far stronger than Sun Crown Mountain, he came here alone, he could not take it down through force.

Alerting the enemy and luring out White Demon was the best method.

But the moment he said that, he heard an icy voice resound: "No need to call them, because I am here already."

Saying so, more than ten figures appeared partway up the mountain.

The demons saw this and cheered loudly: "Boss White Demon! Boss White Demon has come to save us!"

Ye Fan watched with caution, he saw that all of the people who came were Gu Masters, they were stronger than the ones on Sun Crown Mountain. Among them, there were many demonic path and lone cultivators, there were also several famous people with their own unique traits.

But what truly attracted his attention was the woman at the center of them.

This woman was dressed in white clothes, her silvery hair was shiny, like a tassel, it extended to her waist, her deep blue eyes were clear like a lake, they were calm and peaceful, her skin was pale like snow, her face was cold and aloof, but her unparalleled beauty could not be concealed.

At this moment, she was lying down on a bamboo chair, she was relaxing and her eyes were shut, like she was resting. There were four snowmen carrying her chair.

Ye Fan's heart shook.

He had roamed outside and seen many things.

But in terms of appearance, Bai Ning Bing was simply a divine beauty! The only person comparable to her in looks was Shang Xin Ci.

"Boss White Demon, we have tried our best to defend, we waited for you so desperately. You have finally arrived." At this time, a demonic path Gu Master tumbled and crawled towards Bai Ning Bing, calling out loudly as he showed a fawning expression.

"You, who avoided the enemy and refused to fight, deserve death." Bai Ning Bing opened her eyes slightly, blue light flashed in her eyes as that kneeling Gu Master froze completely at the next moment, he was beyond dead.

The demons were shocked, the few experts behind Bai Ning Bing shook, they recalled the terror when they had first met her.

Ye Fan was also shocked, before he burst into anger. His good first impression of Bai Ning Bing was completely gone, it was replaced with deep anger.

"As expected of a demon! You even kill your own men!" Ye Fan shouted, jumping down the rock, staring at Bai Ning Bing angrily.

Bai Ning Bing smiled lightly, stretching out her jade finger, pointing lightly at Ye Fan.

At that moment, Ye Fan felt a cold sensation, covering his left leg.

He looked down, only to see that on his left leg, a huge piece of ice had instantly formed.

"What move is this? I had already used my defensive killer move, but it could not block it at all?!" Ye Fan was extremely shocked.

All along, he had used these methods without fail. But now, it had completely failed in front of Bai Ning Bing.

"What cultivation level does White Demon have? My methods were given to me by Lady Shang Qing Qing, a Gu Immortal! It was actually useless!! Looking at her expression, she still has not put in all her effort. Will I die in this battle?" Ye Fan's heart shook intensely.

He had greatly underestimated Bai Ning Bing, to think that their difference in strength was so huge. But after his shock, Ye Fan quickly calmed down, his battle intent surged in the face of despair.

Chapter 1166: White Form Immortal Snake

"Come, even if I die, I will only die in the battlefield!" Ye Fan shouted, his eyes were shining with a threatening light.

The demons licked their lips, they gritted their teeth, they were going to charge up, wanting to kill Ye Fan and cut him into pieces.

But Bai Ning Bing suddenly said: "Isn't it too boring to directly kill him? Go one by one."

These words saved Ye Fan's life, it greatly delayed the timing of his death.

After spending so much time with Bai Ning Bing, a demonic path expert who knew of her personality stepped up with shining eyes: "Since Boss White Demon wants to watch a show, allow me to kill this person, as long as the boss is happy, it will be our fortune."

The demons heard this and all mentally badmouthed at this demonic path expert for being shameless, they were envious and jealous, why did they not speak first, this was the best chance to bootlick!

But soon, they no longer had such thoughts.

Ye Fan was in a desperate situation, but he displayed great might, killing a number of demonic path Gu Masters.

Even though his methods were useless against Bai Ning Bing, they were more than enough to deal with the rest.

"Interesting." Bai Ning Bing watched the entire battle while relaxing on the bamboo chair, it was as if the people dying were not her subordinates, but strangers instead.

Ye Fan felt a chill regard her aloof nature, he felt disgust towards her: "This White Demon might look like a peerless beauty, but she has a vicious heart, she cannot compare to Lady Xin Ci. Birds of a feather flock together, the Black Demon guy who was with her is likely not a good person either!"

"Ah!" Suddenly, Ye Fan screamed.

It turned out that his right arm had been pierced by multiple icicles from the inside. At once, his entire right arm was pierced, flesh was exposed, his pale broken bones could be seen, his blood was about to squirt out but it was frozen by the frost energy.

Ye Fan's right arm was crippled!

"Alright, continue." Bai Ning Bing said plainly.

The demons had low morale, but seeing that Ye Fan's right arm was crippled, they saw hope again.

A few more entered the battlefield, trying to take advantage of his weakness.

But Ye Fan got bolder as he took wounds, he ignored his injuries, fighting while disregarding his life, meanwhile the demonic path Gu Masters were fearful for their lives, they did not dare to fight directly, they were slowly losing.

Some were defeated, while others were killed by Ye Fan when he had the chance.

"What do I need such useless people for?" Bai Ning Bing's eyes flashed as blue light flickered in them.

The few demonic path Gu Masters who were defeated and still alive did not even get a chance to shout, they were frozen into icicles, dying on the spot.

Bai Ning Bing was fierce and ruthless, the Gu Masters were trembling in fear, even Ye Fan felt a chill in his heart.

Bai Ning Bing pressed lightly with her right hand, the four snowmen noticed and quickly lowered the bamboo chair.

Bai Ning Bing slowly stood on the ground, looking at Ye Fan with her hands behind her back.

The demons were overjoyed, looking at this, Bai Ning Bing was going to fight!

Ye Fan smiled bitterly, Bai Ning Bing's terrifying strength made him feel deep despair: "There always exists someone stronger than you. I was too overconfident, I deserve the fate of dying here. But before I die, may you answer a question that I have?"

"Oh?" Bai Ning Bing looked at Ye Fan, assessing him as she said plainly: "You are quite brave, few can be so unmoved in the face of death. Very well, go ahead."

"I want to ask, what kind of person is Black Demon?" Ye Fan asked the deepest question in his heart.

Bai Ning Bing frowned, all along she had been having a cold expression, but this change in her expression showed that she was not calm on the inside.

"He..." Bai Ning Bing looked at the moon in the sky, dragging her words.

Ye Fan focused, listening attentively.

But Bai Ning Bing showed a mocking and cold gaze in her eyes.

Ye Fan stared with his eyes wide open, he was instantly frozen into an icicle!

Bai Ning Bing looked at the night sky and bright moon, after a few breaths of time, she retracted her gaze and walked away.

Behind her, Ye Fan's entire body was frozen in transparent ice, he died.

The demons were silent, they were like frightened cicadas.

But Bai Ning Bing only took a few steps when a peculiar black aura appeared behind her, causing her silvery hair to flutter in the air.

"Oh?" Bai Ning Bing's blue eyes shrunk to pin size, she turned around and realized that four figures had suddenly appeared behind Ye Fan all of a sudden.

Among them, one had an ugly appearance, he was an immortal zombie, placing his arm on Ye Fan's shoulder.

He was using an immortal killer move, the peculiar aura that Bai Ning Bing sensed earlier came from it.

Bai Ning Bing's hair was standing, her battle intent rose to its peak at this moment!

Gu Immortal aura burst out from her body, soon, her body started to change, her adam's apple appeared, her body grew taller, her soft and plump chest shrank and became a muscular male chest, her face had turned into one with a sharp dagger-like appearance.

"Hehehe, Bai Ning Bing, your phantom aperture was given to you by my Shadow Sect, it can suppress the transformation path dao marks in you and revert you to your male body, it can also allow you to become a false immortal and own green grape immortal essence, you will be able to refine and use Immortal Gu. But now, you want to use this phantom aperture to fight me?" Ying Wu Xie chuckled.

"A member of Shadow Sect?" Bai Ning Bing squinted, a dangerous cold light was flashing in his eyes.

As he said that, Ye Fan was revived by Ying Wu Xie. The ice around his body had turned into water, he sat on the ground weakly, gasping loudly with a pale expression.

The feeling of life and death, he could feel entirely what true horror was!

His mental state was heavily affected, he could not control himself.

"You cannot kill this person." Ying Wu Xie looked at Ye Fan plainly.

He had luck inspection Immortal Gu, he could see Ye Fan's abundant luck.

Ever since they escaped from Eastern Sea, he had been hiding inside Shi Nu's immortal aperture, devising methods to deal with Fang Yuan's investigative killer move.

Even though there was not much success, after Ying Wu Xie saw Ye Fan, he could feel a resonance in their luck, he knew that their luck was connected.

"Fang Yuan is the owner of Spring Autumn Cicada and was a tool of heaven's will, he returned from the future and knows who has great luck. Killing Ye Fan would harm my own luck."

"As for Bai Ning Bing, he is under Shadow Sect's alliance agreement, I am not afraid he will turn on us. He also has one of the ten extreme physiques, he would be very useful in saving my main body!"

Ying Wu Xie thought over this, while he suddenly tossed out a rank five mortal Gu.

"White form immortal snake!" Bai Ning Bing received it with a perplexed expression, he recognized this Gu worm which had left a heavy impression in him.

"This is a crucial clue in the old bet of the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs. Bai Ning Bing, you are the last bloodline descendant of Bai Xiang, you have the proper status to participate in the bet." Ying Wu Xie said slowly.

Bai Ning Bing was silent before asking: "This is the reason why your Shadow Sect is scheming to rope me in?"

Ying Wu Xie did not answer, he only moved as he left this place.

Hei Lou Lan, Shi Nu, and Tai Bai Yun Sheng followed closely after him.

Bai Ning Bing gritted his teeth, he restrained the cold light in his eyes as he followed them.

Ye Fan was left behind, kneeling on the ground with his arms supporting him, stopping him from collapsing, as he gasped heavily.

As for those demonic path Gu Masters, they were all like statues, when the wind blew, they turned into rotten black mud...

Northern Plains, Become Dragon Mound.

"Sir, you have come to help us, our Chu Sect is extremely grateful." A strength path Gu Immortal greeted Fang Yuan respectfully.

Fang Yuan nodded, looking at the person.

Before encountering Fang Yuan, in order to get Reckless Savage's true meaning and increase his strength path attainment level, Chu Du had spent a lot of time and effort to nurture mortal Gu Masters, to help them become Gu Immortals.

As time passed, he gained a good number of strength path Gu Immortals. Chu Du treated them as disciples, and casually created a sect, naming it Chu Sect.

"Even though Chu Du is nurturing these strength path Gu Immortals, it is not his aim. Strength path is declining, and these strength path Gu Immortals lack Immortal Gu, they are not a threat." Fang Yuan assessed as he looked at Become Dragon Mound in front of him.

This mound was short and flat, it did not look amazing, but it was a true land of fortune.

In Become Dragon Mound, there were lots of transformation path dao marks. These transformation path dao marks could allow the living beings staying here to transform into dragon beasts. There were large numbers of dragon Gu that were produced here before, like golden dragon Gu, water dragon Gu, earth dragon Gu, dragon claw Gu, dragon breath Gu, dragon pearl Gu, and so on.

Unfortunately, after Hei tribe was destroyed, this place was ransacked by several Gu Immortals.

But in the last few months, Bai Zu tribe took control and started to develop, sending Gu Immortals to guard Become Dragon Mound, allocating resources to rebuild it, and return it to its former glorious state.

This was one of Bai Zu tribe's important resource points.

"I have already investigated clearly, this place was originally guarded by Hei tribe's fourth supreme elder. But the developments he had made here were taken away by Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals, no longer present."

"Hehe, Hei tribe's fourth supreme elder has rank seven cultivation level. But the Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal sent here only has rank six cultivation level, it is good for us to act, we will attack this place."

"Everyone is already in position, we just have to attack and fight the first battle!"

"As long as we deal a huge blow to Bai Zu tribe, it will surely make Heavenly Lord Bai Zu wary and give up on Hei Fan grotto-heaven, returning to guard his territory."

Chu Sect's Gu Immortals continued to talk, feeling excited.

If Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was still a lone cultivator like before, Chu Du might have given up on defending Hei Fan grotto-heaven already.

But now that he was taking over Hei tribe and creating his own righteous path super force, even though his territory was expanding rapidly, he gained a weakness.

Strength and weakness in this world were relative.

Like in the past, when Zombie Alliance took revenge on Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Blazing Heaven Demoness did not dare to fight him head on, but they looked to trouble Snowy Mountain's demonic path Gu Immortals, plundering their immortal materials and ruining their collection. Before long, Old Ancestor Xue Hu could not take it anymore, he had to give in to Zombie Alliance."

Chu Du had both brains and brawn, his tactic in dealing with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was definitely the best one.

However, the actual effect would depend on how much damage Fang Yuan and Chu Sect's strength path Gu Immortals can do.

Chapter 1167: Become Dragon Mound

Northern Plains, outside Become Dragon Mound.

The strength path Gu Immortal from Chu Sect continued: "It is not easy to get information on this Gu Immortal from Bai Zu tribe, their Gu Immortals all live inside Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's grotto-heaven, they rarely move around in Northern Plains. Hmm?"

It turned out, when he was still speaking, Fang Yuan had already flown out.

"Quick, come back!"

"Our battle plan has not been established yet."

"Don't be rash!"

"We might have two people on our side while the enemy is alone, but they have the territorial advantage, Become Dragon Mound has a set of Gu formations that can allow them to defend, as long as they last for a moment, there will be an endless stream of reinforcements from Bai Zu tribe!"

The Chu Sect Gu Immortal quickly transmitted, he was extremely frantic.

Fang Yuan did not reply to him, he flew into the air and called out: "Bai Zu tribe, come out, my Chu Sect is taking over Become Dragon Mound."

"What Chu Sect? Never heard of it! You dare to cause a scene in my Bai Zu tribe!" A young Gu Immortal appeared on Become Dragon Mound, showing intense rage.

"We're doomed!" The Chu Sect Gu Immortal had his head in his hands, showing a defeated and aggrieved look: "Why did master find such a person? He is too rash, he is just too rash!"

"The situation was good earlier... sigh!" He shook his head continuously.

Right now, they had no choice but to attack forcefully.

The Chu Sect Gu Immortal was about to appear, when Fang Yuan attacked.

Boom!

A giant hand flew out, crushing the air like an imposing mountain, it had an incredible aura.

Be it the Chu Sect Gu Immortal or Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortal, they were staring with dumbfounded expressions at this move.

The Bai Zu Gu Immortal was the first to react, he shrieked: "Rank seven battle strength! You, you, you, a senior that is pretending to be weaker, aren't you ashamed!"

Saying so, he frantically activated Become Dragon Mound's defensive Gu formation.

After activating the Gu formation, Become Dragon Mound shone in layers of bright light, the entirety of Become Dragon Mound was enveloped by it.

Fang Yuan snorted, the strength path giant hand ignored it, slamming on the formation.

Bam bam bam...

The strength path giant hand had incredible power, everywhere it went, the Gu formation collapsed without resistance.

It could not even last five breaths of time, Become Dragon Mound's defensive Gu formation was crushed by Fang Yuan, it became extremely damaged!

The Bai Zu Gu Immortal had a pale expression, he was only rank six, seeing Fang Yuan's strength, he did not dare to stay, he did not speak, rushing away immediately.

Fang Yuan did not chase him, he flew towards the sky above Become Dragon Mound.

Become Dragon Mound was completely ruined, but it was fine, Fang Yuan had landscape as before Immortal Gu.

However, he could not use it in front of others.

Thus, Fang Yuan used another Immortal Gu.

Pulling Mountain!

Rumble...

Under the Chu Sect Gu Immortal's shocked gaze, the entirety of Become Dragon Mound was pulled up by Fang Yuan, before he opened his immortal aperture's entrance and stuffed it inside.

"He, he, he, actually took away Become Dragon Mound entirely!" Chu Sect's Gu Immortal stammered, he was completely incoherent.

At this point, he finally realized Fang Yuan's words earlier were true, he was not exaggerating to raise morale.

"Junior pays respect to senior." The Chu Sect Gu Immortal lowered his head, flying into the air as he greeted Fang Yuan again.

He was very careful, in a state of nervousness.

Fang Yuan revealed rank six Gu Immortal aura, but the Chu Sect Gu Immortal was extremely suspicious of it! He felt that Fang Yuan was one of those senior great experts who had a strange interest in pretending to be weak!

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, looking in the direction of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

He did not do anything else.

This action was huge, Bai Zu tribe would definitely act rapidly, exacting revenge with all their strength.

Retreating now was the safest option.

He had already obtained Become Dragon Mound anyway.

As for Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals, there were only a few of them, they could not be killed. It was okay to kill Hei tribe Gu Immortals, but killing Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals would truly enrage Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!

That was not a wise decision.

Soon, news that the tribe was getting attacked spread to Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's ears.

"Oh? It seems that Chu Du's force is not small." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was shocked.

"A total of eight Gu Immortals, all of strength path, Chu Du, you have some deeply hidden plans and motives." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu squinted, speaking in an eerie tone.

This rank eight Gu Immortal had to admit, he had underestimated Chu Du.

Not only did he underestimate Chu Du, he also underestimated his force.

Once news got out, the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world would be shaken. Nobody had expected that Chu Du would gather such a group of people around him!

"However, if you want me to retreat like this, you are simply looking down on me, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not waver at all, he continued to stay, considering all sorts of methods to try and enter Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

As expected, once information got out, the Northern Plains Gu Immortal world which had just calmed down went into a commotion again.

Bai Zu tribe was attacked by an unknown force, it suffered a huge loss, losing a number of its resource points. The biggest loss was Become Dragon Mound, the area had simply turned into a giant pit.

Bai Zu tribe was like an enraged lion, it bare its fangs and claws, wanting to take revenge.

But Chu Sect's Gu Immortals came and left quickly, with a well executed battle tactic, they did not lose any members.

A few days later, Fang Yuan looked at the battle reports in Lang Ya blessed land.

"This means, Hei Fan grotto-heaven's danger has not been resolved yet."

"After all... this time, even though Chu Sect attacked at full force, causing a huge commotion, Bai Zu tribe did not suffer a huge loss. The biggest loss was Become Dragon Mound, the rest of the areas were originally quite damaged, they had not been fully restored. And because these strength path Gu Immortals have few Immortal Gu, their battle strength is low, they could only cause little damage."

"All in all, the commotion is greater than the effect, no wonder Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could endure it and continue to attack Hei Fan grotto-heaven without going back."

This way, the situation was in a deadlock.

The fight over the ownership of Hei Fan grotto-heaven was split into two battlefields.

One was Chu Du defending Hei Fan grotto-heaven, while Heavenly Lord Bai Zu tried to invade it. Chu Du was very passive, as Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had the initiative.

The other was Chu Sect attacking Bai Zu tribe's territories, Chu Sect had the initiative, while Bai Zu tribe had to defend.

"In conclusion, Chu Du's side is weaker." Fang Yuan sighed.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu with rank eight cultivation level was much stronger. The reason why he could not display it was because he was trying to invade the grotto-heaven of an even stronger rank eight Gu Immortal.

Gu Immortals with more dao marks would face more difficulty in entering blessed lands or grotto-heavens. Rank eight Gu Immortals could not even enter blessed lands, if they tried, the entire blessed land would burst from exceeding its capacity.

And even though Bai Zu tribe had been created recently, it did not have a weak foundation, it took in many members of Hei tribe, its combined strength exceeded Chu Sect.

Chu Sect was able to have the advantage the first time because it launched a sneak attack, it caught the Bai Zu tribe members off guard.

If they tried this again, the other party would be wary, it would be less easy and safe!

"At this rate, there is a high chance of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu taking over Hei Fan grotto-heaven, however, Chu Du still has his trump cards."

Fang Yuan decided to wait and see.

A few days later, the entire Chu Sect was worried about Chu Du's safety, they wanted to launch another attack and invited Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan rejected them, telling them not to act rashly.

Chu Sect did not listen to Fang Yuan, but soon, Chu Du sent a letter to restrain them.

Even though Chu Du was being attacked by a rank eight Gu Immortal, he had a clear mind, he could look at the situation and assess it accurately. This move was very strategic, he preserved Chu Sect's foundation.

The situation fell into a deadlock again.

"Next, it will depend on how Chu Du reacts."

Fang Yuan did not believe that the great Domination Immortal would stop here.

He forgot about this matter for the time being, the fifth earthly calamity was already over, his focus was on developing his immortal aperture.

After taking Become Dragon Mound, Mini Southern Border obtained another named mountain.

Even though Become Dragon Mound did not look amazing, it had deep foundations, it successfully overthrew Immortal Succession Mountain, becoming the second most valuable mountain after Five Light Mountain.

In Mini Western Desert, there was a rotten dark swamp, filled with dark path dao marks. Fang Yuan had already used enough self will Gu to completely cleanse away the lingering heaven's will in it.

Other than that, in Mini Eastern Sea, there was a new blood lake that was isolated from the outside sea.

This blood lake had the blood of desolate beasts and Gu Immortals added by Fang Yuan, blood asset Immortal Gu was placed in it, floating inside the blood lake.

This Immortal Gu had been overused by Fang Yuan in a previous calamity, it was heavily damaged. Thus, it was placed here, recovering slowly.

Fang Yuan used his divine sense and looked at it, realizing that blood asset Immortal Gu was still quite far from a full recovery.

But this blood path Immortal Gu could already be considered easy to heal.

Other Immortal Gu would require parallel refinement methods to recover. Not only would the difficulty be high, the risk would also be high.

"Among my dao marks, the one most suited to me is my high number of blood path dao marks. But I only have one Immortal Gu, Blood Asset, if I can refine Blood Deity..."

Fang Yuan's plan of refining Blood Deity had been going on for some time.

Inside Lang Ya blessed land, White Hair Continent, Yellow Hair Continent, and Black Hair Continent had been in war for many years.

"Hold on, you have to persevere, our reinforcements are here!" The leader of the black haired Gu Masters shouted, attempting to raise the morale.

On this battlefield, only a small part of the black haired army was left, the rest of the place was occupied by the allied white haired and yellow haired armies.

Black haired Gu Masters fought bravely, but they had limited troops, they were shrinking in number.

Croak!

Right at this moment, the croaking of a toad resounded in the battlefield like thunder.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

A huge tide flowed, sweeping the battlefield, everywhere it went, countless white haired and yellow haired troops were washed away.

At once, the allied army suffered huge losses.

"A black hair rank five Gu Master! Oh no, it is that toad Gu Master Fang Zheng." The allied white and yellow haired armies were in chaos.

"We are saved, it is Fang Zheng..." The black haired Gu Masters had complex emotions.

Under everyone's gazes, Fang Zheng stood on the back of the River Swallowing Toad, he was dressed in a blue robe, entering the battlefield with a rush of his tides.

Rumble!

He suddenly attacked, his offense was extremely strong, rampaging in the battlefield, everywhere he went, troops fell over their horses, the allied army was sent into chaos by him.

Chapter 1168: Lightning Refinement, Ma Hong Yun

"You have finally become a strong expert. In all three continents, your current strength is at least top ten." Fang Yuan's fake will purposely praised in his mind.

Fang Zheng replied plainly: "With enough accumulated growth, it happens naturally."

These last years, he killed mercilessly. Under the pressure of life and death, he was gradually understanding Fang Yuan's emotions when he slaughtered his clan.

He had no choice.

Either you die or I die!

Fang Zheng was still unable to forgive Fang Yuan, but he understood the reason why he did it. His deep hatred had faded slowly as time passed, after Fang Yuan's fake will helped him to escape danger time and time again.

"Run!"

"We are not Fang Zheng's match!!"

Soon, the allied white and yellow haired Gu Master army broke apart.

Fang Zheng did not talk to the black haired Gu Masters, he cleared out the battlefield and left.

Leaving behind black hair Gu Masters who were looking at him with complex expressions as he left.

"So he is that rumored human Gu Master."

"Amazing! In the blink of an eye, victory was decided."

"Unfortunately, he offended the higher ups, and is not a hairy man, no matter how big his contributions are, he can only reach this stage..."

"Even though I am grateful to him, for my own future, I should keep a distance from him."

Lang Ya blessed land.

After receiving the fake will, Fang Yuan had an understanding expression: "Oh, it seems that Fang Zheng is going to be ready soon, but Blood Deity's recipe has not been completed. Should I divert some of my energy towards this?"

Originally, according to Fang Yuan's plans, he was going to use the light of wisdom to deduce Blood Deity's recipe, it was the fastest way.

But the light of wisdom was unusable now. Fang Yuan might as well deduce it himself, it would be more quickly this way than trying to use it again.

But thinking about it, Fang Yuan gave up on this alluring option.

Firstly, he had Hei Fan's time path true inheritance, he did not lack methods, refining Blood Deity was only icing on the cake.

On the other hand, blood path was not doing well in the current period. Once he used it, he would be chased down by all kinds of Gu Immortals. From Fang Yuan's perspective, the five regions chaotic war was the best time to display blood path again.

Ever since he took Become Dragon Mound, these last days, Fang Yuan had been waiting for Chu Du to act while cultivating diligently.

His profits were starting to decline.

Because a large number of the resources in Hei Fan grotto-heaven had already been sold by him.

A lot of the resources in Hei Fan grotto-heaven could not grow in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, he could only sell them and exchange for the things he needed.

This way, his profits increased rapidly.

But these were non-replenishable resources, after a few months, he ran out of them.

Even though Fang Yuan earned a lot of immortal essence stones, he also used a lot of them.

An earthly calamity every two months was simply too frequent. And recently, Fang Yuan had fought in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Eastern Sea, and Become Dragon Mound, he used rank seven Immortal Gu, thus his green grape immortal essence expenditure was huge.

And because he was developing his immortal aperture, he had invested a lot in it. His immortal essence stones came and went like a flowing river, even though the quantity was huge, he was not left with much to keep.

"Currently, the only thing that can allow me to grow rapidly is to use the light of wisdom after settling the soul path trap in my immortal zombie body."

"Other than that, I can obtain information path methods to resolve the alliance agreements that I have. It will allow me to deal with the different forces and relationships more freely, I would be able to make full use of them."

"I can also rise to rank seven and obtain red date immortal essence, it will greatly lower my expenditure, and give me a qualitative growth."

Fang Yuan was aware of his options, but that did not mean he could easily succeed in doing them.

He was at an impasse in his cultivation.

Unless he had a fortuitous encounter, he could only get through these hurdles slowly.

But how could fortuitous encounters come whenever he wanted them? Even if they did, Fang Yuan had to be wary of whether they were part of heaven's will's plot.

Fang Yuan spent two hours cultivating his soul.

In the remaining time, he would use sword eyebrows Immortal Gu to increase his number of sword path dao marks, or go to the outside world and use star eyes Immortal Gu to refine the stars in black heaven.

Other than this, he had to spend a lot of effort in training his time path killer moves, to gain more proficiency to use them in actual battles.

He was mainly working on developing his immortal aperture.

Speaking of which, the sovereign immortal aperture's initial stage arrangements were not completed yet.

The reason was that he had too many Immortal Gu. For him to be self sufficient and not rely on the outside world, he would need to rely on the production in his sovereign immortal aperture to feed all of his Immortal Gu.

At that time, his initial stage developments would be completed.

Unfortunately, Fang Yuan had many rank eight Immortal Gu, he had just started gathering the food of attitude Gu and wisdom sword Immortal Gu, there was no follow up yet.

He had no choice, this was his limit.

Every day, he was making the most of every second, he was very stingy towards the use of his time on specific objectives, but his time and energy were limited. Fang Yuan could only think carefully before cultivating the most important aspects that he had chosen.

Such hard work caused Fang Yuan to improve rapidly.

Almost every day, he made great progress.

The sovereign immortal aperture defied heaven itself, Fang Yuan's hard work was simply inhuman, he was ruthless towards others, but was even stricter and more cruel towards himself.

With these two elements, his immortal aperture's development was rapid, Fang Yuan's strength was rising all the time.

Half a month passed like this, until Fang Yuan finally received Chu Du's letter.

In the letter, Chu Du invited Fang Yuan to help, once they succeeded, he would pay Fang Yuan hugely.

Chu Du spoke very courteously and humbly, almost as if he had forgotten Fang Yuan was his ally.

"Chu Du could control himself for so long, it is quite extraordinary. Fine, I will make the trip." Fang Yuan was mentally prepared long ago, he immediately left.

A day and a night later, he arrived at the secret meeting location.

When he reached, many Gu Immortals had already arrived.

"Senior, you have arrived." The one who came to welcome Fang Yuan was the Chu Sect Gu Immortal who had went with Fang Yuan to take down Become Dragon Mound.

"Allow me to make the introductions, these are experts that master has called for reinforcements. This is senior Hao Zhen."

Hao Zhen had the appearance of a middle aged man, he had a beard and a muscular body, he nodded at Fang Yuan.

"This is senior Chou Lao Wu." Chu Sect's Gu Immortal continued.

Chou Lao Wu had a dismal looking face, his body was thin and dry, his back was hunched, he smiled at Fang Yuan with his uneven yellow teeth, his appearance was extremely ugly.

"This is senior Li Si Chun." The Chu Sect Gu Immortal said with an evasive gaze.

This Gu Immortal was quite unique.

He had a square face, with thick brows and huge eyes, his nose bridge was very tall, his chest had thick black hair that was exposed, he was a man but he wore a flowery skirt.

Seeing Fang Yuan, his eyes shined brightly as he pulled his flowery skirt, saying seductively: "Oh my goodness, it's a handsome little brother."

The Chu Sect Gu Immortal shuddered, he immediately moved past this person, arriving at the final Gu Immortal.

"This is senior Immortal Wang[1]."

Immortal Wang had a short stature, he had a red nose and triangular little eyes, looking at Fang Yuan as he said: "We have already introduced ourselves, you are the last one here, why don't you introduce yourself to us?"

Fang Yuan smiled plainly: "I have nothing much to say, I am just a lone cultivator. You can call me Liu Guan Yi."

"Liu Guan Yi." The Chu Sect Gu Immortal quickly memorized this name. This was the first time he had heard Fang Yuan's name, because he easily chased away the Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal and even took away Become Dragon Mound, he had developed a strong interest and curiosity in Fang Yuan, and even a little admiration.

In fact, he was not the only one, the other Chu Sect Gu Immortals also paid a lot of attention to Fang Yuan.

After all, they mainly cultivated strength path. Fang Yuan's strength path battle strength was immense, in this world where strength path was declining, he was like their shining beacon of hope.

"Liu Guan Yi." Hao Zhen muttered, seemingly trying to remember this name.

The others also etched this name deep in their minds.

To be invited by Chu Du, and have the guts to deal with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he was definitely not ordinary.

Hao Zhen and the rest had rank seven cultivation level.

Of course, Fang Yuan was currently using familiar face, he was also emitting rank seven aura.

"Darling Liu, I heard that you uprooted the entirety of Become Dragon Mound and took it away. You are so capable!" Li Si Chun laughed in an enticing manner, approaching Fang Yuan.

All of the immortals felt goosebumps over their bodies.

Fang Yuan was unmoved, he stared at Li Si Chun with a cold expression, he said plainly: "Stay away from me."

The hearts of the other invited immortals shuddered.

Fang Yuan emitted a trace of deep killing intent that was bone-chilling, these invited immortals were all knowledgeable people, they instantly knew that this person was an evildoer who had killed countless people and was filled with ruthlessness.

The Chu Sect Gu Immortals around them had little experience, they could not sense Fang Yuan's ferocious nature, the Gu Immortal who was doing the introductions for Fang Yuan earlier said: "According to master's arrangement, us Chu Sect Gu Immortals have low battle strength, we will not participate. We will be relying on you seniors, once we succeed, master will definitely compensate you well."

"Tell us about the battle plan." Immortal Wang said.

The Chu Sect Gu Immortal said some shocking things: "Master has devised a conclusive plan, seniors, we hope that you will work together and attack Iron Eagle blessed land!"

At the same time, Snowy Mountain, first peak.

The refinement path Gu formation was shining in golden light, it was so condensed it was almost solid, firmly cast over the peak of the snow mountain.

Within the light, Lady Wan Shou and Old Ancestor Xue Hu were standing in front of Ma Hong Yun.

Lady Wan Shou was extremely tired, she was carefully taking out a ball of lightning.

The ball of lightning was fist sized, there were sparks inside, creating thunderous sounds, the exterior was protruding at times, at one glance, one could tell this lightning ball was unstable.

"What, what are you trying to do?! No, no, ahhh!" Ma Hong Yun screamed, he had a frantic expression, but his entire body was immobilized, he could not move.

"This is the final crucial step." Lady Wan Shou said, pushing the lightning ball towards Ma Hong Yun.

The lightning ball quickly fused into Ma Hong Yun's chest, vanishing instantly.

"AHHHHH—!" Ma Hong Yun was hit by intense waves of lightning, his body was shaking as he raised his head, he was screaming loudly with all his strength.

[1] Wang here is 汪 which is Chinese for barking Back

Chapter 1169: Sudden Attack on Iron Eagle Blessed Land (1/2)

Lightning crackled.

Ma Hong Yun quickly fainted as his eyes rolled over, saliva leaking out of his mouth. He had completely lost consciousness, but his body was still shaking intensely.

The lightning started out strong and slowly weakened, until it vanished.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's expression sank.

Ma Hong Yun's lightning refinement failed!

If they succeeded, why would Ma Hong Yun still be around? He would be refined by lightning, his flesh and bones would be gone, only a lump of golden luck essence would be left.

Lady Wan Shou let out a gasp, there was paleness on her beautiful face.

She was the one using lightning refinement on Ma Hong Yun, it was a crucial step in refining fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu. Now that she failed, Lady Wan Shou suffered a heavy backlash, she was injured.

"Dear." Old Ancestor Xue Hu had an anxious tone, he expressed concern in his gaze.

Lady Wan Shou smiled at him lightly, saying softly: "Don't worry, I can endure such a level of injury. I just need to rest for half a day and I will recover."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu let out a breath: "That is good."

Pausing for a while, he continued: "Even though we failed this time, it is fine, this is only the first attempt! We have prepared ample refinement materials."

"That's right." Lady Wan Shou acknowledged: "Even though we failed once, and have to start over, this refinement path Gu formation preserves much of our beforehand successes, the second refinement will definitely go smoothly. Let me rest for half a day, after I recover, we will start over."

How could Immortal Gu refinement succeed at the first attempt?

Especially rank eight Immortal Gu, the success rate was absurdly low.

In the past, when Hei Fan refined years flow like water Immortal Gu, he failed consecutively, he even lost confidence in it after many failures.

Thus, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou did not put this failure to heart.

They were very confident.

"Dear, why the rush? It is fine if you rest for a few days. You may not know yet, another storm is brewing in Northern Plains, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Chu Du are fighting over the ownership of Hei Fan grotto-heaven. Right now, they are in a deadlock, but I am sure Chu Du has backup plans, he has just not used them yet." Old Ancestor Xue Hu smiled, explaining the details to her.

"Oh?" Lady Wan Shou heard this and joy flashed across her face.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was refining fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, the risks involved were not just the rank eight Immortal Gu refinement itself.

Northern Plains had other rank eight Gu Immortals, they were unwilling to see Old Ancestor Xue Hu obtain a rank eight Immortal Gu and become even stronger.

Thus, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had to keep a close watch on these rank eight existences.

Since Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was fighting with Chu Du now, for Old Ancestor Xue Hu, it was a wonderful thing.

However, after Lady Wan Shou heard his words, she shook her head firmly, rejecting Old Ancestor Xue Hu's suggestion: "I only need half a day of rest. This refinement path Gu formation was created by Sun Ming Lu, who mimicked Regret Pool. It has several functions of Regret Pool, but it can only last for a day. Resting half a day is the limit, I need to refine Gu using the rest of the time."

"So that's it." Old Ancestor Xue Hu realized, he said with much concern: "Dear, it has been hard on you."

"No matter, it is an extremely exciting thing for me to be able to refine a rank eight Immortal Gu." Lady Wan Shou's eyes shone with dazzling brilliance.

That night.

Moonlight shone on the grasslands, several figures approached Iron Eagle blessed land stealthily.

They were Fang Yuan, Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, Li Si Chun, and Immortal Wang.

Iron Eagle blessed land was Hei tribe's headquarters originally, but after they were wiped out, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu took over and made it the main base of Bai Zu tribe.

At this moment, Iron Eagle blessed land was hidden in empty space, it could not be seen from the outside.

Fang Yuan took a glance, only to see that the green grass was reflecting the moonlight like a lake, it was extremely lush. The night's winds blew on one's face, like the hands of one's lover.

It was a harmonious scene, but Fang Yuan and his fellow Gu Immortals were overflowing with battle intent, flames were burning in their hearts.

Chu Du's battle plan made Fang Yuan feel admiration towards him.

Chu Du endured for half a month, it was not a short time. He planned secretly and gathered his strength, bursting it out as he attacked the enemy's base.

If Iron Eagle blessed land were to be successfully taken down, it would greatly influence Bai Zu tribe. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu might truly be forced to return and give up on Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

"Chu Du has some brains indeed. He is taking advantage of Bai Zu tribe's inner conflict." Hao Zhen smiled.

"Hehe, Bai Zu tribe took in Hei tribe, they assimilated the Hei tribe Gu Immortals. Even though the Hei tribe Gu Immortals changed their surnames to Bai Zu, they have genuine Huang Jin bloodline, they are being ostracized. Just now, almost all of Hei tribe's Gu Immortals were sent out to defend the important resource points. But the Bai Zu Gu Immortals were staying guard inside Iron Eagle blessed land." Chou Lao Wu added.

Because Chu Sect's Gu Immortals were hidden, they could attack at any time. Bai Zu tribe's outside resources could not be unguarded. This type of defense mission was very difficult, it was far more dangerous than guarding Iron Eagle blessed land.

After all, the Gu formations at the resource points were rebuilt after they were destroyed earlier. Because these points were far from each other, when a single Gu Immortal defended one area, it was easy for many enemies to attack them at once.

"Darling Chu is simply a heroic genius! I was thinking earlier, which resource point should we choose to attack this time for darling Chu. But to think that we would attack Iron Eagle blessed land directly, ah, every time I think about darling Chu, my heart pounds so quickly. He is really amazing!" Li Si Chun curled his flowery fingers as he clutched his chest, showing a look of attraction and infatuation.

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu beside him felt their hair standing, they quickly moved away from him, as far as possible.

"Alright, we have to strike fast! Who has a method to break into Iron Eagle blessed land, why are you not going ahead with it?" Fang Yuan asked coldly.

Li Si Chun's eyes shined brightly: "Darling Liu is so cool, I am really moved."

Fang Yuan said expressionlessly: "F*ck off, will you."

Li Si Chun gasped, holding his chest as he took a few steps back, shaking his head: "I am so upset, my heart is about to shatter!"

As if he could not stand Li Si Chun's amorous words, Immortal Wang stood up.

Like what Fang Yuan had estimated, among them, someone had a way to break into blessed lands rapidly. This was not Fang Yuan's confidence in these strangers, it was his confidence in Chu Du. He was an intelligent person, why would he not think of this when devising a plan to attack Iron Eagle blessed land?

Immortal Wang's throat emitted a sound, his aura rose intensely as countless Gu worm auras emanated from his body.

With a bright flash, Immortal Wang turned into a giant hound.

This hound had white fur, like snow, it had four strong limbs and a big head, its eyes were pale and colorless, without any pupils.

Li Si Chun gasped as he cried out: "Ah, this is an immemorial desolate beast, heaven swallowing hound?"

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu looked at each other, feeling joy and surprise. Did it mean he had rank eight battle strength?

Fang Yuan shook his head calmly: "Even if he became a heaven swallowing hound, he only has rank seven cultivation level, how can he have rank eight battle strength?"

If he did, why would Fang Yuan, Hao Zhen, and the rest need to come? Just Immortal Wang alone could take down Iron Eagle blessed land.

Furthermore, if he had rank eight battle strength, he would be famous in Northern Plains, how could Chu Du invite him over so easily?

At this moment, the heaven swallowing hound that Immortal Wang turned into burst out with countless Gu worm auras again.

These auras intertwined, instantly, another immortal killer move was conjured.

The heaven swallowing hound suddenly opened its mouth, biting at the space in front of it.

Space shook, a shadow was torn out, entering the heaven swallowing hound's mouth.

Next, shocked shouts could be heard.

"Who is it?!"

"You dare to devour our Iron Eagle blessed land!"

"Enemy attack!!"

Like the shattering of a mirror, a huge gap was created, Fang Yuan and the others could see the scene inside Iron Eagle blessed land.

The Bai Zu Gu Immortals reacted quickly, several figures flew over, wanting to block Fang Yuan and the rest.

Immortal Wang turned back to human form, saying weakly: "I need to recuperate, it is up to all of you now."

Seeing his pale face, turning into the immemorial desolate beast was clearly beyond his limits, or perhaps, that immortal killer move earlier had a strong drawback.

Boom!

Fang Yuan stomped, creating a huge pit on the ground.

Before Immortal Wang finished his words, he had shot out like a cannon, charging over imposingly.

He was the first to invade, entering Iron Eagle blessed land.

"Such guts!"

"Look at our Immortal Gu!!"

The Gu Immortals from Bai Zu tribe faced him, among them, there were rank six and seven Gu Immortals, they attacked fiercely.

Fang Yuan snorted, pushing with his right hand.

With a loud sound, air burst as a huge giant hand slammed in that direction.

Fighting offense with offense.

Fang Yuan displayed incredible battle strength, he was extremely powerful. The strength path giant hand crushed the layers of attacks by the Bai Zu Gu Immortals. Thereafter, it flew towards the Bai Zu Gu Immortals.

But after blocking the attacks earlier, the strength path giant hand did not have enough force left.

A Bai Zu Gu Immortal attacked fiercely, with a swoosh, countless golden needles flew out of his mouth, in the blink of an eye, it pierced countless holes in the giant hand, before flying towards Fang Yuan.

A cold light flashed deep within Fang Yuan's dark eyes.

Sword escape Immortal Gu!

In an instant, his speed rose drastically, he flew deep into Iron Eagle blessed land like a flying sword.

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were shocked by his speed.

Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, and Li Si Chun, these three immortals behind him were very shocked too. They were hoping that Fang Yuan would be in front, diverting the firepower away from them.

But would Fang Yuan let them take advantage of him?

At the next moment, a Gu Immortal from Bai Zu tribe chased after Fang Yuan relentlessly. The other Gu Immortals remained on the spot, blocking Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, and Li Si Chun.

Countless attacks flew out like torrential rain.

A chaotic battle ensued, the Gu Immortals could not care about anything else, they were all stuck here.

Fang Yuan flew into the sky!

His investigative methods had been activated long ago, he could see many traces left behind during the battle of Hei tribe.

Chapter 1170: Sudden Attack on Iron Eagle Blessed Land (2/2)

Even though Iron Eagle blessed land was taken over by Bai Zu tribe, it had only operated for a short time, even though it was being renewed, it was still far from Hei tribe's prime.

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan's eyes shined, he could see many eagle nests floating in the sky.

"There are few resources on the ground, but the sky has at least a hundred eagle nests. It seems that Bai Zu tribe's strategy is to develop Iron Eagle blessed land's specialty and fully place effort in raising iron crown eagles and other desolate beasts." Fang Yuan realized.

This was clearly a good strategy.

Raising desolate beasts and selling them in treasure yellow heaven would grant a huge profit for each of them!

"Last time, I could not be here for the destruction of Hei tribe, this time, I can earn a huge profit and snatch all of these eagle nests!" Fang Yuan felt excitement.

He was very perceptive, at one glance, he could tell that in the entirety of Iron Eagle blessed land, the most valuable thing were these eagle nests.

And there was a crucial point, these eagle nests were easy to take, unlike the other resources.

"Evil scoundrel, stop!" Behind him, a Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortal was frantically shouting.

"It seems that I need to get rid of this problem." Fang Yuan sneered, turning around and charging towards the pursuer.

This pursuer was called Bai Zu Wei, he had rank seven cultivation level, and was the leader of the defenders of Iron Eagle blessed land.

Just earlier, he was the one who sent out all of Hei tribe's Gu Immortals to the resource points in the outside world to defend them.

He felt that Iron Eagle blessed land was still safe, but Chu Du's strategies had outmaneuvered him.

This attack came too quickly.

When Fang Yuan and the others attacked, it was like lightning had struck Bai Zu Wei's heart.

If Iron Eagle blessed land suffered a huge loss, as the leader, he would have to bear the responsibility. Thus, he was very anxious now, he made up his mind, even if he had to put his life on the line, he had to defend Iron Eagle blessed land!

Thus, Bai Zu Wei's facial muscles moved when he saw Fang Yuan charging at him, he showed a ruthless expression, he did not dodge, instead, he rushed at Fang Yuan with an even fiercer stance.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's gaze shined, he saw that his opponent's body was shining in golden light.

"A metal path Gu Immortal? He seems to be very confident in his defense." Fang Yuan had this thought in his mind as he turned around, flying in the backward-left direction.

Sword escape Immortal Gu's speed was extraordinary, but he did not gain any distance from Bai Zu Wei.

He used his immortal killer move, his speed was not any slower!

"Even though Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals have always lived inside Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's grotto-heaven, they are not weak at all because of this rank eight Gu Immortal's nurturing. Then... let me see your investigative methods." Fang Yuan's body shook, he used the immortal killer move myriad self.

Rumble!

At the next moment, countless Fang Yuan phantoms appeared, filling up half of the sky.

Bai Zu Wei's expression of rage and anxiety froze.

He used his investigative killer move next.

His eyes turned golden, two rays of light seemed to be shooting out from his eyes, as he started looking around.

"My investigative immortal killer move was created by Heavenly Lord himself! No matter where you are hiding, how can you escape my detection?" Bai Zu Wei was confident.

But next, after a few breaths of time, he was stunned.

"How, how can this be? Where is his true body? I can't see it?!" He was extremely shocked.

He would not know, even though his investigative killer move was good, Fang Yuan's familiar face was immensely better!

The former was created by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, but the latter was a move famously used by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

Boom boom boom.

Eagle nests broke open as Fang Yuan manipulated the myriad self army, attacking these eagle nests with full force.

In the eagle nests, there were young eagles and eggs that had not hatched yet.

Their homes were wrecked, the young eagles were chirping, moving out and fighting with Fang Yuan's phantoms.

Fang Yuan's phantoms had low quality, they could not fight against the young desolate beast eagles. However, the number of phantoms was too high, they could attack from every direction, the young desolate beast eagles could not defend the nests.

Soon, eagle nests were destroyed as they fell from the sky.

"No!" Bai Zu Wei shouted, rushing over, using a metal path killer move to try and catch an eagle nest that was falling. He next carefully placed it on the ground as it descended.

Using this chance, Fang Yuan revealed his true self, he used strength path giant hand and grabbed an eagle nest, stuffing it into his immortal aperture.

His immortal aperture's entrance opened and closed, stuffing an eagle nest inside.

Bai Zu Wei saved the eagle nest in front of him, he had just let out a breath of air when he saw this scene.

Immediately, his eyes turned red as he furiously shouted: "No! Damned thief, return our eagle nest!"

Saying this, he pounced at Fang Yuan with a ferocious aura.

Fang Yuan's lips curled, he smiled sinisterly as he entered the myriad self army, manipulating these strength path phantoms to scatter.

Bai Zu Wei was stunned!

His investigative method could not expose familiar face. He could only attack randomly, betting on chance. But how could his luck surpass Fang Yuan, who had dog shit luck Immortal Gu, and had also used Connect Luck on four lucky people?

Like this, Fang Yuan manipulated the myriad self army, attacking eagle nests everywhere. Bai Zu Wei was alone and could not find Fang Yuan's true body, he could only rush everywhere, desperately salvaging the situation.

Fang Yuan used this chance to strike, taking more eagle nests into his immortal aperture.

Bai Zu Wei roared angrily, but he was helpless to stop him.

His lungs were bursting from anger, he screamed at the top of his lungs: "Shameless thief! Fight me fairly and openly if you have the balls to do so!"

Fang Yuan ignored him.

Bai Zu Wei screamed again: "You cowardly bastard, you are running around like a rat, how dare you invade my Bai Zu tribe?!"

Fang Yuan stored another eagle nest.

Bai Zu Wei had bloodshot eyes, his voice was hoarse: "You will not remain smug for long, you have offended Lord Heavenly Lord Bai Zu! Even if you run to the ends of the world, we will find you and deal with you!!"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, chanting on the spot: "One two three four, five six seven eight, the eagle nests are in my hands, what can Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals do to me?"

Guh.

Bai Zu Wei spat out a mouthful of blood from pure anger.

In fact, these eagle nests were managed by him, he poured his blood and sweat into each of them.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would not care about these things, he trusted and gave him the authority to manage them, but Bai Zu tribe did not have much resources, Bai Zu Wei was putting in a lot of effort to try and increase the resource production, these eagle nests were his biggest hope in helping Bai Zu tribe ascend and break free from financial problems.

But these beautiful prospects were ruined by this accursed Fang Yuan.

"I will not let you off, I will not let you off even if I die!!" Bai Zu Wei screamed, he was spitting out blood and having a shrill voice, but the hatred in his voice made Immortal Wang, who had just arrived, feel a chill down his spine.

"How many eagle nests did this Liu Guan Yi take, to make Bai Zu Wei so enraged?" Immortal Wang reacted, he felt envious and jealous, he wanted the person Bai Zu Wei was cursing to be himself!

Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, and Li Si Chun were still fighting.

"Where is Immortal Wang?"

"He entered the place. This dog actually went on a detour and made a new entrance at the back."

The three immortals conversed, they were anxious and furious.

They wanted to go inside too and scavenge for resources, but Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were blocking their entry.

These Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals could not be killed.

Fang Yuan knew this, Hao Zhen and the rest also knew that this was their bottom line.

Bai Zu tribe was just established, they only had these few Gu Immortals, they were all nurtured by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

If they died, it would mean becoming enemies with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu without any hope of reconciliation. If Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not take revenge, he would not have any face to remain in Northern Plains!

Attacking Iron Eagle blessed land and making Bai Zu tribe lose some resources, or even killing some Hei tribe Gu Immortals was fine. The important thing was, these Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals could not die. Chu Du had placed much emphasis on this point before they went.

Chu Du did not want to be a mortal enemy with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

In terms of strength, Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were inferior to Hao Zhen, Chou Lao Wu, and Li Si Chun, these three rank seven Gu Immortals, but they were united and fought together, the three immortals were actually suppressed instead.

Li Si Chun shouted: "Let's retreat first!"

The other two immortals reacted, immediately moving back.

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals chased after them, as the three immortals split up.

"Quickly come back! This is the outside world of Northern Plains, we are not reinforced by Iron Eagle blessed land. There are already enemies inside the blessed land, let's go back and help Lord Wei!" Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals chased for a while before returning to Iron Eagle blessed land.

The three immortals saw a chance and flew back immediately.

Among them, Li Si Chun went to the entrance created by Immortal Wang, successfully getting into Iron Eagle blessed land.

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were panicking, the entrance could not be blocked anymore, even if they went to the bigger gap in space, they could not change the situation.

They were also concerned about Bai Zu Wei's safety.

After all, three rank seven Gu Immortals had already entered Iron Eagle blessed land.

"Let's go find Lord Wei first!"

This was a wise decision.

Without anyone guarding it, Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu got into the blessed land as well.

"Quick, quick, we are the last ones in."

"Go and see what resources there are, and get them for ourselves!"

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu were extremely hurried.

Gu Immortals needed resources to cultivate, this was their foundation for cultivation!

Without resources, they could do nothing.

This time, the immortals came to attack Bai Zu tribe, their own objective was to gain benefits. Without profits, how could anyone resolve themselves to offend a rank eight Gu Immortal?

"Alright, these soft jades are all mine!" Li Si Chun licked his lips, unsatisfied.

The soft jade beach in front of him was newly built by Bai Zu tribe.

Unfortunately, there were only a few hundred soft jades on the beach, the largest one was only basin sized, Li Si Chun was not satisfied.

"This is the third resource point I have found, there are so little resources. Damn, Bai Zu tribe is so poor, what's the point of trying to become a super force." Li Si Chun stood with his hands on his waist as he cursed.

"Oh? Wait, no!" He raised his head, looking at the sky with a flickering gaze.

"Damn, why did I forget about this?!" He patted his forehead, rapidly flying into the sky.

There were only three eagle nests in the sky.

Countless Fang Yuan phantoms were still flying in the sky, diverting Bai Zu Wei's attention.

Fang Yuan's true body was hidden among them, no matter how Bai Zu Wei cursed him, he refused to come out.

Chapter 1171: Wind Thunder Roar

Thankfully, Bai Zu Wei was no longer as stifled as before.

He chased Immortal Wang all over the place.

Immortal Wang turned into a falling star hound, he was fast as he ran, shouting: "Why are you only chasing me? I did not even get a single eagle nest, it was all Liu Guan Yi! Are you blind? Do you have a brain?"

"You will all die, you will all die!!" Bai Zu Wei was beyond angry.

He could not find Fang Yuan's true body, he could only take it out in Immortal Wang.

Immortal Wang was strong, but he did not dare to make a killing move against Bai Zu Wei, so he could only run away.

Thanks to him drawing Bai Zu Wei's attention, Fang Yuan successfully obtained another eagle nest.

"Ah!" Bai Zu Wei charged towards him, but Fang Yuan smiled, using the same move to hide among the myriad self army.

Bai Zu Wei roared loudly, he was extremely angry, countless golden needles rained down like a storm, pouring.

Countless myriad self phantoms were destroyed, but Fang Yuan used it again, replenishing the phantoms.

This tactic was too shameless, Bai Zu Wei was breathing roughly from anger.

At this time, Bai Zu tribe's other Gu Immortals arrived.

"Ah, where are our eagle nests?!"

"Lord Wei, are you alright?"

"Scoundrel! Return out eagle nests!"

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were furious, they were currently experiencing Hei tribe's Gu Immortals' feelings when their headquarters were attacked and taken over, the rage and helplessness they felt.

At the same time, Li Si Chun arrived too.

Hearing the screams of Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals, he easily understood what was going on.

He looked at the falling star hound that Immortal Wang had turned into, saying enviously: "Immortal Wang, you truly made great gains!"

The falling star hound who was full of injuries heard this and burst out angrily, speaking human language: "Woof! What damn gains, I did not get a single thing!"

Li Si Chun rolled his eyes, pointing at the falling star hound: "Sigh, who are you kidding? Look at how petty you are, I am not after your gains."

Immortal Wang was almost jumping from rage: "Woof! So be it if you do not believe me, all the good stuff has been taken by that crafty Liu Guan Yi!!"

Li Si Chun was stunned, before looking at the army of myriad self phantoms, his eyes shined: "To think that darling Liu has such amazing methods, I am truly seeing him in a different light."

As he said that, something happened over there with Bai Zu tribe's immortals.

Green light burst into the sky, a huge green giant formed, its imposing aura enveloped the entire battlefield.

"None of you will escape!" The green giant shouted, it was loud as thunder, echoing in Iron Eagle blessed land.

Immortal Wang, who had become a falling star hound, saw this and ran rapidly with all four legs!

Li Si Chun screamed: "Oh mother! Ancient battle formation, Green City Rampage!"

Before finishing his words, he turned around and ran.

Ancient battle formation Green City Rampage, it was an amazing method that could rival rank eight Gu Immortals. After Heavenly Lord Bai Zu recruited the four supreme elders of Hei tribe, he obtained it and gave it to Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals to learn it.

This time, the Bai Zu Gu Immortals were using this formation for the first time in battle.

Boom!

The green giant clapped.

Golden light shone, instantly destroying all of the myriad self phantoms in the battlefield.

Fang Yuan's true body was hiding in an eagle nest, he had transformed into a small eagle, his heartbeat was accelerating.

"As expected of Green City Rampage, my myriad self phantoms were instantly destroyed, yet the three eagle nests were unharmed. By gathering everyone's strength, the attacks of the Bai Zu tribe immortals became much stronger, and their manipulation also became more precise. It is a pity... they are still unable to find me."

Familiar face was this useful!

Without luck inspection or similarly special methods, it was almost unstoppable.

The green giant's eyes burst out with golden light, the Bai Zu Gu Immortals activated all sorts of investigative killer moves, but they could not find Fang Yuan.

Bai Zu Wei snorted coldly, suddenly moving the giant's hand, grabbing an eagle nest and putting it into his immortal aperture.

"Hmm? He became smarter." Fang Yuan sighed, activating myriad self as he moved his real body.

He could not enter Bai Zu Wei's immortal aperture along with the eagle nest.

Even though that was Bai Zu Wei's greatest weakness, Fang Yuan did not have methods to break out of the immortal aperture, he was likely to be stuck inside.

For just three eagle nests, it was not worth the risk.

He had already taken more than eighty eagle nests!

"He is here indeed! Die!" The green giant screamed, golden light flashed as the myriad self army was decimated, only Fang Yuan was left.

Next, the green giant waved its hand as a dark green wind blade was formed.

The wind blade slashed at Fang Yuan with incredible speed.

Fang Yuan used myriad self again, hiding among the phantoms.

But the wind blade turned into numerous blades, slashing their respective targets..

Fang Yuan spat out a mouthful of blood, his time path defensive killer move was instantly broken, his ribcage had multiple fractures, his spine was nearly snapped, he had suffered a huge blow!

This was the terrifying battle strength that matched rank eight existences!

The wind blade had already split into countless ones, Fang Yuan was only hit by one of them.

He wanted to dodge, but after the wind blade split up, its speed rose tremendously, he could not evade it.

Man as Before!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan healed completely.

The green giant was very confident in this move, seeing that Fang Yuan was unharmed, it was enraged, charging towards him angrily.

Fang Yuan sped away as he flew.

He decided on a direction and flew towards Immortal Wang.

Immortal Wang saw that Fang Yuan was luring Green City Rampage over, he was so shocked he barked non-stop, his four dog legs moved like a windmill, desperately running for his life.

Fang Yuan quickly got closer to him.

Green City Rampage was chasing him relentlessly.

"Woof! Don't come, don't come here!"

"Woof! Liu Guan Yi, you took all the benefits, and you still want to drag me down with you! You are too ruthless!!"

"Woof! Let me off, we are friends of Domination Immortal!"

Fang Yuan had a cold expression, he ignored these words, he was bent on making Immortal Wang his cannon fodder.

There was no choice, Green City Rampage's speed was faster than sword escape Immortal Gu.

Without cannon fodder, Fang Yuan could not outspeed Green City Rampage!

Immortal Wang saw that Fang Yuan had run ahead of him, while Green City Rampage was right behind.

At this moment, he was filled with intense rage and killing intent!

He had mixed in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world for so many years, he had never suffered like today before. This Liu Guan Yi, this pretty boy! He did not give a good impression at first glance, and after attacking Iron Eagle blessed land, he earned the most, Immortal Wang did not even get a single eagle nest!!

The important thing was, he was trying to use him as a sacrificial lamb now.

Immortal Wang almost attacked Fang Yuan.

But he restrained this urge.

The reason was obvious, before this battle, they had gathered into a temporary alliance, they were restrained by dao marks. If he attacked an ally, he would face a terrifying backlash.

This was necessary.

Because Fang Yuan, Li Si Chun and the rest were not close, when they worked together, they needed an alliance agreement, that was the basis of trust!

And the one who created the alliance agreement was a Gu Immortal in Chu Sect that Chu Du had chosen.

"At least you are still smart." Fang Yuan smiled coldly, he was a vigilant person, he naturally was on guard against Immortal Wang's attacks.

Sword escape Immortal Gu continued to fly, his green grape immortal essence was expended drastically, Fang Yuan flew faster and shrugged off Immortal Wang.

But he could not break away from the green giant.

This was the ancient battle formation Green City Rampage, ranked third in the past! It was only weaker than Heavenly Giant Solor and Golden Heavenly Saint.

If he did not scheme, Fang Yuan would be caught by the green giant eventually.

Doing something like this which harmed an ally also caused him to suffer some backlash. But the extent of it was mild, because Fang Yuan did not attack his ally.

Immortal Wang was anxious, his dog fur was standing up, he could feel intense killing intent from Green City Rampage.

"Quickly save me!" Immortal Wang shouted, feeling despair.

"Don't worry Brother Wang, we are here to help you." Far away, Hao Zhen shouted.

Beside him, there was a Gu Immortal, it was Chou Lao Wu.

Immortal Wang heard his words and was overjoyed, quickly shouting: "If I am saved, I will definitely thank you guys!"

Hao Zhen nodded, speaking to Chou Lao Wu softly: "Brother Chou, let's start."

"Alright." Chou Lao Wu burst out with an intense aura that shot up into the sky, a large amount of his red date immortal essence was expended at once.

Around his entire body, a dark green wind was enveloping it, forming a gigantic ball of compressed winds.

"Wind—" Chou Lao Wu growled.

"Thunder!" Next, Hao Zhen cried out at the sky.

His muscular body was upright like a spear, he was floating in the air, countless lightning sparks were flickering, turning the area of a hundred steps around him into a plasma pool.

Next, Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen opened their mouths, bellowing loudly towards the green giant which was still far away —

"Roar!!"

Double immortal killer move — Wind Thunder Roar.

First, the dark green wind ball flew out, forming into a horizontal tornado. It was like a world destroying serpent, moving forward with destructive force.

Next, the lightning plasma shot towards it, fusing with the tornado in an instant, forming a thick wind and lightning pillar.

The pillar moved extremely quickly, it shot out and flew several meters above the ground, along the way, intense air currents were formed, digging huge trenches along the grassland on the ground.

Two breaths of time later, the wind and lightning pillar crashed into the green giant's chest with an unstoppable force.

Peak rank seven battle strength!

The green giant stood on the ground and braced itself, raising its arms in defense.

After several breaths of time, the attack dissipated, while the giant was still standing.

"If I were to be hit by wind thunder roar, I would die for sure. Worthy of Green City Rampage!" Fang Yuan flew as he watched the battle of two sides.

Immortal Wang was still running without even looking back, he was afraid that any pause would cause him to die there.

"No wonder it can rival rank eight Gu Immortals, let's run!" Hao Zhen had a pale expression, the use of wind thunder roar was extremely taxing on him.

Chou Lao Wu was not feeling good either, the two quickly retreated.

The green giant almost perfectly blocked wind thunder roar, but unexpectedly, it stopped moving after the attack, staying completely still.

"Something's strange." During this period, most of the battling Gu Immortals had fled a huge distance.

At the next moment, they saw that the green giant broke apart all of a sudden.

Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals were all spitting out blood, they fell towards the ground.

Chapter 1172: Unresolvable

The ancient battle formation was broken, Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals suffered a huge backlash.

"Lord Wei!!" Someone cried out.

Bai Zu Wei was the key person controlling the formation, after the ancient battle formation was broken, he suffered the biggest damage, he actually died on the spot.

Bai Zu Wei was the number one person below Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, the core of Bai Zu tribe's Gu Immortals.

To think that after Bai Zu tribe was created, when he was about to reach the prime of his life, he died in their base camp.

This shocking change not only made the Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals feel deep sadness, Fang Yuan and the rest who invaded Iron Eagle blessed land also turned solemn.

A member of Bai Zu tribe died!

The enmity was huge now!!

Fang Yuan had a heavy mood.

Li Si Chun, with his flowery appearance, had a pale expression as he asked: "What, what do we do?"

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu had even worse expressions.

"How could this happen? Green City Rampage can rival rank eights, our wind thunder roar cannot cause such harm to him." Chou Lao Wu could not believe this.

"They were not familiar enough with the formation..." Fang Yuan had a realization in his mind.

The ancient battle formation Green City Rampage was powerful, but it was not so easy to use successfully.

The four top supreme elders of Hei tribe could use it well, that was because they had spent a huge amount of time practising it.

But the Bai Zu tribe Gu Immortals had only practised Green City Rampage for a short period of time.

And now was their first true battle in using it, it was understandable that they had made some errors.

"The matter is huge now, let's all discuss, what do we do now?" The immortals left the battlefield as Hao Zhen called out.

"Hmph, you two are the ones who killed him, what does it have to do with me?" Fang Yuan sneered, flying away.

"You!" Hao Zhen was furious.

Chou Lao Wu quickly said: "Liu Guan Yi, we are all in the same boat, do you think the Heavenly Lord will let you off in his rage?"

But Fang Yuan ignored him, he continued to retreat, quickly entering the clouds, vanishing from everyone's vision.

The other immortals were still flying, but they were silent and uncertain.

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu felt panicked and flustered.

Chou Lao Wu tried to calm himself down, he broke the silence: "Liu Guan Yi is such a scoundrel..."

Before he finished his words, Immortal Wang interrupted: "Ah! I am heavily injured, I need to seek treatment, I will take my leave first."

He turned into a falling star hound and changed directions, running away.

Li Si Chun saw this and thought quickly, smiling: "I am skilled at healing techniques, wait for me Immortal Wang, I'll help you."

Saying this, he followed behind Immortal Wang, swiftly leaving the place.

Chou Lao Wu looked at this in disbelief, he stared with wide opened eyes, cursing: "This dog shit Wang, he is so shameless! To think we saved him! If we'd known this in advance, why would we even help?!"

Chou Lao Wu looked at Hao Zhen, all of the negative emotions inside him were alleviated by a bit.

After all, he was not alone.

Other than him, Hao Zhen had also attacked.

Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen had a good relationship, this was rare among demonic path Gu Immortals. Once this happened, these two unlucky brothers' relationship would grow closer.

But this did not help matters.

The two looked at each other, Hao Zhen had a stiff expression, he said in a heavy tone: "Since this has happened already, there is nothing we can do. Now, we can only rely on Chu Du."

Chou Lao Wu's eyes were shining, he was like a drowning person who saw a floating log: "That's right, you are right. We were invited by Chu Du to help him, he cannot abandon us! Let's go find him!"

Fang Yuan did not stick around, he immediately returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

"The situation is a little complex now." He frowned slightly, analyzing the situation.

Originally, this attack on Iron Eagle blessed land was rather successful.

Fang Yuan and the others attacked Iron Eagle blessed land, they destroyed and took away a lot of resources, it was a huge blow to Bai Zu tribe.

If that was all that happened, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would have to retreat, to defend his base.

He had created a super force after so much work, he had squeezed into the cracks between the Huang Jin tribes, obtaining his own territory. This expended so much of his time and effort, he had even paid a huge price!

If he continued to attack Hei Fan grotto-heaven relentlessly, allowing Fang Yuan and the others to continue attacking them, the situation would become very unstable.

Bai Zu tribe's reputation would be completely ruined before it was even established. Other forces and Gu Immortals would gather like hungry wolves, targeting Bai Zu tribe like how they attacked Hei tribe.

Once such a situation occurs, even Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would feel very troubled.

Because he was not the only rank eight in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

In order to defend his hard work, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had to either take down Hei Fan grotto-heaven quickly, or wisely give up on it and return to stabilize the situation, and fortify his base.

Attacking Hei Fan grotto-heaven quickly was not feasible for Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. If he could, he would have already won by now.

Chu Du had noticed Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's greatest weakness, thus, his tactic aimed at his weakness, it was truly brilliant and impressive.

But unfortunately, how could simply a person's strategy completely determine the outcome?

At the crucial moment, an unexpected mishap occurred, a rank seven Gu Immortal from Bai Zu tribe died!

Fang Yuan naturally knew that Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu acted to save Immortal Wang because they were after the reward. After they help Immortal Wang break free from Green City Rampage, how could Immortal Wang not thank them heavily with compensation?

"The two of them were the last to enter Iron Eagle blessed land, their gains were unable to satisfy their appetite. This is why they wanted to earn a fortune from Immortal Wang. It was a pity, they overestimated the Bai Zu Gu Immortals, and caused this terrible outcome." Fang Yuan shook his head and sighed.

This way, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was sure to take revenge.

If he did not, his reputation would go down the drain, how could a rank eight Gu Immortal be unable to protect his own people? He might as well go die in that case!

This was more unforgivable than having Iron Eagle blessed land be completely destroyed.

Forget about managing any super force, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would lose all of his reputation.

"This means that, Chu Du and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's conflict is now unresolvable. And I am Chu Du's ally, who had also joined the battle in Iron Eagle blessed land."

At this point, Fang Yuan was also dragged into it.

Even though his circumstances were better than those of Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen.

"What should I do?" Fang Yuan paced around in the secret room, thinking hard.

He had the alliance agreement, he had no choice. His desire towards information path inheritances grew even stronger now.

He thought about it for a while, there was a solution that was not really a solution.

"In the worst case, I can only get Chu Du into Lang Ya Sect. Lang Ya Sect is already part of the variant human alliance, by then, we can use the immemorial rock dragon against Heavenly Lord Bai Zu."

Thinking about this, Fang Yuan saw hope in getting Chu Du to join Lang Ya Sect.

Originally, Domination Immortal Chu Du had the pride of being a human Gu Immortal, how could he lower his head and join a variant human force?

"Or maybe, Chu Du still has his trump cards?" Fang Yuan thought of another possibility.

Of course, he also had another solution, that was to leave Northern Plains directly.

He had the sovereign immortal body anyway, he was unique, he could survive in any region. He was unlike other Gu Immortals, for example, when a Northern Plains Gu Immortal leaves Northern Plains, a foreign region's heaven and earth qi would cause their immortal aperture to become unstable, it might even break apart, trying to undergo tribulation was courting death.

"If I cannot fight you, I can still escape." Fang Yuan thought. So-called reputation and pride were not obstacles in his way.

Of course, unless he had no choice, Fang Yuan would not want to leave Northern Plains.

Over here, he could use Lang Ya Sect's power and live well. If he left, he could not use immortal tribulation tempering aperture. He could also not use Luo Po Valley which had already been sold to Lang Ya Sect. There were also lots of other problems as well.

Southern Border.

At dawn.

Far away, the dawn sky was white like marble white.

The fog in the mountains fused with the fragrance of the grass and trees, giving off a cooling feeling.

Two figures were descending from the cloud layer.

One was rank seven, the other was rank six, they resembled youngsters. They wore deep green short sleeve shirts and long black pants, they also had jade leggings.

"Big brother, they said third supreme elder went crazy? Do you think it is true?" The rank six Gu Immortal asked.

The rank seven Gu Immortal had a grim expression, he sighed and answered: "Ever since us righteous path forces started the super dream realm exploration, two Gu Immortals have already fallen unconscious, and one Gu Immortal's soul was completely destroyed. Third supreme elder went crazy... I'm afraid it's true."

"Ah." The rank six Gu Immortal gasped: "Third supreme elder has such high cultivation level, he is a senior among rank sevens, already having gone through two grand tribulations, how could he go crazy?"

The rank seven Gu Immortal shook his head: "Exploration of the dream realm has nothing to do with cultivation level. Other than bringing back third supreme elder now, we have to take over his role. Little brother, you need to be careful, he is a good example, do not succumb to the dream realm."

"Don't worry big brother! Even though there is a prophecy on Great Dream Immortal Venerable, I know my limits, how could I court death?" The rank six Gu Immortal had a fearful expression.

The two immortals spoke casually, passing by a nameless peak as they continued flying, before vanishing in the sky.

"They went in." Hei Lou Lan said.

Currently, besides her, there was Ying Wu Xie, Shi Nu, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and Bai Ning Bing.

"This super Gu formation was set up by Chi Qu You, he used up a great number of Immortal Gu from the Southern Border righteous path super forces, as well as countless mortal Gu. The defense is really tight!" Shi Nu said heavily.

With such a powerful defensive Gu formation and a large number of righteous path Gu Immortals defending it, with just the power of Ying Wu Xie and the others, they could not break through.

Ying Wu Xie however, smiled lightly: "This Gu formation is not a problem. The dream realm is still expanding, every once in a while, the formation has to be reset, at that time, the righteous path Gu Immortals have no spare energy to care about other things, that is the time to attack. What truly obstructs us is this dream realm."

Saying this, he spoke more slowly as he sighed eerily: "I have lead soul into dream, but I do not have a method to unravel dreams."

"Fang Yuan does." Hei Lou Lan transmitted.

"Him?!" Ying Wu Xie's heart shook, his gaze suddenly became very complicated.

Chapter 1173: Crazed Demon Cave

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Tens of thousands of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu figures floated in the air, looking down towards Chu Du.

The expression and attitude of the Heavenly Lord Bai Zu figures were completely different from before, all of their faces were grim and heavy.

"Chu Du! Hand over the murderers and Hei Fan grotto-heaven, I can spare your life."

Tens of thousands of mouths spoke at once, the loud volume reverberated in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Chu Du stood on the ground, raising his head and looking.

Compared to the numerous Heavenly Lord Bai Zu figures in the sky, he was all alone, seemingly lonely and weak.

However, his body was upright and straight like a spear, his domineering aura shrouded his body, he could resist Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's imposing display without wavering.

"Hmph! You are attacking my grotto-heaven, and you want me to surrender? So what if that Bai Zu tribesman died, this is your punishment and a price to pay for attacking me."

Chu Du spoke plainly, his voice was echoing in the grotto-heaven.

The group of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu figures still wanted to speak, but Chu Du activated his immortal killer move at the next moment.

Inner strength self detonation!

The immortal killer move's range covered the entirety of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Inside the Heavenly Lord Bai Zu bodies, inner strength was appearing out of nowhere, it expanded until it reached its limit.

Next, all of the Heavenly Lord Bai Zu clones self-detonated at the same time, it was an incredible sight.

At once, the overwhelming army was completely destroyed by Chu Du in one move.

"Domination Immortal!" Outside the grotto-heaven, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's true body frowned as he gritted his teeth, fuming with rage.

Not long ago, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had received a letter from his tribe, he was informed of Bai Zu Wei's death.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was naturally very upset, and also furious.

Bai Zu Wei was nurtured by him singlehandedly, he was like a child that he had raised.

To think that after building the tribe, and having just having started building their foundation in Northern Plains, he died, it was truly regretful.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu quickly noticed that if this matter was not dealt with properly, it would cause a huge crisis!

"If I do not take down Hei Fan grotto-heaven and kill the murderers, my reputation would fall drastically, people would think I am weak, Bai Zu tribe would be pushed aside."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would not allow that to happen.

But his earlier call for surrender did not work.

"Domination Immortal Chu Du! This person is as tough as a rock on the seashore, just waves alone cannot stop him. Then let me show him a tsunami." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had a firm expression.

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

"Lord Domination Immortal, it is my, Hao Zhen's, greatest honor to be acquainted with you!"

"Lord Domination Immortal, I, Chou Lao Wu, admires you and solely you alone."

Somehow, at some point in time, Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu were brought into Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

They were hidden underground, after Chu Du killed all of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's illusory clones, they showed themselves.

Originally, they were worried, but Chu Du rejected Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's offer of surrender with a firm tone, their doubts were dispelled, they felt deep admiration towards him.

"You two." Chu Du faced them, having a sincere expression: "You both got into trouble because of me. If I submit to the threat of a rank eight Gu Immortal and abandon you, I will be letting down my title as the 'Domination Immortal'. That is definitely not my style and demeanor as Chu Du!"

"Lord Domination Immortal, what do we do now?" Chou Lao Wu asked.

Chu Du smiled lightly: "Don't worry, this Hei Fan grotto-heaven is not ordinary. Earlier, I alone was able to defend it. With the help of both of you, we have no worries."

Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen nodded, but the worry in their faces did not go away.

Chu Du continued: "Of course, simply defending will eventually lead to failure, right now, we are in a passive situation. I have already sent a letter out, I am inviting friends to fight with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu once and for all!"

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu finally cheered up.

The former said: "Lord Domination Immortal, you can firmly control the situation, we are at ease."

The latter added: "Fame and reputation attracts people. Relying on Hei Fan grotto-heaven to defeat a rank eight Gu Immortal is definitely an incredible achievement. If we use benefits and fame to attract them, Gu Immortals will surely come to help us."

Saying this, Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu looked at each other, before saying loudly to Chu Du: "We are willing to shoulder the cost of inviting help."

Domination Immortal laughed: "No need for that, this was my problem to begin with, how can I watch without paying a price?"

Saying this, he held the hands of Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu, saying in a moved tone: "Fortune and disaster comes together, whether it ends up as fortune or disaster will depend on our hard work. If we can defend the grotto-heaven, I am willing to give up sixty percent of the space here to both of you. It was fate that brought us together, from today onwards, I hope that the three of us can go through thick and thin together, regardless of poverty or wealth!"

A huge amount!

Chu Du promised that after success, he would give sixty percent of Hei Fan grotto-heaven to Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu directly.

At once, Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu's eyes shined, their hearts were pounding.

This was Hei Fan grotto-heaven, it had no calamities and tribulations.

As long as they defended it, Chu Du would give them sixty percent, they would get thirty percent each!

This was simply a godsent fortune.

Hao Zhen's body shook, he had a look of excitement: "Through thick and thin together, regardless of poverty or wealth!"

Chou Lao Wu was so moved his eyes were red: "Meeting Domination Immortal is the greatest blessing in my life."

The two of them had no alternatives to begin with.

Chu Du not only took them in, he even gave them great benefits, at once, their passions were burning!

Bzzz bzzz bzzz....

Waves of buzzing noises entered their ears.

A change occurred, large numbers of distorted shadows appeared in Hei Fan grotto-heaven's sky, some even appeared on the mountains and in water.

Next, from these distorted shadows, figures of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu walked out one by one, there were even desolate beasts, some were ruthless two-legged beasts while others were flying with flapping wings.

The three immortals had solemn expressions.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was an enslavement path cultivator, he could not enter Hei Fan grotto-heaven, but he could send a large number of desolate beasts in.

No, not just desolate beasts, even ancient desolate beasts.

There were even ancient desolate plants, their roots entered the soil as they changed the terrain into their temporary camps.

"Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is finally using his true methods!"

"We have to take action, kill, kill, kill!"

Chu Du called out loudly: "Good, both of you, go kill these fierce beasts. I will manage the situation, I will prevent Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body from entering the grotto-heaven."

If Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's true body came in, they could not compete.

There was an enormous difference in strength between rank seven and eight.

The reason why Chu Du could resist Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was because he was using Hei Fan grotto-heaven as a barrier!

Lang Ya blessed land.

Inside the cloud city's secret room, Fang Yuan was seated as an Immortal Gu moved to his side.

This Immortal Gu, in terms of width and length, was the size of an adult's finger, it was silver and blue in color, shining with bright light. It was like a centipede, but instead of having multiple pairs of legs, it had soft and thin hair instead.

This was the rank seven Immortal Gu Sword Eyebrows.

At this moment, Fang Yuan was using sword eyebrows Immortal Gu to increase his sword path dao marks.

The secret room was dark and eerie, but sword eyebrows Immortal Gu was shining with silver light, it was flying around Fang Yuan as it drew a beautiful arc of dazzling light in the darkness.

A while later, Fang Yuan stopped his cultivation for now.

After the fifth earthly calamity, Fang Yuan had been using sword eyebrows Immortal Gu to increase his sword path dao marks.

He also had fixed times for cultivation daily, going to Luo Po Valley to cultivate his soul.

All in all, sword eyebrows Immortal Gu was quite useful, but it was a rank seven Immortal Gu, unfortunately.

Fang Yuan was only rank six, using a rank seven Immortal Gu had a huge burden on his green grape immortal essence.

Thus, Fang Yuan could not freely use sword eyebrows Immortal Gu. It was because his pressure from the calamities had decreased to the extent after the fifth earthly calamity, along with his good financial status in earning immortal essence stones, that he could undergo this cultivation.

"Oh? Chu Du sent a letter." Fang Yuan had just stored sword eyebrows Immortal Gu into his immortal aperture when he felt something, he sensed a letter Gu.

Through treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan retrieved the letter Gu, his consciousness entered it as his expression changed.

Chu Du had told Fang Yuan about the situation inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he also told Fang Yuan his firm attitude.

When Chu Du wrote this letter, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had not asked him to surrender yet, and had not sent in his army of beasts, but Chu Du had anticipated it.

In the letter, he said: "The might of a rank eight cannot be resisted. Even with the grotto-heaven's help, the inevitable failure is only delayed."

"He is quite aware, I see." Fang Yuan praised before continuing to read.

Chu Du asked for Fang Yuan's help in inviting reinforcements for him to resist Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. At the same time, he told Fang Yuan about his following plans.

Inviting reinforcements to defend Hei Fan grotto-heaven so that Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could not have any gains was not the important point.

The important thing was that other forces and Gu Immortals were not happy with Bai Zu tribe. As long as Heavenly Lord Bai Zu realized that he could not continue to attack Hei Fan grotto-heaven, if he did not return to stabilize the situation, the Bai Zu tribe that he had worked so hard to create would break apart.

That was the only way to get Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to leave.

Lone cultivator Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not have this weakness. But after taking over Hei tribe and creating the righteous path super force, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had to defend it.

Undoubtedly, this plan would work, it was also the only way to deal with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

Fang Yuan had thought of it earlier as well, Chu Du's plan and his were the same.

"Who is Chu Du asking for help? This letter shows much confidence, but he is only asking me to go to Crazed Demon Cave to ask for reinforcements. There must be some capable people."

Crazed Demon Cave!

One of the ten great fierce areas in Northern Plains.

Who was cultivating in seclusion there, who would make Chu Du think of drawing support from their power?

Immediately, Fang Yuan felt a strong sense of curiosity.

Because Crazed Demon Cave was different from the other fierce areas.

If it were Tai Qiu, even though it was dangerous, it was still possible for people to cultivate there in secret. Lang Ya Sect was already doing that now.

But Crazed Demon Cave was created by Limitless Demon Venerable singlehandedly, the cave was filled with demonic sounds, other Gu Immortals would go crazy uncontrollably, before losing all their senses. In history, even a rank eight Gu Immortal had lost their reasoning because of it and became a lunatic.

Chapter 1174: Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics

Of course, since Chu Du was asking Fang Yuan to go and invite people from Crazed Demon Cave, he had also given Fang Yuan some methods to defend against the demonic sounds, and some information regarding the patterns, strengths and weaknesses of these sounds.

"Regardless, I have to go."

Chu Du and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu were competing over Hei Fan grotto-heaven, this originated from Fang Yuan's actions. He had benefits linked with Chu Du, he was also involved with the attack on Iron Eagle blessed land, all in all, he was deeply related to the issue.

Fang Yuan acted quickly, immediately setting off.

Using the super Gu formation, he teleported out of Lang Ya blessed land, heading towards Crazed Demon Cave.

There were no issues along the way.

More than ten days later, Fang Yuan stopped in the air, looking down.

On the ground of flat yellow soil, there was a huge cave. The surroundings of the cave were a circular shape, spanning hundreds of kilometers. There was a thick rainforest in the cave, having both yellow and green colors. From time to time, desolate beasts growled, large numbers of featherless birds flew out, their red bodies made Fang Yuan think of pterosaurs.

It was a scenery of wilderness.

Fang Yuan descended, as the cave got bigger in his vision, until it eventually filled it up.

As he went down, Fang Yuan was completely shrouded by the rainforest in the cave.

Entering the rainforest, the humid and moist air enveloped Fang Yuan.

The branches of the trees were thick and large, but sunlight was very intense. Vines were hanging on the tree trunks, or intertwining on them, Fang Yuan could not find a place to land at times.

Creak creak...

Far away, many strange monkeys with grey fur were chasing each other on the trees.

Suddenly, a motionless 'vine' moved up, openings its bloodthirsty mouth as it swallowed dozens of grey monkeys into its stomach.

In truth, this was a desolate beast tree python that had successfully hunted its prey.

The grey monkey group was in a commotion, they called out loudly, their voices attracted the king of the monkeys, it was also a desolate beast.

The desolate beast tree python continued to retreat, it was already full, its goal was achieved, it did not want to fight the grey monkey king.

The grey monkeys were not insistent on revenge in nature, the monkey king saw that the tree python was leaving and did not chase it, only calling out loudly.

But at this time, there was a sound echoing in the place.

"Oh no, demonic sound." Fang Yuan quickly used his Gu worms, using Chu Du's method to defend against the demonic sound.

Ordinary methods could not block demonic sounds.

But Chu Du's method worked against it with immediate effect. Fang Yuan felt like the demonic sound was gone, as if it never existed.

The vocalizations of the monkey king and the tree python could be heard now.

Influenced by the demonic sound, the two desolate beasts which were going to leave suddenly engaged in combat like they had gone crazy.

This was not just an intense battle, it was a battle to the death.

The two desolate beasts fought to the death, they were entangled, rolling around as many trees were snapped, countless living beings died.

The monkeys around them also went crazy, not only did they attack their allies, they even self-mutilated, banging against hard rocks or digging out their own eyes with their fingers.

The peaceful rainforest became chaotic, there was roaring everywhere, many life forms went into madness, fighting each other as dust clouds rose, an intense bloody smell was emanating.

Fang Yuan maintained his composure and calmness.

But the surrounding birds were all attacking him, even the ants and bees nearby were suiciding as they attacked him.

"This is Crazed Demon Cave..." Fang Yuan sighed internally, using Gu worms to defend himself.

He was clear-minded, he had many strong methods to survive in this crazy environment, he did not feel much pressure.

After all, these crazy life forms were not targeting him alone, they were attacking at will, acting like maniacs.

The demonic sound continued for a while before vanishing.

The noisy rainforest became silent at once.

The wild beasts that were mixing around earlier were corpses now, they had severed limbs and incomplete corpses scattered all over the rainforest. At some places, their blood formed into small rivers, nourishing the ground. Countless snapped trees obtained sufficient nutrients and rapidly grew again.

Far away, the two desolate beasts who fought had died.

The tree python's thick and long body was coiled around the monkey king multiple times, while the final loop was around its neck, snapping it completely.

But the monkey king struggled before dying, tearing apart the python's stomach. All of the monkeys that it had eaten were freed, but they were all dead.

The tree python was near death, as the demonic sound faded, it regained clarity, before the light in its eyes faded.

It lost its life.

Fang Yuan had a thought as he rushed to the battlefield, keeping these two dead desolate beasts in his own immortal aperture.

"If I were you, I would not waste my effort. The life forms in Crazed Demon Cave, be it flying birds or land-based beasts, even Gu worms and plants have no value. The corpses of these desolate beasts cannot be sold in treasure yellow heaven, because the dao marks in their bodies are completely chaotic." A voice could be heard.

"Who is this?" Fang Yuan was shocked.

Even though he had been using familiar face, and the time path killer move three breaths future vision, the latter could only let him see events related to himself three breaths later.

'See' was not 'hear'.

Three breaths future vision had its flaws.

Like right now, Fang Yuan could not foresee voices.

But soon, Fang Yuan 'saw' the future, a white robed Gu Immortal with a middle aged appearance came out of nowhere, he was behind and towards Fang Yuan's right, about ten steps away.

Fang Yuan was fully focused, but he was still looking around.

Three breaths of time later, towards his back, at the right, a white robed Gu Immortal appeared in that very spot.

This Gu Immortal had a pale face and black beard, he had long wide sleeves and eyes that were shining like stars, his disposition was extraordinary.

Fang Yuan quickly turned around, looking at this foreign immortal with a nervous expression.

The white robed Gu Immortal smiled as he said: "Don't be afraid, friend, I am Not Immortal."

Fang Yuan was exposing rank six aura now, but the white robed Gu Immortal was rank seven, his aura was not concealed.

"What?" Fang Yuan was perplexed.

"My title is 'Not Immortal', I live in Crazed Demon Cave. The Gu worm that you have is the token that us Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics gave to Chu Du." The white robed Not Immortal smiled.

Fang Yuan realized, hearing Not Immortal's words, there were two other people in Crazed Demon Cave. He quickly greeted: "Junior greets senior, I came here without an invitation because we need senior's help to assist Lord Domination Immortal."

"Hehehe, us Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics have lived here for hundreds of years without bothering with the outside world, if Chu Du wants to join us, we will gladly welcome him. But if he wants us to leave Crazed Demon Cave, that is absolutely impossible." Not Immortal smiled.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan had an anxious expression, but he felt nothing on the inside.

Regardless of whether Not Immortal was saying this to elevate his own value, just Domination Immortal Chu Du alone was not someone who toyed around.

Chu Du definitely had a close relationship with the three immortals here, he had a plan if he asked Fang Yuan to come.

"Since Chu Du gave you the Gu worm, I suppose he has also given you many methods and the traveling route as well?" Not Immortal asked.

"Yes." Fang Yuan nodded.

Not Immortal assessed Fang Yuan involuntarily, to make Chu Du entrust him like this, what capabilities did this Gu Immortal junior have?

"In that case, follow me. Hehe, you were quite lucky, I came out here for a breather. Crazed Demon Cave is getting more dangerous in recent years, the routes are changing, follow me, if you take a wrong step, you will face the consequences yourself." Not Immortal said as he entered the rainforest.

Fang Yuan hesitated, before moving and following him.

The two entered deep into the rainforest and went into a hole, arriving at the second layer.

Crazed Demon Cave had nine layers, the second layer was an incredibly hot land of burning rocks. A large amount of rocks were piled up together, big and small, the large ones were like huge elephants, the small ones were like pebbles.

A moment later, the two immortals arrived at the third layer.

The third layer was covered in white fog, a large number of fog Gu were living here, along the way, Fang Yuan saw figures of large fierce beasts moving about in the fog.

There was a very large quantity of cloud bamboo.

It was this special bamboo, on the same scale as the rainforest in the first layer, that created the endless fog here.

Next, Fang Yuan saw the image of a city in the fog.

A tall city with markets and vendors, countless people were moving about rapidly, but there was no sound, it was a peculiar scene.

"That is Fog City, the vengeful souls who died gather and form here, there is no point looking at it." Not Immortal, who was in front, informed.

Fang Yuan was slightly shocked, he knew about Fog City, this was the first time he saw it. Souls that could form Fog City were at least Gu Immortals, and a large number at that. With Fang Yuan's current strength, if he entered it, he would definitely die, there was no way to escape.

Crazed Demon Cave was one of the ten great fierce areas in Northern Plains, it was naturally very dangerous.

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics including Not Immortal were living here permanently, their strength was naturally not low.

Under Not Immortal's lead, Fang Yuan entered deep into the cave without much danger, he got to the sixth layer.

"Even we do not dare to enter the bottom three layers casually, it is too dangerous. Come, let me bring you to Gu Immortal Pang Shan, he has the most interaction with Chu Du, he was the one who recommended Chu Du in the first place. Chu Du knows our rules, but he still asked you to come here, he definitely has his objectives. Pang Shan should know."

Under Not Immortal's lead, Fang Yuan met with Gu Immortal Pang Shan at a small valley in the sixth layer.

A huge person!

Pang Shan was dozens of meters tall, he was situated in the valley, he was using the valley as his chair, he was in a half lying down position.

He made Fang Yuan think of that Leshan Giant Buddha back on Earth.

Pang Shan opened his eyes slightly, waking up from his sleep.

"Oh? Chu Du is asking for reinforcements... hmm, we did have an agreement before." Pang Shan said in a deep tone, speaking very slowly.

"As expected. What agreement?" Not Immortal stroked his beard and asked.

"Lend him Immortal Gu and killer moves to resolve his alliance agreements." Pang Shan replied slowly.

Chapter 1175: Do Not Care

"Oh?" Fang Yuan heard Pang Shan's reply and felt extremely shocked.

During this period of time, he had been looking for a way to remove his alliance agreements, but to think that it would show up in front of him like this.

At once, Fang Yuan felt extremely complex.

He had thought that Chu Du was here to ask for reinforcements, but to think that Chu Du's true intention was to remove alliance agreements.

"Chu Du had such a backup, but he had not used it yet, only activating it now, evidently, asking the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics for help has a price."

Crazed Demon Cave was a special place, demonic sounds often played, causing dao marks to become chaotic and all immortal materials to become useless. Because of the special environment, Gu Immortals here could not connect to treasure yellow heaven at all.

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics were isolated from the world.

And Domination Immortal Chu Du needed to guard against Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's invasion, he could not leave. He was unable to act personally and leave the defense of Hei Fan grotto-heaven to others.

Thus, even though Chu Du and Fang Yuan did not know each other for long, because of their closely linked alliance relationship, at this moment, Chu Du had to ask Fang Yuan to come, exposing the secret of Crazed Demon Cave.

"No, Chu Du is very shrewd. He might be intentionally exposing this to me."

Fang Yuan had a thought flash in his mind.

If this guess was accurate, then Fang Yuan could not clearly guess Chu Du's intention.

Fang Yuan was skilled at scheming, so was Chu Du, the Domination Immortal that could make the super force Liu tribe feel helpless, how could he be a simple brute?

Immediately, Fang Yuan held his breath as he asked Pang Shan: "According to what I know, Lord Domination Immortal has many alliance agreements, they are of different sources, they are not purely information path alliance agreements, there are also other paths that could attain the result of information path."

Fang Yuan was spouting nonsense.

However, Chu Du had roamed Northern Plains for so long, he had to have relationships with people, he definitely had many alliance agreements.

Not Immortal stroked his heard and kept silent, smiling lightly.

Pang Shan spoke slowly, but his voice was filled with confidence: "No matter what alliance agreement it is from whichever path, my method can resolve it. Because my Immortal Gu is called 'Care'."

Immortal Gu Care?

Fang Yuan did not conceal the shock inside him, it was shown all over his face.

Care Immortal Gu, almost everyone knew about it.

Because it was in the top ten of the List of Mystical Gu.

In the past, it was ranked third.

But after the battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Fang Yuan's identity was exposed, everyone knew that he was a person from the future who had used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth.

Thus, Spring Autumn Cicada went from seventh place to third.

Care Immortal Gu, which was originally third, became fourth.

The List of Mystical Gu was constantly changing.

Of course, the top ten seldom adjusted.

Spring Autumn Cicada was related to Red Lotus Demon Venerable, the latter was incredibly mysterious, there was little information about him in this world compared to the other venerables. As for rumors regarding Spring Autumn Cicada, not everyone held the same view. Fang Yuan's example proved Spring Autumn Cicada's immense value, the status of this Immortal Gu rose drastically in everyone's minds, its ranking rose as a result.

Most of the top ten mystical Gu were related to rank nine venerables.

The fourth place care Gu was refined by Limitless Demon Venerable when he searched for the secluded domain of heaven and earth 'Care' that was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Fifth place was qi escape Gu.

Sixth place was combat relocation Gu, it originated from Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

Seventh place was connect mind Gu, it came from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

And for the number one mystical Gu, it was refined by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

According to \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter four, section twenty-four —

Ren Zu wanted to save his own children, but he encountered a beastman along the way, he was affected by fear Gu.

Fear Gu made Ren Zu fear everything, he was unable to advance due to his fears.

Ren Zu was tormented by his fear, he was in deep agony, he consulted self Gu.

Self Gu answered: "Then let me eat it."

Ren Zu waved his hand: "No, no. I want nothing more than to avoid fear. If you eat it, this fear will stay with me for life. This is too risky."

Ren Zu asked cognition Gu.

Cognition Gu said: "Oh human, you want to conquer fear, you need to have courage."

Ren Zu was troubled: "I used to have courage Gu as my companion, it is the friend of faith Gu. But afterwards, because I encountered the hairy men, due to failure Gu, it left me."

Cognition Gu said: "I'll teach you a method, hide fear Gu deep within your heart. Move forward after that and courage Gu will come to you. Courageous people are not fearless, they are just hiding fear deep within their hearts."

Ren Zu was more troubled now: "Oh Gu, what are you thinking? Precisely because of fear, I cannot advance, thus I need courage. But you are telling me that to obtain courage, I need to move forward first."

While they were talking, a Gu worm flew over.

"Is it courage Gu?" Ren Zu was overjoyed, before feeling disappointment.

Because this Immortal Gu was not courage Gu, it was love Gu.

Sometimes, love comes to you on its own.

Love Gu said: "Oh human, I can smell hope and fear from you, as love, they are my food."

Ren Zu was overjoyed: "You can take fear away, but hope is mine, I cannot give it to you."

Love Gu refused: "Only hope and fear can nourish me together, that is how I survive. Oh human, then I can only stay by your side."

Ren Zu did not have any good feelings towards love Gu, he was not very willing, but love Gu said: "Don't chase me away, with me around, you can summon courage Gu."

Indeed, after Ren Zu called out, courage Gu flew to his side a while later.

"Ah, this is the aura of love. Oh, and fear too." Courage Gu landed in Ren Zu's heart with much satisfaction.

It was actually good friends with fear Gu, the two were playing as they flew around Ren Zu's heart.

Fear and courage are often within one's grasp.

Ren Zu had courage, his fear dissipated by a huge amount, he could move on again.

"Oh Ren Zu, I want to thank you, you are the reason why I broke free from fear." Before Ren Zu left, the beastman came to him.

"I have two Gu here, one is loyalty, one is betrayal. Choose one, this will be my token of gratitude towards you." The beastman said, taking out two Gu worms, holding one in each hand.

Ren Zu did not know which to choose.

Love Gu said: "Choose loyalty, you already have fear."

Cognition Gu said instead: "Go choose betrayal, you already have courage."

Ren Zu was troubled, he asked the beastman: "Can I take a look at them first?"

The beastman said: "Of course."

Ren Zu thus obtained both loyalty Gu and betrayal Gu, but to think that after he took them, loyalty Gu turned into betrayal Gu, and betrayal Gu turned into loyalty Gu.

Ren Zu was puzzled.

The beastman explained: "Loyalty to others is betrayal to oneself, betraying others is loyalty to yourself."

Self Gu spoke at this time: "Oh human, choose betrayal. Since you are walking on your own road, you will need to betray others, and even betray yourself."

Ren Zu made up his mind, he chose betrayal Gu.

The beastman kept loyalty Gu, before leaving, he told Ren Zu: "Oh Ren Zu, you have betrayal now, you cannot go to a place called 'Care'. At that place, betrayal will harm you, but if you do not 'Care', then betrayal cannot harm you at all."

Ren Zu nodded: "Thank you beastman, I will remember your advice."

...

In Crazed Demon Cave.

At Pang Shan's will, Immortal Gu Care flew out of his immortal aperture.

He said to Not Immortal: "Even though I have care Immortal Gu, it is not enough."

Not Immortal stroked his heard: "I understand!"

He took out an Immortal Gu.

"This is Immortal Gu 'No'."

The two Immortal Gu were different in appearance, they floated towards Fang Yuan.

Pang Shan and Not Immortal took out their respective wills, as well as their own red date immortal essence.

"We will trouble you to bring these to Domination Immortal. By then, he will have no lingering worries, he would not be restricted by the backlashes of alliance agreements." Not Immortal said to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was a little stunned

Two rank seven Immortal Gu were lent out like this, they were so casual about it, was their relationship with Chu Du really that close, or were they influenced by Crazed Demon Cave?

Two wills carrying Immortal Gu and immortal essence entered Fang Yuan's sleeves.

Fang Yuan said goodbye as he asked before leaving: "May I ask both seniors, if I want to borrow these Immortal Gu in the future, what should I do?"

Pang Shan did not speak, he opened his eyes slightly before shutting them, falling into deep sleep again.

Not Immortal smiled and did not speak.

Fang Yuan sighed internally, he turned around and left.

Not Immortal did not send him off.

But Fang Yuan had already memorized the route, he managed to move along the route without any danger.

Chapter 1176: Crazed Demon Agreement

The route to leave Crazed Demon Cave was much shorter than going in.

Some days later, Fang Yuan arrived in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

"To think that Chu Du also has a super Gu formation, and has even set it up to transport Gu Immortals in and out of Hei Fan grotto-heaven." Fang Yuan felt admiration towards Chu Du's foresight and preparation.

This was his backup.

As long as he set up a teleportation Gu formation in the outside world that was not discovered, Chu Du and the others would not be trapped in Hei Fan grotto-heaven by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

This showed that even though Chu Du resisted Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and had a strong attitude, he was not just being rash and reckless.

"Brother Liu, you have arrived." Chu Du was already standing outside the formation, waiting for Fang Yuan.

Seeing Fang Yuan, he showed joy on his face.

Fang Yuan sighed: "Fate toys with people, if there were no mishaps, Hei Fan grotto-heaven would have already become a peaceful paradise."

Fang Yuan looked around, only to see that Hei Fan grotto-heaven had rising smoke and flames, beast growls could be heard, there were large pits on the ground, fierce battles were happening far away.

Chu Du introduced at an appropriate timing: "Hei Fan grotto-heaven has huge space, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is continuously sending in desolate beasts to invade, but I have already invited several experts, they are staying guard at different locations, while I am here to prevent Heavenly Lord Bai Zu from coming in personally."

Fang Yuan had a solemn expression, his gaze held deep meaning: "Brother Chu, you have heavy responsibilities, I did not disappoint you, I brought what you need."

Saying this, Fang Yuan waved his sleeves as two wills flew out from them.

The wills flew to the air and turned into the figures of Not Immortal and Pang Shan, from the outside, one could vaguely see the immortal essence and Immortal Gu that they were carrying.

Fang Yuan did not keep these two wills in his own immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture could not be exposed.

In this current situation, the wills of Not Immortal and Pang Shan could not be targeted.

Along the way, Fang Yuan had thought of harming these two wills and taking those extremely precious Immortal Gu for himself.

But this was very unlikely.

The main reason was that Fang Yuan had an alliance agreement, once he attacked, it would activate, he would die from the backlash.

Secondly, these two Immortal Gu were not easy to snatch, because the Gu Immortal's will was not just carrying the Immortal Gu, the Immortal Gu itself inside it was filled with will. With just a thought, these two Immortal Gu would self-detonate.

"Thank you." Chu Du said as he kept Pang Shan's will in his immortal aperture directly.

This small detail was noticed by Fang Yuan, he noted it internally.

The immortal aperture was the basis of a Gu Immortal, it was the most reliable source of resources, one would not expose it to outsiders normally. Chu Du seemed to greatly trust Pang Shan.

Chu Du said to Not Immortal's will: "Not Immortal, you can stay with this ally of mine."

Not Immortal stroked his beard, smiling at Fang Yuan: "My main body guessed correctly, you really chose this person."

"What do you mean?" Fang Yuan asked, he was filled with questions and suspicions on this trip to Crazed Demon Cave.

Chu Du explained: "I will summarize it. Crazed Demon Cave is one of the ten great fierce areas in Northern Plains on the surface, but it was actually specially created by Limitless Demon Venerable in his later years, to pursue the secrets of eternal life."

"Limitless Demon Venerable refined the legendary derivation Gu, he hid inside Crazed Demon Cave and did experiments and Gu refinements on it, hoping to reach a breakthrough."

Limitless Demon Venerable!

Eternal life!

Fang Yuan's eyes shined brightly: "Did Limitless Demon Venerable succeed?"

Not Immortal's will shook his head: "We are unclear on that. Limitless Demon Venerable's whereabouts are not listed clearly in historical records. The conclusion is, he went missing mysteriously, whether he succeeded or failed, we do not know."

"However." Not Immortal's will said: "What Chu Du said is true. Crazed Demon Cave was indeed where Limitless Demon Venerable stayed in his later years, derivation Gu is currently at the deepest layer of Crazed Demon Cave. Around derivation Gu, there is a huge super Gu formation set up."

"Derivation Gu..." Fang Yuan muttered.

This Gu was extremely famous, not just Gu Immortals, even almost all Gu Masters knew about it.

The reason was that it was inside \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Towards the end of \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, after the seven heavens broke, Ren Zu's ten children died one by one, and Ren Zu was about to die of old age. But at the end, Ren Zu gathered the corpses of his ten children and sacrificed himself, all entering the stomach of derivation Gu. Derivation Gu's stomach burst, exploding as the light of life spread across the land, creating the first batch of mortals. These mortals did not have Ren Zu or the ten children's aptitude, but they could cultivate after awakening their aperture.

Humanity thus grew and developed, forming today's size. During this process, ten rank nine venerables were born, each of them led their own era and left deep marks on the world.

Eventually, today's situation in the five regions was formed.

"Limitless Demon Venerable actually obtained derivation Gu, was he trying to imitate Ren Zu, and create the human race again?" Fang Yuan sighed in shock as he asked.

"That's not the case." Not Immortal answered: "Ren Zu created humanity, it is an unparalleled method of human path. Limitless Demon Venerable, however, cultivated rule path, he wanted to use derivation Gu to derive new dao marks, eventually using these dao marks as clues to reach eternal life."

"Using derivation Gu to derive dao marks?" Fang Yuan was shocked.

Chu Du nodded: "Even though this is the estimation of the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics, Crazed Demon Cave has physical proof of it. The demonic sounds inside Crazed Demon Cave were the result of Limitless Demon Venerable's super Gu formation. His motive was not to make all the living beings go crazy, that was only the side effect, his true motive was to cause changes in the dao marks in their bodies, to create brand new dao marks."

"So that's it!" Fang Yuan's mind shook, he thought about it and asked: "Does that really work?"

Not Immortal followed up: "The deeper you go into Crazed Demon Cave, the stronger the demonic sounds. Among chaotic dao marks, new dao marks do indeed form. But these new dao marks will be transferred to the deepest layer due to the super Gu formation, us Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics want to get through these obstacles of dao marks and enter the core of the super Gu formation, to control derivation Gu and make this super Gu formation work for us!"

"Precisely as a result, the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics need my strength." Chu Du said.

Fang Yuan realized at once, he had a guess.

As expected, Chu Du's following words affirmed his guess.

"At the lowest layer, all sorts of dao marks of all paths are present. The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics have their own specialties, but their strength path attainment is below mine. Thus, they invited me, wanting to use my understanding towards strength path and methods to resolve their obstacles in terms of strength path dao marks."

Not Immortal's will sighed: "It is not about helping us Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics, it is about helping yourselves. We, the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics have been in Crazed Demon Cave for hundreds of years. Even though we are making progress, it is not evident. The secret of eternal life, it is not something the three of us can obtain with just our power. We need you, and you need us, only by working together can we obtained the fruits of Limitless Demon Venerable's labor."

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics went through hundreds of years without much progress, they could only recruit new people to help.

Chu Du was their target.

And Chu Du thought that Fang Yuan was suitable, because of Reckless Savage's true meaning, Chu Du felt that he was going to sustain his cooperation with Fang Yuan for a long time, they had to obtain deeper connections.

Thus, he gave the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics' token to Fang Yuan and asked him to find them.

Among the three eccentrics, Not Immortal and Pang Shan saw Chu Du's intent, thus they were very warm to Fang Yuan.

"Chu Du, you are a strength path great expert, right now in Northern Plains, no, in the five regions, you are an authoritative figure of strength path. It is not strange that you were chosen by the three seniors of Crazed Demon Cave, but what abilities do I have to be chosen?" Fang Yuan asked.

Chu Du laughed loudly: "Brother Liu, don't be so humble. You are a transformation path rank seven Gu Immortal, you can disguise as a rank six without showing any flaws. I saw your tribulation, even though I only took a look, the power of the calamity was immense, it shows your deep foundation. Looking over the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world, in terms of transformation path achievement, hardly anyone can compete with you."

"What? He is a rank seven Gu Immortal?" Hearing Chu Du's words, even Not Immortal's will was shocked.

He assessed Fang Yuan again: "Impressive! His transformation path foundation is truly deep, be it my main body or Pang Shan's main body, we could not tell."

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly.

This was mainly due to his immortal killer move familiar face.

Of course, there was also the impression left on Chu Du by the calamities.

Familiar face was indeed a transformation path immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan knew: even though his transformation path attainment level was not low, his foundation was superficial. He was relying on familiar face to make others misunderstand him.

But this misunderstanding was quite good.

Fang Yuan thus used familiar face to raise his aura from rank six to rank seven.

Not Immortal felt Fang Yuan's aura change and stared with wide opened eyes, completely shocked.

"I was not intending to deceive you, but I was going into a dangerous place, I had to conceal myself for survival, I hope you will not blame me." Fang Yuan apologized to Not Immortal's will, speaking politely and having a sincere tone.

Not Immortal's will quickly waved his hand: "I have learned much. Indeed, Domination Immortal has good foresight."

His attitude had changed drastically.

Interaction between Gu Immortals mostly depended on strength.

Chu Du was solemn: "Brother Liu, are you willing to join us in the search for the secret of eternal life, Limitless Demon Venerable's achievement in his later years?"

"Of course I am willing." Fang Yuan was similarly solemn.

Not Immortal's will stroked his beard: "Then after this battle, can Brother Liu go to Crazed Demon Cave, we will set the Crazed Demon Agreement!"

"Alright." Fang Yuan replied curtly.

"Next, Not Immortal can follow Brother Liu." Chu Du arranged.

This arrangement was very sincere!

If Chu Du kept Not Immortal and Pang Shan's will, he would have both Immortal Gu 'No' and 'Care'. He would be able to break his agreement without facing backlash.

But if he separated both Immortal Gu, 'no' Immortal Gu would be in Fang Yuan's hand, while care Immortal Gu would be with Chu Du, not only can it dispel Fang Yuan's suspicions, it would also let Fang Yuan feel the sincerity of Chu Du and the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics.

However, Fang Yuan waved his hand, saying something overbearing: "If both of you can trust me, I will keep 'no' Immortal Gu. Not Immortal's will and immortal essence can be kept by brother Chu."

Not Immortal's will was dazed before stroking his beard.

Chu Du laughed: "Brother Liu, oh, you are seriously vigilant. Alright, we will go with that."

Chapter 1177: Contest Over Hei Fan Grotto-heaven (1/3)

Several days later, Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Stiff horse hooves stomped on the ground, a black desolate beast horse was charging towards Fang Yuan while running like the wind.

Fang Yuan sighed internally.

He could have dodged, but a trench was behind him, inside the trench, there were the multicolored guts that Chu Du had placed before.

After placing these multicolored guts, they needed to absorb enough earth qi and nutrients before they could be relocated again. If they were forcefully moved, they would be destroyed.

Thus, a lot of the resources in Hei Fan grotto-heaven were moved back into his own immortal aperture by Chu Du. But some of the resources like the multicolored guts could not be taken away in the short term.

Ever since Fang Yuan brought the two Immortal Gu to Chu Du, he was asked to defend this place, to protect the multicolored guts from harm.

Of course, his services were not free.

Chu Du had already promised Fang Yuan that in the end, he would give half of the multicolored guts that were left to Fang Yuan, as payment.

Flying bear transformation!

Fang Yuan's body shined with dazzling light.

After the light faded, he turned into a huge white bear, using his firm chest to block the charge of the desolate beast horse.

Flying bear Fang Yuan took five to six steps back, almost falling to the ground.

But the desolate beast horse went to a standstill, shaking its head as it felt dizzy.

"Nice strength." Fang Yuan said, the pain in his chest made him grind his teeth, but the words he said turned into the growling of the bear.

Flying bear Fang Yuan breathed roughly for a few seconds, seeing that the desolate beast horse was still dizzy, he pounced at it.

Boom!

Dust clouds rose, the surrounding scenery shook.

Flying bear Fang Yuan slammed the desolate beast horse to the ground, raising his huge bear paws as he struck at the horse.

The horse was crying out in pain, struggling under Fang Yuan's body.

It had great strength, but Fang Yuan was unmoved, he suppressed the horse firmly.

"Thankfully, I added flying bear strength Gu into my flying bear transformation killer move, I have the strength of an actual flying bear. Otherwise, I would not be able to suppress this desolate beast horse."

Fang Yuan felt secretly glad as he acted more quickly.

In a while, the desolate beast horse had saliva foaming out from its mouth, its eyes rolled backwards as it fainted.

Fang Yuan chuckled, deactivating the killer move as he turned back to human. He next opened his immortal aperture, storing the desolate beast horse into his sovereign immortal aperture.

"This is the third desolate beast." Fang Yuan thought to himself, having a distracted gaze.

He was at the rear. Dao marks were more abundant here, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would not choose to send his desolate beasts here, it was difficult for them to reach this place and not worth it.

After Fang Yuan learned about the secret of Crazed Demon Cave, he expressed his willingness to join in, he and Chu Du's relationship progressed further.

In order to defend his benefits, Chu Du sent Fang Yuan here to guard the place.

Even though the battle was intense, Fang Yuan had an easy time.

These last few days, the desolate beasts that had gone past the front lines numbered to three, two desolate beast horses and one desolate beast shark fin wolf.

Fang Yuan treated them as his practice partners for transformation path.

He killed the first two, he only captured the desolate beast horse from earlier.

"The desolate beast horse earlier had no shadow, it should be the famous shadowless horse of Northern Plains."

The shadowless horse had no shadow. This was an obvious trait, even though Fang Yuan had not seen this desolate beast before, he could recognize it.

Even though the shadowless horse was a desolate beast, it was quite a rare one.

It was not commonly sold in treasure yellow heaven.

Mainly because shadowless horses were low in numbers to begin with.

This shadowless horse was Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's desolate beast, after Fang Yuan kept it into his immortal aperture, he immediately used perceivable dao Immortal Gu to inspect it.

Indeed, Fang Yuan realized that on the shadowless horse's body, other than dark path and light path dao marks, there were also many enslavement path dao marks.

After several attempts, Fang Yuan realized he could not get rid of these enslavement path dao marks, thus, he gave up and killed the shadowless horse.

This shadowless horse was enslaved by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, placing it in his immortal aperture would only cause it to destroy the environment.

He might as well kill the shadowless horse and sell the horse bones and flesh in treasure yellow heaven for some profits.

A living shadowless horse had greater value, but it was Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's property, others could not enslave it.

Other Gu Immortals were not idiots, they would not buy this problematic horse.

Furthermore, selling this shadowless horse openly would naturally be discovered by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he might use his relationships to buy this horse indirectly.

Not only would he gain the attention of a rank eight Gu Immortal, he would also be strengthening his enemy. Thus, Fang Yuan killed it.

After cutting up this shadowless horse and processing it, Fang Yuan put up a portion of it into treasure yellow heaven for sale.

He realized that these last few days, the two desolate beast corpses that he tossed into treasure yellow heaven had almost no popularity.

These two desolate beast corpses were taken out from Crazed Demon Cave, the monkey king corpse and tree python corpse.

Before selling them, Fang Yuan had used perceivable dao Immortal Gu to inspect them.

He realized that the monkey king and tree python corpses had all sorts of dao marks. Normally speaking, desolate beasts would only have dao marks of one specific path.

Obviously, the demonic sounds in Crazed Demon Cave had caused this situation.

The demonic sounds were created by Limitless Demon Venerable's super Gu formation, it could make the listener go berserk, while also transforming their body's dao marks into all sorts of strange dao marks.

Fang Yuan thought about it, he retrieved these two desolate beast corpses and placed them back into his sovereign immortal aperture.

The longer he placed them in treasure yellow heaven, the more fees he would incur, it was not worth the price.

Other than these desolate beast corpses, Fang Yuan also brought back large numbers of mortal Gu. Among which, day Gu, month Gu, and year Gu were the highest in number. Other than those, there were Gu worms of other varieties.

Ever since Fang Yuan obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, he had been purchasing these mortal Gu in treasure yellow heaven. When he used a time path immortal killer move, it expended a lot of them.

Other than day, month, and year mortal Gu, Fang Yuan's greatest need in terms of mortal Gu was self will Gu.

But self will Gu was very rare, Fang Yuan mainly asked the hairy man Gu Masters in Lang Ya Sect to refine them, expending his sect contribution points.

Fang Yuan had been asking in treasure yellow heaven if anyone was selling heavenly crystals.

Up until now, he had only found two.

One was a rank eight Gu Immortal, they wanted to trade with materials, but Fang Yuan did not have what they wanted.

The other was rank six, due to a fortuitous encounter, they obtained half a piece of heavenly crystal, they wanted to sell it since they did not need it.

Fang Yuan wanted to buy it, but a Gu Immortal who wanted heavenly crystals even more appeared, buying it with three times the usual price.

Fang Yuan thought about it and gave up. Even though he had a lot of resources, the fifth earthly calamity was coming at that time. It was not worth it for that tiny heavenly crystal.

"Oh?" At this time, Fang Yuan suddenly received Chu Du's message, he asked him to reinforce Li Si Chun, the situation over there was very dangerous, he needed backup.

These last few days, this was the first message that Fang Yuan received.

He immediately went to the battlefield.

There, Li Si Chun and Immortal Wang were already in a tough battle.

A group of desolate beast wolves were encircling them, they were huge in numbers, there were a hundred of them.

But Fang Yuan was not surprised.

He had obtained much intel from Chu Du.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had an immortal killer move, it could create clones of desolate beasts to form a clone army.

There would only be one actual desolate beast, but if it could not be found, these clones would quickly replenish themselves endlessly.

Each desolate beast had one figure of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu seated on them, they were clones as well.

"Then, which one is the main body?" Fang Yuan frowned, at the next moment, he used myriad self.

Countless strength path phantoms filled the sky as they charged at the wolf group.

"It's Liu Guan Yi!" Li Si Chun sensed as he cried out in joy.

Immortal Wang snorted coldly, last time, Fang Yuan made him bait, his impression regarding Fang Yuan was at rock bottom. Right now, even though Fang Yuan was here to help, he was not grateful.

The myriad self army and the wolf group tangled together.

Two breaths of time later, the myriad self army broke apart, they were almost completely killed by the wolf group.

Matched against Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's cloning killer move, Fang Yuan's myriad self really paled in comparison.

Myriad self had huge potential, it was an immortal killer move combining strength path and enslavement path, but as his opponents got stronger, its usefulness was falling drastically.

In the past, the myriad self army could fight. But now, it had become Fang Yuan's method of concealing his true body.

Even though they had quantity, they lacked quality and battle strength.

Myriad self giant hand!

Only after Fang Yuan used myriad self first style was there a change in the situation.

Against the strength path giant hand, the desolate beast wolves could barely resist.

Snowy Mountain blessed land, first peak.

The refinement path Gu formation was activated, shining lights were enveloping the peak of the mountain, like a miniature sun.

"Third time." Lady Wan Shou breathed in deeply, she was holding onto a condensed lightning ball as she got closer to Ma Hong Yun who was in the formation.

Ma Hong Yun shouted: "No! No! Let me off! I am going to die, I will die!"

The lightning ball entered his chest.

Clap clap clap.

Countless sparks appeared on his body, Ma Hong Yun's eyes were turning as the whites were exposed, he no longer leaked out saliva, but blood instead.

He fainted again, after a while, the lightning vanished.

"I failed again." Lady Wan Shou's vision turned dark, an intense dizziness almost made her collapse to the ground.

She forced herself to continue, disregarding her injuries and healing Ma Hong Yun instead.

Ma Hong Yun had to be alive for the lightning refinement to work.

"Hmm? This guy's cultivation level actually rose by one rank." During the process of healing, Lady Wan Shou discovered an anomaly.

"Is it because of the lightning refinement? Indeed, some relic Gu were used, it can raise the Gu Master's cultivation level."

"Dear, are you alright?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu arrived at this time.

"No need to worry." Lady Wan Shou was still pale, but she smiled to Old Ancestor Xue Hu: "I just need to rest for a while to recover."

Chapter 1178: Contest Over Hei Fan Grotto-heaven (2/3)

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

The desolate beast wolf group that numbered to a hundred was charging towards them.

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu stood side by side, having solemn expressions.

They looked at each other before using their strongest technique again, immortal killer move —— Wind Thunder Roar!

Bam...

The wind and lightning pillar swept the battlefield, at once, the earth shook, the sky trembled, few desolate beast wolves were left, they had suffered immense damage.

Fang Yuan and the others were right beside Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu, their expressions changed.

Every time they saw wind thunder roar, they felt their hearts shaking, such battle strength was truly at the peak of rank seven. Those desolate beast wolves were mostly clones, even weaker than their true bodies, they could not withstand wind thunder roar.

Even two true bodies died. The final one had been lucky enough to survive this wind thunder roar because it was at the back of the group.

"Kill it, we cannot let this true body escape. Otherwise, in a few hours, it will have another group of clones protecting it again!" Gu Immortal Wei Ming shouted, pouncing at it.

This Gu Immortal's eyes were shut, he was a blind man. He had rank seven cultivation level and incredible battle strength. He became blind on purpose as he pursued battle strength.

"Be careful, there is a fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf!" At the next moment, Immortal Wang shouted frantically.

Wei Ming's body froze, at that moment, a fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf appeared out of nowhere, its sharp fangs were about to bite Wei Ming.

Wei Ming snorted coldly, his body retreated backwards towards the left like an illusory shadow.

The fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf bit, but it missed by an inch, its sharp teeth did not land on Wei Ming.

Wei Ming broke out in cold sweat, suddenly saying: "Oh no!"

At the next moment, the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf opened its mouth as a lump of green wind shot towards Wei Ming like a plasma cannon.

Wei Ming's defenses lasted for a short while before they were torn apart, his entire body was shredded into countless pieces of flesh.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone stood arrogantly on the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf's head, he had a cold expression as Immortal Gu aura emanated from him.

"You ran away quickly, but next time, you will not be so lucky." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu said coldly.

"So close, so close, thankfully, I used my body replacement killer move!" The real Wei Ming showed himself, he had managed to escape.

"This happened again." The immortals' gazes focused on Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, they had heavy hearts.

The fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf was an ancient desolate beast, it had rank seven battle strength. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone could use Immortal Gu, coordinating with the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf. He would observe the situation and use the Immortal Gu at appropriate times, because of that, their combined battle strength was many times higher!

At the start, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was sending large numbers of desolate beasts to invade Hei Fan grotto-heaven. But now, he gained a deeper understanding of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he could use desolate beasts and clones to create battle opportunities, to even send in ancient desolate beasts.

Every ancient desolate beast was accompanied by a clone of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. This combination had appeared many times already, it was gradually changing the battle situation.

Immortal Wang immediately turned into the falling star hound, saying human words: "Brother Hao and Brother Chou, quickly retreat. This fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf has hidden itself, it probably is attempting to target you two."

Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu had pale faces, they were very weak.

Wind thunder roar was powerful, but using this move had a huge price.

For the following period of time, Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen would have reduced battle strength, their usefulness would fall drastically.

This contest over Hei Fan grotto-heaven had been ongoing for days. Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu's wind thunder roar was a powerful tool, especially useful against desolate beast groups.

All the Gu Immortals agreed on this.

Thus, for the eventual victory, the Gu Immortals were intentionally protecting the lives of Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu.

Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen also understood this, they immediately retreated.

"I will escort you." Li Si Chun flew to them.

Fang Yuan, Immortal Wang, and Wei Ming were left.

"Quickly settle this ancient desolate beast, about three thousand li away, another ancient desolate beast has appeared." At this time, Chu Du sent them a message.

"I will block it from the front, the two of you find a chance to kill it!" Immortal Wang howled, turning into the falling star hound to face the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf.

Fang Yuan and Wei Ming cooperated, one flew into the sky while the other went to the back, attacking at the same time.

An intense battle ensued.

Immortal Wang was temporarily matched against it, Fang Yuan found a chance and flying sword Immortal Gu flew over.

Ding!

With a loud sound, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone used his Immortal Gu and blocked it.

"Use an immortal killer move, what can an Immortal Gu do on its own? Woof!" When Immortal Wang felt anxious, he would subconsciously bark like a dog.

"What do you know?" Fang Yuan sneered in disdain.

At the next moment, Wei Ming attacked, a light path immortal killer move destroyed Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone.

It turned out, Fang Yuan had attacked on purpose to draw the attention of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone, so that Wei Ming could find a chance to attack.

As they continued to fight, the Gu Immortals in Hei Fan grotto-heaven started to develop some coordination.

"They are just clones, they have limited intelligence. But this type of Immortal Gu usage is truly incredible!" Fang Yuan sighed internally.

He had already felt this many times.

Destroying the Heavenly Lord Bai Zu clone did not destroy the Immortal Gu. It seemed like the Immortal Gu was also a clone that was with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone.

It was unknown how Heavenly Lord Bai Zu managed to do that.

Thus, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's strength was only slightly weakened, he did not suffer much losses.

Next, the three immortals attacked the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf.

This ancient desolate beast was covered with dao marks, it had incredible defense. Fang Yuan used flying sword Immortal Gu but could only puncture its skin and fur. After piercing deeply into its flesh, it could not move anymore. Even the immortal killer move sword mark targeting death was inefficient, a lot of its power was negated by the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf's dao marks.

Thankfully, without the help of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone, the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf's intelligence alone could not match the three immortals.

During this period, many distorted shadows had appeared in the sky, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was attempting to send in more clones to help the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf.

But Fang Yuan and the rest discovered them in time and attacked, preventing the Heavenly Lord clones from reaching the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf.

Minutes later, this fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf was killed and cut into pieces by Fang Yuan and the rest, they split up the flesh into three portions evenly among themselves.

The death of an ancient desolate beast was quite a loss to Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

But in this situation, in order to take down Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he had to continue!

Fang Yuan and the others had severe losses too, especially Fang Yuan, his green grape immortal essence expenditure was huge.

"We have been fighting a lot these last days, if this continues, my green grape immortal essence will be used up." Fang Yuan showed no expression, but he was getting anxious internally.

The other Gu Immortals were rank seven, they used red date immortal essence to activate rank seven Immortal Gu, it was fitting.

But Fang Yuan used green grape immortal essence, it was very hard and inefficient.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan had good finances, he sold desolate beast and ancient desolate beast corpses from time to time, sustaining his expenditure.

After killing this fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf, the three immortals went to the next battlefield, they had no time to rest.

The situation was getting worse.

Some days ago, Fang Yuan could still hide inside the trench and guard the multicolored guts.

But recently, he had to go around helping out the others.

Right now, he was like a firefighter, he could not rest, he had to travel and help out the different battlefields.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body was blocked by Chu Du, but he had incredible methods, he continued to send in ancient desolate beasts and desolate beasts, it caused the situation in Hei Fan grotto-heaven to tilt in his favor.

A moment later, Fang Yuan and the rest arrived.

It was a heavenly dragon, it had seven claws and a terrifying dragon head, it was an ancient desolate beast.

Someone was already fighting the heavenly dragon, in order to defend Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Chu Du spent a lot of funds getting more Gu Immortal experts to help him, other than Immortal Wang's group.

This female Gu Immortal, Sang Qing Qu, was one of them.

Her path was very special, it was actually theft path!

This was the path created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, there were few inheritances regarding it.

Sang Qing Qu was at a disadvantage, she was unable to hold much longer, even though she had stolen a lot of mortal Gu from the heavenly dragon's body, it had little effect on the enemy.

Fang Yuan and the rest quickly went to help, attacking the ancient desolate beast heavenly dragon.

This time, they were not as lucky as last time.

After spending a lot of effort, the immortals finally killed Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone.

Killing the heavenly dragon took multiple times as long as the last beast, because the heavenly dragon could fly and was very fast, it was not easy to hunt.

After killing this heavenly dragon, Fang Yuan's mood became grimmer.

In the battle, his immortal essence expenditure was several times that of before. Currently, his usage was greatly exceeding his gain in immortal essence stones. At this rate, in a few days, he would be out of immortal essence.

The Gu Immortals gathered together and split the heavenly dragon corpse, when Chu Du spoke: "Quick! The battle earlier was a decoy by Heavenly Lord, he has already planted a field of desolate plant snow willows here, we have to get rid of them, once Heavenly Lord gets a foothold in here, the consequences will be severe."

Fang Yuan and the rest noticed how dangerous the situation was, they did not dare to wait, they acted immediately.

A moment later, they arrived at the scene, the situation was far more severe than they had expected.

Not only was there a field of desolate plant snow willows, there were a hundred ice spike divine apes to guard them. Snow willows had an abundance of snow path dao marks, the ice spike divine ape was also ice path, the two complemented each other, and countless Heavenly Lord clones were moving around the snow willow forest, setting up Gu formations.

"We have to destroy this camp, the longer we drag on, the greater his advantage." Chu Du said: "If there is no other way, I will act myself!"

"You should stay there and defend against Heavenly Lord. If his main body comes in, we are all finished." Hao Zhen quickly responded.

He and Chou Lao Wu had also arrived, even though he had not recovered, the situation was dire, they had to risk their lives.

At the next moment, six Gu Immortals split up and charged towards the snow willow forest, engaging in an intense battle!

Chapter 1179: Contest Over Hei Fan Grotto-heaven (3/3)

"Huff, huff, huff..."

Fang Yuan floated in the air, breathing roughly as he looked at the battlefield.

An intense battle had ended.

The battlefield was completely deformed, there were many pits with mangled corpses of ice spike divine apes inside, flames that were created with fire path killer moves were still burning quietly. There was frost mixed with blood, snapped bones and flesh, as well as leaves from the desolate plant snow willows.

The Gu Immortals were either injured or dead.

They were all injured, but the one that died was the theft path female Gu Immortal.

She had not been killed by the heavenly dragon, but was killed by the cooperation of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clones when she rushed to assist in the battle, losing her life.

Fang Yuan was also injured.

His left lung was punctured by an ice spike, an icicle with the size of a javelin was still stabbed into his chest.

His lower limbs were covered in a thick layer of frost, much of his flesh had already gone necrotic.

The sovereign immortal body had a huge advantage, that was the non-conflicting dao marks. But this was also a major flaw. Once Fang Yuan was hit by an attack that penetrated his defenses, he would take the damage fully, the attacks would not be weakened by the dao marks in his body.

In this battle, Fang Yuan learned deeply about the weak point of the sovereign immortal body due to this trait.

"My defensive killer move is still too weak."

"Blood asset Immortal Gu is still recovering, I cannot use bloodstained conqueror's robe. My time path defensive methods are not exemplary either."

Even though Fang Yuan obtained Hei Fan's true inheritance, the true core Immortal Gu, Years Flow Like Water, was sealed. This Immortal Gu had a huge flaw, once its aura was leaked, it would draw immemorial year beasts to it.

Once something of rank eight battle strength entered Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, he would definitely lose, he would only be able to leave his body as a soul and give up on the sovereign immortal body.

Hei Fan's true inheritance had very outstanding defensive methods, but they used Years Flow Like Water as the core.

Fang Yuan's current defensive killer move used year Gu, the effect was weaker. It was what Hei Fan used in his earlier days. When he reached rank seven, he stopped using it.

"Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is an enslavement path rank eight indeed, truly formidable!"

"Even though he is outside the grotto-heaven, and only using his clones to battle, he can still fight to this extent, I am truly inferior."

"And the distortion of space to send desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts into the grotto-heaven, it is truly extraordinary!"

In this battle, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu sent in a hundred ice spike divine apes and a large number of desolate plant snow willows. During the process of fighting, distorted shadows appeared constantly, even though the Gu Immortals desperately tried to block them, two icefall divine apes still managed to get in.

Ice spike divine ape.

Icefall divine ape.

The two were closely related.

The former was a desolate beast, it had jade green eyes with frosty azure pupils, the hairs on its body were like icicles all over it. The latter was an ancient desolate beast, its body was like snow, its eyes were bloodshot, its fur was like icicles stabbing towards the sky.

Fang Yuan was familiar with the ice spike divine ape, long ago, Lang Ya blessed land had one.

Later, Fang Yuan borrowed it to defend Hu Immortal blessed land, he defended against a wave of attacks from Immortal Crane Sect.

After that, the ice spike divine ape died during the battle to defend Lang Ya blessed land.

Fang Yuan had also fought against the icefall divine ape.

That was during Hei Lou Lan's immortal ascension, the tribulation in the northern icy plain, because of Reckless Savage's true meaning, it turned into the divine ape.

"Right now it seems, the icefall divine ape created from the tribulation cannot match a real divine ape in battle strength."

"Actually, if these desolate beasts and desolate plants are all there is to it, it is not difficult to deal with even though it is troublesome. Most importantly, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clones are manipulating and controlling them, that makes a completely different story."

"Especially the desolate beasts and desolate plants, they form into troops and move as one. They have incredible battle strength when enslavement path killer moves are used, it is very shocking."

Fang Yuan recalled the entire battle, he could see how powerful a rank eight Gu Immortal was.

Even though his main body did not enter the battlefield, by just directing the battle in the grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan was not his match.

They were able to win in battle because all of the immortals gathered their strength.

"Such a miserable battle, if we were to fight a few more of those, my green grape immortal essence would be completely dried up."

"Year Gu has fallen in terms of years, I need to parallel refine it."

"Healing my injuries also consumed a lot of time and immortal essence."

Fang Yuan could not bear such expenditure.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's losses were more severe than Fang Yuan's.

Fighting up to this point, Chu Du's side had been relying on Hei Fan grotto-heaven, dragging on this battle into a deadlock, the two sides were truly in a battle of attrition.

The Gu Immortals expended their immortal essence, while Heavenly Lord Bai Zu expended the foundation in the grotto-heaven. Both sides could not back down, they were trying to see which would be unable to continue first.

The following battles became more intense.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's attempts might have failed, but there was an effect.

He had attempted to create temporary bases in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, after he stabilized a foothold, he sent in ancient desolate beasts, causing Chu Du's side to have much difficulty in defending.

Looking at the entire battle in Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had initially sent clones to attack the different resource points and target Chu Du's foundation. He succeeded.

Next, he sent in large numbers of desolate beasts and caused the battle to tilt in his favor.

Now, he changed his battle tactics, he built temporary bases and forced the Gu Immortals to attack him instead.

Even though Chu Du, Fang Yuan and the rest had the advantage in numbers, and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was just alone, he controlled the entire situation, suppressing Chu Du, Fang Yuan and the rest.

Even though Fang Yuan and the others resisted strongly, they could not stop the situation from tilting in Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's favor.

Both sides were persisting.

But Fang Yuan was the first to lose in attrition.

He was a rank seven Gu Immortal on the surface, but in truth, he had been using green grape immortal essence the entire time.

Chu Du's expression was quite ugly.

Especially when he was alone with Fang Yuan, he put away his front and showed an expression of worry.

He said to Fang Yuan: "I have already recruited all the people I could possible rope in."

"But this battle's eventual winner will be Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. Even though we did not fight against his main body, we are unable to challenge the foundation of a rank eight."

"The real key in deciding victory is not in this battlefield, but the Bai Zu tribe outside."

Chu Du was clear about the situation.

He and Fang Yuan had the same idea, after all, great minds think alike.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu himself had no weakness, his only weakness was the Bai Zu tribe that he had just recently created.

Chu Du's arrangements were taking effect in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Rumors were spread.

"Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is attacking Hei Fan grotto-heaven, if he succeeds in getting the place, his strength will rise to a new level."

"Even though Bai Zu tribe has just been built, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is holding it up, their only weakness is their weak foundation. Once Hei Fan grotto-heaven becomes Bai Zu tribe's territory, in decades, Bai Zu tribe will surpass every Huang Jin tribe."

"Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is a lone cultivator, he does not have Huang Jin bloodline, the strengthening of Bai Zu tribe is actually beneficial towards the survival of demonic and lone immortals."

...

All sorts of rumors and discussions were going on, the main topic was on Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's threat, and the emphasis that he was not a descendant of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's bloodline.

Not just this, there were some Gu Immortals pretending to be from Bai Zu tribe, causing trouble everywhere and provoking the super forces.

Bai Zu tribe's leader, Bai Zu Wei, had already died on the battlefield, and Bai Zu tribe's new leader did not have enough capability, he was facing huge trouble, he was telling Heavenly Lord Bai Zu about the difficulties and danger Bai Zu tribe was facing, and that they had enemies on all fronts.

But Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was unmoved.

He replied: "This is Chu Du's ploy. Chu Du is neither from the righteous path nor has the Huang Jin bloodline, if our Bai Zu tribe deals with him, those people from Huang Jin tribes would be most pleased."

"Chu Du let out these rumors and pretended to be us, purposely provoking those tribes, this is his scheme, it shows that he is weak now on the inside, only putting up a front."

"The other tribes are not idiots, they could tell what Chu Du was doing, but because of my deterrence as a rank eight, they did not dare to do anything."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu has excellent astuteness, he was clear of the situation, he was determined to take down Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

He had chosen the best timing.

Yao Huang and Old Ancestor Xue Hu were busy refining Gu. Five Elements Grandmaster was busy dealing with Longevity Heaven, and even though Prince Feng Xian was doing nothing on the surface, he was secretly retrieving blessed lands.

For Fang Yuan, it was becoming harder and harder to endure as time passed.

To increase his amount of green grape immortal essence, he had to start selling desolate beasts in treasure yellow heaven.

He originally had two spinefin star dragonfish, he sold them to replenish his immortal essence stones out of necessity.

This was starting to harm his immortal aperture's foundation.

Earlier, he had been in a positive feedback loop due to his financial management and growth, but now, he was facing a vicious downward cycle.

Undoubtedly, this was a warning signal.

"In terms of blessed land foundation, I surpass Chu Du, but green grape immortal essence is my greatest weakness, thus, I was the first to burn out among the immortals. It seems that after this battle, I need to advance to rank seven as soon as possible!"

The battle situation was becoming more intense, temporary camps were already being built, Chu Du had to act in person and destroy them all.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu chose very good timings, on multiple dangerous occasions, he nearly managed to arrive with his true body.

Fang Yuan secretly asked Lang Ya Sect for help.

He said to Lang Ya land spirit: This was the best chance to recruit Chu Du.

But Lang Ya land spirit caved in when faced against a rank eight Gu Immortal. He clearly expressed that Lang Ya Sect would not help. If something happened to Fang Yuan, he had to keep Lang Ya Sect a secret, if he revealed anything, the alliance agreement would kill him.

"Even though I can still hold on, I have thought about it, the battle result has been decided, there is no point in wasting more resources." Chu Du decided to give up. He did not conceal this thought from Fang Yuan, he looked for Fang Yuan to talk about it.

Fang Yuan had already been wanting to back out, he quickly agreed.

However, just as Chu Du and Fang Yuan were talking about their retreat plans, the commotion in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world changed.

All of the Huang Jin tribes, the righteous path super forces, united and wanted to pass judgment on Bai Zu tribe.

To think that at the final crucial moment, a change for the better had arrived!

Chapter 1180: Heaven and Human Path, Grandmaster Discusses Dao

Some days ago.

Longevity Heaven.

This was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's rank nine grotto-heaven! Golden light enveloped the Four Desolations, an azure hue shone over the Eight Extremities.

Four Desolations and Eight Extremities, these formed the terrain of Longevity Heaven, much like how sovereign immortal aperture had the nine heavens and five regions.

And at the heart of the Four Desolations, at the center of the Eight Extremities, an Immortal Gu House was shining in a profound white light, shooting towards the skies. It resonated with the entirety of Longevity Heaven, emitting a loud humming sound.

Rank eight Immortal Gu House, Calamity Luck Altar.

Three floors of round altars with multiple pillars holding it up, white jade railings and shining aurora.

Eight Gu Immortals in Longevity Heaven were standing at the center of the nine corners of Calamity Luck Altar, doing their best to concentrate in controlling the operations of Calamity Luck Altar.

At the center of Calamity Luck Altar, lightning was flashing, dragons were dancing, luck was steaming, as clouds enveloped the area.

A Gu Immortal's figure was seated on the ground, resisting the might of Calamity Luck Altar.

Around him, there was a ring, it was flying around and surrounding his body, emitting light in five colors.

"Five Elements Grandmaster, you might have rank eight cultivation level, but inside the Calamity Luck Altar, you cannot turn this around! I urge you to surrender, when our Four Desolation Immortals awaken, perhaps you might have a chance of survival." The leader of the eight Gu Immortals, Heaven Extremity, snorted and said.

It turned out that the Gu Immortal trapped in the center of Calamity Luck Altar was one of the five rank eight existences in Northern Plains — Five Elements Grandmaster!

Five Elements Grandmaster laughed loudly: "The rank eight Immortal Gu House is nothing impressive! You Eight Extremities have combined forces to manipulate it, after suppressing me for this long, even using the might of Longevity Heaven to try and kill me, but now, you have not even broken through the first layer of my five elements ring. Heaven Extremity, you have the face to ask me to surrender?"

Heaven Extremity sneered: "That is because you do not know the mystical power of Calamity Luck Altar! Its true ability is to reverse calamity and luck, turning calamity into luck, and luck into calamity. By interlinking calamity and luck, it becomes unceasing. This is the profundity of heaven and earth luck! As a mere lone cultivator, how can you possibly understand?"

Hearing the words heaven and earth luck, Five Elements Grandmaster's smugness vanished, disappearing from his face.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created luck path, his entire life's cultivation was summarized into three parts, self luck, all living being's luck, and heaven and earth luck.

Among which, heaven and earth luck was created during Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's later years, it was grand and deep, deciphering the mysteries of heaven and earth. Five Elements Grandmaster had stalled in his advancement now, he could not break through on his own, thus, he sneaked into Longevity Heaven and tried to steal the heaven and earth luck true inheritance.

But to think that even though the Four Desolation Immortals were asleep in Longevity Heaven, the defense still exceeded Five Elements Grandmaster's expectations.

After some fighting, Five Elements Grandmaster was trapped inside Calamity Luck Altar, he was suppressed by the Eight Extremities, unable to get free.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had three rank eight Immortal Gu Houses in his life, I've known about Calamity Luck Altar since long ago. But reversing calamity and luck, just what constitutes as reversing calamity and luck?" Five Elements Grandmaster thought for a moment before asking.

The Eight Extremities looked at each other, evidently surprised.

But soon, they reacted.

Heaven Extremity sighed internally: "I have long since heard that Five Elements Grandmaster has an incredible thirst towards knowledge, when he was mortal, he hid his identity and went around learning from different masters. After becoming a Gu Immortal, in order to obtain some experience and guidance from Gu Immortals, he was willing to be at their beck and call. This time, he actually asked his enemies for guidance inside the formation. He is truly passionate! However, an ignorant person fears nothing, if I inform him of the truth, I can strike a blow at his confidence and morale!"

Thinking of this, Heaven Extremity spoke: "Right now, the outcome has been decided, it is fine even if I tell you. Calamity Luck Altar was purposely left in Longevity Heaven by Ancestor Giant Sun, it was to defend Longevity Heaven. Reversing calamity and luck, we can turn calamities and tribulations into our own good luck. Right now, you came to invade Longevity Heaven, it was our human calamity. By using this Calamity Luck Altar, we can turn this difficulty into good luck, turning disaster into fortune. You will end up contributing to Longevity Heaven's eternal existence."

"Superb, brilliant!" Five Elements Grandmaster listened with shining eyes, he asked again: "If a human calamity is like this, then what about earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations?"

"We naturally reverse them as well, heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities do not cause any damage, they instead become nourishment for our Longevity Heaven." Heaven Extremity said proudly.

Five Elements Grandmaster had wide opened eyes: "Longevity Heaven is a rank nine grotto-heaven and has not absorbed any fragments of the immemorial nine heavens. By relying on Calamity Luck Altar, it can go through all of its calamities and tribulations?"

"Hahaha! You are already a rank eight Gu Immortal, but you do not even know about the origins of calamities and tribulations?" Heaven Extremity laughed in disdain.

Five Elements Grandmaster was not upset, he asked humbly: "I hope you can teach me, Heaven Extremity."

Heaven Extremity sensed Five Elements Grandmaster's earnest attitude and the disdain inside him vanished, turning into traces of admiration.

He sighed, answering: "Why do humans have calamities and tribulations? The truth is, not just humans, but desolate beasts and desolate plants also have them. Like the thousand snakes haze tree, it faces the tribulation lightning."

"The origin of calamities and tribulations is in the principles of heaven. Heaven takes away surpluses while replenishing deficits, it emphasizes on balance and maintains this over cycles. Any existence which breaks the cycle of balance will face calamities and tribulations."

"But humans possess the greatest intelligence. Thus, we are more of a threat than beasts or plants. Gu Immortals can manage their own small worlds, it draws wariness and attacks from heaven."

"What is calamity? What is luck?" Heaven Extremity suddenly asked.

Five Elements Grandmaster had a realization, he spoke immediately:" I understand. Heaven takes away surpluses while replenishing deficits, the so-called calamity takes away surpluses, while luck replenishes deficits."

Heaven Extremity raised his eyebrows: "You answered correctly, that is exactly the case! And my Ancestor Giant Sun was extremely talented, he created luck path. It targets the operations of the principles of heaven. Self luck true inheritance replenishes oneself. All living being's luck takes away others' surpluses to replenish oneself. While heaven and earth luck takes away heaven and earth's surpluses to replenish oneself."

"So that's it." Five Elements Grandmaster sighed deeply: "No wonder Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not enter Heavenly Court during his life."

Heavenly Court followed the will of heaven, and upholded justice for heaven.

Meanwhile, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path usurped the authority of heaven and earth. When nature operated according to the principles of heaven, and an individual was determined to be too strong and breaking the balance, it would generate calamities and tribulations to suppress them. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path avoided calamities and tribulations, and in the section of heaven and earth luck, it directly turned calamities and tribulations into fortuitous encounters. Heaven and earth suppresses me, it wants to take away my surpluses to replenish others' deficits, then I shall go ahead and take away heaven and earth's surpluses to replenish my own deficits!

As the saying goes, there is nothing to say if there were opposing objectives!

"If heaven cannot use calamities and tribulations to destroy Longevity Heaven, it will use human calamities to destroy it." Heaven Extremity continued: "And you, Five Elements Grandmaster, were subconsciously influenced by heaven's will, eventually becoming the human calamity that is here to destroy my Longevity Heaven! What a pity that you, a great rank eight, were influenced by heaven's will without even knowing it."

"Hahaha, I have learned much." Five Elements Grandmaster laughed grandly: "Even if it is heaven's will influencing me, so what? This is also my own intention! And I believe that man will triumph over heaven. No matter how vast heaven's will is, it cannot compare to the will of humans. Throughout the long history of humanity, we were so weak and feeble, pushed aside and humiliated everywhere, until we became the overlords of the world today, suppressing all variant humans and other life forms under our feet! The human race is the one that destroys the balance the most, but can heaven suppress us? There were ten rank nine venerables in human history, and countless Gu Immortals among us, we roam heaven and earth, we can capture stars and overturn mountains and rivers, what can heaven do?"

Heaven Extremity laughed, the other seven also expressed joy.

This joy was the joy of meeting a companion, someone who shared similar understanding and aspirations as oneself.

Heaven Extremity's laughter faded: "It seems that you, Five Elements Grandmaster, have also been reading \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> frequently."

"Of course. \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> contains Ren Zu's human path true inheritance! Every Gu Immortal who cultivates to a high level will try to benefit from it. Unfortunately, I do not have the wisdom and comprehension ability, I can only read the meaning that human path triumphs over heaven path. I had once heard that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created self luck and reached an impasse where he stalled. He only obtained an inspiration after reading \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, creating all living being's luck. After that, he went on to ascend to the Immortal Venerable throne, before creating heaven and earth luck." Five Elements Grandmaster continued.

Heaven Extremity nodded: "Indeed."

Five Elements Grandmaster went on: "I am a Northern Plainsman, born and bred here. Even though I do not have the Huang Jin bloodline, I admire Giant Sun Immortal Venerable greatly. Human path triumphs over heaven path, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path is deeply using the essence of human path! The trend of the rule of humanity cannot be overturned, it cannot be defied. Even heaven is not its match! Do you all agree with me?"

"Of course that is the case." Heaven Extremity replied arrogantly.

Five Elements Grandmaster smiled lightly: "The trend of humanity is clear to everyone here. But the trend of Northern Plains, can you see it clearly?"

Heaven Extremity's expression changed: "What are you trying to say?"

Five Elements Grandmaster said calmly but loudly: "Right now, Northern Plains' trend in terms of humanity is that the demonic path is rising up while righteous path is shifting lower. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed, allowing many lone immortals and demonic path members to gain strength. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu created Bai Zu tribe personally, allowing the righteous path to have a different bloodline."

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's hereditary monarchy was indeed a grand aspiration, but it was really quite restrictive, Northern Plains is not his to begin with. It belongs to all Northern Plainsmen. The death of a person is like the snuffing of a candle, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's influence has affected Northern Plains for so long, so many years! It is time to change!"

"A load of nonsense!!!" Heaven Extremity was furious, the other seven extremities also started berating angrily.

Five Elements Grandmaster was very tranquil: "You are angry and furious, that is because of the fear in your hearts. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Huang Jin tribes, they have dominated Northern Plains, ruling over it, it is starting to decline now. Just like the ten great ancient sects in Central Continent, they seem strong, but they are rotten on the inside, there are many internal conflicts and useless members. What about the lone immortals and demonic cultivators? Look at Northern Plains' rank eight Gu Immortals, how many have Huang Jin bloodline?"

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu is demonic path, I am a lone immortal, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu turned from lone to righteous path, Prince Feng Xian is a member of Gong tribe, but he is not of Huang Jin bloodline. Only Yao Huang alone is holding up the Huang Jin tribes' reputation."

Chapter 1181: Sudden Changes, Benefits are Key

Five Elements Grandmaster: "Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is a forewarning, while Bai Zu tribe's creation is an obvious sign. Next, the influence of the Huang Jin tribes will start to fade away."

"Because this is the trend of humanity in Northern Plains!"

"You say that I was affected by heaven's will, that is not so! I was rushed here by the tide of humanity, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's reputation can no longer intimidate me, he has been dead for too long!"

"Next, more Gu Immortals will be discontent with the Huang Jin tribes, and covet your wealth. Northern Plains is full of battles, Northern Plains Gu Immortals have bravery and fighting spirit, suppression would only be met with even more resolute and crazed resistance."

"I am just the first person to come to Longevity Heaven. Next, more and more will come here. Are you prepared for it?"

There was silence.

The Eight Extremities were so angry they were trembling, having cold expressions.

Heaven Extremity had a stiff expression, he smiled forcefully: "Amazing rank eight Gu Immortal, amazing Five Elements Grandmaster. You want to convince us that instead of being wiped out by this trend, we should merge and ride the wave, imitating Gong tribe to take in more lone immortals and demonic cultivators, to recruit a rank eight Gu Immortal like you?"

"We do not have a deep feud, we can cooperate." Five Elements Grandmaster said solemnly: "Even though the Four Desolation Immortals are rank eight, they have little lifespan, they cannot move around freely. I have no such problems."

Heaven Extremity laughed maniacally: "Hahaha! You? You are looking down on the foundation of the Huang Jin tribes! Or rather, you are looking down on Ancestor Giant Sun! If not for you, us Eight Extremities would have gone to rebuild Eighty-Eight True Yang Building already. And that Bai Zu tribe is merely a short-lived flicker. Such impure bloodline and he wants to be in the righteous path? Heavenly Lord Bai Zu? Is he worthy?! The righteous path of Northern Plains are the Huang Jin tribes!"

Liu tribe's base camp.

Xuan Bai blessed land.

"Ah, the Longevity Edict!" Liu tribe's first supreme elder was extremely shocked, he quickly knelt down and received it.

Liu tribe was one of the super forces, a Huang Jin tribe, the descendants of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Meanwhile, Longevity Heaven was the rank nine grotto-heaven of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, among the Huang Jin tribes, it represented supreme authority.

Liu tribe's first supreme elder received the Longevity Edict.

The Longevity Edict was golden in color, it resembled a token, but it was in essence, an information path Immortal Gu.

He felt a sensation and understood the information in the Longevity Edict.

Liu tribe's first supreme elder frowned: "Longevity Heaven has orders for us Huang Jin tribes to work together and deal with Bai Zu tribe?"

This order caught him off guard.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was fighting with Chu Du, the entirety of Liu tribe's Gu Immortals were happy to see this.

Bai Zu tribe took over Hei tribe, their forces bordered Liu tribe. Because Bai Zu tribe had a rank eight Gu Immortal, Liu tribe had a very vigilant attitude, while feeling deep wariness.

And Chu Du had a feud with Liu tribe, his reputation as Domination Immortal was mostly due to Liu tribe to begin with.

The contest between these two, in Liu tribe's opinion, was one foe fighting another. Liu tribe was watching on the fence, wanting to see them both suffer losses.

Chu Du was in trouble, Liu tribe felt good seeing it, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had taken revenge for them.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu suffering losses would cause Bai Zu tribe's reputation to fall in the future, it was a great thing for Liu tribe. Nobody would want a fierce tiger to live around them, a weak neighbor was better than a strong one.

"But now that the Longevity Edict is out, we have to follow it."

"My Liu tribe is close to Hei tribe's former territory, once this battle starts, we will face pressure many times that of the other tribes."

Liu tribe's first supreme elder left his information on Longevity Edict, on the Immortal Gu, before letting it go, as the Longevity Edict tore through the sky.

Next, this Immortal Gu would continue to visit the other Huang Jin tribes.

Back to the present time.

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Chu Du and Fang Yuan, who received this information, were surprised and overjoyed.

"All of the righteous path super forces, the Huang Jin tribes are attacking Bai Zu tribe, this way, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu is bound to retreat." Fang Yuan spoke with a smile.

"The Huang Jin tribes that have never gotten along are acting in unison at such speed, I wonder what happened." Chu Du was confused.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined: "Perhaps Longevity Heaven sent an edict."

"Longevity Heaven?" Chu Du's expression changed, he thought for a while: "It seems that is the only reason."

In fact, the situation of the forces in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world was quite similar to Central Continent.

Central Continent had ten great ancient sects, Northern Plains had the Huang Jin bloodline super forces, Central Continent had the Heavenly Court ruling above, while Northern Plains had Longevity Heaven that stood in the sky.

More similarly, the ten great ancient sects were the lower level sects of Heavenly Court, while Longevity Heaven similarly had great influence on the Northern Plains Huang Jin tribes.

Perhaps in the past, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had imitated Central Continent, purposely creating this situation.

"Why did Longevity Heaven suddenly send an edict, ordering the Huang Jin tribes to work together and deal with Bai Zu tribe? Bai Zu tribe is backed by a rank eight Gu Immortal." Chu Du thought, feeling doubts.

What made him unable to comprehend it was, if Longevity Heaven wanted to deal with Bai Zu tribe, the best time to strike was when Hei tribe had just been destroyed.

But at that time, Longevity Heaven did not act. So why did they wait until now? Was Longevity Heaven also interested in Hei Fan grotto-heaven?

Thinking of this possibility, Chu Du's heart sank.

"No matter what, we need to make use of the remaining time and talk to Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, ending this conflict. Immortal Gu 'No' and 'Care' were prepared for this moment." Fang Yuan reminded.

Chu Du came back to his senses, he said solemnly: "You are right."

He immediately sent his clone to converse with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

Right now, Chu Du was the owner of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he had made many arrangements here, the Gu worms that he sent out were not detected by others.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had more information than Chu Du.

He knew that right forces, the righteous path forces were coming at Bai Zu tribe because Longevity Heaven had directly sent a Longevity Edict!

He was very shocked, he did not know why Longevity Heaven was suddenly finding trouble with him.

In the past, when creating the tribe, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was worried about Longevity Heaven, he was waiting for a response from them.

Longevity Heaven's silence made Heavenly Lord Bai Zu feel like he had probed its bottom line. He thought: As a grand rank eight, Longevity Heaven might not want to deal with him, after all, there was no good reason for it.

The commotion and change in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world made Heavenly Lord Bai Zu very perplexed.

"Yao Huang and Prince Feng Xian are righteous path Gu Immortals, Prince Feng Xian might not come, but Yao Huang is a true Huang Jin bloodline member. Other than that, there is still Longevity Heaven. Hmm... Five Elements Grandmaster has a good understanding of Longevity Heaven, I might be able to get some information from him."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu thought quickly, the situation was turning for the worse rapidly, he felt immense pressure on him.

He was still unaware that Five Elements Grandmaster was already fighting with Longevity Heaven. In fact, the current situation was caused by the conversation between Five Elements Grandmaster and Heaven Extremity.

"As for Hei Fan grotto-heaven..." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's gaze became dark, he assessed: "I cannot take it down for now, I should stop. I cannot waste any time and energy now, I need to put all my effort into defending my hard work."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu wanted to retreat.

The reason why he wanted to take down Hei Fan grotto-heaven was due to the loss of his reputation, it might cause a commotion and result in severe losses to Bai Zu tribe's interests.

But now, Bai Zu tribe was in a crisis. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's own interests were severely infringed now.

This situation was truly the worst, how could Heavenly Lord Bai Zu have any effort to spare for Hei Fan grotto-heaven!

But in this situation, Chu Du's Gu worm arrived in Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's hands.

"Oh? As expected of the Domination Immortal..." After understanding Chu Du's intention, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's gaze became dark and eerie.

The contest for Hei Fan grotto-heaven ended at once!

What made the Northern Plains Gu Immortal world shocked was, Chu Du not only came to a resolution with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he even gave up a portion of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, and created an alliance with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!

After achieving the alliance agreement, Chu Du let Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body into Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Using Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's deterrence, he went on to deal with those demonic path and lone immortals that he had invited earlier.

These Gu Immortals were facing Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body, how could they dare to resist, they could only lower their heads to Domination Immortal.

Chu Du successfully resisted Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, using the power of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he forcefully subdued many lone immortals, gathering everyone and creating Chu Sect on that very day.

Chu Sect.

Using Chu Du's words in his speech: This was the first Gu Immortal sect in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world! It had extraordinary meaning.

Fang Yuan watched coldly from the side, even though Lang Ya Sect was the actual first sect in Northern Plains, Fang Yuan could not help but gasp in admiration towards Chu Du's incredible performance.

Chu Du had truly outdone himself.

He gave up a portion of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, but he managed to obtain a rank eight reinforcement, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was also a deep schemer.

Northern Plains' situation gave him huge pressure, he had to find external allies.

And Chu Du could guess his mentality, thus he created Chu Sect, it was far easier than for Heavenly Lord Bai Zu when he created Bai Zu tribe.

Chu Du was not all alone, these last years, he had nurtured many strength path Gu Immortals.

And with Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he had a huge basis for development.

Meanwhile, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu needed Hei Fan grotto-heaven as a backup plan for the entirety of Bai Zu tribe.

Thus, the two sides turned from enemies to allies.

Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen, who accidentally killed Bai Zu Wei, were just punished mildly, before they were spared.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could no longer bother with these two insignificant figures at this point.

Thus, Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu felt immense gratitude towards Domination Immortal, they became the two most loyal people in Chu Sect.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world had changed too rapidly.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, who was at the peak of his life earlier, having created his own tribe, was now facing the attack of all the Huang Jin tribes.

Chu Du and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, who were fighting to the death earlier, were now allies.

Ordinary Gu Immortals might be dazzled by these turns of events, but for people like Fang Yuan, it was very clear.

No matter what commotion or changes there were, the key concern throughout was still benefits, it had never changed!

Chapter 1182: Leaving Hei Fan Grotto-Heaven

Inside a Gu formation.

Fang Yuan sat quietly on the ground.

Chu Du, as well as the wills of Pang Shan and Not Immortal, were in front of the formation.

"Start." Chu Du said plainly.

The wills of Not Immortal and Pang Shan formed into human shapes, nodding as they activated their Immortal Gu.

One rule path Immortal Gu — No.

The other was also a rule path Immortal Gu, top ten in the List of Mystical Gu — Care.

Red date immortal essence was rapidly expended, the two Immortal Gu were shining in their own profound lights. The two profound lights had different colors, one was black and empty, the other was red and warm like fire.

The black and red lights entered the Gu formation.

Chu Du took action at an appropriate timing, activating this Gu formation, to fuse the power of Immortal Gu No and Immortal Gu Care into it.

The two profound lights fused under the guidance of the Gu formation, creating a half black and half red spiralling pillar of light.

The light pillar completely covered Fang Yuan's body, without any leaks.

A moment later, the light pillar stabilized, it was no longer as distorted as before.

"It is ready." Chu Du reminded.

Fang Yuan thus said: "You will not be able to imagine what is hidden under the northern icy plain, I almost died there..."

He spoke quickly, detailing what happened when he was undergoing tribulation in the northern icy plain, and the terrifying human calamity that he had faced.

The secret of the snowman and rockman tribes in the northern icy plain was revealed to Chu Du.

"To think that there is such a situation! The empty northern icy plain actually has such a powerful variant human force, they have been hidden all along!" Chu Du was extremely shocked.

The wills of Not Immortal and Pang Shan also shook, showing their stirred emotions.

A moment later, the black and red lights faded, the Gu formation stopped its operation, Fang Yuan slowly stood up, getting out of the Gu formation.

He was safe!

Originally, he was a member of the four race alliance, and a guest elder of Lang Ya Sect, he was not able to expose the secrets of the snowmen and rockmen to outsiders.

But because of the Immortal Gu No and Care, along with Chu Du's cooperation, Fang Yuan was able to breach his alliance agreements without facing any harm!

These two Immortal Gu were meant to be used by Chu Du.

Chu Du's intention was to come to a consensus with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. After defending strongly and refusing to relent in battle, they would eventually settle at an agreement, defending Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Chu Du had long since planned that if there was no choice, he would secretly sacrifice Hao Zhen and Chou Lao Wu, to protect Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's reputation, and express his sincerity.

But the actual situation was far better than he had expected.

Perhaps the alliance of all the righteous path forces in attacking Bai Zu tribe had made Heavenly Lord Bai Zu feel strong external pressure.

Because of that, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not list any requirements of executing the murderers, he only gave them a light punishment on the surface.

"It is to the credit of these two Immortal Gu, otherwise, I would have no way to explain this situation to you." Fang Yuan pretended to be relieved, he sighed deeply to himself.

Of course, he had withheld some information from Chu Du.

For example, Fang Yuan did not expose Lang Ya blessed land.

Fang Yuan was a vigilant person, he was not going to tell Chu Du everything, he was used to keeping trump cards at hand.

Chu Du said in a heavy tone: "By the looks of it, we cannot continue to undergo tribulation in the northern icy plain."

"Indeed." Fang Yuan nodded, he started to avoid mentioning things related to the four races alliance.

Because the two Immortal Gu No and Care had stopped activating, if Fang Yuan breached the alliance agreements again, he would face intense backlash, he would either be severely injured or dead!

The two Immortal Gu, No and Care, had incredible abilities, but they had to be activated constantly.

Because they had to be used together to allow the Gu Immortal to breach alliance agreements without suffering any damage.

But they could not remove the restrictions of Fang Yuan's alliance agreements completely.

This was a method that resolved the situation but did not solve the underlying problem.

"Regarding this, what are your opinions?" Fang Yuan asked directly.

The wills of Not Immortal and Pang Shan looked at each other.

The former shook his head: "Crazed Demon Cave contains the secret of eternal life, our main bodies would not leave it. As long as humanity is not extinct, we will not come out. The variant humans can develop all they want, even if they become many times stronger, they are not the match of humans."

The latter said: "If we are to deal with the variant humans, it is easy. We just need to announce this information, and the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world will go after them."

"No, that way, the northern icy plain will get destroyed. If a huge battle occurs, the icy plain will not remain. And we would not be able to get anything from it, we might even get exposed and implicate Brother Liu." Chu Du shook his head.

"I'm just saying." Pang Shan's will grumbled.

Indeed, if the variant human force underneath the icy plain was exposed, a huge battle would occur. By then, Fang Yuan would be trapped in the middle, he would not have an easy time.

Fang Yuan listened to their words, the worry inside him dissipated by a lot.

Fang Yuan had to tell Chu Du about the situation in the northern icy plain, because they had set an alliance agreement. There would be many opportunities to cooperate in the future.

If Fang Yuan concealed it, he would be greatly restricted.

Chu Du did not attack the variant human force in the icy plain, that was within Fang Yuan's estimations. After all, right now, Chu Du's focus was no longer on tribulations and Reckless Savage's true meaning, it was how to control the situation and cooperate with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to resist the attacks of the righteous path super forces.

And the wills of Not Immortal and Pang Shan also made Fang Yuan realize the mindset of the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics.

"It seems that these three are bent on researching Crazed Demon Cave. The commotion in the outside world cannot lure them out."

Fang Yuan thought about it, he could understand the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics.

If he did not have so much trouble, he would also do the same thing as them.

Unfortunately, Fang Yuan was in a lot of danger, not just Shadow Sect, but also the pursuit of Heavenly Court and other various aspects.

"However, if they know my true identity, how would they react?" Fang Yuan looked at the three, his thoughts were drifting.

After talking for a while, Chu Du kept the two Immortal Gu and the wills of Not Immortal and Pang Shan in his own immortal aperture.

Next, he and Fang Yuan left this underground camp together. After leaving the cave, they got back to the surface of Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

Hei Fan grotto-heaven was currently developing.

Large numbers of variant humans, rockmen, feathermen, and minimen were laboriously working.

Many Gu Immortals would often raise variant human slaves.

Right now, Chu Sect had allied with Bai Zu tribe, these variant humans were slaves that came from Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe.

"Greetings to first supreme elder and second supreme elder." Hao Zhen saw Fang Yuan and Chu Du, quickly taking the initiative to greet them.

Chu Du took the opportunity to create Chu Sect, he even roped in Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was originally unwilling, but Chu Du gave him special treatment, Fang Yuan's alliance agreement for Chu Sect was very loose, it was not restrictive.

And because Fang Yuan intended to continue working with Chu Du, this allowed them to have another layer of relationship.

Chu Du asked about the development status of Hei Fan grotto-heaven, Hao Zhen answered that they were all at the initial stage, but the different Gu Immortals had taken out their resources and relocated them here. There was a crucial point, Fang Yuan had also put in a lot of effort, contributing a lot of resources.

These resources were originally from Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

After going through many places, they were back at their original spots.

Even Fang Yuan did not expect that.

Why did he contribute this huge amount of resources?

Firstly, using the two Immortal Gu No and Care was not free, Fang Yuan had discussed with Chu Du, using this as the compensation.

Secondly, Fang Yuan sold some resources to Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

Inside Hei Fan grotto-heaven, a large portion was Chu Sect's territory, but a small portion belonged to Bai Zu tribe now.

The entirety of Hei Fan grotto-heaven became the symbol of alliance between Chu Sect and Bai Zu tribe.

Fang Yuan and Chu Du said goodbye to Hao Zhen, after flying for a while, Fang Yuan said to Chu Du: "Alright, you don't have to send me off."

Chu Du had a worried look: "Didn't you just obtain Hei Fan's true inheritance. In my opinion, delaying the calamities and tribulations by slowing your immortal aperture's rate of time is most stable. After all, you have just undergone so many battles, if you undergo tribulation after going back, there is a huge risk."

Fang Yuan smiled: "How can there be gains without risks. Furthermore, you are around, if I encounter any sudden danger, I will seek help from you."

Chu Du had an apologetic expression: "It is a pity that Chu Sect was just created, we have strong enemies against us, there is unrest now, otherwise, I would go with you. Have you chosen the tribulation location?"

"Not yet, I need to think about it." Fang Yuan shook his head.

Chu Du opened the grotto-heaven's entrance.

"See you." Fang Yuan stepped out of the grotto-heaven, flying away without looking back.

Chu Du shut the door again, sighing internally.

Fang Yuan was not easy to control, he was very decisive. And Chu Du still had desire towards the immortal tribulation tempering aperture method, but the current situation was very complex.

Fang Yuan's battle strength and his status with the variant humans made Chu Du see a lot of value in him.

Fang Yuan wanted to deepen his cooperation with Chu Du, wasn't Chu Du also thinking the same?

As Fang Yuan left Hei Fan grotto-heaven, in Southern Border, Bai Ning Bing arrived at Jade Pot Mountain.

"Why did you bring me here?" Bai Ning Bing asked directly.

Hei Lou Lan and the others were wondering too.

Ying Wu Xie, who was leading the way, stopped walking, he turned around and smiled: "Bai Ning Bing, you are too weak. This Jade Pot Mountain has our Shadow Sect's arrangements, it has already formed an Immortal Gu. We will take it out and increase your battle strength, so that you can deal with the bet of the Five Xiangs."

"Bet of the Five Xiangs? What is that?" Bai Ning Bing frowned.

Ying Wu Xie laughed loudly: "It is too early to tell you now."

Bai Ning Bing frowned even more deeply now, snorting coldly: "The part about you I hate the most is that air of mystery that you use."

"Insolence!" Shi Nu stared angrily at Bai Ning Bing, he was very unhappy about Bai Ning Bing's arrogant attitude towards Ying Wu Xie.

"No matter, it's no bother." Ying Wu Xie laughed, he did not mind Bai Ning Bing's attitude at all.

Chapter 1183: Entering a New Blessed Land

Fang Yuan successfully returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

At this moment, his divine sense was in the sovereign immortal aperture.

"I have inspected it eighteen times, there should be no problems. But even if any problems occur, the newly hatched upper extreme heavenly eagle is only at the power of a desolate beast, even if it rebels, there is no danger."

Fang Yuan thought in his mind.

He was inside Mini Purple Heaven in the sovereign immortal aperture.

An ordinary eagle nest was floating in the sky.

Inside the nest, other than an upper extreme heavenly eagle egg, there was nothing else.

Within the surrounding hundred li, Fang Yuan had placed many strength path immortal zombies, desolate beasts, and even the walking meat tree here temporarily, to ensure there were no accidents.

He hatched the upper extreme heavenly eagle once again!

Fang Yuan began to move.

A large amount of fresh blood was taken out by the strength path immortal zombies, before activating Gu worms and fusing the fresh blood perfectly into the upper extreme heavenly eagle's egg.

Fang Yuan had done this once before.

But back then, Fang Yuan used Hei Cheng's blood. This time, Fang Yuan was amply prepared, not only did he change the upper extreme heavenly eagle's memories, he even did some changes to Hei Fan's arrangements left on the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

This way, Fang Yuan could use his own blood to hatch the upper extreme heavenly eagle. It was not like before, using familiar face to conceal himself and become close with the upper extreme heavenly eagle, obtaining the acknowledgement of this immemorial desolate beast.

He went step by step, smoothly progressing, there were no unexpected mishaps.

Eight days and nights later in the immortal aperture, the upper extreme heavenly eagle hatched again, as the baby upper extreme heavenly eagle emerged.

"Chirp, chirp."

The upper extreme heavenly eagle saw 'Fang Yuan' and immediately jumped at him affectionately.

This 'Fang Yuan' was not Fang Yuan's real body, it was a strength path immortal zombie, using familiar face to turn into Fang Yuan's appearance.

Even though it had just hatched, it was not small, when it raised its head, it had the height of a youngster.

The young eagle treated Fang Yuan as its parent, it surrounded him and flapped its wings, chirping and jumping around, extremely happy.

"Alright, alright." Fang Yuan smiled warmly, stretching out his hand and stroking the upper extreme heavenly eagle's head.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle obediently stayed still, its chirping became softer and more intimate.

"Come, eat." Fang Yuan took out a thick and long heavenly crystal.

The heavenly crystal was white and gold, in a translucent state, placing it in front of the young eagle, all of its attention was drawn to it.

Its dark eagle eyes shined with bright light. It began to peck the heavenly crystal, as it broke apart like tofu, the young eagle ate it and swallowed the crystal very quickly.

The young eagle trusted Fang Yuan deeply, it did not hesitate in consuming the heavenly crystal in Fang Yuan's hands.

After eating six heavenly crystals, it stopped in satisfaction.

Its tummy was bloated, the young eagle had become plump, it sat on the ground and chirped, slapping its tummy with its wings continuously, it was very cute and lovable.

"Full?" Fang Yuan smiled warmly, sitting down while leaning on the eagle.

The eagle felt a strong sense of safety, it let down its guard, shutting its eyes as its head lowered, lying on Fang Yuan's lap as it fell asleep.

Fang Yuan stretched out his hand, stroking the young eagle's feathers.

Its newly born feathers were yellow and soft, together with its body warmth, it was very comfortable to touch.

In the following days, Fang Yuan manipulated the strength path immortal zombie as he stayed by the upper extreme heavenly eagle's side.

Other than deepening their relationship, he was also keeping a close eye on it, in case of accidents.

"I have enough heavenly crystal eagle nests." Fang Yuan's divine sense left the eagle nest.

Taking a look, in the surrounding hundreds of li, there were many eagle nests.

There were nearly a hundred eagle nests, Fang Yuan had taken them from Iron Eagle blessed land.

Fang Yuan chose the largest eagle nest as the temporary home for the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

The original heavenly crystal eagle nest had already been completely eaten by the previous upper extreme heavenly eagle, nothing was left.

But now, even though the heavenly crystals in the nests could not nurture the upper extreme heavenly eagle, there was still a pile of them, taller than an adult.

Among these heavenly crystals, a small portion came from Lang Ya land spirit. Fang Yuan had exchanged for them from Lang Ya land spirit using sect contribution points.

The bulk of them were obtained from Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, after Chu Du and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu allied, Fang Yuan had transacted with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu through Chu Du.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was a rank eight Gu Immortal, he had a grotto-heaven, he had a huge stock of heavenly crystals.

In order to get this transaction, while revealing the secrets of the variant human in the northern icy plain to Chu Du, Fang Yuan also told him about the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

Actually, this was already no secret.

Chu Du might have known, while Heavenly Lord Bai Zu definitely knew, because he had taken in the supreme elders of Hei tribe as his subordinates.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu desired the upper extreme heavenly eagle greatly, but currently, he needed Chu Du as an ally. And Chu Du wanted to deepen his cooperation with Fang Yuan, because of all these reasons, Fang Yuan easily succeeded in getting this transaction.

Fang Yuan paid a lot of resources.

But these resources were originally from Hei Fan grotto-heaven anyway. To purchase these heavenly crystals, Fang Yuan sold them all without hesitation.

Be it Chu Sect or Bai Zu tribe, they needed these resources greatly.

Because of their battle, both sides had expended a lot of their foundation, they needed replenishment. And the even better thing was, these resources were originally produced in Hei Fan grotto-heaven, they suited the environment and did not need to adapt.

After successfully hatching the upper extreme heavenly eagle, Fang Yuan settled down and observed it for some more days.

After he confirmed that the upper extreme heavenly eagle had no issues, Fang Yuan immediately left, using Lang Ya Sect's teleportation Gu formation to get to Tai Qiu.

The sixth earthly calamity was about to arrive, there was little time, why was Fang Yuan going to Tai Qiu?

He could not undergo tribulation in Tai Qiu.

Because it was too dangerous.

Ancient desolate beasts and ancient desolate plants lacked intelligence, they were easily influenced by heaven's will, and would form into a giant beast tide.

Fang Yuan followed a route and moved.

He used familiar face, constantly changing his appearance, disguising himself as ancient desolate beasts or desolate beasts to travel, moving in Tai Qiu.

Fang Yuan did not dare to go to the center of Tai Qiu, it was extremely dangerous, there were many wild Immortal Gu there and even immemorial desolate beasts!

Thankfully, his destination was not at the center of Tai Qiu, it was at the fringe.

Three days later, he successfully reached his destination.

The ground in front of him was uneven, even though there was a lot of giant grass, it could not conceal the traces of battle here.

Some mangled corpses were scattered here.

Fang Yuan's gaze swept through the surroundings, he did not discover any danger, he let out a breath of air and relaxed.

"In the previous earthly calamity, I gained a lot of dark path dao marks. This time, I used Dark Limit to hide from heaven's will, the effect is many times better! Thus, I am still safe."

"Then next is..." Fang Yuan mobilized his Gu worms, inspecting the surroundings.

He was very careful, he searched meticulously.

There was a rank seven Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture, Fang Yuan had specially borrowed it from Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. Lending Immortal Gu was also part of Fang Yuan and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's deal. Other than this, there was an immortal killer move.

With this rank seven Immortal Gu as the core, Fang Yuan used the immortal killer move.

Not long after, he had a discovery.

"Good, I recalled correctly! It is here!"

The immortal killer move allowed Fang Yuan to discover a blessed land. It was hidden in empty space, concealed here in the air.

"Good eagle, it is up to you now." Next, Fang Yuan opened the immortal aperture, letting out the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle had grown multiple times in size after these days, but it was still young, it had shiny feathers and sharp eagle eyes, it was quite strong and vigorous looking.

It flew in the sky, carrying Fang Yuan on its back as they flew multiple times in a circle, under Fang Yuan's guidance, it sensed something and changed directions, aiming towards the ground and about to crash.

When it was three meters from the ground, the upper extreme heavenly eagle suddenly went through an entrance, as it vanished from Tai Qiu along with Fang Yuan.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan arrived at a completely new blessed land!

Chapter 1184: Annexing Han Dong Blessed Land

This blessed land was very unique.

The entire terrain was a shallow beach.

Jade green water that was less than three meters deep, large numbers of rocks piled on the beach, like ink on a casually drawn canvas, they resembled strokes and lines that weaved together.

There were many pools of green water, some formed lakes, some formed tiny seas, it was distributed like a pieces of a chessboard.

"This is quite similar to Dong Fang tribe's Jade Pool blessed land." Fang Yuan thought to himself.

But he was aware that this place was different from Jade Pool blessed land at its core.

Jade Pool blessed land was filled with many deep pools, there were tens of thousands of them, resembling the stars in the sky, forming a beautiful sight. And inside the jade pools, the water was different and bred countless aquatic species.

But the water here was connected to the same source. Because there were crevices between the rocks that formed the terrain of the beach.

Fang Yuan looked, there were large numbers of fish and prawns, all sorts of aquatic insects and mortal Gu. Under the beach, in the crevices, there were seashells, mussels, seaweed, and others.

But what was most abundant was a type of snake.

This snake was pinkish red in color, it was small and delicate, about the size of an adult's thumb, smaller ones were only a few centimeters.

This was a spirit snake.

Gu Immortal Han Dong specialized the most in this transformation.

This was Han Dong's blessed land.

Han Dong was one of the Traveling Three Elites, back then when Dong Fang Chang Fan possessed Dong Fang Yu Liang and tried to revive, he had used the immemorial ruin bat corpse to create a temporary base.

By the time Fang Yuan and the rest got there, Gu Immortal Han Dong from the Traveling Three Elites had already died here.

The Traveling Three Elites were Lu Qing Ming, Su Guang and Han Dong.

They were lone cultivators, rather famous ones.

When the three worked together, they could use an immortal killer move that gathered light, forming a chariot that could travel quickly.

In the Gu Immortal world, when some Gu Immortals develop close relationships, they would help each other and cultivate together. As time passes, when they become more familiar, if they were talented, they would comprehend and create new joint immortal killer moves.

The Traveling Three Elites were like this, the wind thunder roar of Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen was similar.

Among the three of them, Lu Qing Ming was a wind path Gu Immortal, his signature move was entangled wind, it was very powerful and maneuverable.

Su Guang was a light path Gu Immortal, while Han Dong cultivated transformation path!

He was a transformation path rank six Gu Immortal, this Han Dong blessed land was a rank six blessed land.

Fang Yuan floated in the sky, at this time, a pinkish red spirit snake slithered over towards Fang Yuan.

"Hiss hiss hiss!"

The spirit snake was translucent without scales, its flesh was pinkish, it did not have bones, just one red line held its body from head to tail together.

It hissed at Fang Yuan, showing animosity in its tone.

This was different from the other snakes.

Fang Yuan could understand it, as the hissing turned into words in his ears: "Who are you? Why did you invade my home? Quickly leave, you are not welcomed here!"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "I came here because I want to be your master, what are the conditions for that?"

"Hiss hiss hiss!"

The pinkish red spirit snake hissed unhappily.

Fang Yuan nodded, feeling overjoyed, he thought to himself: "So Han Dong's obsession before death has to do with Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang."

It turned out that Han Dong blessed land's condition was very simple yet strict.

The spirit snake in front of Fang Yuan was the blessed land's land spirit, created after Han Dong's death, fusing his obsession with heavenly power.

This land spirit would only acknowledge Lu Qing Ming or Su Guang.

When either of them arrived, this blessed land would belong to them.

From this point, the Traveling Three Elites truly had a close relationship. Han Dong's obsession before dying was to leave all of his assets to his two good friends.

"In that case, I will bring Lu Qing Ming here. We are good friends." Fang Yuan spouted nonsense.

"Hiss hiss hiss!"

Spirit snake asked: "Is that true? You can find Lu Qing Ming? That is wonderful."

"In fact, he is nearby. Because your main body died here, Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang have been thinking about it. But Tai Qiu is too dangerous, thus, they asked me for help, and we finally found you after so long." Fang Yuan started his chain of lies, he neither was flustered nor did his heart beat faster.

The spirit snake slithered around, moving its body, it was very excited.

Next, it made an agreement with Fang Yuan, in just a few minutes, Lu Qing Ming would arrive.

"Thank you, truly, you are a good person!" The spirit snake's attitude changed, it was very welcoming as it opened the entrance, sending Fang Yuan out.

"You must find Lu Qing Ming!" Seeing Fang Yuan off, the spirit snake closed the entrance longingly.

Fang Yuan flew in a circuit outside, storing away the upper extreme heavenly eagle and using familiar face to become Lu Qing Ming.

He came back and waited for a while, before the blessed land's entrance opened.

"Lord Lu Qing Ming... sob sob sob." The spirit snake was at the entrance, seeing 'Lu Qing Ming', it started to sob uncontrollably.

Fang Yuan consoled it as the spirit snake's mood lifted.

The spirit snake asked: "Lord Lu Qing Ming, where is your friend from earlier? He is a nice person, he actually brought you here."

"He is a kind and helpful person, he is very dependable. He has already left, he said that there is no point in staying here, he has already done his part." Fang Yuan continued with his fairy tales.

The pitiful land spirit could not see through familiar face, it thought he was speaking the truth, immediately acknowledging Lu Qing Ming as its master.

"Hiss hiss hiss!"

The spirit snake coiled around Fang Yuan's shoulder: "From now on, you are the owner of this blessed land."

Fang Yuan immediately changed his tone: "Wonderful, I've thought about it, I will give this blessed land to that friend of mine from earlier."

"Hiss?!"

The spirit snake was stunned.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Since I am the owner of this place, I have the authority for that, right?"

"Hiss... hiss."

The pinkish red spirit snake lowered its head, it was upset but it still responded, acknowledging Fang Yuan's words.

Fang Yuan immediately left, in a moment, he got rid of familiar face and returned in his original appearance.

Very successfully, the spirit snake acknowledged him as master.

"Hiss hiss hiss!"

The spirit snake said: "From today onwards, you are the owner of this blessed land. Sigh, even though I am sad, this is Lord Lu Qing Ming's wish."

Next, there were even more saddening words coming out of Fang Yuan's mouth: "Since you acknowledge me as your master, work with me, assimilate this blessed land into my own blessed land."

"Hiss? Hiss, hiss, hiss, hiss hiss!"

The spirit snake was completely stunned, before becoming frantic: "What? Why must we do that? If we do that, I will disappear!"

"Of course I know that. But by fusing into my blessed land, I can skip multiple calamities and tribulations, it is helpful to me." Fang Yuan continued.

The pinkish red spirit snake thought of something and cried out: "To annex my blessed land, you need to be at least a transformation path master."

"I primarily cultivate transformation path, I am a grandmaster!" Fang Yuan replied mockingly.

The spirit snake lost all its vigor, its head was lowered to the ground: "Fine, you are the owner of the blessed land, you can do whatever you want, I will cooperate."

Immortal apertures could annex one another.

There were many restrictions and requirements in this.

Firstly, a smaller immortal aperture could not engulf a bigger one.

Secondly, dead apertures could not devour others.

Finally, annexing immortal apertures required specific attainment levels. To annex a rank six blessed land, one needed to have master attainment level in that path. For rank seven blessed lands, one needed grandmaster attainment level. and for rank eight grotto-heavens, one needed great grandmaster attainment level!

Once these requirements were met, another person's immortal aperture could be devoured and become part of one's own immortal aperture!

There were many benefits in this.

Firstly, the resources inside the annexed immortal aperture would be completely transferred into the other immortal aperture without any need for relocation.

Secondly, one would gain a portion of its dao marks.

Thirdly, and the most crucial point, the skipping of calamities and tribulations!

For example, Hu Immortal, an enslavement path lone cultivator from Central Continent, had died during her fifth earthly calamity, from the blue charm lightning shadow. Even though the blue charm lightning shadow remained, the fifth earthly calamity of Hu Immortal blessed land was passed.

If a Gu Immortal annexed this blessed land, they would gain all of the resources inside Hu Immortal blessed land, at the same time, they would receive a portion of the blessed land's dao marks, and they would skip at least one calamity or tribulation, to a maximum of five. Furthermore, the countdown towards their next calamity or tribulation would be reset.

Southern Border, Jade Pot Mountain.

Ying Wu Xie's group arrived at the interior of the mountain.

"To think that Jade Pot Mountain has jade soil on the surface, producing beautiful jade that is renowned in Southern Border, but the interior is actually an icy land, it is truly another world here." Bai Ning Bing stood inside the icy cave, sighing in shock.

As they got deeper into Jade Pot Mountain, the temperature lowered, frost energy emanated, even though the Gu Immortals had defensive methods, they still felt a strong chill assaulting them.

Ying Wu Xie suddenly paused his steps, he seemed to have sensed something, he spoke while looking forward at the empty space: "We are here. This is a rank six immortal aperture left behind by a strength path Gu Immortal of Shadow Sect."

Next, Ying Wu Xie turned around and said to Hei Lou Lan: "Hei Lou Lan, this is for you. You have enough strength path attainment level, you can annex this immortal aperture. This way, your upcoming calamities and tribulations will be bypassed."

Hei Lou Lan's expression changed.

She had the Great Strength True Martial Physique, one of the ten extremes, her calamities and tribulations were immensely powerful.

Annexing an immortal aperture could resolve her problem, but it sacrificed her potential for growth in the future, only to obtain some short term benefits.

She hesitated, but eventually gritted her teeth, walking forward.

Ying Wu Xie internally nodded at this, he understood Hei Lou Lan's feelings, he spoke: "In a Gu Immortal's cultivation journey, pursuing potential and long term growth is not wise. If you cannot survive the upcoming tribulation, then there is no future to speak of. Don't worry, this blessed land contains strength path dao marks that are not fewer in number than your ten extreme physique tribulation. Shadow Sect's cultivation methods are not something you can imagine. But how much you can actually absorb is up to your own fortune. Because the annexing of others' immortal apertures will often result in a reduction of dao marks gained to some extent. It is far less than stuffing a Gu Immortal's corpse into your immortal aperture directly and allowing it to break down naturally."

Hei Lou Lan's body shook, the anticipation in her gaze became heavier.

Ying Wu Xie could not help but think of Fang Yuan, he added in his mind: "Of course, the sovereign immortal body is exempt from this."

Chapter 1185: Unexpected Joy

"What is going on?" Fang Yuan was confused.

Under the cooperation of the blessed land's pinkish red spirit snake, he successfully annexed Han Dong blessed land, turning it into a portion of the sovereign immortal aperture.

Thus, a shallow rock beach appeared in Mini Northern Plains, within the sovereign immortal aperture.

In the shallow beach, there was clear jade green water, with all sorts of fish and prawns in it, they could be seen swimming in the clear water. Between the crevices of the rocks, algae and seaweed flowed with the waves, there were even seashells and conchs.

There was a great number of pinkish red spirit snakes, some were moving alone, exploring the crevices. Some formed into groups, swimming in the green water, resembling a ball of red threads as they moved together. Some spirit snake groups moved in hundreds, it was a grand sight.

What was worth mentioning was that there was a desolate beast pinkish red spirit snake.

It was resting in a crevice between some rocks, it seemed to be in deep sleep.

Even when the entire blessed land was engulfed, it did not wake up.

Fang Yuan moved the whole of Han Dong blessed land over, the assimilation was simply perfect.

Normally, if Fang Yuan took out these resources and planted them into his sovereign immortal aperture personally, he would need to dig rivers and create their habitat.

In that case, because of the change in environment and difference in dao marks, much of these resources would wither and die. Like what happened when Fang Yuan took away Hei Fan grotto-heaven's resources, he had to constantly sell the resources in the outside world.

Because these resources could not grow in the sovereign immortal aperture.

It was not worth the effort in trying.

But now, Fang Yuan directly annexed the immortal aperture, he saved a lot of trouble.

The resources in Han Dong blessed land, be it the fish, prawns, or plants, did not need to adapt to a new environment. Because Fang Yuan moved the entire environment over directly!

This way, Fang Yuan had completely, with one hundred percent efficiency, taken over all of Han Dong's accumulation of resources over his life, and instantly absorbed them.

"Han Dong blessed land only produces one valuable thing, that is the spirit snakes. He can already nurture desolate beast level spirit snakes, even though this blessed land is low grade, to reach this extent of development is already outstanding."

Thus, Fang Yuan could inherit Han Dong's business and sell the spirit snakes.

Spirit snakes were a type of mutated beast, but they had a high ceiling of growth, they could reach a peak of ancient desolate beast level.

Fang Yuan assessed it, this rock beach was the foundation for raising spirit snakes. The profits it generated for him slightly exceeded the star fragment grass fields that were in Mini Blue Heaven.

Fang Yuan put these resources aside for now.

There were other, stranger matters.

Firstly, Han Dong blessed land's land spirit, that pinkish red spirit snake, was still around in the rock beach.

It did not die!

"Hiss hiss hiss?!" The pinkish red spirit snake twisted its delicate body, shaking its head, even the land spirit itself was confused.

The blessed land was annexed, the land spirit would die, this was common knowledge in the Gu Immortal world. But when it came to the sovereign immortal aperture, logic was meant to be defied.

Fang Yuan did not expect this at all, he was mentally prepared to sacrifice the blessed land's land spirit.

But to think that this happened.

Fang Yuan's will descended to the rock beach, forming into a human shape.

THe pinkish red spirit snake slithered over, happily hissing at Fang Yuan: "Hiss— hiss hiss hiss!"

"Master, master! What is going on, I actually did not die. I am still alive, master, master, you are amazing!"

Fang Yuan's will laughed: "Of course, this is my secret art, solely created by me, it is unique in this entire Gu Immortal world. You think I wanted to harm you? But you are truly loyal, you were willing to sacrifice yourself, and give everything to me."

The pinkish red spirit snake's eyes were shining, it had deep admiration towards Fang Yuan: "Hiss hiss hiss!"

"Wow, my master is so amazing, master's talent is higher than heaven! I am truly so blessed to have a master like you."

Fang Yuan's will nodded in agreement: "Alright, even though I have created a secret art to annex immortal apertures of others, this is the first time I used it. How much control do you have over this rock beach?"

The spirit snake answered: "Same as before, master, master, you are so amazing!"

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's will pondered, before saying: "Then, little spirit snake, can you control any other areas?"

The spirit snake tried and shook its head: "No master, I cannot."

"It can only control its original territory huh..." Fang Yuan's will thought and said: "Then, can you try and leave this rock beach?"

The spirit snake was very obedient, it immediately tried.

Unfortunately, as Fang Yuan had predicted, it could not leave the rock beach at all.

"Thus, the little spirit snake can only manage this rock beach in the future..." Fang Yuan felt a slight pity.

He lacked a capable individual to manage the sovereign immortal aperture for him. Earlier, he had hoped that there would be someone like Little Hu Immortal to manage the place for him.

After all, the sovereign immortal aperture was just too big, Fang Yuan's divine sense needed time to just look over it completely, it was a hassle to manage. It used up a lot of his time and energy over typical days.

The appearance of the pinkish red spirit snake was a somewhat unexpected and joyful surprise.

Fang Yuan had wanted to let it manage the sovereign immortal aperture for him, but now it seemed, forget about the sovereign immortal aperture, it could not even manage the whole of Mini Northern Plains.

Because it could only move around in its original territory.

"Forget it. This rock beach can be taken care of by the pinkish red spirit snake, it can sense any issues immediately if they occur. Why must I be unsatisfied?"

Fang Yuan quickly got over it and continued thinking calmly.

The pinkish red spirit snake was not destroyed, it still existed, this was just one aspect that shocked Fang Yuan.

The other aspect was in dao marks.

"I annexed Han Dong blessed land, but I actually absorbed all of the dao marks of the blessed land, what is going on?" Fang Yuan was puzzled.

According to the logic of the Gu Immortal world, when Gu Immortals annex immortal apertures, the dao marks they gain would be greatly reduced from the total amount.

But Fang Yuan obtained everything!

Before annexing the blessed land, Fang Yuan had used perceivable dao Immortal Gu to inspect the number of dao marks in Han Dong blessed land. Its transformation path dao marks were the highest in number, about seven thousand, followed by water and earth path dao marks, about a thousand each. Time path, space path, fire path, and other dao marks were mixed in and varied in numbers, some were less than a hundred, some were a few hundred.

These dao marks were all absorbed by Fang Yuan. As Han Dong blessed land completely fused with him, it became a part of the sovereign immortal aperture.

Results by testing with perceivable dao Immortal Gu proved this point.

"I kind of understand why." Fang Yuan thought for a while, realizing something.

What caused this situation was very likely to be the trait of non-conflicting dao marks that the sovereign immortal body had!

Ordinary Gu Immortals, even those of the ten extreme physiques, when annexing immortal apertures, would face conflicts between different dao marks. The Gu Immortal's dao marks were like the owners of the house. And the annexed dao marks were like guests.

If guests want to enter the house and refuse to leave, even attempting to become the new owners of the house, the original owners would chase them away.

Eventually, the original owners will take in a batch of guests that they like, and these guests would suit the nature of the owners, they would be of the same path. As for the other paths' dao marks, they would be chased out, few of them could enter the house and become new owners.

But Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body was different.

This house was open and invited any guest to stay. Because dao marks did not conflict, the original owner could allow any newcomer to stay without any issues!

"It is all encompassing. Not only are dao marks non-conflicting, even land spirits can be taken in, it is like the huge world outside, there is nothing it cannot contain." Fang Yuan suddenly felt a trace of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's incredible fortitude and resolution.

The sovereign immortal body was formed from sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it was deduced by Spectral Soul singlehandedly, expending a great amount of time, effort, and resources, eventually refined through great danger.

This Immortal Gu was the embodiment of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's beliefs and mindset.

Fang Yuan could not help but praise internally: "Spectral Soul Demon Venerable reached the apex through killing, he created soul path and was invincible in the world. But after he died, his soul went to the door of life and death, he went a step further and broke the limits he faced during his lifetime, reaching a state of being akin to that of a sea which all rivers flow into, becoming an all-encompassing being, he was truly incredible!"

Non-conflicting dao marks made Fang Yuan's body very fragile, but the advantages greatly outweighed the disadvantages.

Fang Yuan could use strong defensive methods to negate this weakness. But the great benefits it brought could not be replicated through other means!

After annexing Han Dong blessed land, Fang Yuan's final gain was also his main objective — skipping calamities and tribulations.

He succeeded.

Originally, his sixth earthly calamity was impending.

But after annexing Han Dong blessed land, not only was the sixth earthly calamity skipped, the countdown until the next calamity, and he even jumped forward by four calamities.

"I have already passed five earthly calamities, with the sixth coming soon. Now that I skipped four, I have already passed the ninth earthly calamity, and my first heavenly tribulation would be next!"

Gu Immortals pass tribulations time and time again, it is like they were obtaining the acknowledgement of heaven and earth.

The achievements of predecessors would be enjoyed by the person who annexed their immortal aperture.

Even though Fang Yuan was not very clear on the reasoning behind this, it was proven countless times in history by many Gu Immortals: Annexing other people's blessed lands would allow one to skip their tribulations.

This was also a way to undergo tribulations, but in actuality, there were huge restrictions and tough conditions to meet.

And the disadvantages were not small.

"Sigh, after annexing this strength path immortal aperture, even though I gained a lot, I lost a lot of future potential in exchange for the current gains." Inside Southern Border's Jade Pot Mountain, Hei Lou Lan had also annexed an immortal aperture.

But her expression was very gloomy.

Chapter 1186: Ice Soul Immortal Gu

Even though Hei Lou Lan obtained a lot of resources, and her greatest weakness was alleviated, her gains in dao mark were very little.

Making an estimation, it was less than thirty percent of the immortal aperture's dao marks.

She skipped more than ten calamities and tribulations directly.

This was an immeasurable loss to Hei Lou Lan!

Because of her having one of the ten extreme physiques, every time she underwent tribulation, it would be extremely strong. Fortune and disaster came together, whenever she succeeded in passing the tribulation, the dao marks that she gained would be much greater in number.

More than ten calamities and tribulations, it was not just earthly calamities, but a heavenly tribulation as well!

Considering this, her losses were huge.

Even though undergoing tribulation was a dangerous thing, for a bold and fierce character like Hei Lou Lan, she was not afraid of difficulties, she was only afraid of being ordinary.

"Even if I am unwilling, what can I do? I am stuck deep in the abyss, it is not up to me..." Hei Lou Lan sighed internally.

Ying Wu Xie observed her appearance, seeing Hei Lou Lan's gloomy expression, he smiled internally as he said: "Alright, let's continue traveling."

The group passed the icy tunnel, getting even deeper into the mountain.

Eventually, they arrived in front of a wall of ice.

Through the white wall of ice, the immortals could see countless hearts inside.

These hearts were blue, there were about at least a thousand of them.

Bai Ning Bing did not know of them.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng screamed: "Oh heavens, these are ice hearts, they are all ice hearts."

Hei Lou Lan's expression also changed: "Not just ice hearts, there are twin ice hearts, the latter is a rank seven immortal material, and in such quantity."

Even the normally quiet Shi Nu gasped: "Unimaginable, Jade Pot Mountain actually has such an abundance of wealth. If Southern Border's Gu Immortals knew about this, a storm would be whipped up, in order to fight for these ice hearts, they would fight until rivers of blood flowed!"

Jade Pot Mountain was not uninhabited, there was a village on the mountain, with the surname Yu.

Jade Pot Mountain produced jade stones and jade Gu, Yu clan village relied on these resources for survival.

Among mortal forces, Yu clan village, which had many rank five Gu Masters, was very powerful. But to Gu Immortals, they were not worth mentioning.

Who could have thought that Jade Pot Mountain, controlled by a mortal force, could have such a quantity of rare immortal materials stacked together!

Ying Wu Xie sighed deeply: "Jade Pot Mountain is nothing special on the surface, it is easy to ignore. Even my Shadow Sect also found this place due to a fortuitous encounter. But the ice hearts formed naturally here are not so high in quantity. My Shadow Sect's Gu Immortals had secretly set up a Gu formation to turn this place into a Gu breeding ground."

"In the past, this place had nurtured ice heart Gu, but they had been taken away. There is still one ice heart Immortal Gu here, it was not ready earlier, but now it has completely formed. Bai Ning Bing, come here and retrieve this wild Immortal Gu using the method I taught you."

"Alright!" Bai Ning Bing said without hesitation.

She took large steps ahead.

Next, using Ying Wu Xie's instructions, she stretched out both hands and placed them on the wall of ice, which was covered in frost energy.

Without using any defensive methods, Bai Ning Bing's hands were completely frozen, frost energy assaulted her as a thick layer of frost formed on her arms.

Hei Lou Lan saw this and raised her eyebrows.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to speak, he had an expression of pity.

Ying Wu Xie smiled lightly, Shi Nu was expressionless, not saying a word.

Bai Ning Bing endured the intense pain as frost energy traveled through her body from her arms, soon, she felt her body turning stiff, even her mind was becoming frozen.

The intense threat of death assaulted her in both body and mind.

But she was unmoved.

Inside her clear blue eyes, a firm, determined gaze could be seen, she was even more stubborn and cold than this ice wall.

"Endure it!"

"Even if I die, it is nothing much."

"Hmph, dying from frost like this, it is interesting too isn't it..."

"Furthermore! Shadow Sect suffered a huge blow, they need manpower. Ying Wu Xie tried so hard to recruit me, how could he let me die like this?"

As expected, a change occurred in front of Bai Ning Bing.

Inside the wall of ice, the blue ice hearts were shaking together, the vibrations were small initially, but got more intense with time.

More than ten breaths of time later, the wall of ice made a loud sound, cracks were forming before the immortals' eyes. Soon, they were covering the wall of ice like a spider web, one of the cracks went deep into the interior of the wall.

The aura of Immortal Gu leaked out.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng almost wanted to help out.

This was a wild Immortal Gu, it was very hard to catch, if they did not take action now, it would be too late!

But Ying Wu Xie was unmoved, he watched silently.

Since he kept motionless, Hei Lou Lan and Shi Nu also did not act.

Bai Ning Bing could not move.

She was completely frozen, frost energy had permeated her entire body, she was close to death.

But this person who was dying greatly attracted that wild Immortal Gu which had broken out of the ice.

This wild Immortal Gu flew over slowly, entering Bai Ning Bing's hold.

In the immortals' vision, this Immortal Gu was about the size of a baby's fist, resembling a spider with a white body and eight claws, as well as a back with blue flowery markings that showed the appearance of a vengeful ghost screaming.

Rank six ice soul Immortal Gu!

Bai Ning Bing focused her mind, opening her phantom aperture's entrance.

Ice soul Immortal Gu directly flew in.

When the phantom aperture's entrance closed, Ying Wu Xie immediately acted, healing Bai Ning Bing's injuries, dragging her back from the edge of death.

"Good, ice soul Immortal Gu is already in your aperture, it has nowhere to escape, refining it will be extremely easy." Ying Wu Xie clapped and smiled.

Hei Lou Lan's gaze shined, she suddenly spoke: "I understand, this ice soul Immortal Gu has a close connection to Bai Ning Bing. Because Bai Ning Bing has the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique!"

"Indeed, the aura of the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique has an intense attraction to ice soul Immortal Gu. Thus, I asked Bai Ning Bing to capture it without using any defensive methods. It was to completely release the aura of the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique without any concealment!" Ying Wu Xie nodded, explaining.

"But if Bai Ning Bing's vitality was too high, the wild ice soul Immortal Gu would hesitate. Thus, only when Bai Ning Bing was on the verge of death, would ice soul Immortal Gu feel that she was no threat and go towards her automatically."

"So that's it." Tai Bai Yun Sheng realized.

"Lord Fang Yuan is so wise!" The loyal Shi Nu also said.

"Hahaha." Ying Wu Xie raised his head and laughed: "My Shadow Sect is huge and has many resources, being with me will give you all great benefits. Like this wall of ice, my Shadow Sect had spent a thousand years mimicking a natural environment, creating this Gu refinement ground."

"The cultivation methods that my Shadow Sect has are unimaginable to all of you. If you aptitude is low, we will raise it. If you have few dao marks, we will increase them. Everything is possible."

Hei Lou Lan's heart shook.

Ying Wu Xie's final words were clearly directed at her.

"This fellow, he has learned how to be a true leader, he is really improving rapidly." Before Hei Lou Lan could continue thinking, Ying Wu Xie waved his hand: "We're leaving! Next, we will take over Bai Xiang grotto-heaven!"

Northern Plains.

"I skipped too few calamities and tribulations." Fang Yuan sighed, he was not happy about this.

At almost the same time as Hei Lou Lan, who was unhappy over her major losses, wanting to skip as few calamities and tribulations as possible.

Fang Yuan sighed, the number of calamities and tribulations skipped did not match his expectations.

If possible, he wanted to be a rank seven Gu Immortal at the very next moment!

The endless number of battles in Hei Fan grotto-heaven made Fang Yuan realize his biggest flaw. His cultivation level was too low, his green grape immortal essence was not efficient.

As Fang Yuan's identity got more complex, the dangers he faced also became greater.

In the past, Fang Yuan could control the future well, because he was alone. Now that he had many alliance agreements, he could not help himself.

And with the trip to Eastern Sea, he did not manage to exterminate Shadow Sect, the growth of Ying Wu Xie and the rest made Fang Yuan feel immense pressure.

Thus, he would rather sacrifice his future potential and raise his battle strength rapidly.

"Without the present, how can there be a future?"

"Potential is good, but to have room for development, one needs to spend time."

"The true attitude for cultivation is to be practical, everything is for the sake of our present reality."

Fang Yuan's losses were even more severe than Hei Lou Lan's, but he did not feel any pity or loss, he had a resolute and determined gaze.

"But, Han Dong had already gone through two heavenly tribulations and more than twenty earthly calamities. I annexed his immortal aperture, but I only progressed by four earthly calamities."

"Is this because the sovereign immortal aperture is too big, the effect of skipping calamities and tribulations from annexing immortal apertures is not very evident?"

Fang Yuan thought about it from all angles, he felt that the sovereign immortal aperture was the cause.

Rank six Gu Immortals face an earthly calamity every ten years, and a heavenly tribulation every one hundred years. After three hundred years, after three heavenly tribulations, they would become rank seven.

During this process, if it was split into three, Fang Yuan was nearly one-third done.

"This is not fast enough, I need to hit rank seven as soon as possible, it would give me a huge boost in battle strength in terms of sustainability! Financially, I will also grow rapidly."

"If only Han Dong blessed land is not enough, I will have to annex more immortal apertures."

"Even though the gains in dao marks cannot compare to undergoing tribulation myself, I can save a lot of time, I can deal with challenges and dangers from all aspects more easily now."

"Furthermore, when annexing blessed lands, I get all of their dao marks without any losses. Even though it is still a loss, I just need to kill some Gu Immortals to make up for it!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan had a ruthless light flashing in his eyes.

After uncovering another advantage of the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan discovered a new way to cultivate.

His original method was to go with the natural flow, undergoing tribulations and obtaining a great number of dao marks and true meaning. But this method was too slow, his battle strength rose slowly, what grew the most was his immortal aperture's foundation. It was not suited for Fang Yuan, it would only make his situation more dangerous.

Currently, Fang Yuan was going to use the method of annexing immortal apertures and skipping calamities and tribulations, to rapidly raise his cultivation level. When his cultivation level rises, his battle strength would also rise. Fang Yuan would use his new battle strength to kill more enemies and annex their apertures, to avoid undergoing tribulation himself, it could also allow his immortal aperture's foundation to grow, and he would gain dao marks as well.

This method allowed Fang Yuan's battle strength to grow at the fastest speed, but his immortal aperture's foundation would increase more slowly. But it was suited for Fang Yuan's situation, it allowed him to have a better chance at survival!

Both cultivation methods could create a cycle of benefits for him, they just had their own advantages and strengths.